<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject7831</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Willow House Investigation - Day Three, Final </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-09 06:12:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [[Part 1](https://www.reddit.com/r/nosleep/comments/69c4h1/willow_house_investigation_day_one/)]

[[Part 2](https://www.reddit.com/r/nosleep/comments/69p2ge/willow_house_investigation_day_two/)]

I started this log in order to keep a written account and diary of hard cold facts.  There were only two options in my mind.  One being that we would describe the logical ways in which these phenomenon were occurring, the other being an account of facts that could not be reasonably explained. "Facts" and "evidence" now seemed like the candy I would eat as a child.  Sweet, indulgent, plentiful and deceptive but without nourishment, without truth, without sustenance.  I craved the mundane now that I had seen the lie of it. More than ever before I wanted that assured false sense of reality back.

The night following our previous investigation was distressing to say the least. The night I arrived home, showered and turned in, it began.  I recall awaking from a nightmare only to find that I was still in it.  I could feel cold limbs pressing my shoulders to the bed, holding me on my back as my eyes widened and I tried to scream.  The limbs were hard, cold and sectioned like the limbs of an enormous exoskeleton. What I saw before my eyes was little more than the dreamy swimming darkness that seems so rich with the life behind the eyes as you squeeze them shut.  But I could feel it. I could feel the cold dead weight on my body.  I could feel the putrid snorting breath on my face seeming to come from both sides.  I could feel a pain, no not a pain, a pulling in my chest as I began to fear blacking out.

I could also feel that sensation rise in me.  It began as a stirring just above my genitals.  The stirring turned into a warm whirlwind that quickly shot upwards through my throat as I hoarsely yelled.

"No!" The shout hung in the dead air.  The room now devoid of everything.  The room now empty, quiet, real.

I pulled the blankets off of me and ran for the standing lamp to illuminate the space and confirm what I already knew.  It was gone. Over. Whatever I had experienced was finished, as sharply as if a mesmerist had clapped his hands loudly bringing his subject out from hypnosis. I could not sleep.  I considered reading, but was far too distracted.  I thought about taking a bath to calm down but I could not bring myself to sit naked and vulnerable in the bathroom with the door shut or open. I headed to the fridge to make myself a snack and a drink.  That's when I heard my ringtone from the bedroom.

"Jesus Jason, what the fuck are we doing... I can't do this, it has too...I think..." It was Thomas and he was clearly hysterical. "It fucking... Fuck man are you there?"

I assured him I was listening.

"It followed me man. Fuck, It's here... or it was and...." He took several long breaths.

"Me too Tom.  Just minutes ago." I felt for him. I understood his terror.

"It was everywhere.  Slamming doors, opening drawers.  I swear my house shook, I don't know what the fuck to do man, what do we do?" 

Clearly neither of us would sleep tonight and I decided that we should get together. I knew that I would feel much better if I was not alone.  Shit. Alone. Neither of us.  The disparate thoughts coalesced in my mind and I started to feel a panic before I had even formed the thought.

"Tom, have you heard from Sam?" I asked hurriedly.

He hadn't.  Neither had I.  It seemed reasonable that if this thing had followed us both, then it must have followed Sam as well.  I told Tom that I was on my way to his place which was very close to Sam's.  I called her several times on the way, and each time I got no response.  By the time I arrived, I was beyond consolation thinking of her and had Tom ready on the road near his house to swing straight over to Sam's apartment building.

Buzz. Buzz. Another and another.  No answer was forthcoming.  We had seen her car in the lot outside the building so we knew she was home.  The sinking feeling in my stomach was stopped short when we began to hear muffled banging from inside.  

We looked at each other and both simultaneously said "We need to get in there".

"Kick the door open!" Thomas yelled.

"You've got to be kidding I'm not doing that. You do it." Embarrassed by my immediate childishness in an emergency.

We looked around and decided that we could reach the kitchen window if we moved some trash barrels below it.  We would smash it if we had to, but once I was up I discovered that I could easily push both the screen and window up.  In a series of extremely clumsy motions I was over her kitchen sink and pulling Tom into the apartment.  We followed the banging sounds into her bedroom tripping over the clutter of dirty clothes and knocking over her bong along the way.

The banging was coming from the closet in her bedroom. We could see the door reverberating with the assault it was receiving from the inside.  My feet remained planted quite far back as I cautiously reached out and turned the doorknob.  When the door swung open we saw our friend.

Her eyes were wide and red and full of tears and mascara. Her face and arms seemed covered in scratches, some bleeding moderately.  Her ankles were bruised.  After a moment of slow recognition she sprung from the closet and embraced us both sobbing into our ears as she hung on our shoulders.

That night we sat in the diner until 3am talking and comforting each other as we shared our experiences. We talked until we felt that we had turned these nightmares into stark facts. Facts we could speak about in the light of day.  War wounds that soon we became somewhat proud and exhilarated to bear.  We also got to business. Samantha managed to reach her friend and relay the evenings happenings.  Once she understood the severity she agreed to meet us the very next day at the Willow Street house and do anything possible to end this.

***

The conversation I had with Mrs. Felworth the next day was quite strained.  She was clearly unable to sleep or cope with what was going on.  I informed her that we would visit that day with the sole intention of removing this thing from her home, and that we were part of it now with her.  I tried to ensure her so that she did not feel alone.  I'm not sure that it worked, but she was certainly eager to try, and agreed to host us that evening after Lily's Karate class.

Thomas, Samantha, Dawnstar and I had planned to arrive at six o'clock.  We had packed up all of our gear this time wanting to document and study everything possible tonight.  We had five camera's and one portable, the recorder, EMF reader, a pair night vision goggles, flashlights and headlamps, one digital and one film camera, as well as a container of holy water. 

Our van cruised down the highway when Dawnstar said dreamily. "It found us".

That very moment we heard what sounded like a gunshot, as the van veered hard to the right towards a ditch.  I managed to pull hard on the wheel keeping us swerving back and forth between the breakdown lanes, narrowly missing an SUV, until we could safely come to a stop. We had blown a tire.  Or a tire had blown.  With all of us working on it we had the spare on in all of ten minutes and proceeded.

We getting very close to the house when I saw something in the road and slammed on the brakes, screeching to a halt.

Before us maybe five feet from the hood of the car stood a Buck with a full rack of antlers.  It was standing perfectly still, and facing the side of the road. It was almost entirely covered in blood, and the eye that we could see from our side had fallen from the creature's face and hung.  Even with a single busted eye visible the animal seemed stunned.  We looked around for the car that must have hit the buck, but the stretch of road was empty.

We heard rustling in the van and looked back to see Dawnstar, in her little hippie dress and sweater, tearing through her large pack.  She extracted two knives, one with a black handle, and one with a white one.  She tossed the white handled knife back into her pack and exited the vehicle.  We were all too stunned to speak.  We just watched her.  We watched her proceed languidly up to the creature in the road before us and slowly put a her hand to the side of it's face, clearly not bothered by the blood and flesh there.  Her frame looked minuscule near the beast but after a moment she rose onto her bare toes and with one quick slash cut the animal's throat.  She didn't move back, or even remove her hand from stroking it's face.  She did raise her other hand and hold the animals chin up as blood charged from it's neck in pulses that slowly grew more infrequent.  After a time, the animal fell and Dawnstar returned.

She calmly cleaned and returned her knife to her bag.  Then whispering something to herself she wiped the blood from her fingers between her eyes in a small vertical line. She cleaned her hands and looked around to each of us in turn, unfazed by our shocked faces.

 "It made a mistake.  We're connected now." This was spoken very naturally, in light of what we had just witnessed. "Let's get there. You can drive around."

We did.  And we arrived shortly thereafter.

***

Mrs. Felworth was quite taken aback by Dawnstar's appearance being that she had blood on her forehead, but with some limited conversation about what had happened on the way, and assurances that she was a person who had some experience with situations like theirs, she was welcoming.  Once again Lily remained in her room as we setup our gear. This time Dawstar had some setup to accomplish as well. She removed three long wooden slats from her bag, white and covered in symbols.  She placed them in the shape of a triangle under the kitchen table. She then poured table salt in a large circle on the hardwood floor in the den several feet from the table. We focused on our equipment and did not question or interfere with what she was doing.  Seeing what I had just seen earlier I trusted this person to have the knowledge and wherewithal to accomplished what she had promised she could.

Once we were prepared Mrs. Felworth brought her daughter out in her little sleeping gown to sit at the table with us.  She looked angry and defiant.  She was clearly not happy to see us and we sat in silence for a moment.

"Lily.  Last time we were here I lied to you.  I want to apologize.  That was not very nice of me." I pleaded with my eyes.  It took her several moments to meet them.

Eventually her face and body relaxed and she smiled. "It's ok.  I lie too sometimes."

"Thank you Lily.  You're quite grown up to be able to forgive me for being mean." We needed her cooperation, and I was happy that I was able to be the one to get on her good side.  Tom had always been so much better with children than I.  "We want to talk to Mister Thin-Man one last time.  Would you let us use your board?  We have a new friend for him to talk to." I nodded towards Dawnstar.

She agreed and ran happily to her room, grabbing and setting up the board on the table just as she had before. She looked at Dawnstar for some time before slowly handing over the planchette to her. It was if Lily had not wanted to, but could not resist.

Dawnstar took it softly from Lily and addressed her directly. "You know that we won't be friends don't you Lily?"

"Yes" Lily looked down at her lap.

"You know why too, don't you? You know that Thin Man does not belong here.  That he is bad for people, even if he seems friendly."

Lily stayed quiet.

"I am calling upon the spirit that is called Thin-Man, Mister Thin-Man. Come and speak with us at my behest!" This was a loud as I had ever heard Dawnstar speak.

Her hands instantly shot around in circles on the board at speed. She bent her head backward and closed her eyes as her body jeered with the circling motion of her arms.

  "I feel you here. Give me you name spirit!" She demanded.

In rapid succession she received T...H...I....

"By the highest and by the lowest, Give me your true name!" She interrupted the response.

T...H...I...

"Lily, do you have crayons and paper?" She asked playfully. When she said that she did, Dawnstar had her fetch them and bring them to the table. "Now Lily, I need you to draw for me.  I want you to think of Thin-Man, think about what his skeleton must look like underneath.  Can you draw it? Like a stick figure."

"Sure, I'll try." She agreed.  She drew a long bent line and then three sets of branched lines across it.  "That's him I think."

Dawnstar told her she did an excellent job and took the paper, and then a lighter from her pocket.  She let go of the board and held the paper over Mrs. Felworth's tea cup and flicked the lighter.  Everyone pushed back in their seats from the table when we saw the Planchette jerk.  No one was touching it now, but it moved several inches, resting over the "No" printed on the board.

Dawnstar put her instruments down and returned her hands to the planchette.  "You have one last chance, I demand by the most high and by the dwellers of the most low. By the winds, the fire, the tumult of earth and by the sea, I demand that you give me your true and faithful name!"

A...Q...R...A...B...U...A...M...E...L...U

"I need everyone to leave the table now and go into the den.  Stand in the circle but please do not disturb the salt." Dawnstar's command was both quiet and unquestionable.

We did as she asked, Mrs. Felworth guiding her daughter over.

"Aqrabuamelu, I command you to leave this location. I command you to leave these people. I command you to disperse to your abodes and trouble us no longer." She stood now and pushed the table back towards the counter top, revealing her triangle on the floor. "I bind you here until you commit to what I ask.  I bind you spirit in the name of Michael. I bind you, and will cast you into the brass pot unless you disperse and trouble us no longer."

She then withdrew a small brass kettle with a lid from her pack and placed it on the table.  Just her body language indicated that this was a severe threat.  She was not someone to be trifled with.  We did not understand it at the time, but it was clear that she knew what she was doing.  This was rather comforting for a time.

"The fire and the pot, or the past Spirit!  The fire and the pot or the past!" Dawnstar repeated this over and over several times.

In that moment the house came alive.  The lights flickered.  The boiler roared.  The floorboards across the home creaked randomly.  Then we saw the door to Lily's room swing violently outward smashing a doorknob sized hole in the wall.  The wind picked up gusting outside, and the shutters banged against the exterior of the house.

"One last time, Aqrabuamelu, The fire and pot, or the past!" She was shouting now over the din.

It was Lily's voice that now shrieked. "You're hurting him!" She ran full speed from the circle into the kitchen as if trying to stop what was happening, distraught of the pain that her Thin-Man was being made to endure. The moment she reached the space where the table had been, the lights went out completely.

For a moment, just for one moment I had seen it.  This hanging light green glow in the kitchen.  It was low to the floor with a tail that reached back and up over it's own mass. Just a glimmer of a shape in the lightest fluorescent mist. And then the lights came back on.  And there was nothing of it left.  There was also no trace of Lily.

Dawnstar put her face into her hands and sobbed. "No, no, no" she whispered through her tears.

"Lily! Lily where are you?" Mrs. Felworth became frantic and started running around the home.

The rest of us looked at each-other dumbfounded with no idea how to proceed.  So we took up the mantle of trying to locate Lily. The house was small and it quickly became clear that she would not be found unless  she answered our calls.  Luckily the front door was the only exit possible so we locked all of the windows and returned to speak with Dawnstar about how to proceed.

Before we could question her I saw it.  There was something strange, a familiar shape at the wall.  It was the hole that the doorknob had made in the wall near Lily's room, there was something there that caught me.  It was an eye.  The green pupil of Lily staring through that hole from the inside of the wall.  And then it was gone.  She had seen me see her and fled.

"She's in the wall!" I shouted quickly. I ran to the corner where I had placed the portable camera on the side table.  I grabbed it and flipped through the menu until I reached infrared, and quickly turned it to the side of the house on which I had seen Lily.

The image was blurred, but well defined.  On the view-screen I saw little Lily's shape, all red against a field of blue, and before her was a tall skinny shape with an upraised tail that towered over his head leading her down the thin corridor between the walls. Everyone gathered behind me examining the screen as we began to follow.  Once we reached the hallway we watched, mouths agape, as the figured climbed upward.

"The attic!" Mr's Felworth said.

She reached up and pulled the string hanging in the hallway, bringing down a collapsible staircase and we cautiously climbed the stairs into the dark attic.  Be the time we got our bearings, and I located the heat signatures in my camera, I found Lily's shape directly above us.  I looked up to find her perched on the rafters above our heads, back hunched, on her hands and knees, as if protecting her stomach from a bully.  We pulled some furniture below her and climbedto her level, carefully pulling her off of the beam that she was curled upon.  

A small shine caught my eye from underneath where she had been.  I could not see well in the dark but felt something smooth with my hand.  I lowered myself down with Lily over one shoulder and a small cold object in my right. We got her downstairs before trying to speak with her and ascertain if she was ok.  She seemed well enough. She was crying and angry that we were going to make her friend go away.  She was very clear about this.  After some assurances and many questions from her mother, Lily agreed to lie down and take a nap on the couch.

I peeled open my hand to reveal the item I had found in the attic. It was a small gem, similar in appearance to amber.  Inside the gem was the body of a scorpion, frozen in time, it's death eternalized by the whims of man. Next to the scorpion seemed to be a very tiny sliver of paper with indiscernible minute scribbling upon it.

"This is it." Dawnstar drew a white cloth bag from her pocket and used it to scoop up the gem from my hand, and cinched the top closed with two white strings. "It will be over now."

We all spoke for some time after that, and then took our leave.  From what I understand the item in question went on quite a journeythe next day.  It was brought to the ocean, it spent some time upon a mountain top.  It was cast into a bonfire.  It's remains were then buried deeply at a crossroads in the wilderness outside of our town.  What I do know is that the moment that object was found and removed, the thing that had been plaguing the Felwroth's and us had stopped.

Lily was sad for some time, but got over it, and returned to her normal self.  The electrical and other issues at the Willow Street house abated.  Thomas, Samantha and I were troubled by no further visits in the night. Dawnstar did not speak openly to us about the experience, preferring to leave it in the past, but clearly she had been successful.

We had done our job. We had done good work.  We had had a real experience. 

And all we could think about was locating the next. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-08 18:56:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> We ended up leaving it with her. It was quite clear that the ruse was up. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-07 04:35:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> posted </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-07 04:35:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> posted </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-07 04:34:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> posted </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Willow House Investigation - Day Two </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-07 04:33:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [[Part 1](https://www.reddit.com/r/nosleep/comments/69c4h1/willow_house_investigation_day_one/)]

Coming home after our first day at the Willow house felt just like that. Coming home.  After some time to think about, perhaps obsess about, our experience at the home I came to a conclusion.  It was the same conclusion that any rational person would land upon after some time and attention.  Our interaction with the Ouija board was simply coincidental.  When you thought about it, it would make perfect sense for my mind to connect a young child with "Sweetness".  Beyond this there was honey on the table that Mrs. Felworth was using in her tea, as well as talk of perfume.  There were many influences that would have triggered my subconscious to pull up the words "Taste Sweet".  The fact that Lily had a condition causing too much glucose in her bloodstream was mere coincidence.  Easily explainable by random chance.  Had I "divined" those words at any home in any situation there would be some similar such correlation. I was sure of it. 

I was embarrassed having let myself slide down the mental slope that so many people do.  I had lost my critical mind and had been a shill as soon as I had had a single strange experience.  I discussed these conclusions with Jason and Samantha who generally agreed with my assessment that this was certainly not proof of anything.  Samantha was a bit resistant but in the end she could not deny that the connection between the words we saw spelled out and the condition that Lily has was more likely coincidence than proof of something more dark or menacing.

Over the following days we reviewed the tape from the recorder, digitized the video interview and reset all of our equipment.  We had already promised to return, though now it seemed like we had maybe jumped the gun on that decision.  Even so, we would return once more and see if we could shine some light on the situation for Mrs. Felworth.  I really did feel for her, she was worried about her daughter, and frankly, I was as well.  It did not seem healthy for a child of six to be so attached to a spirit board.  It did seem like it could become a psychological issue, though I would hesitate to share that opinion with her mother.  This thinking lead me to begin forming a plan.

"So we'll just fake it?" Samatha looked somewhat incredulous as she adjusted her septum piercing.

I assured her it was for the best, and in the best interest of Lily.  She didn't like it but she agreed not to interfere.  I had decided that at our next meeting I would use the board again.  This time I would spell out a prepared set of messages that would inform Lily that Thin-Man had to leave and that we should take the board home with us to keep it safe in case he ever wanted to talk to her in the future.  It was not a complex or well thought out ruse, but you don't necessarily need a high level of skill to fool a six year old. We hoped that without her daughter constantly "speaking to a spirit" that Mrs. Felworth's anxiety would be greatly reduced.

We arrived at the Willow Street home on the 17th, about a week after our first visit and began as we had on the prior visit. There were pleasantries, basic equipment setup and all parties were present at the kitchen table within twenty minutes of our arrival.  Samantha was giving me dark glancing looks as if she was having trouble feeling great about what we were about to do, but she remained quiet.

"Lily, I want to thank you for letting me use your board. It was a very nice talk I had." I smiled and spoke calmly.  "I have a few more questions for your friend though, could I ask him?"

I reached out for the box and Lily did not object.  Honestly she seemed a bit distracted and withdrawn.  I focused on getting the message through to her and reassuring Mrs. Felworth with my eyes as I unpacked the board. Within moments I was circling the planchette again, faster than last time and with a completely clear head.

"Mister Thin-Man, why are you here?" I looked up as I addressed him, as Lily had done .

With complete control and clarity I darted the my hands around the game board to spell out "Lily was sad."

"Is that true Lily?" I asked "I'm sure you've been sad, but you're not sad now, right?"

Lily agreed. I continued my conversation.  I spelled out the whole story.  Thin-Man had come to make Lily feel better, but he should really be at home.  At home he had beautiful things and friends.  He just could not stand to see Lily sad because she was special. The plan went better than expected and withing ten minutes everyone was agreeing, even Lily, that she was fine now and that he could go home.  Lily even made an effort to convince "the spirit" that she wanted him to go and be happy, and that she would be ok.  Thin-Man suggested that the board should go home with our group so that we could dispose of it properly and everything seemed settled as I ended the conversation and pushed the planchette toward the friendly "Goodbye" on the board.

I never saw that word beneath the clear warped plastic.  Before I could reach it all the lights in the house suddenly cut out, leaving us all in utter darkness. Silence reigned as our eyes began to adjust, just starting to make out silhouettes in the dim lights from the street lamps outside. Suddenly out of that darkness came two words.

"You Lied." It was Lily's voice but it held a level of severity that was quite unlike anyone her age and life experience.

I wrenched my head to my left and gasped as I felt a sharp pain in my shoulder. In the sporadic motion I managed to kick the table hard which sent everyone in the room into a frenzy of standing and trying to get their bearings. 

"Thin-Man is angry." Lily stated matter-of-factly at the exact instant that the lights flickered back to life and we were illuminated once again.

"Jesus!" Jason spat as he reached for the back of my shoulder, and pulled my t-shirt down. "You're hurt, lets wash that."

I could not manage to bend my neck enough to see the wound, but I would find out later that I had a rather large set of semi-circles cut into my back.  The highly resembled a bite mark that I had seen when one of my nephews bit his sister.  Unlike that one, mine was rather wide, and the punctures were far more random and misshaped. It was as if the biter had three rows of teeth, each row missing sixty percent of it's inhabitants.  The punctures were scattered at varying depths.

Jason ran to the sink and snatched up some paper towels to run under the faucet.  He stopped dead just staring down for long enough for us all to begin to wonder.

"What is it?" Mrs. Felworth asked concerned, holding a reassuring hand at the back of her daughter.

"The water." He said quietly, almost to himself.  He slowly moved the faucet back and forth a number of times before continuing. 'It's draining counter-clockwise."

"So what?" Mrs. Felworth asked, shocked to be distracted by something so trivial.

"It shouldn't.  We're in the Northern Hemisphere.  It's the Coriolis effect.  Water drains clockwise in the North and counter-clockwise in the Southern hemisphere. This..." he was hypnotized."This is impossible."

Samantha jumped up and grabbed the portable camera, positioning it over the sink to validate the claim.  It was true.  Sam, Jason and I stood transfixed watching the water circle unnaturally around and completely forgot about my minor injury.  Once documented in detail they returned to their task of cleaning my wound and Mrs. Felworth was able to provide a sterile pad to cover it.

Turning back towards to the table my eye caught the spirit board, where the planchette was now resting perfectly over the word "Hello." Only Mrs. Felworth noticed what I was looking at and we shared a dark meaningful stare for several moments.

I asked permission for our group to be excused for some time and the mother said that she would read to Lily until she went to sleep.  She assured us it would likely only be ten minutes or so. We said our goodnight's to the young lady and headed out onto the front porch to converse.

"It hurt you, it affected the real world!" Samantha harped immediately into excitement.  "We have it on tape, that and the water.  We have something here!"

I asked Jason his opinion before offering my own to find that he was also convinced that we were experiencing something unexplainable. I had not choice but to agree.  The silence before my "bite" was complete.  If anyone in the room had gotten up to fake it, it would have been heard clearly.  No one had moved.  No one who we could see in the room anyway.  We additionally discussed the water, Jason having read of such phenomena in a number of famous paranormal cases. And then there was the perfectly timed change in lighting at both the start and end of the incident.  There were too many coincidences, mixed with a fair number of indisputable oddities.  The fear and pain of the injury started to turn into excitement, not quite matching Samantha's.

"We have to be careful. About them." He looked through the window on the porch towards Lily's bedroom.  "We can't be excited in there.  We have to be serious about this.  They could be in danger."

"You're right." I confirmed. "If we all truly think that this is something unexplainable, something other-worldly, they could be in danger.  It would be like having a disease that you don't understand.  We need to find some way to help them, and try not to focus just on gathering more evidence."

We all sat silent, each of us sightly depressed by the fact that any attempt to focus on proving what was happening here could cause danger for this little family.  We knew that our first priority needed to be to stop these occurrences, but could not bury the desire to cause more incidents to occur and then document them.  Even just the material we had collected so far was impressive and likely get our group quite a lot of respect once we edited and added them to our website.

 Once we were all on the same page as far as our conclusions and course of action we re-entered the home to find Mrs' Felworth sitting at the kitchen table smoking a cigarette.  We had not seen her do so on our last visit and she did not typically smell of Tobacco.  Her level of stress became immediately apparent, especially when she rose and began to question us.

"You've been here twice now. What is this. What is going on? Are we safe? How do we get rid of this thing?" Her eyes were red, and cheeks flushed.

"Ma'am, we usually come to cases like this and disprove them.  Many times people misinterpret sounds, smells, and other things as ghost activity and most of our job is finding realistic causes of the phenomenon." I explained sympathetically.

"No! But you got hurt, it hurt you." My calm explanation had apparently done little good . "And the water, the lights..."

"We believe that these are true experiences.  We cannot explain much of what happened tonight and we believe you.  We agree with you. None of us can explain what is happening here rationally." 

"Good." She relaxed a bit and puffed at her Newport. "So what now.  You know it's real, how do we get rid of it?"

"Well. We have some options I suppose.  You could try spending time away from the house, and if that works you could consider moving." I offered.

"I can't just buy and sell houses. I'm not rich, I've sunken every single penny into this place, and between the purchase and her father's funeral costs I have nothing left." She was becoming despondent.

"In that case.  I would suggest that we take a spiritual route.  We fight the spiritual with the spiritual.  We could call in a priest from our parish and he could cleanse the house." I was not able to think of any better plan.  I was embarrassed that my best idea was one inspired by 1970's horror movies.  I had never come across the need to cleanse a house of a force like this.  I had no real advice or ideas.  I only had what I had seen in heard in popular media.  It was the best I could offer.

"A Priest?" rolling her eyes "We're not Christian.  We're not religious and the last thing I want is some Priest in here blaming us for being sinners who don't accept Jesus.  I just... I'll try it but...."

Samantha caught my attention and spoke up. "There's another way. Do you remember my friend Dawnstar?"

I remembered her. She was one of Samantha's more normal friends, at least in appearance.  She looked like a model California beach community resident set against a plethora of goths and punks who typically kept company with Sam. She was spacey though, and could be very strange when she spoke.  She was heavily into practicing meditation, puling tarot cards, laying out crystals and the like.  A bright and sunny person, but how she chose to spend her time made her an outcast.  This is probably what led to her spending time with Sam and her pack of riff-raff.

"What about her?" I asked.  I had not seen her in about a year at this point.

"She's part of a group.  They meet twice a week to..." She glanced at Mrs. Felworth and then back at me. "To practice and experiment with situations like this.  They know what they are doing.  I think that they can clear the house."

"Like Wicca?" Mrs. Felworth perked up and actually seemed a bit excited about this idea.

"Something like that yes, but also different." Sam was addressing the mother now. "I've seen them do things.  Things that assure me that they might know how to fix this."

"When can they come?" She was clearly on-board.

We made plans to return with one or more members of the morbid little club over the next few days.  We parted ways and had yet another heated discussion on the way back.  I couldn't sleep that night.  Every time I turned, my shoulder burned. Each time it burned I had a surge of wonder and excitement that made my heart race.  We had experienced something real and startling this night.  Something beyond anything I had hoped for.  We had proof of something beyond what scientific laws could explain.

***

Update:

The day after this investigation as we organized the captured material and footage, we found something we had not expected. Once we had synced the time codes on our video footage to the audio that we captured on the tape recorder, we found a voice.  A voice that did not belong to anyone in that room.  The moment the lights went out, just before Lily spoke and I was injured, you could clearly hear on the audio tape (but not the video) the words "They Lie! They Lie Lie Lie!" in a dark, thin, shrieking voice.

[[Part 3](https://www.reddit.com/r/nosleep/comments/6a383q/willow_house_investigation_day_three_final/)]
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-05 20:30:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I agree. Its what I've come to after some rest and a day to ponder it. I think I actually lost a bit of my senses while it was happening. Its interesting to see how most people are misled in their conclusions from their perspective, but we will return with our skepticism intact shortly. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-05 15:30:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yes, this is why I reacted badly to seeing my hands spell that out.  It felt like I was saying something of the sort in front of her mother.  Of course I would never think like that but it did make me really self-conscious.  As if my subconscious had thoughts like that. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Willow House Investigation - Day One </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-05 04:38:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This is an official accounting of the investigation that took place on Willow Street, in October 2016. Members present were myself, Jason Renaud, and my associates Thomas Burgher and Samatha Bennett. Each can substantiate the experiences and offer up noted materials to support the claims made about the case.

I personally took the call from Mrs. Felworth approximately a week ago on October 9th and made some basic notes regarding her experience.  She and her daughter Lily had moved into a new home less than a month previous and reported several classic signs of haunting. Being somewhat familiar with the idea of spirits and general spirituality she decided to call our investigatory group and ask that we visit the home to assess what was happening. She seemed reasonable but slightly flaky on our call.  She was a devotee of meditation, yoga and had some dealings with people who considered themselves modern pagans.  My original impression was one of her wanting to believe that there was something other-worldly happening in her home.  That was until she began to speak about her daughter Lily.

Once the subject of her child came up she expressed nothing but a mortified attitude concerning what they had been through together.  She was clearly worried, and as much as I was sure that there were reasonable explanations for all of the phenomenon she mentioned, I decided that we should visit.  Even if only to allay her fears with twenty of the most common issues that made people believe that their homes were haunted.  We would tour her basement, showing her the knocking pipes.  We would point her toward old or faulty wiring that caused electrical issues.  We would locate the dead rodent that was certainly causing the stench that she mentioned.  This work was satisfying to us. All of us left investigations like this without being let down by the absence of a discovery, but instead happy to have helped a struggling parent.

We arrived at approximately six o'clock once I was able to pick up my friends.  The home was rather unimpressive, worn, but new enough to detract from any sense of history expected in common claims of haunting.  The yard and siding were somewhat unkempt, and the porch boards creaked as we reached it to put down our packs.  

Mrs. Felworth greeted us almost before we could ring the buzzer and ushered us in, helping with our gear.After a short moment of pleasantries I let her know that it was best if we began setting up a small cadre of equipment before speaking and she let us do so.  We did not bring all of our equipment this day, not expecting much, but we did setup a camera in the kitchen where we would interview the mother, and prepared the portable camera as well as our EMF readers and tape recorder for EVP analysis.  We did not expect much, but it was best to have these at minimum for any investigation.

"Is Lily home tonight?" I asked as Tom and Samantha were finalizing the setup.

"Yes, she's playing in her room. Do you want to speak with her?" She sipped her tea.

"Not yet, let's discuss what you've experienced before we bring her out and see if we cannot find some explanations." Tom and Samantha finished up and we all sat at the kitchen table together.  "So we understand that you've been smelling something strange, the lights are flickering and you've been hearing noises at night."

Mrs. Felworth look at me with some small disdain.  "Um, yes, but more than that. They all... they coincide with other things.  It's rarely just one thing."

"They all happen at the same time?"

"No, not necessarily those things but... " She looked to her left to Lily's room before proceeding. "The other night I went to use some perfume, as I was about to go out with a friend.  Lily had a sitter. Anyway, before I could reach the bottle on my side table it fell and smashed. On it's own.  And then there was this horrible smell."

The three of us looked at each other pondering that. Either could be explained quite readily, but certainly the combination of the two made a realistic explanation more difficult.

"That's not all." She seemed like she was desperate for us to understand.  "It fell on carpet. Soft carpet. But he bottle shattered."

I told her that it this was certainly intriguing, though it was certainly possible that the perfume had reacted with the carpet in a way to produce that smell.  It was likely some sort of chemical reaction. She confirmed that she did not have any more of that style of perfume so we could not test the theory. We moved on.

There were more examples like this.  She would feel a hand on her shoulder coming out of the bath and going down the hallway at the exact moment that the lights flickered.  She had seen a shadow cross the east window of the house, while a door slammed on the west wall behind her.  She would lose things only to find them days later wrapped in a tissue, or in the exact place she had thought she had left them days prior.  

"And then there is Lily." She looked down, deeply into her tea cup. "She's been, well, talking to someone. On a spirit board."

At this point Samantha sat upright from her slouch and began paying attention.  Thomas and I kept an extremely healthy skepticism about these sorts of things, but Sam was always the first to be excited about pursuits of this sort.  I don't know if it was part of the goth culture or if she was simply a serious horror fan, but she lit up at the mention of Ouija.

"Does you use it with her? Do you get responses?  What are they like?" Sam asked in quick succession startling the client slightly.

"No, Lily uses the board alone. I've never tried it myself.  But she does get answers.  It scared me so I packed it up and put it on top of the fridge a couple days ago, underneath the counters.  She had it again the next day and... was not herself for a few days.  It scared me so I let her keep it."

I told her that we were interested in speaking to Lily about that with her permission after proceeding to do a sweep of the house.  We toured the small two bedroom home rather efficiently noting any signs of common problems along the way.  We ran the water at each faucet to test for loose pipes that might create noise, or any dark water that might explain a foul odor.  We found no issue there.  We used the EMF reader and did an visual inspection of the wiring.  It was dated, but we could find no signs of gnawed wires or other damage that could explain the lights flickering.  We looked for any sign of infestation, rodent or insect, without result. After a time we returned the the kitchen table with no more information or explanation that we began with, and decided to get Lily to come speak with us.

Thomas greeted her immediately and spent a few minutes describing the things he liked about  her room. He was excellent with children and clearly made her feel comfortable with her new visitors. They were laughing about something in "Minecraft" before the silence fell and Lily turned to everyone and spoke.

"You wanna talk to him now?" Lily turned slightly toward her room.

Silence fell on the room heavily, and at that moment the lights in the kitchen began to flicker.  I shot a look at Thomas and then the camera.  He nodded affirmatively.  We were recording.  

"Talk to who sweetie?" Thomas asked her softly.

"Thin-man. He said you were gonna come talk to him." Her hands were on her hips now, as if she was accusing us of something.

Thomas asked her if he had told her we were coming as I met Mrs. Felworth's eyes.  She slowly shook her head no.  I took this to mean that she had not told Lily who we were and why we were there.

"Sure Lily." I said. "If it is ok with your Mom, let's talk." I spoke slowly but clearly.  

Her mother confirmed and Lily ran happily into her room to get her Ouija board, bringing back to the kitchen table. She slapped it down and unpacked it expertly, as if she had done so many times before.  The board was a standard variety game board that you could purchase anywhere, though it was a bit older and worn around the edges. The moment she had the planchette on the board she placed both of her little hands on it and looked up.

"Mister Thin-man. Hello." She giggled as the planchette wiggled back and forth under her fingers.  "That's how he says Hi now."

"Can you ask him what his name is?" Samantha prodded her.

"Umm.." her hands moved swiftly toward the "no" on the board.  "He doesn't like when you ask that. I just call him Thin-man."

"Can you ask him when he died?" Samantha tried again, giving the impression that she had also done this several times.

She agreed and asked him out loud.  She voiced out each letter as the planchette sped across the board.  "D... I...D...N...O...T. Ha, did not. He didn't die silly."

At this point because there was no possible way we could consider this evidence, I decided to change our tack. There was no way that we could trust that Lily wasn't simply spelling things out as she was only one on the board, and even if it was subconscious, it meant very little towards any kind of proof. In addition to this I was concerned about a child this age getting attached to a spirit board,  and began asking her how often she used it. I also asked her what kinds of things they talked about.  Each question was met with vague answers.  She said she used it once in a while when she wanted to talk, and that they talked about "all sorts of stuff."

All the while her hands were circling the board, around and around.  They began striking and stopping at letters once again, and spelled out the word "hand."

"He wants you to use the board." She looked at me and lifted her hands.

"Me?" I asked, somewhat startled by the request.

"Yep, your turn."  Lily spun the board around so that it was upright for me and sat back.  "Just make circles and see if he says something."

I looked at my partners and Mrs. Felworth before tentatively placing my hands on the planchette.  I was both expecting nothing, and fearing that something would actually happen.  I made a clockwise circle with the planchette, around and around. Everyone was dead silent and I could start to feel the silence like pressure in my ears.  I circled and circled, and felt heavier and heavier pressure on me as I did so.  The silence became oppressive and my head began to droop as if I was hypnotizing myself.  I struggled to cling to this idea as I began to feel somewhat nauseous, telling myself that this was how these things worked.  You get hypnotized running your hands in circles and bring up your subconscious to spell things out. I decided to try anyway.

"What do you like about Lily, Thin-man?" I was trying to keep things simple and natural, just as Thomas had broken the ice by complimenting her room. 

T..A..S..T..E.. the planchette pulled at these letters. It felt like my hands were being dragged along with it, not controlling it.  I tensed up and fought against the impulse, stopping completely.  Feeling that I had broken the illusion, I relaxed a bit.  The moment I relaxed it began again.

S...W...E...E...T

I looked up at Mrs. Felworth feeling shocked and rather embarrassed by what I had spelled out.  I pulled my hands away as if I had been caught doing something heinous.  The only thing worse than my embarrassment was the look in her eyes.  

Mrs. Felworth shot up from her seat. "Ok, thanks for showing us that Lily. You did a great job.  Why don't you go play, it's late and everyone needs to go home soon."

Lily was disappointing but did what she was asked. She made a point to say goodbye to each of us before packing up her board and returning to her room.  The moment her door swung closed, Mrs. Felworth began to leak tears in a steady stream.

I tried to reassure her. "This is perfectly natural.  Lots of kids have imaginary friends, this is just like that.  I don't see anything to worry about, it's just a developmental phase."  I was no psychologist but this seemed both true and comforting.

"You don't get it." She shook her head, tears dripping from her cheeks onto the table.  "This is not imaginary.  You were the only person on the board, and there's no way you could have known."

"Known? Known what?" I was perplexed.

"Lily... she's..." she sniffled. "She is Hyperglycemic.  It means she has very high blood sugar."

Silence fell again as what she was saying sunk in for all three of us.  I was the only one touching the board, and she was right.  I did not know this fact about Lily.  Yet it was my hands, or maybe not, that had spelled out those words about why the Thin-man liked Lily so much.  She tasted sweet.

Having had enough we decided to part company.  We also agreed that we should come back and do some further testing, and further documenting.  At this point I could not come up with any reasonable theory to explain what had just happened.  And an unanswered question like this demanded further work.  It seemed that perhaps something here was amiss.  Something unexplained was happening.  It was everything that the three of us in the group had hoped for, and also the last thing we expected or were prepared to deal with.  We left on good terms and had quite a heated discussion on the long ride home.  We plan to return within the week after we decide on our course of action.

[[Part 2](https://www.reddit.com/r/nosleep/comments/69p2ge/willow_house_investigation_day_two/)] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Roads of New England </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-03 00:24:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Some nights when the humidity is just right and the skies are clear, the glazed and mirrored cobblestone streets jump at you unawares.  Even after a few drinks, a small pile of pills and two days without sleep they can startle you. Shock you back to lucidity.  That certain flavor of clarity that you can only compare to sobriety, even though it's well beyond the intensity at which anyone sees the waking day. 

They jumped at me that night.  The dull textured curves of each stone seemed to eject themselves from the road toward my windshield.  I had been dreaming, but then I was awake. I can only imagine what it looked like when my boat of a Chrysler skidded twenty feet sideways.  What I do know is that it felt like an eternity on the inside of the behemoth. Regardless of the fact that I was in town and quite far from the ocean, there was still that sinking feeling of flying off into the distance.  Like a tether had been cut and I would hopelessly float through space counting the seconds of slow dreary emptiness.

The world stopped. The sounds ceased. I even sensed the smell of burning tire subside in a matter of seconds.  The buzzing inside my skull remained. There was no noise from the vehicle when I reset and turned the key.  Scanning the streets I found no one out at this hour.  I should not have been out at this hour myself, if I had not heard about a new speak-easy opening on North Willow. It was another place I didn't belong, among the young, naive and hopeful. The rich and carefree.  I had stayed for hours watching them soak up ten dollar drinks and smoke electronic cigarettes. Not a real person among them. No men, no women, just a conglomerate of children who had somehow become important for no particular reason.

I was determined not to let them end me.  Half of them had refused even to acknowledge me at the bar, while the others had bought me drinks with scorching pity in their eyes.  It was enough. I would not let their little hipster enclave end me like this.

I left the car, just like my father had taught me before the end.  I can still feel his hand on my shoulder and his ice blue eyes boring into mine the day he handed over my first set of keys.

"Wear your belt. Don't speed in your own neighborhood." Father had obviously had a list for me. "And if you've had some drinks and fuck up, just walk away.  They can't give you a breathalyzer if you're not there."

The man was not a great parent, but tried to do me a service.  That's how he was.  Always ready to offer a hard piece of advice from his own experience.  Always ready to try to keep you out of the cesspool that his life had become.  Always ready to accept the worst in you, and teach you how to live with it properly.

I took his advice and decided to try to find somewhere to sleep it off.  By the time the morning came I would sort out what to tell the police.  By that time I would be cleaned up and presentable.  I decided that I could even pass it off like I had gotten a concussion.

Elm, Franklin, Maple, Grove and Cross streets. I spun in a circle trying to get my bearings and remember motels in the area.

Wait. Cross? Cross Street?  I stared at the sign building a mental image of the town.  I turned and verified the many landmarks I recognized.  The Laundromat, the Dunkin Donuts, and the package store were all within spitting distance.  But then there was also Cross Street, between Maple and Grove, standing out like a void of understanding, like a dark gap in my internal compass.

I stumbled forward peering down the dark street.  It appeared entirely residential, with no storefronts, hell it didn't even seem to have street lights. I told myself that I must not know the street since there seemed to be little of interest on it, until I saw the small illuminated sign in the distance.  I covered my eyes, blocking out no light whatsoever as I squinted enough to make out the letters "B B".  The building sat at the very end of the street where it seemed to dead end.  The porch was lit gloomily in a dark red color.  It was the only color or light on this street and I could think of no other housing in this area.  I began to walk.

This walk also seemed to go on forever, looking left and right and taking step after step that seemed to get me no closer to my goal.  More and more I could make out the deteriorating cedar shingled exteriors of the homes on either side, if you could call them homes.  Some were entirely crumbling, others offered vast pools of standing water around the foundations.  Front doors hung at wide angles and shutters were disturbed and creaked in the slight breeze.  The smell of decaying plant matter began to overtake my senses.

I stopped looking to my sides and focused instead on the growing red glow of the porch light ahead of me. I walked and walked.  Assaulted by the growing stench of putridity, and starting to feel woozy again now that the adrenaline had surpassed. My legs began to fail me and it was all I could do to focus on my goal and get there before I was sick or lost consciousness.

I made it to the steps before dropping and vomiting violently over myself and the wooded steps at my feet.  My eyes bulged and burned as my consciousness seemed to be projected forward in the tumult of bile and whiskey spewing from me.  I raised my head gasping for breath once the sickness subsided. That is when I saw him.

My father.

Dead for twenty years.  He was standing on the porch looking down on me shaking his head.  I could recognize the particular pattern of oil stains on his coveralls. I could smell the rolled tobacco and gin all around him. He reached a hand down to me and his eyes burned with a strange light as he addressed me.

"I hoped you wouldn't join me."

Like the reflection on wet cobblestone, those eyes startled me out of my state.  I was running before I could even recognize the decision to do so.  The adrenaline was back and it carried me for what felt like miles.  My heart raced. Sweat poured from my body.  And still my legs pumped like a machine, until my foot caught something in the street and everything went dark.  Not as dark as Cross Street, but empty.

It was days later, when I awoke in the hospital that I learned about my discovery.  I was told by the officers attending to the door of my room that I was found spread out and unconscious on the hood of my car.  Apparently, while running back towards it, I had tripped over the tangle of bike in the street.  The bike's woner was ten feet behind my car, a limp, lifeless, broken little bearded man who I understand was named James.

Even today, years later I can appreciate this one thing about that night.  Prison is heaven, having managed to escape Cross Street. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-05 06:24:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yes, but we're polyamorous :) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Philadelphia: Jason Miller Lecture on Saturday March 4th! </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-02 15:53:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Vigo The Trumpathian </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-31 16:59:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Unexplained Incident in New Haven </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-10 00:06:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Greetings everyone.  My name is Dwayne.  I'm a state trooper out of New Haven Connecticut.  I've been on the force for almost 20 years and a few months back something strange happened that I've not been able to shake.  I've always been a bit of a drinker but ever since that night things have been bad.  I've been irritable, out of sorts and frankly drinking through each day.  I'm hoping that maybe sharing this with someone will help.  I can only imagine what my ex would say, so I'm turning towards the anonymous internet instead.

It was a fair day and I was cruising down 95 heading back to the station when I got the call.  "Young woman causing a scene crossing interstate 95." This was the entirety of the report. I called in to get the mile marker and found that I was relatively close.  I had been in a hurry to get off of work that day to see my daughter, but frankly the idea of seeing her mother was enough to encourage my to respond. I called in that I was on my way and headed toward the reported scene.  

This internet age is crazy.  Before I even reached the location I was watching a Youtube video of a young girl running and spinning in circles in the middle of the highway.  Sammy at dispatch had texted the link partially so I would know what was happening, but mostly because Sammy was a bored busy-body who loved gossip and glamorization.  Regardless, by the time I reached the scene I immediately recognized her.  She was hard to miss.  She was half naked, with the rags of a white camisole as her only protection against the elements.  She was crouched with her shoulder pressed alongside the concrete barrier and frantically peeking over, and then ducking back down.

I positioned my car to protect her from the flow of traffic and called in my position.  I carefully got out of the car, and approached her a gently as I could.  I had spent years dealing with domestic disputes, which more often than not, included some paranoid, drug addled husband.  The state of this woman looked very familiar, and I knew not to provoke someone as high as she must have been.

She saw me coming from long off and locked eyes with mine as I, step by step, got closer.  I held my hands low, palms down, showing that I was not a threat.  I was good at this and it worked.  She let me get within speaking distance without becoming startled, though her eyes were wild and full of trepidation.

"Sweetheart, I'm here to help you."

She ignore me, instead popping her head up and looking over the barrier to the opposite side of the highway.  I looked and saw nothing.

"You're in danger, young lady"

She spun her head to eyeball me intensely.

"Yes!" she whispered forcefully.

"Ok. Let me help you.  Get into the car and we'll leave."

I walked towards the car, looking over my shoulder to see her positioning and preparing to follow me like a cat.  The moment my door was open she darted from her position and was in the back seat of my cruiser faster than I would have imagined possible.

I pulled away and headed back to the station, all the while looking at her in my rear view.  She was cut, bruised, scraped and clearly not well.  She kept darting from one window to another looking for something.

"You're going to be ok now.  Can you tell me what happened?"

"They're coming."  She was distracted, still on the lookout.

"Did someone hurt you?  Are they here?" I slowed the car a bit in case the perp was in the local vicinity.  She did not answer, yet her answer was clear.  She was obviously worried about being found by  the people who hurt her.  I called into dispatch telling them that I had secured the girl, and that I was on my way back now.

She completely flipped out.  She started kicking the seat behind me, spinning her body and screaming.

"No! No!  They'll hear! They'll find us!" tears were streaming down her cheeks.

"Shh. It's ok. You're safe with me.  They won't be able to hurt you.  Do they have a police scanner? Is that what you mean?"  I was now starting to realize that this girl might not be crazy or drugged.  Her eyes were clear, and although highly disturbed, she did not seem to have the classic signs of a tweaker.

"They will hear." She lowered her voice, looking into my eyes in the mirror.

"Ok. Ok. No more radio.  We'll get you back to the station."

She calmed a bit and fumbled with her hands between her knees.  We only had a few minutes left until we reached the station and the detectives would take over.  My curiosity got the better of me and I continued to ask questions.  I knew that this was perhaps my only chance to actually figure out what was happening, and frankly the idea of tracking down the scum that hurt this young girl was exciting.

"Who did this.  Do you know where they are?"

"Elsewhere.  They took me.  They took me long ago and.... it's different. That place. They found me, and they're looking again.... to take me back, to take me." She was slow and despondent now.

"What does it look like, the place?  

"It's... It's bad, and purple.  It comes in waves but they hurt.  They pull at you, tearing. And the flashes, they... they pull too... but... your brain, your eyes."

This was getting nowhere fast.  I decided that I was not likely to get any legitimate information at this point and stopped.  My silence was interrupted by her fresh screams.  She held her temples with the palms of her hands, fingers extended, shouting "They're here now, they found me!"

Over her deranged shouting I heard the break of my radio, and answered it.  

"Car 19, this is dispatch, what's you're location?"

This was so routine as to be automatic for me. I looked out the drivers side window to check and replied instantly.

"Mile marker 36."  Then something stuck me. "Sammy?"

Silence.

"Sammy, that you?". I got nothing in return. "Hello?"

Silence.

And then it was too silent.  I looked in my rear view to nothing but an empty seat.  I jammed my breaks and pulled to the breakdown lane,  and ran out of the car.  I checked the back thoroughly to find nothing. No one.  She was just.... gone. There was no sign she'd ever even been there.

I came back to the station empty handed.  I was questioned about what was going on.  I told them the truth.  I told them every single part of what I'm telling you.  What I got in return was a 3 week leave, and to never be looked at without concern since.  I still have my career, but no one on the force treats me the same.  I don't treat myself the same.  I learned on that day that there was something enormous and unexplained among us.  I was no threat to it, probably not even a consideration compared to that.  But "that" exists.  My reality is theirs.  They are here, and there is nothing I can do about it.

I just pray that they never want me. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-08 21:40:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thanks so much!  So wonderful of you to share. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> I Met Someone *Wrong* on OkCupid [Part 5] </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-08 19:08:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [[Part 1](https://www.reddit.com/r/nosleep/comments/5hug40/i_met_someone_wrong_on_okcupid/)]

[[Part 2](https://www.reddit.com/r/nosleep/comments/5i1n3o/i_met_someone_wrong_on_okcupid_part_2/)]

[[Part 3](https://www.reddit.com/r/nosleep/comments/5i8ujt/i_met_someone_wrong_on_okcupid_part_3/)]

[[Part 4](https://www.reddit.com/r/nosleep/comments/5looog/i_met_someone_wrong_on_okcupid_part_4/)]

I awoke screaming.  The memories of that day flooded me immediately and I thrashed, my vocal chords screaming in pain.  Then I realized there was no pain. I turned my head to the left to examine my wound to find something that shocked me out of my immediate reaction.  There was no wound. No missing finger. There was however blood, dark and crusty on my hand and smeared down the side of the bed to the floor.  I gripped my hand, waggled my fingers and stared in astonishment to see that I was whole.  

"You're ok." Erica whispered from the bedside at my feet.

I raised my head as high as I could to see her, sitting in a small folding chair, hands folded in her lap.  The skin around her eyes were red and she looked like she had not slept for some time.  The sides of her mouth twisted as she struggled to meet my eyes with hers.

"Erica, let me out.  Get me out of here!" My voice sounded like an old jazz singer who smoked two packs a day.

She looked down at her feet, and remained silent.

"Let me out!" I managed a hoarse yell.

"Shhh. They'll hear you. Please, please be quiet." she pleaded.  "I'm so sorry.  You don't understand.  I'll explain everything. Just keep it down before they hear us."

She cautiously put her hand on my leg.  Her head darted to the right, and then to the left.  I saw her nostrils flare as she inhaled in each direction, and held the silence for several moments.  After a minute she relaxed and removed her hand and lowered her head into her palms.

"This was the only way." Tears streamed down her cheeks.  "The only way you could survive.  They were going to kill you, because.... because of me."  She wept openly now.  Though I was overcome with anxiety I still found myself able to give her time to process.

"I knew that they would never let me be with an outsider.  I just... I thought that if I was careful, they would not find out.  I needed to be in the world, to be part of something normal.  To get away and have something of my own, something normal." Her words were rapid and desperate. "I needed that.  I'm sorry, I should have known. I can never have that, and now...."

"Now what? what are they going to do to me?"

"They won't kill you.  They can't kill you now."

I was overcome with frustration at this answer.  I'd had enough of being in the dark.  I instinctively raised my fists until the chains stopped the motion and raised my head.

"Tell me! Tell me what's going on! You owe me that!" My guttural voice shocked me.

"You're one of us now.  You're a Lycanthrope.  I did this, I made you this.  I'm so sorry but it was my only choice.  The only way to save you from elimination.  They would have killed you without blinking an eye. But now they can't.  We don't kill our own kind, and now you are one of us."

I let this sink in.  I had known it already. I had subconsciously understood what was happening.  Having someone actually say it outright helped me to accept the facts, though it still took me some time and effort to accept the obvious.

"So I'm... I'm a werewolf now? And your friends there cannot kill me?  So what now.  Are they planning on keeping me chained as some kind of pet?"

"The council has been discussing you for hours.  The local chancellor of the Order is on his way to partake in the decision making.  My assumption is that they are going to stay very close to you as things develop until they can trust you.  I assume that your training will begin as per normal once they are finished."

"What do you mean by my training?  What is the Order?  What do you people do?"  The more information I received led only to more questions.

"Listen, I don't have much time.  I am expected at the council shortly to receive their ruling, so I'll try to answer quickly.  We work for the Order. You could say that we are the military branch.  We're their right hand acting as mercenaries and are allowed to continue to exist in return.  It is very rare that we can reproduce, which makes you very special.  Only one in a hundred manage to survive the trauma I put upon you and survive... and turn.  That's why our prime directive is to never destroy our own kind.  Our line is too precious, too rare and the Order insists that we consistently grow our numbers.  You will be trained in how to fight.  How to turn. And use your senses to accomplish the Order's goals.  How to retain your purpose through the transformation.  You will be trained to be one of us, until they feel you can be trusted, and then you will be their soldier, and our brother."

I listened intently, taking it all in.  Before I could ask another question, Erica stood and told me that she must leave.  That the council would be back in session until the morning, and that I should get some rest for tomorrow.  She clearly rejected any further conversation, apologized again and left swiftly.  She left me in that dank empty room.  Chained, overwhelmed, and in complete despair.

My mind raced, going over everything she had said.  Remembering the torture and it's lack of lasting impact.  Remembering those men, those "brothers".  What they looked like, how they acted.  They were animals in the bodies of men, dispensing pain like hapless goons.  I smelled the filthy, hairy, sweaty truth around me.  And I knew.  I knew that I could never be a part of this.  I focused on planning my escape.

The memory of this night is still painful for me.  The desperation, the pain, the blood, and the madness that took over my being is beyond my comprehension.  The plan was fast and dirty, and the action began before I could even consider any other option.  I began tearing at the mattress with my finger nails.  It was probably thirty minutes before I made any real progress, and in that process I had damaged my right hand quite badly.  I tore two nails completely off of my fingers by the time I managed to get through the outer material, and both my hands and the mattress were thick with blood.  

Knowing that I would heal was of no comfort to the pain of the moment, but I continued frantically.  My fingertips could now grasp the metal springs inside the mattress and I rapidly pulled and pushed them back and forth trying to generate friction.  This process took another agonizing thirty minutes, but I did finally managed to dislodge a four inch piece of steel spring.  This was likely only possible due to the advanced age, and rusting wear on the metal.

I pressed the end of the coil against the metal bed frame to straighten enough of it to suit my purposes. Once I had this tool I set to work on the locks that held the chains together around my left wrist.  I began to worry that even if the council was tied up all night I might never succeed.  There was no turning back.  Someone would surely see what I had done, had I tried to hide the tool for another time, so I persevered.  After an hour I gasped as I heard the "pop" of the master lock opening on my left cuff.  I set to work on my feet and right hand.  These went much more quickly now that I had a feel for the methodology, and soon I was free of my bonds.

And like that, I was up.  I sped around the room, checking the door, examining the walls, and then searching through the large trunk in the corner.  I found a machete and tucked it into my belt against my back.  After examining my inventory and surroundings I decided on my best course of action.  There was no way that I was getting through the door, so I turned my sites on the wall.  I located a position in the west wall that was clearly above ground. I could see where there had been a basement window there previously.  I also hoped that this now patched portion of concrete might be less stable than the rest.

I was relieved to find that the battery-pack-powered saws-all that I had found in the trunk was charged and functional.  I readied myself for the noise it would make.  I knew that it might bring my "brothers" and prepared myself for needing to fight if they came through the door.  After ensuring that the machete was easily drawn, I began pressing the running saw into the creases in the concrete.  I was about eighty percent through tracing a body sized square when the blade broke.  I cursed, and ran back to the trunk to retrieve the small sledge hammer, and began smashing at the center of my framed outline.  In a ten minute fury of smoky, pounding and rubble I could soon see the woods and had enough room to escape.  

Even though I had moved the trunk to this wall in order to lift myself through the hole, I still tore my chest and stomach badly as I dragged my body though the tight space.  The concrete ripping at my skin was excruciating but I knew that time was of the essence.

And then I was free.  Bloody, torn, bleeding profusely, and free.

I tore through the woods toward the nearest road.  I did not make it far before my body began to make it very clear that it was finished.  I imagine that it head been at least twelve hours since I had eaten, or had any water. I had lost a lot of blood and overexerted myself for hours straight during my escape.  The falling stars beginning to overtake my vision convinced me that I had very little time left.

I ran in circles, moving outward to locate somewhere to hide. To find some salvation of any kind that might ensure that I could not be tracked or found.  What I did find at the last possible moment was the driveway to the complex, in which sat one single car.  It was a polished, pitch black Jaguar. And to my relief it was empty.

I found the car unlocked, and quickly checked for keys as my legs began to give out on me.  No such luck.  I did the only thing I could in the last few moments of consciousness.  I got into the trunk and pressed my body as far back as possible after closing the lid tight.

And once again, darkness took over.
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> I Met Someone *Wrong* on OkCupid [Part 4] </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-03 01:23:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [[Part 1](https://www.reddit.com/r/nosleep/comments/5hug40/i_met_someone_wrong_on_okcupid/)]

[[Part 2](https://www.reddit.com/r/nosleep/comments/5i1n3o/i_met_someone_wrong_on_okcupid_part_2/)]

[[Part 3](https://www.reddit.com/r/nosleep/comments/5i8ujt/i_met_someone_wrong_on_okcupid_part_3/)]

I apologize for the delay in updating.  If you understood what has been going on, which you will soon, I'm sure you will understand.  I am currently at a library in New Jersey, and frankly not very happy about being back in the exact same spot that I was in when I last wrote. Let me try to catch you all up.  I'm hoping that some of you may have some advice for me.  The comments last time were helpful in thinking about different ways I could proceed, though frankly the outcome has not been very successful.  It may take me a couple posts to cover everything that's happened since last I posted though.

Several people mentioned that I had no idea what I was up against with "The Order" in it's size, scope and reach.  Once I settled and recovered from my sister's death I realized that this was true.  I realized that this notion of going in, guns blazing for revenge, was a completely illogical and suicidal maneuver. I also took into account much of the advice given regarding how to mask my scent and perhaps deter the pack from locating me.

In the end I decided that information gathering should be my first goal, and that I needed to proceed cautiously.  I cashed out the debit card that I had and bought some supplies at a local hunting store.  I bought and adorned a set of "Scent-a-way" hunting clothes, applied some apple cider vinegar to my boots and around my body, and stole off into the night towards Erica's house.  This seemed the only move I had to get more information about what I was facing.  Knowing where she lived was the only lead.

I parked my rental about a half a mile away, behind a small church at about 10 pm and begin to hike up the hill to her home.  I was careful not to approach it directly, but to cut a circuitous path around the back of her house. When I got within a decent viewing distance I stopped behind cover and watched the house. I was astounded at my luck.  Only minutes after I arrived at this position I saw her exit the back door and walk into the woods.  Keeping a safe distance I slowly and quietly trailed her through the thicket.  She eventually reached a large patch of bamboo growing alongside a small cliff and began chapping at stalks using the machete she had brought with her.

This was my chance.  My chance to speak to her alone and find out what was really going on. I slowly began to approach with my hand gripping the 9mm in my jacket pocket.  She stopped dead and spun around as soon as I was a thirty feet behind her.  

"Erica, it's David." I said quietly, trying to ensure that I did not startle her.

"David! What the fuck are you doing here, are you crazy?" she dropped the machete and ran towards me. "You can't be here! You need to leave now!"

She gripped my shoulders hard. I could feel her nails digging in, even with the thick hunting jacket between us. She lowered herself looking pleadingly up and into my eyes while she began to repeatedly whisper the word "no" and close her eyes.  In a moment I noticed why. Over her shoulders I could see several yellow reflective eyes in the thicket behind her.  There were at least five but I instantly assumed that there were just as many at my sides and behind me. They were all moving, bobbing left and right, and getting closer fast.

"Fuck!" I shouted starting to turn to attempt to flee.

She held me hard, it was almost as if there was no possible way I could turn my body as she looked at me deeply in the eyes, and whispered "I'm sorry."

The searing pain made me scream for only seconds until my vocal cords tore at which point there was only silence, and my vision was filled with crimson.  Erica, in a split second, had drawn her arm back and slashed my chest.  I saw no weapon in her hand but the instant agony I felt made it clear that she had harmed me greatly.

There was the pain. There was the red overtaking my vision.  And then the red turned to black.

***

I awoke.

The first thing I recall as I awoke was the searing white light burning my eyes.  The pain in my head was splitting, but dissipated quickly and I was soon able to get a feel for my surroundings.  I tried to sit up to no avail, finding that each of my limbs were restrained.  My wrists and ankles were wrapped in thick leather cuffs, each wrapped through large eyelets with heavy chains.  I was strapped down onto a dirty mattress and metal bed frame that looked like it had been stolen from an abandoned prison.  I looked down at my bare chest to where I had remembered being hit or stabbed but there was no obvious injury. I quickly concluded that perhaps I had been injected with something.  That could explain both the pain and the quick loss of consciousness. The room around me was almost entirely empty.  Just bare concrete walls, sections stained in a variety of colors and patterns that made my head spin. 

There was one door in the room.  It was a large steel freezer door with the handle removed.  The only other item in the room was one old rotting trunk in the corner.  I did not like this look of this.  The single light above my head swayed very slightly back and forth, making the shadows of that box waver slightly, drawing my gaze toward it again and again.

I thought about screaming and quickly decided that it was in my best interest to take some time to think.  Even if it's only affect was to delay what was coming.  I focused on perceiving anything I possibly could about what was going on around me.

Now that my eyes had adjusted to the light I started to notice that there was something strange about the room.  As dirty as it was, and even though the lighting was not very bright it had a strange feeling to it.  It was very crisp, like everything here had been meticulously outlined.  I began to listen closely and I could hear footsteps and muffled speech. The steps did not sound as though they were being made on the flooring though, they had this soft low impact.  They sounded like someone in heavy boots stomping on the ground.  My hopes were raised slightly thinking that clearly this room was near an exterior wall, and that it must be a very thin one for me to hear the men outside.  Perhaps if I managed to escape my bonds I could use the metal bed frame to get through the cinder block over time.

My attention followed the sounds of the people outside. I felt like there were three of them.  They smelled quite strongly, their mildew-like scent assaulting my nose and I traced their movement across the wall in front of me.  I could feel their presence.  The sound and the smell all accumulated into this almost vision-like sensation of their forms playing in patterns on the wall.

Something was wrong with me.  My pulse quickened and I began to hyperventilate.  Something was really wrong.  My only thought was of change.  I needed to be up.  I needed to get a hold of myself. Just sit up and put my face in my palms, or my hands on my pounding heart.  I twisted and turned, pulling, almost turning the bed over with my thrashing.

"He's up." I heard very clearly from the corner of the room.  The voice was coming from outside, but I could then feel them moving.  Then a door opening, then steps, then the door next to me unlatching.

The three men that entered were dirty, smelly and intense.  They each looked like they had been Hell's Angel's in a past life, and then had taken up hunting and camping for a year straight.  There was no "Order" to these men.  They were like animals.  Clothes torn. Stains everywhere. Each a patchwork of leather, denim, camouflage and grease.

The darker man moved to the corner, squatted and opened a can of dip, pressing some between his gums and dark teeth.

"Wayll Eddie, herie is." One of the still standing men said to the other, while the squatting man remained silent in the corner. "Watchya think then?"

"Jaysus, really?  For this scrawny fuck?" The other standing man replied.

He moved toward me, and I tried my damnedest to sink my body back into the bed away from the approaching man.  He was big, about six foot two, wide shouldered and muscular. He bent over me closely, putting his face inches from my own. His smell and his greasy pock-marked skin began to make me nauseated to the point of heaving.  He then drew in a long nasal breath moving his head down from my face to my chest.

I started to retch. He stood straight, drew back his arm and slammed it with all his force into my stomach, pinned on the hard mattress.  My body tried to curl up and protect my core, but was prevented by my restraints.  I cannot even explain the pain, the fear of not being able to breath, the sheer primal instinct that took over to protect myself.  The two men laughed and pushed at each other as they watched my pain.

"Ain't much to lookat, but hay, maybe he got something special inside, Dane." Eddie said back, answering Dane's question. 

They both laughed repeating "Yeah something special on the inside..." as they walked over to the box in the corner and began rooting around in what sounded like a pile of tools.

"Aight, let's see" Dane said now coming back at me with something in his hand.  "Maybe issin his foots?"

He bent over my legs, and pulled off my sock.  The pain from the gut punch just starting to subside, I raised my head as best I could to look.  He had a pair of rusty garden shears in his hand and pressed them against the bottom of my left foot. I pleaded. It was all I could do, as tears started to stream down my face.

"She ain't no foot girl Eddie. Maybe she likes somethin' else? Ya think?"

"Oh, yeah maybe that's it!" Eddie pulled at my belt and put the shears hard against my crotch. 

I screamed. I yelled for help. I twisted, swore, spat, and leaked frothy spittle and tears.

"Naw, I think HE likes that more than she does." Eddie stood straight removing the shears as I quieted down into a whimper. "Awww... she must love those though.  Lookat those lily white hands.  There ain't an ounce a' work on those.  Ain't they just lovely Dane?"

"Yays they is!  I wish I had dem lovely fingers a' his. Like a baby's."

"A'right you can have one." Within seconds Eddie had the pinkie finger of my left hand between the blades of those rusted shears, and a second later the pain once again overwhelmed my consciousness. 

As I began to black out I remember seeing Eddie throw something to Dane as they danced and laughed.  They were making a game of tossing my finger back and forth as they circled they room like monkeys.

They man in the corner stood up slowly looking right into my eyes.

"Not much to look at, true.  But he is one lucky fuck." These were his first and only words this day.

Then once again, blackness took over.


[[Part 5](https://www.reddit.com/r/nosleep/comments/5ms5j6/i_met_someone_wrong_on_okcupid_part_5/)]
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-14 20:54:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I think that perhaps it took the combination of the plant and that symbol to keep them at bay.  It's the only thing that makes sense, she did have a basket of it in her hand when attacked. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-14 19:51:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I've not been allowing myself to picture that.  I'm still chalking this up to the fact that Erica did absolutely have some emotional and mental issues, even if some of what she said was accurate.  This is just to ridiculous to consider. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-14 19:25:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm worried that that's the case as well. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-14 17:44:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I get the feeling that she has been trying to escape them for some time.  It is because I saw her that they are after me, however at this point I think that she wants out, and is trying to save me. I hope she is ok. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-14 16:49:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I don't have a brother.  I'm not sure where you got that from, I checked my writing to make sure I didn't accidentally type brother anywhere, and don't see that anywhere.  Appreciate your interest though. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-14 16:15:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yes, absolutely. I see that now. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> I Met Someone *Wrong* on OkCupid [Part 3] </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-14 06:28:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [[Part 1](https://www.reddit.com/r/nosleep/comments/5hug40/i_met_someone_wrong_on_okcupid/)]

[[Part 2](https://www.reddit.com/r/nosleep/comments/5i1n3o/i_met_someone_wrong_on_okcupid_part_2/)]

I have to say, I read many of the comments on my previous posts and scoffed.  It seemed at the time that some of the people on this forum were as, if not more, disturbed as Erica was.  I know better now.  You were trying to warn me of something that you understood and I did not.  Hindsight is always twenty-twenty. I want to humbly thank the people who posted the more extreme warnings. You tried to help, and it fell on deaf ears.  I'm currently sitting in a Starbucks in Southern New Jersey, face dirty and teared as I wish, more than anything, that I had listened to you.

I know that it's important to stop for a few hours and post this.  It may very well be the only chance of ensuring that a record of these events can survive. I don't expect any of you to put yourselves into any danger for me, but if i do disappear perhaps this will serve to convince someone that there is something bigger happening here.

After the fire filing of the police report, a representative from my home insurance company met met.  He gave me a prepaid debit card, since I had lost my wallet, with an advance on the future claim.  This turns out to be standard procedure after a house fire and was immensely helpful as I processed the shock of my ordeal.  At first I felt fine.  An hour after I checked into the sparse hotel room I began to not feel so well.  I spent hours vomiting and coping with the sudden onset of emotion now free to flow, now that the ordeal was over.

I had no home. I had almost been killed.  My carefully constructed life was falling apart around me and I had no power in the situation.  All I had was myself and that was crumbling, unable to recover from the trauma.  I won't call it a breakdown, but I had a very difficult night, with little sleep and no comfort.  In the darkest hour I did something I have not done in a number of years.  I called my sister, Evie. 

I love me sister, and she loves me.  That said, we were always extreme opposites and it always made out time together explosive.  While I secured a solid job at an insurance company, she traveled freeloading off of random strangers.  In college when I drank too much, she tried to convince me that alcohol was poison and that I should smoke more marijuana instead.  When I hosted Thanksgiving one year she was suddenly vegan.  You get the picture.

She is always there for me though.  And I have always done my best to do the same for her when she was in need.  I think that she had been in need much more often than me, but that is neither here nor there.  Upon receiving my call and hearing my voice along with some basic details about the fire, she insisted that I get up to her house as quickly as possible.

By yesterday at 10am I was there, pushing aside a multitude of wind chimes to enter her quirky little cabin.  She embraced me until I felt extremely uncomfortable, and  then kept going for another few minutes.  Over a pot of tea that she had actually cultivated herself, I told her the same story I told the police, including all the detail I could remember.  She sat, sipping her tea, and kept her eyes wide, drinking in everything I told her for an hour straight without saying a word.

"Draw it." She said at the end.

"Draw what?"  I was pretty sure that she was trying to induct me into some weird art therapy or something by having me creatively express the events.

"The symbol on your door, draw it for me."

I grabbed a pen from her counter and did as she asked.  

She stared at my drawing and immediately said a word that I recognized from some of the redditor's posts.  

"Thurisaz... I..." she jumped from her seat and left the room.

After a few moments of stunned silence I slowly followed to find her in a small room filled with disorganized stacks of books. This is just like her, I thought.  All ofher money spent of hundreds of off-the-wall books and nothing left to buy a bookshelf. She flipped through and flung three books in the corner before finding what she had been looking for.

"Ok, here it is.  I was right" she moved her finger across the lines of text in the book she was holding.  "This is one of two things, David.  Some interpretations consider this a protective rune, and other interpretations consider it to be a Thorn and describe it as a mark of coming destruction."

"Ok, so it is a mark of something?  It means something in particular?"

"[muttering].... catch up already. What was in it? You said something was in it."

"Oh some plant. The whole symbol was stuffed with this plant."

"What did it look like?"

I described it as best as I could, telling her it had small leaves, tall stalks and little purple flowers.  She seemed to come to a realization, and again began tearing apart her book stacks like a banshee.

"This?  Like this?" she held color photos of the plant I had removed from my door much too close to my face.

"Yes, I think that's it.  What is this about?  What are you thinking?"

She rose and took my hand in hers, holding it warmly.  She lead me back to her kitchen and refilled out tea.  This mysterious act was starting to piss me off, but I let her retain the drama.  Trying to get her to not be dramatic usually made it worse.

"You need to call that girl.  She was trying to protect you" She said matter-of-factly.

"It's some protection symbol then?  Protect me from what?"

"Just... there's something after you David, she was trying to stop it."

"What is it?" I asked, getting more miffed by the second.

We stared at each other for what seemed like minutes before Evie lowered her head.

"The herb that was inside, and charging the protection symbol, was Wolfsbane.  Wolfsbane is only used to protect someone against one thing."

I sat quietly looking at her, until it hit me.

"Oh come on." I stood up quickly. This was too much, and I needed sanity at the moment, not more madness to deal with.

"You had a protection rune on your door, David.  It was stuffed with wolfsbane.  And you said yourself, you heard dogs but there was no sign of them on the camera footage." She was being cautious, I could tell.  She was not saying it outright but trying to lead me to the conclusion that she had clearly made.

Thinking about that rough panting noise did strike a cord.  I was not one to ever possibly consider such an outlandish notion, but there were some congruent facts here. I decided to consider it for a moment and give the idea a fair shaken knowing that in five minutes I could at least say that I had considered it after I blew it off as laughable.

"Ok so basically, you think that Erica came and tried to protective me from werewolves.  That the noise I heard was just that.  That I'm being hunted by, what, a pack I guess?"

"Do you have a theory that fits better?" she had this little smirk as she sipped at her cup.  "Why don't you call and ask her?"

I remembered at that moment that I had in fact picked up a disposable cell phone on the way here to call Erica.  Again, I must thank those who posted this advice.  Calling from a landline was certainly not a good solution.

I called Erica, and I got her on the phone immediately.  I told her who it was and asked her what was going on.  I was in a rush and got right to the point.  She took the bait and made it clear that she had knowledge of what was happening.

"Fuck David, what happened? are you safe?" she was whispering harshly. "How did they get past the door?"

I told her that I had replaced the door, and that they had burned my house down.  I asked who were they were and how I could make this all stop.  I begged her to help me.

"You need to go now.  The Order, they're coming. They will find you, your not safe, hide now.  They're different David, they can smell you, they will find you no matter..."

Then there was silence.  I was shocked back to reality by the busy signal now ringing in my ear.  Repeated attempts to call her back yielded no results.

"So, they can smell you?" Evie had that little smirk on again.  She had obviously heard Erica's side of the conversation.

She beckoned me to follow her as she opened her cabinets and started handing me several containers of salt. She hurried me to her front yard and started pouring a thick stream of it on her front walkway drawing it slowly and meticulously around the house.

"Evie, what are we doing?"

She told me that she thought that this might protect us.  In no uncertain terms she made it clear that we could talk after we drew a complete circle around her house.  Once that was done Evie told me that she was not positive that the salt would stop the things that were after me, and that she needed to do more.  She shot down my complaints and attempts to bring her back to reality.  

I can't even cope with writing this right now, so I'll just give you the facts.  She told me that there was a patch of wolfsbane in the woods just outside her house and needed to get it.  She asked me to collect branches while she was harvesting the herb so that we could fashion another protection symbol.  The woods were bright that night,  with the clear skies and bright moon, which made it very easy to accomplish our work.

Just as both of us rose from collecting, her with a basket of wolfsbane and me with a bundle of branches under my arms, we heard it.  We heard the howling.  The penetrating low tone of wolves around us.  We could hear them in the South and the East coming from the deeper forest.  We could hear them even closer in the West and North near to her home.

I can still see her eyes.  Lit by the moon and weeping slightly, locked onto mine as her torso was unnaturally pushed sideways, and her body followed.  The enormous bundle of ears, paws and teeth had come flying from nowhere, leapt and carried her several feet without a sound.

I left her.  I fucking just ran.  I didn't even look back.  I even felt relief as two more wolves shot past me toward her location.  I'm sorry Evie.  I'm so sorry.

I've got nothing left.  No family. No home. Nowhere to go. No one to help me. Not only that but I am now a person of interest in my sisters death because I fled the scene.  I have no choice but to try to disappear and I can only imagine what it looks like to the police investigating her murder.

So I'm sitting here in a random Starbucks. I'm hunted by police.  I'm hunted by wolves.  I'm haunted by the knowledge that I killed the only person that I really loved. I have nothing left to protect. I'm cornered, and I have only one move.  To find The Order and stop this, or at least avenge poor Evie.  I'd like to say that my pain has lead me to gear up, get angry, and fueled me to bring the fight to them.  But I don't feel that way.  I just feel like my only option, is likely suicidal.  But I have no choice.

I'm getting back on the road now.  I've withdrawn the cash from my debit card, and have an Uber coming to drive my further north.  I plan to find a safe location, attempt to finally act on the information that I now have regarding protection, and locate the Order.  I will update you as soon as I can.


[[Part 4](https://www.reddit.com/r/nosleep/comments/5looog/i_met_someone_wrong_on_okcupid_part_4/)]
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-13 17:11:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Me too. I'm headed to my sister's house now.  I really need to think about making sure that this does not affect her.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-13 16:50:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yes, I did look this up. I do have the right to do so in PA.  Though I'd still prefer to avoid killing someone if possible. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-13 16:33:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This is excellent advice. I am planning on calling her.  You're right, I should be sure to use a burner.  Thank you for the excellent advice. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-13 16:32:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Ha, yes this might help me from being really stupid in the moment if god forbid something like this happens again. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-13 16:31:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The insurance company sent a rep to meet me, and provided me with a prepaid debit card as an advance on the claim.  I learned that this is standard practice for a house fire. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-13 16:30:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yes, they met me and advanced me some claim money for a hotel and food before we process the claim.  I never knew, but there is a whole system for this type of thing. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-13 16:30:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yes, that night a rep met me at the police station and gave me a prepaid debit card as an advance for the future claim.  So I do have money and a temporary place to stay though I think I will be staying with family shortly.  Will update asap.  Thanks for your concern. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
