<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject513</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-09 11:28:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Lolololol thank you for making my morning more entertaining </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-09 05:10:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The worst part is that /r/battlefield_live is the same way and the devs actually listen to those idiots  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-05 20:22:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> In my opinion that is exactly what your proposed changes would accomplish. Killing infantry is part of piloting, its the only real way you make a difference on the game as a pilot and I'm sick of this misinformation being spread. 

Your changes will make things such that one or two determined players could take out planes on their own without an AA gun. Ridiculous. Any decent team will shoot every plane out of the sky. God forbid an enemy pilot you're trying to dogfight has a squad on the ground with your changes   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-05 20:09:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Your changes would make getting in a plane a total waste of time against any remotely decent team. Everything I've read of yours would lead to a game where Infantry hardly die to planes and planes get shot down in about a minute. Oh and pilots wouldn't be able to score much. 

Only change of yours I agree with is that dogfighting should be more rewarding score wise. I also believe they should make it take time for pilots to bail on their planes, to let the people shooting them down get more kills.

I really don't get how the total percentage of vehicle kills for planes going down makes you think Dice should essentially nerf their air to ground capabilities more. 
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-05 16:25:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I can't see it happening, there would be riots </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-05 11:43:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> When we say things like this we sound like the Republicans used to over Obama. They are assholes but I don't think anybodies canceling any elections.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-05 11:38:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> me too thanks  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-05 10:50:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm mad because Dice doesn't consider console users opinions as much when they make massive changes to the game. Its apparent at this point. I'm sick of the massive influence PC BF1 players are enjoying, while being only ~30% of the games playebase.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-05 10:48:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Honestly people on this sub look for anything to complain about they can. They are some of the biggest whiners on the internet. I think the game is going to ultimately end up worse because Dice listened to this sub too much.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-04 18:59:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Because not everyone can slide and aim well at the same time. It takes skill to do well. I'm just pointing out how saying "Hurr durr its just pressing a button" is a bad argument.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-04 18:46:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Not like you're going to hold them accountable and vote D next time. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-04 18:40:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Literally everything in this game consists of "pressing a button" so bad argument.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-04 17:25:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I hate it, adds more randomness to the game and in my mind thats never a good thing.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-04 16:57:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> "kind sir" get out of here with that cringy phrasing  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-04 16:41:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah, maybe get good at it and do it yourself instead of complaining eh? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-04 16:37:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I fly very well and dogfight with the best of them. After looking at my stats I think you'll find I'm not full of shit. 

The 20 kill thing was refering to conquest btw, I used to do 40-60 pretty consistently in conquest. Operations is where the 80-100+ kill games happened. My best was 129-2. I can still pull off 50ish kills in a full op. It kinda sucks though becasue I could easily get 50 kills as infantry in a full op. I miss feeling like my plane was making a difference. Now I feel like I'm picking off stragglers </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-04 15:57:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> oH So S3RiiOUS  on Xbox  I have 9500 kills with the fighter I've played with it quite a bit if that's what you're looking up haha  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-04 15:36:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's a skillful mechanic in the game, don't get why people on this sub complain about how casual it is only to follow up with complaints about the skillful aspects.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-04 15:34:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Please don't slow the soldiers down, they move at a good pace that keeps games lively and gets you to objectives in a reasonable amount of time. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-04 15:32:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You're going to have to use paragraphs if you want that monster read  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-04 15:30:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I assure you I'll never get up to the 80-100 kill games again  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-04 15:29:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> But how could you see planes on Suez when there are no planes on Suez? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-04 04:20:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> People that really understand the mechanics and classes are usually good so it kinda goes hand in hand </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-04 04:12:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thats just the biggest bullshit. That they can hide things under "Budget Bill" status to avoid fillibusters. ACA took 60 votes to get passed and it should take 60 to be repealed.

Why didn't the democrats just use this same underhanded strategy to pass single payer? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-04 03:30:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Players on PC are a lot less casual, and it leads to different game play. I wish dice would balance the game differently for PC and Console, they aren't near the same.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-04 03:22:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You must play on PC because it is not like this at all on Xbox in the games I play. I have something like 11 days of gameplay as infantry, and I have never seen a bomber destroy a tank in a game.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-04 03:12:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah 99% of people are bad at using the bomber and the Attack plane gets shot down near instantly by anyone on an AA. The attack plane and bomber don't dominate shit most of the time, even when they are the only planes in the sky.

They made the best plane kinda bad and it exposed all the other underused planes because as things stand now you're not making a difference against a remotely decent enemy team as a pilot. They will shoot you down with buffed AAs or let you have your pitiful 20ish kills as the trench fighter. A plane or a tank should have the ability to change the game and as things stand right now planes have had that largely taken from them.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-04 03:05:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Guy is clearly not good at the game and his opinions should be ignored </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-04 03:05:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I stopped reading as soon as you said bolt actions are worthless. You clearly are bad at the game and have no further opinions worth looking at. The bolt actions are amazing.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-04 02:57:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Oh my I have a reason to use the Flame variant!!!  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-04 02:56:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Do you think that fix could make it in at some future time? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-04 02:55:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If they did that then literally everyone would run repair tool though, and that would change the game a lot. Tanks would be very hard to kill. 

Also a person that like the Huot? You should do an AMA </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> If the Senate makes changes to a House passed bill, must the bill be voted on again in the House? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-04 01:22:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-04 01:03:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Such a shitty christian. You're the type that makes people hate Christians.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-03 22:54:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Horrible idea that would be abused constantly  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-03 22:49:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This sub is so ridiculously aggressive and negative toward people that play pilot.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-03 22:48:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Lol this guy must not have piloted since the last patch. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-03 22:47:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Nice. Just don't give into some of complainers and remove the elite kits from dom. They belong in domination as a potential gamechanger. Otherwise we might as well be playing call of duty domination.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-03 22:45:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Honestly thats almost better for pilots, means many AAs are never getting used again after being disabled. People don't run repair tool. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-03 22:39:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The fighters have no real effect on the game since they can't really kill anybody.

Its just a big dogfighting fest that results in terrible scores for pilots and no impact for those on the ground. Which is what people begging for these nerfs really wanted.

Attack plane definitely needs that maneuverability buff so some kind of plane can make a difference on the ground again without being shot down every minute.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-03 14:58:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I can already hear the cries of "op dice pls nerf" on here haha </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-03 14:48:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's not as god like on console. I wish dice would balance the PC game differently from the console because nerfing things usually has a harsher effect on us. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-03 14:45:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This guy said deaths at the end of the round don't count, which is bullshit. So idk what you're talking about.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-03 08:01:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> lol

"dice pls nerf"

How about you get good? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-03 07:56:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'll fix that for you:

"This issue doesn't really effect me and fuck pilots lololol" </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-03 07:54:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I give it like 2 more weeks before enough people have this gun unlocked for the "dice pls nerf" crying to start  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-03 07:53:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Support class guns are great, you may just be bad with them. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-03 07:51:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> No, Dice nerfs too much fucking shit already. And as if the hellreigal defensive is better than the MG15 at that role, get a hold of yourself.

The Bar is also a god tier gun in the support class. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-03 06:40:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Someone just wishes they were good at it </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-03 06:39:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Such bullshit, stop spreading it </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-03 06:35:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Congrats on your borderline illiterate Heisman and your loss to Navy  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-03 05:01:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Couldn't be much worse  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-03 01:54:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I love that this is all gamecocks have as the high point of their program   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-02 06:00:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Lol heres the daily "le casuals are ruining muh battlefield" thread  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-01 20:44:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You can always depend on the comments to ruin it for you with cold reality </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-01 13:01:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Well thats always been a feature  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-01 02:13:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> lmao are you serious? There was a time when suicide memes were no less than 1/2 of this subreddit  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-01 02:08:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Well guess what, this is battlefield 1 not battlefield 4 and everything doesn't need to be the same.

Grenades are supposed to be powerful enough to kill people and Dice has taken to steps to keep supports from spamming them every couple seconds like they could when the game came out. They've removed the "magic" resupply as well to appease you people.

But you and people like you will continue to bitch because you just "know" what battlefield 1 should be like since you played battlefield 4. 

I bet you think they should nerf the vehicles and automatico too.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-01 02:03:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That would be a blast.

But I think the villar would destroy everything lol </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-01 02:01:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Oh my god is this subreddit ever going to stop bitching about grenades.

I'm pretty sure most of you won't be happy unless Dice makes all grenades as effective as the mini nade is now. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-30 04:43:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If you're good with the Trench Fighter its still ok. I think they nerfed it a little too hard and should go back for some minor adjusting but they didn't ruin it by any means.

I can't stand the attitude that the Trench Fighter should be ineffective at killing infantry, when that is the entire point of the loadout. "but its good at air to air" yeah and once you've killed the other planes air to air only loadouts leave you with nothing to do. Players that follow this line of thought just want a game where they never die from the air.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-30 04:15:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I don't understand the hate for people that have the 4 or so days of gameplay in the tank/plane it takes to get 100 service stars. Some people like playing in vehicles more than on the ground, and they have a right to.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-29 02:30:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Maybe git gud and kill him noob? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-28 03:52:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> NEPHEW  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-28 03:00:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Was not expecting Williams before Watson  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-27 21:56:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Lol as if I can still wreck people  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-27 13:24:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Nothing can forgive what I've done.

I joined the dark side for the power.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-27 13:21:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Lol I'm still going to planewhore </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-27 12:47:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I've noticed it too, my battery is draining faster as well </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-27 12:09:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I just want you guys to get the CTE on console because I feel like this subreddit receives almost entirely PC perspectives. Balance is different on the two platforms and I fear PC players are getting too much influence, especially considering that they are in the minority of BF1 players. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-27 11:58:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You can't just slow down everything about a game after its been out for 7 months. The playerbase is used to a certain pace.

Things like character movement speed are way too ingrained to be changing much. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-27 11:54:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm going to enjoy still killing all you people with the trench fighter after the nerf. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-26 16:01:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> "Some people are just really good at what they are doing."

And there is the issue 90% of the boneheads in this sub aren't getting. Dice can't make nerfs for the top 1% of players, because then nobody else will be able to use the vehicles.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-25 23:58:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> wahhhhhhh </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-25 20:12:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> AUTOMATICO USER REEEEEEEEEEEEEE

Just kidding OP Fuck the haters nice clip </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-22 22:50:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm pointing out absurdity with absurdity.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-22 21:20:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> inb4 "Dice Tanks should ONLY be able to oneshot infantry with direct headshots! They're like sooooo OP" </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-22 14:08:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> *Nuggies </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-22 12:28:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Must be a girl </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-21 13:45:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I thought so, PC players seem to dislike it more than console players  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-21 13:09:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Personally I think people can bitch all they want dice isn't changing things much. Games been out too long for it. 

Do you play on PC?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-21 13:03:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I think people bitching about planes are just jealous they can't fly   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-21 13:00:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> "skill ceiling is too low" complaints misunderstand what bf1 is trying to be. Dice doesn't want a really high skill gap shooter where the good players lord over others from ivory towers. They want it accessable to everyone.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-21 12:52:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Don't worry op, I'll translate what you really mean. 

"Dice I as a single scout should be able to take out any plane with k bullets it's no fair that vehicles like planes are powerful" </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-21 12:39:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> "it's all planes fault dice wahhhhhh" half the 'bf1 is dying' posts </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-20 18:59:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I am indeed on Xbox. PC players are the majority of the naggers  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-20 15:52:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I agree they should have done a better job with the RSP stuff. 

I just don't think they should balance the game with only PC in mind (there are more console players), as lots of players on this sub seem to think they should. The automatico for example is pretty OP on PC because its easy to hipfire with a Mouse. Meanwhile on console with controllers that aren't great at aiming people using the automatico don't dominate as much. If Dice were to severely nerf the automatico after hearing the PC players, console users would be left with a terrible gun. and thats just one example of the difference in balance between PC and console. 

I almost wish PC and Console just had separate balance and patches.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-20 15:39:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Rich people have it easy what else is new </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-20 15:29:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You're almost trolling by asking that question.

You should know the game has hardly any players from those areas. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-20 15:17:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Might need to sell my scana stock now then  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-20 14:57:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I swear PC players hate this game with a passion compared to console players </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-20 14:56:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Sometimes I feel like the only person in this sub that likes bf1 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-20 14:53:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Only the trench fighter needs a nerf, the other planes are balanced.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-20 14:52:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I can attest that the game is still a lot of fun if you're one of those planes in operations however  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-20 04:28:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I don't think players should ever be banned by an automated system for playing within the rules of the game  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-20 03:38:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> He's not the first person I've seen fair fight banned for doing too well. SpartanHoplite on youtube has gotten banned by fair fight several times for going like 130-0 in bombers  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-18 13:21:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Nah you're a shitty negative Clemson fan that doesn't appreciate what he has. We're better off without people like you.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-17 21:02:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah, leave things alone because ideas like this ruin gameplay and balance in the name of someones urge for "historical accuracy"  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-17 17:58:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> First person piloting? Ew  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-17 14:36:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This bong looks disturbing </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-17 13:55:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Lmao you must be a salty gamecock writing like this about the team that just beat Alabama for the Natty </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-17 04:27:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> No, it doesn't. Once you have the plane you have the plane. If the other guy still gets it then you never had it in the first place, and there was likely a loading symbol around your plane icon. I've messed around in the plane customization menu at the beginning of the round for a full minute without losing my plane more than once.

If someone likes planes they will camp planes.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-17 03:39:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm funny enough a level 50 pilot with 79 fighter service stars. The dart nerf is needed I'll admit.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-17 03:37:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> And I fucking hate people that think they should dictate to others exactly how they should play their video game </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-17 03:22:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm sure that system wouldn't be widely abused or anything </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-17 03:21:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If they really want a plane or tank they can wait at the spawn screen too  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-17 03:15:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Well, they bought the game and its in the game so they can use it whether or not you like it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-17 01:42:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I disagree. If someone wants to only fly planes, they can. If someone else wants the plane, they can wait for it just like the other guy.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-17 01:41:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It'll never happen. Dice allows players to play the classes they want. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-17 01:10:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You must be trolling </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-17 01:06:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This is a battlefield game set in WWI, as repeated by the developers. Its not seeking to be a WWI simulator, its seeking to be a battlefield game. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-16 22:42:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You seriously asking for a jam mechanic in automatics? Introducing randomness that gets you killed to the game is never good. That change will lead to a lot of frustration. The automatic weapons are too easy to use in your opinion, but in mine they are great as is. You just want dice to cater the game to your playstyle. 

       </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-16 21:02:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Well you're essentially wanting to come up to me and fuck up something I enjoy because you played old games. How is that better? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-16 19:51:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Well I do enjoy it, so I'm obligated to defend it so it doesn't get turned into something I don't.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-16 19:29:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I have the premium pass so I'm committed to playing for awhile as long as they dont nerf everything like you want them too. Judge video games off their merits and how much you enjoy them, not your loyalty to them. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-16 19:19:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah, instead cater to the minority and eliminate half the playerbase great idea </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-16 17:52:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> using "the younger generation" as an insult in a video game argument, well there goes whatever credibility you had to me. Enjoy finding another game because I'd rather not play with elitists either. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-16 17:36:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Its exactly what EA wanted because it sells. I don't care if you call me a CoD kid or a causal or anything else. At the end of the day I'm playing to enjoy myself like a lot of others and if they nerf all the things most of you veterans want nerfed, we will move on to something else and not bother with another battlefield. EA is trying to keep the audience it has gained, because it is more lucrative than the minority of veterans playing the game on PC. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-16 17:18:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I don't have any loyalty to the title because every battlefield should have to earn my purchase. I'm not in a cult. I play video games to have a good time. From what a lot of you veterans say you haven't enjoyed battlefield in years because of the casual appeal and I really don't get why you keep playing if you've felt this way so long. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-16 17:13:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's really about the money to dice, which is why a lot of your concerns will likely never be addressed and even get worse to you in future battlefields. More casual games sell and keep selling. from what a lot of bf veterans say this casualising of bf has been going on for years. 

I understand loyalty, but sometimes games change their target audience and leave veterans behind.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
