<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject7761</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-08 20:11:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I wonder if titles like that get a bit predictable after a while, though. I'm a bit put off of books starting with 'The Girl...' at this point, lol.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-08 20:09:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I don't read much poetry, but collections of poetry usually have really beautiful titles. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-08 20:00:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yep, Japanese sentence endings are always beautiful.  (desu) and  (de gozaimasu) I like also.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-08 19:57:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yes, I love colloquial. I remember when I was learning another language, I had to look up what it actually meant, lol. 'Colloquialism' is also good. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-08 19:54:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I definitely think there can be good one word titles, it just depends on what connotations the word has and what it evokes for the reader. I like the title 'Yellow' by Janni Visman, I find any title that has a colour in it evokes interest. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-08 19:33:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I think that's a good point, as well. The title is very much a part of the writer's vision. Often when I write, I try to make any titles inspiring to readers, since that's part of the technique I learnt when studying creative writing. I like to evoke the feel of the story, whilst trying to make it a bit intriguing for the reader.

I've definitely bought books based on cover art. In fact, the book I mentioned in my original post, 'Evening is the Whole Day', has one edition with a beautiful illustration of a flower on the cover, which was what made me choose it. The other edition's cover I didn't find particularly inspiring, so I might not even have picked it up. I am a bit fickle when it comes to book covers... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-08 19:21:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I think Blood Meridian is an amazing title. It definitely suggests the bloody, Western feel of the book. And Cormac McCarthy has one of the most amazing writing styles, as well.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-07 16:08:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Do you think the admin was serious? 

On a side note, the real question the admin's comments raised to me is to what extent should STEM students give up their personal needs for the sake of scientific progress? In that admin's train of thought, a majority of people should be forced into STEM subjects and spend as much time as possible at their work for the sake of progress. In my view, people should be able to do what they want, rather than have to sacrifice for the 'greater good', as long as they take care of their personal responsibilities. Got a bit off-topic there, lol... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-07 15:43:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Definitely, the names of certain countries can be really beautiful. 'Mozambique' is probably my favourite. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-07 15:41:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Nordic languages are beautiful. I think there are some nice English words, but most are generally quite plain. I think American English can sometimes have nicer words than British English, like I prefer 'sidewalk' to 'pavement'.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-07 15:30:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  I just heard of that word this week, and I liked it then. I actually experience this feeling quite a bit, so it was cool to know there's actually a word for it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-07 15:27:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'd never heard of that word before, but that's pretty hilarious it exists. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The importance of book titles </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-07 14:49:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm currently reading Alice Munro's short story collection, 'Dear Life'. I've enjoyed quite a few of the stories in the collection, but I think some of their names are a bit lackluster. One or two word titles like, 'Gravel' and 'Haven'. It didn't really give me any kind of idea of what the story might be like or get me interested in some of the themes or events that might be involved. 

It got me thinking about the importance of titles for books and short stories. This might be something more important for short stories, because there's not always a lot of information about what each individual story is like on the back cover, so you only really have the titles on the contents page to go on.

A book title I absolutely love, and that made me want to pick the book out in the first place was, 'Evening is the Whole Day' by Preeta Samarasan. The contradictory statement and its implications of days filled with darkness was an image that really interested me from the outset. I believe it's actually a quote from a translation of a poem featured in Kuruntokai, a classical Tamil poetry anthology. This ties in with some of the book's themes of Indian migration to Malaysia, and is mentioned in the book. It's such an inspiring title.

How important do you think book and short story titles are? Have you ever bought a book based on the title? Do you have a favourite title? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
