<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject7095</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Thor: Ragnarok is called Mighty Thor: Battle Royale in Japan </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-10 14:39:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-04 16:18:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Literally last month posted that this might happen now that the tech has evolved (hatsune miku). 

Stoked.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-25 04:09:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Inemuri and karoshi dont have handy shorthand english versions because they're not common and/or accepted enough to need them. Sleeping in public is seen as pretty rude in most western countries, so most people dont do it. And death from overwork was something i literally never heard of before i came to japan </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-23 03:08:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I knew this would end up here. 
Also, maybe im being super dumb but I dont even get the humor here. 
The girl doesnt want to have sex, so thinking shes not ALLOWED to have sex will make her feel better about not wanting to? And the guy cares about this why?

I really dont get it, can anyone explain to me why this is even supposed to be funny?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-22 06:08:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Theres always applause -____-'
It makes me so sad.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-19 08:39:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What, no applause?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-18 03:59:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Maybe the most criminally underrated band in post hardcore. All their albums are spectacular.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-13 10:30:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I would say thats true for everyone except Japanese people. This country still uses fax machines. The countrys FIRST debit card has just launched. Netflix hasnt so much as made a dent in the physical RENTAL business - which is still huge. Japan is all about sticking with whats worked in the past.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-13 06:49:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This is a systemic cultural issue wrapped up with a lot of other systemic cultural issues. There is a trend here to an extent, of boys not being interested in girls, in favor of anime and games - which is potentially destructive in and of itself - but the same is also true for a great many girls who have equally no interest in boys. So thats not really the main factor. 

Their work culture makes it wholly impractical to even attempt raising children. They're expected - and in most cases obliged - to work 15-18 hour days as standard, and don't always get paid - or request payment - for that overtime. Why even bother having kids if you cant be a parent? So thats another factor. 

As for the older women having children, trust me its nothing to do with going abroad - most japanese people have an innate aversion to foreign people - and is most likely due to a recent trend of "friendship marriage" marrying a friend to satisfy your familys desire that you get married and have a kid - social norms are very important here - and that these usually happen later in life when people have given up searching for a partner. 

This is a very very complex issue and its relation to MGTOW ideology is tangental at best.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-10 04:16:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Chitose and kaho together in one videowhat sorcery is this </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-08 12:56:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I have to admit, i was always really put off by marinas face on her dvd covers. And I know you - and others - have specifically said her face is one of the best in JAV right now, which always baffled me. 

Until I watched a video and fell in love. Although I maintain she pulls weird faces on her dvd covers.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-07 16:56:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Gadget Hackwrench.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-01 02:36:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Why is there always applause -___-' </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Some speculation about the new live shows (and Japan)... </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-31 16:28:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Seeing as they just announced they're playing at FujiRock (I live in Japan so I'm VERY happy about that, but also pissed off as tickets to fujirock are like $200), now's about as good a time as any to put this idea out there. 

https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=YSyWtESoeOc

Do any of you know about Hatsune Miku? Sorry if it's been brought up here before - im kind of new - She's a virtual singer/pop star in Japan. Her songs are made by her fans and a handful of artists. The company that owns the character scour the fansites for good songs and a lot of producers have actually become famous because of it. 

Her live shows - of which the one posted is very old - basically involve augmented reality. A projection of her performs center stage while a live band are visible through the sheet she's being projected onto. 

It creates the illusion that she's actually on stage with real people - which she kind of is, as the band are all playing live. 

Personally, I would love to see a return to the brit-performance style show, with the characters performing. This tech seems perfect for doing something like that. 

Thoughts?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-27 10:46:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Her instagram was arubajuice but she hasnt been active for a while </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-06 07:32:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> *an NPC, surely </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-06 03:35:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I dont like rating womens attributes out of ten, so i'll abstain from that if you guys dont mind. 

Kaho Shibuya has quickly become one of my favourites. Shes beautiful, insane figure and genuinely funny and - from her instagram - seems like a really nice person. I'd love to hang out with her and play ukelele fall out boy covers all day. 

Also, acting wise - maybe my absolute favourite. ive never seen her and been disappointed.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Please help identifying a song! </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-03 03:06:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Theres a song i heard around 2009, a relatively unknown female singer songwriter. Heres what i know:

- she supported a band called 100 monkeys in london around 2009
- her e.p cover was yellow 
- the chorus had lyrics like: 
--- "come on tear me apart, and make it hurthonestly, you're so handsome when you're mean" 

Anyone have any idea? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-27 07:40:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Wow, no love for Sora Aoi. Surprising.

Ayami Shunka and Sora Aoi get my number 1 spot to share. 

Rio Hamasaki and Shibuya Kaho duke it out for 2 and 3.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-23 03:44:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Sora Aoi on a beach in maui </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
