<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject9615</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-10 04:29:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> There's no excuse.  I was bored.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Why I don't team kill anymore. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-10 04:25:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's just assholish. I just realized that. I've been doing it so long, it's like breaking off a bad habit lol. But you what? It feels good, not tking anymore. I feel like a huge weight has been lifted off my chest. I mean, it's not like I was doing it all the time, but now that I never do it I can even see a slight difference in my gameplay, like I'm more serious so I get more kills. Woopeedoo! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What do you guys think about CP? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-09 22:54:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Me and my girlfriend  (we've been together for 2 weeks) have discussed it and we want to try it lol. I've it doesn't feel as good with a condom, so I'm just gonna try to Cream Pie her without one, she's on the pill and it shouldn't be a problem. I just want to know how generally this sub feels about the famous "Cream Pie" so to speak. We're gonna do it like it pornos where I pull out and leave a trail of cum out of her pussy. Thoughts? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> If someone gifts you a book, and you don't like it, read a summary on the Internet. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-09 19:27:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I was gifted Ready Player One by my wayward sister and I read 60 pages before I called it quits. I just read the key points on the Internet, and when she asked me about the book, I put on a fake smile and talked about how great it was. I suggest you do the same. I know this sounds assholish, but it's better than admitting that the book you were gifted wasn't up your alley. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> My cousin is teasing me with Mario Kart. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-09 08:43:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Like, she has big boobies. And sometimes she wears this Mario Kart shirt that is really tight and then she asks me to massage her back while she studies for school or plays video games.

I have over 30 messages of her in Wassap it's just her teasing me. She's very cunning and if I sleep with her she'll make my life hell. Fucking hell man.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-07 19:00:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> To be honest, I'm not quite sure what else you're getting at either in this post or the one yesterday. I think perhaps the reason why it didn't go down very well is the tone in which you wrote the message - you come across as someone who knows better than everyone else, even though the garbled nature of your posts and your sweeping generalisations suggest otherwise.     


I understand where you're coming from, I really do, but I simply disagree with this statement.  See,that's the exact reason I find reddit so interesting. The different opinions and the like. And by the way, I've seen someone suggest alcohol, and other than a doobie earlier today, I'm completely sober from any hard substances. 

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> So...here's the thing about books (PART 2) </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-07 18:36:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yesterday I made this post and it didn't get well received https://www.reddit.com/r/books/comments/69lwnj/soheres_the_thing_about_books

Today, I want to expand on it. The reason we like book so much is because of escapism right? People prefer fiction books almost nobody reads nonfiction nowadays  (and that's fine!) But...I gotta say, a fiction book vs a nonfiction... let's just say you're selling yourself short. And I'm not talking about those kind of books that you read once and never again. No. I'm talking Lord of the Rings, Catcher in the Rye, House of Leaves, let's see, The Hitchcock Guide to the Galaxy. What you need to do is find a book you love and just read it. It doesn't matter if it's fiction or nonfiction...just...read...the....damn....book! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Is Casual unplayable without a mic now? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-07 04:57:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> One of the reasons I almost exclusively played casual was because I could just play by myself, almost no com required. But since the last update it feels just like ranked. I feel like communication now is necessary on casual and I can't just pop the game and play a few matches without feeling like I'm playing a version of ranked. 
I play on Xbox and it's so much more toxic now. People try to kick you of you don't play good. Or send you messages saying u suck because you made a mistake
 Thoughts? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> So...here's the thing about books. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-06 17:59:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Sometimes books are awesome, right? But what about the other half? The half we don't talk about? The half where that book you're reading doesn't make sense, or doesn't hold up to your standard. And this isn't about only books, take any piece of art, shit on it, and watch hundreds of people turn against that piece of art and also shit on it. It's a slippery slope and I'm actually quite surprised most of you don't see it for what it is: an art gallery show where the strongest survive and the weaker get swept up under the "Critical Eye Rug". </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-03 06:58:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Why should they show all the times he went there and nothing happened?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-03 06:57:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Damn Phillip is absolutely sick of his work right now. You could hear it in his tone when he suggested Tuan wanted to leave.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Thanks Vince Gimple am really glad this show is exist. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-02 20:32:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Do you respect other players? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-02 07:33:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> In Rainbow Six Siege, do you respect other players? What does it take to earn to your F for respect? Skill? Communication skills? Or simply the fact that we're all playing the same game and we respect each other like human beings? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-01 04:17:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Let's just say a little bit of both :) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-01 02:00:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Username checks out :) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-30 21:34:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> There's a chance the comment  would still exist if it was some poor bloke getting roasted  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-30 00:26:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> But it's not a subpar show, 
 
Yes it is

and the show doesn't even have any clear message. 

That makes matters even worse. 

Certainly not a simple one that they try to shove down the audience's throat.

I...didn't need that mental image. At all. 

Why did you make this thread when there's a discussion thread stickied? 

Becuase I felt like it? Lol. 


Is it that you saw the negative and uninformed comments, like your own,

Brb, I'm gonna go make myself a sandwich 


get severely downvoted? Are you too scared to post your own opinion there because you don't want to lose any precious karma?

Ok I'm back. Oh yeah, umm, sure buddy.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Here is what I think of "Dear White People" as a title. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-29 22:00:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Let's forget about the context of the show for a second here.  The people who made that title know exactly what they're doing, they know the average person won't watch their subpar show so they make this controversial title to get a reaction. Same goes for the movie.  It's the equivalent of a click baity title that shows that the only way to creatos could get their message across was to resort to a title worthy of buzzfeed levels of attention seeking. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-29 18:55:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Ahem, step-daughter </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Why did my professor give me a C if I worked for an A? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-28 23:33:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-28 20:48:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> 
schnorb it is like saying chlog it, at least in my book </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-28 03:13:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Is this the new montage by Optic Predator? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-27 01:58:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yes  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> what are you doing </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-26 19:09:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-26 07:13:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This episode really needed some extra screen time. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-25 17:21:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  end up in a ditch somewhere, gagged, with a pipe shoved really deep up my rectum ? No thanks </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Guys I want poople to cum in my ass is there like a cum-in-my-ass club? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-25 16:32:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Is it weird that I want the people who made Rainbow Six Siege to gang up on me? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-25 08:00:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-25 07:28:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You might be a bit gay mate  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-25 03:35:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> She touched his dick without consent. How is that not sexual assault? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-21 10:23:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Oh fuck </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-21 07:57:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Done. Thanks </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-21 07:52:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Jason gets convicted of a murder he never committed. On his death bed, a strange man offers to send him back in time to catch the real murderer.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-21 05:42:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> How hilarious would it be if Romero just died 5 minutes into the last ep.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What kind of depraved shit are you into? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-21 01:30:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm talking about stuff like taking viagra,  driving a nail through the outer skin of your ball sack and getting hard and masterbating.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-19 18:03:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> He knew.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-19 08:45:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm thinking more about a kind of spank-ass- assault fetish.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What do you think about the act of spanking your SO against their will? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-19 08:30:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-19 01:58:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This is about my discussion  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-19 01:13:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Think about the last book that you read. Did you like it? Imagine you're in a public place and you hand the book over to the person next to you. Do you think that person would like it as much as you? What would be the chances?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> How dare you say that the book you loved is a 'must read' </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-19 01:02:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Seriously, let's say I pick some random book in a bookstore, and that book turns out to be absolutely amazing, do you think it would be fair for me to ride that book's back for you, to put you in a soapbox, brandishing this book, or dangling this book in front of you every time, please before doing this with a book you love do some research first before you go around recommending books that you and a handfist of people like, that one recommended yesterday wasn't even written well it was boring </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> How did P E not know anything about the prison camps? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-17 04:10:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> "Did you know anything about the camps?"

"I know they existed."

So...they lived in Russia, for what, 19, 20 years. And they didn't know? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> All my protagonist wants to do is play Zelda and browse xhamster. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-17 02:27:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> And it's really hampering my mystery novel. Worst of all: he's a detective. That's not how detectives act that's not what they do and I'm starting to wonder if maybe this protagonist is a mirror version of myself. Thoughts? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> subservient women in fiction </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-16 18:37:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I want to write a POV of sub woman- kinky stuff mostly. Here's the thing: she works for the KGB, her love interest is a CIA young stud, and her parents died during WW2 by Nazi scums. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> I want people to recognize me for the writer that I'm fucking am. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-10 22:44:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-10 03:51:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You KNOW this one's real.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-09 21:37:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Boobies </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> I'm writing erotica. Is this way out of line? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-08 18:09:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> *He slapped his step-daughter across the face and said, "I've seen your videos you slut."*

*Emily, who had just turned eighteen, reeled back, shocked. "You went through my stuff?" She asked.*

*The step-father smirked. "I looked it up. I knew you were such a whore...You know what? Get on your knees."*

*Emily looked up at him with terrified eyes. "Why?"*

*He forced her to her knees* *"I said get on your knees you fucking whore!"*

*He pulled his dick out and started slamming his own step daughter in the mouth* </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Hurt Bae Asks: Why Did You Cheat? Exes Confront Each Other On Infidelity (#HurtBae Video) </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-08 01:43:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-06 20:37:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I admit that I gotta adjust #9. It's a little overboard. What's wrong with the other messages though?  That's like day to day stuff on xbl lol </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-06 20:33:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So you can report me? Nice try.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-06 20:23:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I remember when trash talking was an accepted part of online competition  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Here are my top 10 messages to send to the enemy team after a match is complete. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-06 20:14:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> I'm gonna go from Xbox to Switch cuz I got banned on Xbox. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-05 10:56:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> I feel like I'm constantly outplaying my teammates yet I'm at the bottom of the scoreboard. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-05 09:55:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm constantly outplaying them. Doing more than fucking them. Yet, no mvp for me. This game rigged man </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-05 01:29:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Neither.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> They say stuff like that all the time. "This game is amazing. This game is the next GOTY". GIVE US EXCLUSIVES </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-05 00:58:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> How I Think Bans Should be Handled. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-04 22:17:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-04 11:30:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> They say stuff like that all the time I wasn't making fun of the guy we banter like that and sometimes pick on randoms but nothing personal  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> PSA: Xbox Live is very sensitive these days. Be careful. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-04 10:43:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-04 04:00:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> How is this what the post is asking?  Lol </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-04 03:55:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Check out Quarry. I feel like it had one of the best directed sequences  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-03 18:02:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The tower scene was one of my favorite moments in the comics and they handled it really good here </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
