<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject7742</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> I Grew Up in Lovecraftville </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-09 00:42:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I dont know who to share this with. But you guys have always been open to new ideas, right? Ive seen you crack open cold cases and investigate weird phenomena before. I need help. 

My psychologist says its probably nothing too much to worry about. He said its not uncommon for people suffering with depression to have feelings of dread or to have creative nightmares. Yeah, he used the word creative. 

I tried talking to newspapers and the media. I even tried talking to a local Marine Biologist named [REDACTED]. My own friends (even the ones I grew up with) have no interest in talking about what I saw. In fact, most dont return my phone calls or texts, anymore. I know what youre thinking, Of course they dont want to talk to you, nut job. Who wants to listen to a crazy person rant and rave about large black masses in the water and leering red eyes in the night? 

My name is [REDACTED] and I grew up in what I now jokingly call Lovecraftville. Most people believe that H.P. Lovecraft created fantastic places using some real-world markers and pure imagination. Most people also think that he simple mixed in real places in order to better blend his imagined locations with the real world. Im telling you, he didnt. 

Im from a town called Groveland on the North Shore of Massachusetts. Its a small farm town nestled on the banks of the Merrimack River. Its so small, in fact, that even people born and raised in New England dont know its there. There is only one 4x3 sign on I-95, running north, that even mentions it.

It started one day on a place called Plum Island, at a beach called Sandy Point. Back in high school, we used to go skimboarding there all the time. Its a great spot. With so few parking spots, so much sand, and being surrounded by water on three sides; it feels like the edge of the world. 

There are so many different cross currents, the water moves constantly. Plum Island River, Rowley River, Roger Island River, Paine Creek, and the Ipswich River (among dozens of other small creeks and tributaries) all converge at this one point before pouring out into the ocean. 

One late summer afternoon, I went boarding by myself. When you live near the coast, you get used to doing a lot of aquatic sports by yourself. Sometimes friends and great weather dont always match up. The sun was just starting to set behind me. Clouds had been rolling through all day, but the sun kept finding its way through. 

That day, however, the water was acting a little out of the ordinary.  Sometimes the tide shifted in one direction only to turn mid draft and swing the other way. Sometimes Id be in the middle of a good run and then get swamped from the side or the water would run out from under me so fast that my board would get stuck and launch me over the nose. Its like it had a mind of its own.

Toward the end of my day, I was on a pretty clean run when I could feel the water come around behind me. I dug in to try to out run it before I got swamped and had to step off. When I looked back, I saw something moving in it. It was long and black, like a snake or tentacle, even. My brain didnt have time to register any of this at the moment. My instincts screamed SHARK! and I dove for the dry, dusty shore a few feet away.

After landing with a thud, I turned to water to findnothing. There was nothing in there. Just my board bobbing up and down in the waves. After a few moments of waiting for something to happen; I waded into the waist deep, myrtle green water. Everyone always remarks how blue the ocean is, but the North Atlantic is Green. You can call it whatever shade you want: Brunswick, Paris, Harlequin, or Olive. But its always dark and its always green. Its at that level that you realize how deep and mysterious it is. Whether you realize it or not, that arcane reptile brain inside of you is silently praying that that shadowy, cryptic place never gives up its secrets. 

I laughed to myself inwardly, trying to shrug off the fear Id experienced; and grabbed my board. The sun was getting lower on the horizon. I put my hand up and registered that I likely had another finger before Id have to head home. Thats enough time for a few more runs before Id need to be home for dinner.

I had just dropped my board on a dead sprint and jumped on when I saw it. About 50 yards off there was a large, black, fleshy, dome-shaped mass. In my distraction, I lost my balance and fell. I skinned the hell out of my side sliding in the mud. blood and salt water poured from sand rash, as I got to my feet and moved up the beach to get a better vantage point 

It was still sitting there, motionless.  It was like a back of a whale without a dorsal fin, or as if someone had turned a submarine nose up in the water. It was mammoth, with skin so rubbery and dark it seemed to absorb light once the slickness of the water fell away. The water around it flowed back and forth, as if some writhing mass moved just below the surface. 

Then, it moved. A slow, deliberate twist that sent waves in all directions and revealed two eyes. They were large and black. They were darker even than its skin and defied anything I could understand. They were cavernous voids of black and, yet, they still appeared to be bulbous protrusions. I could feel it watching me. It was as if it was studying me.

All I remember after that is a few moments of being in a car, racing back down the dusty road to get as far away from the island and that water as I could. The feeling that that Thing sparked inside of me is palpable. Even to this day, I can still feel the writhing, bubbling wash of dread that came over me. My skin had turned to ice and my brain swam with a strange, low hum. But there was something else, an unexpected longing. It was as if there was a part of me that wanted to swim out and touch it. I could feel a desire to run my hands along it slick, rubbery side; and be embraced by the writhing mass below the surface. Luckily, my reptile brain convinced me otherwise and I ran. 

Now like I said, I grew up on the coast and I loved the ocean. But to this day, I still have no idea what that was. Ive searched through everything, from animal encyclopedias to mythology books; and Ive found nothing that explains it. Years later, while at college, I found an abnormal map of the North Shore. It had all the familiar names that I knew: Newburyport, Ipswich, Rowley, Rockport, Gloucester, and Salem. It also had names Id never heard of: Kingsport, Arkham, and Innsmouth. It was a map of H.P. Lovecrafts fictional North Shore. 

When I started to dig into it, I found that Innsmouth looked out onto a rocky formation called the Devils Reef. I want to say that this is where it gets weird; but lets be honest, we are way past that point. What I discovered by studying that map is that the Devils Reef is roughly located on Sandy Point. Look, I know the differences between reality and fiction. Im terrified, not a moron. But what if, he wasnt writing fiction at all? What if he was trying to tell us something important? What if he was trying to prepare us for something?

I wish that were the end of the tale. What happened the night after that Thing came into my life and every night until I left home; has only added to my trepidation. I dont go into the water anymore. 

I havent been able to draw any conclusions about what happened, except for one thing: whatever I saw in the ocean is intelligent and it is curious. If anyone has any direction or information, I would appreciate it. Thank you. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-28 13:38:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I co-host a podcast called on Alternate Reelities. I'm also in charge of the tech/business side of things. At this point, I've found that it's not quite so important where you upload your podcast from, but that it's available on all the major services where people might potentially look (itunes, google play, etc.). Make it as easy as possible for people to find it. I use Podbean, but like you I'm running on a "zero budget" philosophy. So I can't afford, or qualify for any of the added promotional content. And I don't want it at this point. We're still growing and learning.

Hope this helps.

P.S what's the podcast called? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-10 15:01:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Lasers to the face! His one weakness! Arghhh! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-09 19:53:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hero. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
