<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject4988</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-29 14:57:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  If we did not object they could have registered Punk and sold it to AB-InBev the next day, and then we could have been driven out of business.

So their solution to the trademark bullying problem is to become the bully. Got it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-21 14:56:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thank you for this tip! I've found my OneDrive experience to be completely unusable (Chromium 53 on Linux Mint 17.2/18.1). But this is really amazing -- now I can finally utilize my 1 TB of space (via my university). </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-13 22:41:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Sounds like it can honestly go either way! There will be a sharp gradient in snowfall where rain/sleet will mix in and diminish totals, but due to scatter in all the models, nobody knows exactly where it'll settle. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-13 19:40:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Good question, since it looks like you might be in for quite a bit of sleet (and therefore less snow). According to the [scientific forecaster's discussion](http://forecast.weather.gov/product.php?site=NWS issuedby=LWX product=AFD format=CI version=1 glossary=1 highlight=off):

| As it currently stands...for DC/Balt...10th percentile is 1-4 [inches]...50th percentile is 4-8...and 90th percentile is 10-16. 

So it looks like there's a lot of variance in the forecast. South of DC probably means that you'll be in the 1-3" range if there's significant wintry mix. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-13 19:18:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [Here's a GFS precipitation forecast](http://i.imgur.com/hAZWJrW.gifv) that I created using the [same website](http://www.tropicaltidbits.com/analysis/models/). The accumulation in my area (Central NJ) are pretty similar between models, but as /u/wazoheat mentioned, northern New England totals are much higher, and coastal CT/RI/MA storm totals are drastically lower. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-13 18:50:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That's good to know! I wasn't sure how different models compared, but I did realize that the fiducial 10:1 snow-water ratio wasn't going to give the best estimates. Which models do you think give better precipitation forecasts? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Forecast map of total snowfall (GEM - 12z Mar 13) </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-13 16:51:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-03 04:11:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm gonna try my luck with the giveaway. It's been awhile since I've bought any AMD parts, but I do remember helping my friend build his first PC back in 2010 -- I had to recommend the Athlon II X3 (440? can't remember). Looking forward to grabbing a Ryzen for my next build, especially if the value is still this great and the benchmarks are as good as they seem! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-02 03:50:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Wow, thank you! I really appreciate it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-01 19:36:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You might like the Chrome extension called [Disable HTML5 Autoplay](https://chrome.google.com/webstore/detail/disable-html5-autoplay/efdhoaajjjgckpbkoglidkeendpkolai). I have a small [blacklist](http://i.imgur.com/DprSfGN.png) to prevent CNN from autoplaying. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-27 18:38:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What do you think about data-driven philanthropy or effective altruism? In your opinion, is it better to follow your head or your heart? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-23 13:30:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Oh man, I loved that feeling. I was in college when they lost to the Packers in the 2010-11 Superbowl (on my birthday no less) and you could feel the whole city go dead quiet. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-19 19:26:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I picked up the [Wet Scuba Jacket](http://www.superdry.com/mens/jackets/details/48483/wet-scuba-jacket-navy) during last year's half-off sale and within a week, the zipper pin came loose and fell off. I got refunded without much trouble, but the poor quality (control) makes me hesitant to buy any of their stuff again. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-04 15:49:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> People do this in New Jersey too, although I'm not sure if it's because NJ drivers suck, or if it's because I lived in a rural area and everybody drives Ford F150s and I'm one of the few people not driving an American car. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The ordering of these shoe sizes. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-14 13:39:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-25 13:54:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I've got an Asus UX305 with 8 GB RAM and a 256 GB SSD. The performance is fine for me (browsing and coding, but no gaming), and I run Linux Mint 17.2 on it. The only downside are the battery life (about 4-5 hours on Linux) and the poor palm rejection. It's super thin, has a 1080p screen, and a matte bezel, so I think it looks great. And I got it for only $600, which is an absolute steal. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-10 12:48:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Sounds like you're absolutely on the right track since you've already got some research experience under your belt. Physics REUs are extremely competitive and many qualified students don't get accepted; I know that my school's REU acceptance rate is in the single digit percentages, and that we prioritize exceptional students who also attend a liberal arts college or a school with no research opportunities. Try chatting with (aka emailing) professors who work on topics that interest you and ask about any informal research opportunities. Start reading some of their papers. If nothing comes to fruition, ask around your own school for research projects. Continue honing your skill set -- depending on which field of research you want to do, that might mean going through some textbooks (especially if you want to do theory), or familiarizing yourself with commonly used software or programming (root if you want to do high energy experimental physics or astrophysics), or being comfortable in a machine shop or lab environment (maybe if you want to do condensed matter experiments). Also don't be afraid of applying for an internship that's outside your intended field of research -- so long as you find it interesting, it can be of huge benefit to you!  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-13 01:05:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That is quite a large eye. Is Nicole an annular hurricane? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-06 22:57:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yes, you can see it on the [radar image](http://tropicalatlantic.com/recon/radar/al/2016/Matthew/NOAA/30/radar/2016-10-06-191830-25.867N-78.350W-NOAA-3-PPISPDF_Center.png). The second eyewall has a 75 mile diameter and the inner one has a 12 mile diameter.

EDIT: [Here's a nice radar loop](http://gfycat.com/OrneryMajorBarnacle) of both eyewalls spinning. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-04 12:08:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It looks like Matthew has [completed its eyewall replacement cycle](https://gfycat.com/CautiousSmugDogwoodclubgall) (credit: NASA/Wunderground). The eye is much larger now -- maybe 25 km in diameter.

EDIT: Although the storm is strengthening now, it will likely cross over the mountainous tip of Haiti/Hispaniola, and probably get disrupted. [Here's an elevation map](https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/File:Pic_Macaya_national_park_topographic_map.jpg) of the landfall area. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
