<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject8557</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-10 16:53:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> ...is that how u/KennyEmmy would spell it? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Some Facts About Raiders Of The Lost Ark </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-10 16:51:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Movers for the married </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-10 16:03:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> This actually kinda makes sense </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-10 16:02:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-10 15:48:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Please call customer service (202) 456-1111  to see if we can help.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-10 15:25:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's not really out of place, impertinent or misleading, I think it was fitting even if it's not a direct link to the Russia thing. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-10 15:21:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> USSIA...Yes you can. Not without the letters, but that's not what you said.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-10 13:43:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> How long have you been married? Do you plan on getting remarried if you divorce? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-10 13:40:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Better call it narcissus. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-10 13:38:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I, for one, welcome our bodies' new plump brain overlords.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-10 13:21:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Disagree. Republicans would throw every last dirty word trick in there to make you look bad and the only medium for meaningful political discussion was a joke. Enjoy your gold, but you missed the mark. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-10 04:42:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Gotta sat the comments were better, tbh  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-10 04:29:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I personally believe that would make a good cover and Putin wins in this scenario as well. By and large most people have gotten over it and no major repercussions are getting much coverage. In fact, it's increasingly suspicious that trump has  forbidden the entry solely of news organizations that were covering the Russia ties, has court evidence of, shall we say, extremely fishy ties with upper echelons of Russian politics, and now he fires Comey and that's to say the very least. Add to that the attempt to control media portrayal of the administration, such as the fact that t_d is modded by radicals and manipulated by bots (to the extreme) and the willful ignorance and blind support of trumps supporters, and you've got a problem, to say the least.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-09 17:19:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Well, taking credit hadn't been invented yet. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-09 17:16:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [Here's a list with many of the answes to your questions]( https://www.reddit.com/r/OutOfTheLoop/w/index/retired_questions) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-09 16:18:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Ok, I can go with that. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-09 14:49:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Quite insightful thx  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-09 06:25:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This in DC? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-09 06:12:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's a star, actually.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-09 04:35:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> How do you figure?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-09 04:09:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> No clue...but take my upvote. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-08 23:55:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Considering the sub it's posted to, it's really hard to say. At first I thought it was earnest but now I'm not sure. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-08 23:13:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> DAE find themselves attracted to Nebula's character. I didn't really even think that Karen Gillan is all that attractive, but by the end of the movie, I really liked Nebula... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-08 20:35:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [This is for you.](http://imgur.com/gallery/f0Iu0xE) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-08 20:30:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I like this, so much less stress. thx tho. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-08 20:30:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I have a feeling this is NSFW, Am I right?
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Anti-protest bills would 'attack right to speak out' under Donald Trump </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-08 17:38:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-08 17:36:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That communicate with the aid of satellites  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-08 17:35:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I second this </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-08 15:06:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I just thought it was kind of fair since rural America has so much of the resources and land but fewer people. Now it just appears to be a means to subvert democracy. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-08 14:40:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Well my support has wavered on both sides over the years, but this is the last nail in that coffin.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> I supported the electoral college system until I saw this. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-08 13:44:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Well, I used to support the electoral college system until I saw this t_d post in r/de </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-08 13:42:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Of all the moments on the show, this one always sticks out </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-07 20:11:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-07 19:34:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Oh, hey, thx, I'll post that next time! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-07 19:32:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [Awesome](https://imgur.com/gallery/Bm8CJ)  

Edit: bad link </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-07 19:06:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Very disappointing tbh. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-07 19:05:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I cant seem to find it. If you take it to a good nursery they might be able to ID it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-07 19:03:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Exactly what the other commenters said:

https://photojournal.jpl.nasa.gov/catalog/PIA07784 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-07 17:41:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Let me see if I can find it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-07 17:40:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Original ghost recon L96A1 Sniper Rifle(Accuracy International Arctic Warfare. Thing was accurate AF. A similar version holds the record for longest confirmed kill: [Guinness](http://www.guinnessworldrecords.com/world-records/longest-confirmed-sniper-kill) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-07 17:27:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's a variety of wandering jew. We used to sell this variety at a nursery where I worked. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-07 17:21:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [Source: NASA]( https://pics-about-space.com/nasa-photos-of-jupiter?p=2#img18115538071059824404) 


Edit: [Better Source]( https://photojournal.jpl.nasa.gov/catalog/PIA07784) thx u/skji </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Jupiter From The Southern Pole </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-07 17:19:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-07 17:12:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It is Jupiter. Was just going to post sauce and I realized that. Time for more coffee.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Test </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-07 16:43:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-07 16:35:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Still seems pretty dark to me. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-07 06:59:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Obama's like the same skin color as I am but he's gotta be twice as dark as I was at his age in the pic. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-07 00:22:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If she just disappeared, well, that'd be nice. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-07 00:11:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You do realize that's not the only way they get their guns, dont you? 

Edit: American women with no criminal background are among the biggest suppliers: [Link]( https://en.m.wikipedia.org/wiki/Smuggling_of_firearms_into_Mexico)     </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Alabama Congressman: People who lead good lives dont have preexisting conditions - Salon.com </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-07 00:09:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> "Dog Bone" paperclips </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-06 23:35:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Cloudflare Forwards personal information to hate groups if you make a complaint </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-06 23:33:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-06 23:13:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'd be open to considering that, but I'd also have to say that would be just a start. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-06 23:00:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Kind of a stretch if you ask me, but whatever.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-06 22:25:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> No. I don't think the "free market" is working according to its principles. Unnecessary procedures are common, doctors give prescriptions for pharmaceuticals from whom they receive commissions, pharmaceutical companies charge exorbitant and in no way ethical prices for drugs in the US only, the ability for insurance companies to charge similarly for preexisting conditions. These, among others, should be addressed by legislation, not only because the incentives for ethical business practices are insubstantial, but because this is a democracy and the vast majority(iirc) demands it.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-06 20:53:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Wait, wait, I know the answer to this...

Step 3:???

Step 4: profit </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> ISIS Tells Followers It's 'Easy' to Get Firearms From U.S. Gun Shows </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-06 20:43:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-06 19:28:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> We gotta start doing this for people with mental illness. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-06 19:18:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I think the point is here that health care is too expensive in America and not for any good reason. Saying they take cash snd nobody should expect anything for free is beside the point. We pay significantly more for particularly worse health care than anyone in the developed world. The reason for this is because the health care market has a high barrier to entry and limited competition and limited oversight. The government has implemented laws making things like food affordable and in my opinion, they should do the same with healthcare, especially after considering that many companies are solely in it for the profit as evidenced by the actions of pharmaceuticals, hospitals and insurance companies alike. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-06 08:51:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Is a dog pissing to mark its  territory art? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-06 07:15:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> We gotta start doing this for people with mental health issue. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-06 01:26:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> 



Thank you for your input: u/runningstitch , u/luckinthevalley , u/DoneUpLikeAKipper , u/floridianreader , u/Duke_Paul , u/katelindt . 

After some research, it appears that this was an attempt to bring some of Melville's hidden meanings to literature. There appears to be a theme of cannibalism and violence in this section of the book that contrasts with the peaceful serenity of the preceding chapters. The sharks, a continuation from the previous chapters, here appear to be reflecting the nature of man. When the cook, just a few pages prior, is speaking to the sharks under the capricious orders of Stubb, Fleece the cook says an angel is only a shark well governed. I believe that this comment is something of an insight into the cannibalistic theme of the book, that life eats life. This is further supported by the imagery from chapter 65 in which he remarks that the oxen at the market is a "brother" and the meat eaters "cannibals". 

   Further into the book, at chapter 96 The Try Works, we see the plot become more manifold by the introduction of the industrial aspects of the ship, representing its inherent opposition to the previous chapters' focus on an epic hunting journey. The fumes produced in combination with the line: "the Pequod, freighted with savages, and laden with fire, and burning a corpse, and plunging into that blackness of darkness, seemed the material counterpart of her monomaniac commanders soul." Note that the Pequod replaces the whale's place as the antagonist. From this point onward, Ahab is seen in terms of mechanical and industrial images; as Dean Flower wrote in The Hudson Review: "iron rails, manufactured body parts, carpentry, hammer and forge". 
   To bring all this home, as Pip claims: "I look, you look, he looks; we look, ye look, they look," which brings full circle the concurrent, inseparable cyclical themes in the book of good and evil, cannibalism and brotherhood, serenity and terror. So, in conclusion, the "Ingin" god was an allegory to the cyclical themes of the book which explore the inherent duality of man and life.


Link to source: http://hudsonreview.com/2013/08/vengeance-on-a-dumb-brute-ahab-an-environmentalist-reading-of-moby-dick/#.WQz4_lXytIw </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-06 01:18:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Well, after some research, it appears that this was an attempt to bring some of Melville's hidden meanings to literature. There appears to be a theme of cannibalism and violence in this section of the book that contrasts with the peaceful serenity of the preceding chapters. The sharks, a continuation from the previous chapters, here appear to be reflecting the nature of man. When the cook, just a few pages prior, is speaking to the sharks under the capricious orders of Stubb, Fleece the cook says an angel is only a shark well governed. I believe that this comment is something of an insight into the cannibalistic theme of the book, that life eats life. This is further supported by the imagery from chapter 65 in which he remarks that the oxen at the market is a "brother" and the meat eaters "cannibals". 

   Further into the book, at chapter 96 The Try Works, we see the plot become more manifold by the introduction of the industrial aspects of the ship, representing its inherent opposition to the previous chapters' focus on an epic hunting journey. The fumes produced in combination with the line: "the Pequod, freighted with savages, and laden with fire, and burning a corpse, and plunging into that blackness of darkness, seemed the material counterpart of her monomaniac commanders soul." Note that the Pequod replaces the whale's place as the antagonist. From this point onward, Ahab is seen in terms of mechanical and industrial images; as Dean Flower wrote in The Hudson Review: "iron rails, manufactured body parts, carpentry, hammer and forge". 
   To bring all this home, as Pip claims: "I look, you look, he looks; we look, ye look, they look," which brings full circle the concurrent, inseparable cyclical themes in the book of good and evil, cannibalism and brotherhood, serenity and terror. So, in conclusion, the "Ingin" god was an allegory to the cyclical themes of the book which explore the inherent duality of man and life.


Link to source: http://hudsonreview.com/2013/08/vengeance-on-a-dumb-brute-ahab-an-environmentalist-reading-of-moby-dick/#.WQz4_lXytIw </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-05 23:12:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Congratulations! Two questions:

1. From one guy with melanin in the skin to another, did you experience any racism on your trip? I have been considering a trip in the states, but grew up in a small town and, tbh, I'm afraid of these small town guys and their trucks, guns and sheriff's departments.

2. How much gear did you take? It looks like you traveled super light in the pics.

Thanks in advance. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-05 23:00:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I worked for a Republican Congressman from my district in California when I went to Uni back east and Fox was the only news that ever played on the television in his office.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-05 22:52:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Well, I considered that Melvile may (very well) have been a bit biased in his representations of the Indians, and the book does abound with examples of such language, however, the fact that he doesn't really seem to use other characters in a (presumably) self-deprecating dialogue, makes this one quote really stand out from the others for me. The dialogue with the negroes(pip and the cook come to mind) on board does not have the self-deprecating quality that this event does, and nor does the scene with the Parsee stowaway(I can't remember the name).  In the descriptions he wrote regarding the shortcomings of these peoples, but this is the only event in the book where a character condemns his whole race as something undesirable. This is the evasive quality of this line that compels me to believe I am not fully understanding the context.

Edit: typo </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-05 22:30:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thank you. Much of that was what I was thinking. I studied classics and figured he was referring to more than one god, but had a hard time figuring out what was meant by "Ingen". I still find it a bit ambiguous, but I can live with that. Thanks again. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-05 22:18:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Ok that makes sense...I guess...Why would an indian compare himself to a brutal god of sharks though? Maybe I'm thinking too anachronistically here. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-05 21:56:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> My book has "Ingin" written:

 https://imgur.com/gallery/kq2bg


That said, Indian does seem like the best fit. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-05 21:45:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Well, I'm not sure, why would the god be an Indian? And why would he capitalize Ingin and not god? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-05 21:25:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Here's the quote in its entirety: "Queequeg no care what god(not capitalized) made him shark," said the savage, agonizingly lifting his hands up and down; "wedder feejee god or Nantucket god; but de god wat made shark must be one dam Ingin."

Edit: ingen to ingin in post and comment </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Trying to Understand a Line from Queequeg in Moby Dick </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-05 21:22:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The last sentence in chapter 66, The Shark Massacre: "wedder fiji god...one dam Ingin", what does he mean by "Ingin"? I can't figure out for certain what he means and the footnotes look over this word. Indian doesn't quite make sense, Ingenioius wouldn't make sense either and he capitalized it so I assume it's a proper noun. Thanks for your help in advance. I'll post the whole quote if requested. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-05 20:28:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I got staples stock  

Edit: here's my referral link

http://share.robinhood.com/barretp5 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-05 20:23:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Go after the administrators salaries. Often there are unnecessary multiple administrators getting paid 6 figures. It may do well to expose them and try to rationalize better salaries for teachers. If you're organized and anticipate the tough questions it will likely improve the prospective outcomes on your behalf.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-05 00:34:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Nobody likes you automod, go eat worms! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-04 17:27:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You're welcome! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-04 16:58:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> How was holding on to the leash not a bad idea in this case? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Test </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-04 05:57:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-04 05:51:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Fellow Redditors,

 I was misinformed and it's a Rendering:
https://saturn.jpl.nasa.gov/resources/7639/?category=graphics

I apologize for the misinformation and hope you aappreciate it nonetheless.  


Edit: Wrong link </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Closest picture of Saturn yet, credit to Casini </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-04 05:47:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Face sitting done right </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-04 01:28:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Face sitting done very well </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-04 01:28:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-04 00:53:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So the rest of us can appreciate it. I hope that clears it up for you.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Containers are fun </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-03 18:20:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-03 17:57:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> https://www.reddit.com/r/Pareidolia/comments/6917fo/looks_like_i_found_the_sorting_hat_from_harry/ </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Looks like I found the Sorting Hat from Harry Potter </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-03 17:56:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-03 17:55:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That's better, I'm reposting this with that, thank you  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-03 17:37:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thx, I'll pull it. Thought you guys might like that. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-03 17:28:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I think I responded to the wrong thread. My apologies.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-03 16:54:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Voters to Ex-DNC chair: stop subverting our goddamn democracy! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-03 15:46:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Maybe you gotta do some soul searching. 
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-03 12:03:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I can't believe I'm blocking r/garlicbreadmemes, but this is downright juvenile and doesn't belong on the front page of reddit.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-03 11:56:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> https://www.reddit.com/r/news/comments/68w8qu/an_older_teen_who_was_in_the_car_when_his/ </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-03 11:54:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I got an answer for you. https://www.reddit.com/r/news/comments/68w8qu/an_older_teen_who_was_in_the_car_when_his/ </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-02 17:18:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Try R/thathappened or r/incels </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-02 00:23:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Lol </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Cop makes a great example for other riders by biking against traffic on his cell </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-02 00:18:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> How do you guys feel about police riding against the flow of traffic with one hand on his handlebars and the other on his phone? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-02 00:11:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-01 21:47:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah, I thought so too. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-01 17:30:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> My bad  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-01 15:36:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Why does it seem like the penalty for this is harder than the penalties given to wall street execs for this sort of thing?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-01 15:01:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> My bad, I'll use quotes next time. Didn't even think about it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-01 08:03:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This dudes probably full blown Bates Motel material  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-01 07:17:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I think if Jack London wrote a book for the movie interstellar it would  be amazing.


 Melville writing LOTR would be incredible, if boring sometimes.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> I couldn't afford a new window so I just put some bars over it and put a dolls head inside. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-01 05:58:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> I see your chrome Land Rover and raise you this holographic Hyundai </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-01 05:52:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-01 05:14:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's like a perfect parody, but in real life. Fitting that I find it comical yet depressing.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-01 05:05:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Did it float? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-01 03:50:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I will... (sobbing) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-01 00:58:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Ty! Him threatened...smh. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-01 00:14:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Mouse Liver: 0/10 even with rice. Thx u/dabilee01! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-30 15:48:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah, there have never been black intellectuals, like W.E.B. DuBois, Frederick Douglass, George Washington Carver, Earnest Everett Just, Benjamin Banneker, Charles Drew, etc.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-30 15:24:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You realize you've just defined the exact opposite of the common usage of the word nigger, right?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-30 04:16:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It was a joke...oh well I guess I'll pull it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-30 04:14:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I had a cat that would eat the whole thing and leave the liver. It was pretty gross.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
