<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject4287</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> eBay probably got its name from Pig Latin </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-28 19:29:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-19 14:02:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> In fairness, we could likely relax trade of dairy products where hormones were not used. I suspect there's plenty of dairy products in the US that would satisfy the same safety standards as Canadian dairy. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-19 01:45:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> On one hand as a consumer I would like very much to not have to spend so much for milk. However, if this issue actually gains some traction, I feel like the buy-out of Canada's dairy industry given their lobbying strength will be staggering.

Maybe I should go buy a cow while I can... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What happened?: Canadian dairy farmers being very unfair to U.S. counterparts, Donald Trump says </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-19 01:45:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-19 01:44:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> On one hand as a consumer I would like very much to not have to spend so much for milk. However, if this issue actually gains some traction, I feel like the buy-out of Canada's dairy industry given their lobbying strength will be staggering. 

Maybe I should go buy a cow while I can... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Redditors nostalgic for 'sweding' movies on YouTube inspired from movie Be Kind Rewind; IamDangerWolf posts his hilariously sweded version of Men In Black posted yesterday </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-06 20:20:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-23 15:37:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Anyone reading anything good? I'm about halfway through Stephen King's IT, and going to need something new for the New Year.

Generally prefer sci-fi.. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-05 17:41:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hey, I re-posted it, come to the new thread, I'm really interested to hear your side. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-05 17:29:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Related to Canadian Politics specifically regarding international push back on trade treaties: 

 A trade deal between the European Union and hardly threatening Canada was almost scuppered by a recalcitrant Belgian province concerned about the effects of globalization on local workers.

Globally sentiments are turning away from globalization, open borders and trade, towards strengthening national identities. 

From /u/mymainmannoamchomsky in /r/economics: 

Two interesting passages that get to the crux of the issue here:

In the beginning of the article:

 It used to be generally accepted that reducing trade barriers increases prosperity and promotes peace, benefiting investing and recipient countries and promoting international cooperation in solving problems around the world.

And at the end of the article:

 In recent years we have also commenced a race to the bottom in areas like labor standards, environmental protections and capital requirements for banks. Businesses evade stiffer rules by moving elsewhere, hindering national aspirations to improve in these areas. The remedy is international dialogue directed at establishing global minimum standards, harmonizing approaches.

We were sold the first: Comparative advantage will increase output - it's an economic fact - both countries will be far better off as firms use the particular advantages of their home economy and specialize.
But really it was the latter: Countries used "global trade" as a way to transcend the rules of any particular nation. The free trade ended up being an apple plant assembling phones in China shipping to Apple US who sells the phones. Multi-nationals traded with themselves (which is basically arbitrage, not trade). </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Larry Summers: It's Time for a Reset </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-05 17:28:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-05 17:26:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Is it pro-globalization? He pretty explicitly states that global trade treaties have mostly served only to skirt labor standards and environmental protections. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-05 17:23:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah, the original title is just "It's Time for a Reset", I went with the same title used on the /r/Economics post that grabs a quote from the article to contextualize the content. So I would have thought this is still in keeping with Rule #1. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-05 16:56:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That isn't too surprising, as the sentiments of the region certainly don't exclusively reflect centre-left sentiments, so one would expect it to usually have a few representatives on the right barring a big upset like 2015. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [Xpost from r/Economics] Larry Summers, former U.S. Treasury Secretary: Its Time for a Reset. Everywhere, anti-globalization is on the rise. We need to promote responsible nationalism. We must stop a race to the bottom in areas like labor standards and environmental protections </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-05 16:46:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-04 04:25:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Is it too much for me to dream that there could be a resurrection of Canada's [Technocracy movement](https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Technocracy_movement)? 

Doesn't look like it was ever an official party, but I could slap a maple leaf on that red ying yang and get the ball rolling! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-03 20:56:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I get the feeling you're joking, but it already isn't that unusual for transactional softwares to poll users to get their opinions on a range of topics. Or just collect data on habits, etc. This data can be purchased by the state already I believe... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-03 20:49:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That's a really good point.

Thinking of workarounds, the best I can come up with is physical submissions could hypothetically shuffled and tallied after-the-fact, and electronic submissions could simply be recorded without submitter data to an independent server than tax submission. 

However, it definitely doesn't preserve a perfect anonymity... One could argue it's on par with going into a polling location and they already have your name on the rolls, but yeah... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-03 19:59:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  This will have a disenfranchising effect on the poor, and individuals who are traditionally less likely to file tax returns, as they have far less to gain from it.

I'd mentioned this in a comment above, but if Basic Income ever takes off it will be necessary to ensure that low-income and impoverished individuals are in the Revenue Canada system. If there's a political soft-referendum element to tax submissions, I suspect there would be a much stronger organized effort to engage these individuals rather than simply letting them fall through the cracks, which is what we currently do.

 Moreover, it moves tax returns into a direction that requires more from people. Tax returns need to be far easier, and ideally, should be as pre-filled out as possible for individuals to receive the maximum amount of returns possible.

This is a fair point, but asking people to fill out a couple of multiple-choice questions separate from their personal return isn't exactly making the return itself more complicated. 

 It's an idea that's good in theory, but really, at the end of the day, we have a representative democracy for a reason, and I'd prefer a group of chosen individuals be making decisions while in constant consultations with their constituents.

Again, a fair point; however, it would generate a fascinating set of additional data on the sentiments of Canadians to inform our representative democracy's decision making.
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-03 18:27:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> In fairness, accountants are professionals, and you have to reveal many things like your income and various other personal details about your life to them, if you choose to use them. 

As professionals, I feel there would be little impropriety in their also having an awareness of this additional information. No more than the professionalism of a Revenue Canada employee or other public service worker. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-03 18:02:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I've heard it suggested on numerous occasions that the current tax system infrastructure could be utilized for things like Basic Income. It occurred to me, that if there was a political incentive to get as many people in the Revenue Canada system, particularly individuals in poverty/low-income, this would be really good way to close some of the cracks that people in our society fall through. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [Policy Idea] Conducting "soft" referendums through annual Income Tax submissions to Revenue Canada? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-03 17:48:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I thought I'd throw this out there as a topical policy idea for discussion on whether there's an easier way than full-out referendums to get direct feedback from the electorate on sticky policy issues.

Sometimes the question of whether an administration has a proper mandate from the electorate to make a major reform can be difficult to resolve. Particularly when the issue at hand is whether an administration selected by one electoral system has a clear mandate to change to a new electoral system. Obvious conflicts of interest there...

It's a fair point that a referendum from the electorate might be the only proper method to change the entire system of how Canadians select elected representatives.  However, there's a real danger that if the current government goes through with a referendum and the electorate chooses to maintain the status quo, that's a lot of political capital burnt to achieve nothing. 

Similarly, during an election parties have massive policy platforms, and while the electorate might agree with a large proportion of a party's policy agenda, there may be several issues where a plurality of Canadians would prefer something else. 

Questions of whether ~~the mob~~ the electorate should take too great a hand directly in the selection of policy and governance notwithstanding, it would be nice to have some clear polling data on where most Canadians stand on certain issues. 

**Therefore, be it resolved:** 

**Would it be useful to have a section in Canadian's income tax returns where they could make selections on desired policy initiatives. Basically, annual 'soft' referendum questions, without the pageantry and expense of full-out polling places, ballots, volunteers, etc.**

Good idea? Terrible idea? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-02 21:39:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Lol, there is a fair argument to be made for that. However, I would take terrorist Alan Rickman over Billy Bob, I think. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-02 21:23:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> the PS?

We try to have pretty regular fun-times, and it's a small company so it's easy to organize stuff. I think the next shin dig might involve building and setting off model rockets, still on the fence over whether or not including alcohol will be a major liability there. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-02 20:42:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> My company decided to have some special team-building this evening. We're going to drink egg-nog, eat pizza and watch Die Hard (best Christmas movie ever). Maybe even Die Hard 2 if there's time. :D </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-30 08:26:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I have to admit, I wonder if it had gone to full vote what the spread of the senate membership would have been, and how that would impact how this new system is portrayed. 

Really they've only kicked the can down the road, at some point a similar situation will pop up and finger-pointing about who is and isn't partisan will resume.

I really hope the senate can somehow develop a brand of objective, non-partisan, review of HoC legislation though.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-29 21:00:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The interesting thing here is the pace of technology is also rapidly increasing. I wonder what sort of simple policy changes could improve flexibility/efficiency within these bureaucracies. 

Personally, I'd recommend hiring more cooperative education employees for short-term roles within the ministries and give them a mandate of developing simple efficiency improvements to systems during their placements. 

Another option (not mutually exclusive) would be to set up an interdepartmental competition for developing improvements. 

The hard part would be driving adoption if anyone actually developed anything useful... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-27 17:14:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I don't know if Trudeau was right to broadcast the statement he did following Castro's passing, especially as PM rather than just his personal feelings as a private citizen; the guy was unequivocally a dictator that committed terrible acts.

However, there was an interesting run-down over in /r/AskHistorians on Castro cross-posted from /r/neutralpolitics that drew [similar conclusions](https://www.reddit.com/r/AskHistorians/comments/5ez8b2/was_fidel_castro_a_good_guy_for_lack_of_a_better/dagsnc0/) as Trudeau's statements. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-27 17:04:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I feel like a lot of gridlock that occurs in a typical democratic institution is a result of individuals needing to get re-elected, and thus needing to represent the limited interests their constituency. 

These senators really aren't answerable to anyone during their service, so hopefully the only things that will motivate them to stand in the way of legislation progressing are genuine convictions towards making it better. 

I'm also generally very pessimistic, but I have a lot of hope for this reform. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Historic land deal with Algonquin peoples signed by federal, Ontario governments </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-18 18:22:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-10 03:03:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So, a couple years ago I started a startup halfway through my PhD. I just moved back to Canada after spending the summer in silicon valley, and starting this month I'll be able to afford to pay myself a livable salary for the first time. 

The whole thing could very well still fail, but I'm finally feeling stable, and hopefully defending my PhD soon too! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-11 08:17:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Well, it's less about "salary" when you're in business for yourself, because the success of the company is your success. 

Also, agreed, you can't really do conventional "engineering" jobs as a business without a license. However, anything conventional is going to be a saturated market where you wouldn't be able to compete without a ton of experience anyway.

The key is to find a real problem that doesn't have a good solution, and then build an organization to offer a solution (or more simply, make 'something' that people want), business and work will follow. 

Further, you can still gain expertise, and depending on where you're working and who you're working with, you can still gain expertise towards gaining a license. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-11 04:12:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Another option is to consider entrepreneurship. If no one will hire you, become your own boss. 

Even if you fail doing this, the network you'll develop will probably let you become employed despite any record you're saddled with. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-18 17:22:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Figured PhD/postdoc job market would suck. Started a company instead. Then you make even less unless it takes off. Still have my fingers crossed. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-04 21:13:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Mutated cancer cells often have receptors/markers on their exterior that you can use as targets for therapies. e.g. the EGFR receptor is a common one. Making your own body produce antibodies against certain targets is effectively a vaccine. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-24 14:27:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The whole thing is a non-story compared to the legislation under debate, and the new rules the Libs were trying to implement. 

Trudeau tripped up a little, the NDP took it a little too far and briefly embarrassed the entire country to get to the PM. Still, give it a couple more weeks and I suspect all of this will fade from anyone's radar, particularly the electorate that seems not to have cared much in the first place. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-20 21:19:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I must know, you had a shark incident?

I don't think I'm going to have much time to go swimming and stuff, it's more of a work trip that won't include much down time.

It would be a shame to go all the way down there and not go look at the Pacific for a while.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-20 19:21:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I thought the Bay Area was Silicon Valley... I better figure this out before I leave.

Still haven't In-n-Out'd yet, definitely on the list.

Also, no worries, the ocean and its various critters definitely have my respect. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-20 19:18:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> SOON. :p </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-20 16:39:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm moving to California. :) (but just for the summer probably) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-20 01:07:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That's actually a really interesting play. A responsible use of the not-withstanding clause could show that it's not the legislative nuclear option it's portrayed to be. 

I like it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-19 17:17:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I watched, I'll admit it's confusing. Trudeau reaches through and then Mulcair gets very upset. I don't get it.

How long were they standing there like that with Brown behind Mulcair before Trudeau walked over I wonder...  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-19 17:04:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Did this all happen off camera? I didn't see any of that...

Also, to play out the analogy, if I was trying to get back to my desk for an important work task that needed to get done, but my boss was chatting with his friends at the water cooler blocking the way, I don't know if I'd be upset that some other team's boss tried to reach through the crowd to help me through. 

This is like helping a person get off the Subway levels of bumping. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-19 15:33:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So wait... he parted a crowd of loitering MPs to let Brown through? That's the "manhandling"? This whole episode seems so unbelievably contrived. Especially after the earlier games on Monday.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-06 19:31:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Just last night, I finished reading Pathfinder by Orson Scott Card. 

It was pretty cool, and offered a nice bridge between Sci-Fi and Fantasy tropes. Also the theme of how time is experienced (and could be manipulated) was pretty interesting. It reminded me a little of reading a Brandon Sanderson story in the sense of there being a pretty cool world and premise governed by a system of rules that the characters are bound within. 

Time travel is pretty complicated though, and Orson Scott Card is a little hand-wavey with some of the paradoxes. Also, the main character is a little too exceptional in his personal capabilities. However, all in all, I enjoyed it a lot.

I'll probably keep reading the rest of the trilogy.

As an aside, this was also the first book that I acquired from a "little library" on someone's lawn, while walking around California, so that was pretty sweet.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-04 23:03:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Pretty groovy, I feel like I'm looking at a protein. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-01 01:01:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Watched a ton of these puttering around Mountain View this past week. They're pretty adorable. I think they'll do exceptionally well once they hit market. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-07 21:44:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Reports like this are what make me lose faith in democracy altogether... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-03 18:19:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I think it's a good idea, a greater diversity of ideas will generate more interesting and effective policy options. Especially as concerns grow that the entire institution of government can't keep up with the speed that society is changing. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Is there a polite term for white people in Cantonese? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-26 15:40:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm often referred to (I hope affectionately) as a gwei jai by my partner's family, and I've grown up around Chinese communities my whole life, but never came across a formal or polite terminology.

Thanks! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-24 19:16:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> He was pretty good in his half of From Dusk Till Dawn too. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-12 22:53:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> **Girlfriend Filibusters Saturday Night Plans with Never-Ending Afternoon Nap.** </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-10 22:36:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Was Bush-Harper warm? Obama-Trudeau feels warm on a par with Reagan-Mulroney.

I'm sure there's some kind of warm-relation metric that someone published somewhere... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-18 00:26:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Can't they have an arm just reach out and grab the rocket as it's landing? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-02 04:51:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Melancholy Mountain

A place for being overwhelmed with longing for a lost time and place. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-23 03:42:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's true, but I want to believe that a nuclear technology that isn't capable of having meltdowns can win people over.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-22 22:42:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Nuclear could become the watch-word of the 21st century and Canada a major supplier of technology and natural resources to prevent carbon proliferation. 

I wish the federal government had put resources into developing a thorium reactor that could be exported similarly to the popularity of the CANDU reactor.  It could become a major source of funding for Canada into the 21st century, as we possess some of the largest thorium reserves in the world.

I may be mistaken, but I think developing Thorium nuclear power technology is actually part of the LPC party policy... can't remember if it actually passed or not, but it should have.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-14 20:34:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> In the US with Obamacare they've made a lot of impressive strides towards paying providers based on patient outcomes rather than fee-for-service.  i.e. healthcare providers get paid more when people get home and get better without needing to be re-admitted. Instead of getting paid more if a patient gets a post-operative surgical complication or hospital-associated infection that keeps them bed-ridden for 3 months. 

If the insurance is public, i.e. single-payer, and set up with incentives for standard of care instead of fee for service, healthcare outcomes will improve. 

Also, right now in Canada we mostly have fee-for-service despite it being a publicly delivered.  We don't pay providers for better patient outcomes. They're paid more in some ways to persist in being inefficient.

Keep in mind, I'm not saying people should be able to go and use their own money to purchase healthcare services.  I'm saying keep the public insurance, but lose the notion that delivery of that service should also be a public institution.  Also, have a strong regulatory component so that the delivery of those services is still held under the microscope. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-14 19:38:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Something I've always failed to understand: why can't we have public insurance but private well-regulated healthcare?

If you need care, you should receive it.  However, it would be nice to get the competitive advantages of an open market system.  I don't see why as nation we can't have both... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-14 19:34:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This is a fair point; however, even if we were receiving global market rates, at $35 the margins really aren't there right now. I worry the other players will succeed in pushing us out at this rate. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-12 18:44:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Let me preface this by saying your mother's attitude seems outrageous.

Out of curiosity, have you ever thought of trying one of those new walk-assist exoskeletons like companies such as Bionik are making? Might help you achieve additional normalization with family members that reject your disability. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-12 17:38:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  but the First World War was pretty much inevitable. Europe was an armed camp by 1914


It seems inevitable looking back a hundred years, but I'm sure with a couple shifted events the militarism that gave rise to the 'powder keg' might have been prevented. Imagine if the Spanish Flu had occurred a decade or so previously for instance. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-12 17:18:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I noticed Statute of Westminster Day in my Google calendar yesterday listed as a Canadian holiday and was reading about it.

Sometimes I wonder what the world would have been like if the world wars never happened and Imperialism had continued unabated.

Probably no computers or rockets... A lot more steampunk perhaps. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-09 16:06:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Great to see, but why are we still using hen eggs when advanced cell culture platforms can be used and scaled more easily with outbreaks? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-11-29 19:01:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I can't understand caving to NIMBYs when you're at the beginning of a new mandate. I feel like now is the time to piss off as many people as possible that have no proper leg to stand on with their arguments.

They should approve the project, and use the time till the next election to let the decision become popular, as it very likely would. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-11-25 23:47:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I like to think the economics of cell culture meat will demolish emissions from live-stock.  

Being able to produce large quantities of hamburger meat (or whatever meat) straight from cells is going to be safer from a QA perspective (fewer chance of prions, etc.), be a comparatively minuscule footprint, cheaper in the long run.  Probably taste identical.  

In the mean time, authentic meat can become a luxury item and make money that way. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-11-24 22:23:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I was startled by just how much I loved this movie.  I wish I'd gone back to see it in theatres again before it finished its run. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-11-12 03:34:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I spent several confused minutes reading this article before realizing that the picture is Campbell Clark the author, and not Mlanie Joly the new Liberal heritage minister, nor Shelley Glover the former Tory minister... I'm clearly quick on the uptake tonight. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-11-09 03:23:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  there is no way for the Parliament to negotiate at this stage

What about the "side letters" that haven't been released yet, can they still be renegotiated?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-11-09 01:58:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I feel like the same way an amendment process is built into a constitution, an international trade agreement should have room to adjust as the global economy continues to emerge. 

Who knows what the dominant technology and consumer products will be in 20 years?

Trying to get everything right the first time in a closed door negotiation seems like a recipe for disappointment. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-11-09 01:03:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's kind of fascinating seeing different individuals come in on opposite sides of supporting or rejecting TPP based on differences in the vision of what the Canadian economy (and global economy) will be in the future.  

It's a little troubling that the provisions have TPP have been written with little room for alteration and renegotiation over time. 

I'm still looking forward to reading a good pro/con analysis of the deal based on various sectors. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-11-08 04:44:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I know you're playing devil's advocate here, but some of us walk down empty halls of empty labs that used to be filled with scientists. Labs that will take years to re-establish themselves so that Canada doesn't fall behind the rest of the world in research.

Things weren't just shifted to applied science, research was diminished all over.  

I get that it's a matter of ideology whether it's worth it as a society for the state to fund research.  However, culturally speaking, beyond the arts and sciences what do we produce as a people that has any lasting importance? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-11-07 21:25:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I don't even mind that this is the Chronicle meets Hancock, looks pretty watchable. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-10-30 13:49:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> There's this sour beer from St. Catharines that's really good called Wild Child from Black Swan brewery.


I had it at a local Mexican place that adds a pineapple guava syrup to it. Pretty damn delicious. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-10-28 14:09:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Especially the non digital content that was outright destroyed.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-10-28 05:37:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  something along the lines of *regularly* down vote

Agreed, in the years I've been on this sub I've only downvoted a person once that I can remember.  I still feel a little shame about it, and a little repulsed at how exulted I felt silencing dissent against my perceived righteous opinion. 

Someday, when I'm Shogun, I hope I can remain benevolent... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-10-28 02:59:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Nice! Not going to lie, after the election I thought to myself, "Hey wait a minute, there's going to be funding again... Maybe I should actually give this whole academia thing a second thought!" </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Canadas New Government May Be a New Beginning for Science </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-10-27 14:44:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-10-25 15:27:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Realistically, you're right. However, I suspect the first long bill the Liberals introduce will be declared omnibus by the Conservatives, and they'll be accused of being hypocrites. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-10-25 15:03:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It would be interesting to have a more firm line for when a package of legislation is too long. Is it by topic, by page length...

I suspect this will be a law in and of itself eventually. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-10-25 14:34:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I would be extremely upset if the Liberals ever began passing omnibus legislation. However, I'm curious how this community would react if they introduced an omnibus repeal of the various laws that very likely are unconstitutional anyway.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-10-24 17:33:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Only if it's a duplex for the PM's family and the leader of the oppisition's family. Also, the house has a shared kitchen/dining area. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-10-23 22:00:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Question for all: Given the success of Liberal parties federally and provincially in recent years, what is the likelihood that Trudeau might try to take his mandate to open the constitution? (assuming an increased willingness to cooperate)

Sub-question: Assuming Trudeau decided to go for it, what outstanding constitutional updates might be included if such an action were taken? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-10-21 04:14:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's so expensive keeping people locked up, releasing nonviolent drug offenders makes too much sense regardless of the fact that they violated the law at the time. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-10-21 04:10:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I think the Liberals always insisted they would legalize only following a best-practices study of where legalization has already occurred.

I could see them decriminalizing in the interim towards full legalization though. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-10-20 04:20:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Holy crap, majority territory. Not sure how I feel about this. Might be too much too soon. Still, easier job for the GG. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-10-15 20:13:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> An extraterratorial seat would be a nice addition, if only because those MPs could be called ETs. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-10-15 16:02:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If we can take the implosion of the Liberal party as any kind of model, then the CPC will struggle for a couple years before selecting a former prime minister's son as the party leader.

Calling it now, my money is on Ben Mulroney getting into politics.

**Edit:** If Ben isn't up to the job, maybe Catherine Clark can come out swinging. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-10-15 15:08:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hopefully if the Libs form government they keep their promises on bipartisan electoral reform. Personally, I'm hoping in the next five years to have ranked ballots for instant runoff as well as a selection of seats devoted to national popular vote awarded proportionally.

It still won't be perfect, but more fair, and hopefully the greens can finally get a good toe-hold to build on. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-10-12 23:11:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> He was definitely higher earlier in the year...  I think the best impression Mulcair gives is when he's railing away on the gov't as leader of the opposition.  His authority and leadership really came through in those question period clips.  I don't know if that continued as well into the debates, which might have diminished voters' earlier impression of him. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-10-04 23:49:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The electorate is pretty split, there might be a fair amount of support after the election for obstructionism. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-10-04 23:36:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thirty senators who aren't in caucus aren't going to rubber stamp anything though. Omnibus legislation would likely disappear to an extent. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> If the NDP formed the next government, even with a majority, would they be able to get any legislation through the Senate? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-10-04 23:26:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The NDP favours abolishing the Senate, it occurred to me this might be necessary to accomplish any legislative agenda at all. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-10-02 02:33:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It would be interesting to have a regular poll of scientists and economists for ranking the acceptability of policy decisions.

Personally, I would prefer to know what the people who know the most think of the policies that politicians are pushing.

Some opinions shift dramatically when you have expertise in a particular area. For instance the average person, if they go into cardiac arrest, or a family member does, want physicians to do everything they can to save them.  However, a [startlingly low number of medical physicians desire the same attempts at resuscitation for themselves](http://ideas.time.com/2012/01/16/what-doctors-know-and-we-can-learn-about-dying/?xid=gonewsedit google_editors_picks=true) if they go into cardiac arrest, many getting "no code" tattoos or medallions, and signing advance DNR orders.  

  Only about 8% of people who go into cardiac arrest outside of the hospital are revived by CPR. Even when your heart stops in the hospital, you have only a 19% chance of surviving.

Given the choice, many physicians elect to forgo the violent medical interventions that many of their patients are given.

A lot of policy is written with the best of intentions and ends up being a nightmare in its execution. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-10-01 18:36:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'd love to see a full accounting of the cost of the unwinnable legal challenges and constitutionally unfeasible legislation the government has passed.  

If you had a majority government - a significant legislative opportunity - can you imagine spending so much of your time and energy on passing and fighting over bills and laws that obviously violate the Charter?

I hate that so much of our politics is about scoring points, and I'm not just referring to the party in power. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-09-28 01:18:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hear hear!

Really though, it's a nice compromise on the constitutional side of things. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-09-27 17:06:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> :P

We gotta find a way to hang out again soon. School stuff probably won't bring me back to QC any time soon, but let me know if you are visiting ON.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-09-27 17:01:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I didn't realize Legault also had a writing credit, I'm going to have to look up his other stuff and see if I can grab it at the library! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-09-27 02:08:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I saw another show called Series Noire that I was going to try next.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-09-26 21:17:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I wonder how this plan would adjust if the Liberals brought the GST back... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-09-26 01:05:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Has anyone been watching some of French Canadian content that Netflix Canada has up right now? I started watching "19-2" a couple weeks ago. Holy crap, for a police procedural show, it will totally knock you on your ass. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-09-20 15:28:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Interesting article, though I'll wager having an actor say "Stephen Harper isn't perfect..." won't win voters over like McGuinty's more personal admission of fallibility.

Also, why did the author dovetail to Energy, Defense, and general party niceties as the real perception problem of the CPC? Are there polls suggesting that's where they're hurting? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-09-19 14:23:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This is the first time I've realized that the movie must take place in 1980.

(The quarter is from 1958, and it's been travelling 22 years to reach the man who married into the gas station.) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-09-16 00:33:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I don't think you're going to need to wait 20 years for a potential treatment.  

People talk about the rate of technological advancement, but that's always so vague it can be difficult to derive real hope.  You might appreciate learning more about [CRISPR](http://www.radiolab.org/story/antibodies-part-1-crispr/) (this is a link to a podcast called RadioLab that gives a great explanation of what CRISPR is for a lay person) a new tool that sort of erupted onto the biotech scene last year.  

There's a good chance that this tool will be used to help correct your boyfriend's mutation and countless others like it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-09-15 18:56:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Come on, science isn't politics, it's empirical fact. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-09-12 01:53:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  Nice hair though.

I missed that little catch phrase at the end first time I watched this. Delightful. :) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-09-10 21:37:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> As long as we don't have any creepy mausoleums where we taxidermy QEII* and put her in a glass sarcophagus, I'd say bring on the necrocracy. 

*Perhaps just a couple of her favourite Corgis would be reasonable. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-09-09 19:37:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I've insisted on this sub in the past that - for a monarchy loophole - we should make QEII Canada's reigning monarch in perpetuity (i.e. even after she dies).

Keep all the heritage, but simultaneously break from the future royals.

An immediate benefit is it won't be necessary to re-mint any currency. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-09-06 20:47:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Depends on your interpretation, but I'd suggest the contrary to this. (Unfortunately it's a bit of a spoiler to recommend the book at all based on OP's request, and answering this question). </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-09-06 14:42:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Haven't read that one yet, though it's on my list, is it pretty good? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-09-06 02:40:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> American Gods by Neil Gaiman was pretty entertaining. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> If the Liberals are Grits, and the Conservatives are Tories, does the NDP have a playful nickname? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-09-01 14:54:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If a nickname doesn't exist yet, what would be a good one? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-08-31 19:04:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I would love to see a federal plan to help municipalities implement housing first programs. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-08-29 00:44:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I acknowledge the premise and conclusion of your argument regarding the relationship between government and the civil service.  You're right that it is necessary, the same way members of the judiciary don't stand up in public advocating one set of gov't policies over another, as the perception of neutrality is important to maintain.

It occurred to me that under a hypothetical scenario where a government is abusing their mandate to the detriment of the country, such that members of the civil service feel the need to offer public protest or dissent, **the only suitable protest is to resign**. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-08-28 22:51:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This is the greatest simile I've ever read. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-08-28 22:32:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> ~~Regardless of the guidelines~~, being an employee of the government should ~~not~~ implicitly abdicate the rights of an individual to [outright public] dissent or protest. 

~~The rules should be changed.~~

**Edit:** (IMHO) The civil service is capable of offering protest and dissent, but only in the form of resignation. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-08-28 22:06:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Being a federal employee should not be some implicit abdication of an individual's rights as a citizen to dissent and protest publicly against the government.  Especially during an election, and when the subject of that protest has nothing to do with the employee's specific area of work.

On another note, that's a pretty catchy tune. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-08-22 17:29:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> /u/palpz is rightly asserting that all media will possess an institutional bias. 

However, some are going to be worse than others. I'm reminded of the scene from Mr. Smith goes to Washington, where the main character finds out that because his opponent owns all his state's newspapers, none of his constituents realize what's actually going on and in actuality view his actions as nefarious. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-08-22 13:43:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hmmm, now I'm wishing I read the original earlier... Anyone have a link to a cached copy? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-08-07 01:56:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That introduction comparing Harper to Walter White from Breaking Bad was absolutely delightful. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-08-02 17:07:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I totally support what they're going for, the whole forced modesty thing IMHO makes our society weirder and repressed in the long run. 

On a personal level I'm pretty sad I missed such a rally in my own back yard. :'( </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-31 17:44:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I was reading a similar thread in /r/fantasy of someone in Rothfuss/Sanderson withdrawal and someone recommended the [Gentleman Bastards series by Scott Lynch](https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Scott_Lynch#The_Gentleman_Bastard_Sequence).  The fourth book is coming out this year, and  I burned through the first three pretty quickly and found them highly enjoyable.  The 2nd and 3rd are better than the first.

The series is about a group of con artists in a fantasy setting, and the cons are all pretty clever. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-31 16:55:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What do you think of what that company Oxitec has been up to with using the transgenic males to wipe out large populations of Aedes aegypti?

[Article](http://www.the-scientist.com/?articles.view/articleNo/43574/title/GM-Mosquito-Cuts-Wild-Type-Numbers/) for anyone unfamiliar. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-19 23:43:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What is democracy if not glorified vote-buying? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-19 03:16:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Canadian investors are notoriously skittish. A large part of Canada's capital markets are actually American money anyway, but it would be nice if startups didn't need to leave to California to get a decent seed round.

That being said, the reason why everyone goes to Silicon Valley to get funded is because there's a ton of money being thrown around, to the point where they're calling it a startup valuation bubble. 

That wouldn't be good for Canada, but somewhere in the middle would really turn things around. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-19 00:00:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The startup ecosystem in KW is definitely growing, now if only the investment ecosystem could match it. Most of the startups coming up have to make pilgrimages to the US and other countries to get it. Then it's coin toss whether they come back afterwards. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-15 16:51:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The surplus is really more of an idea, or political narrative, than a tangible algebraic reality. 

Rest assured, there will be a surplus. However, if something goes really wrong with the economy, like say the collapse of the housing market, the gov't will be running the severe risk of gloating about something nobody cares about anymore. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-13 05:36:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I appreciate that they provided a politically stable administration over the course of the financial crisis and the recovery. 

Sure, I didn't like all the policies they enacted, but for the most part I had confidence in the Canadian state in a very tumultuous period. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-12 23:13:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Regarding a clear negative, strictly looking at poultry and dairy products, these are very expensive due to Supply Management, making Canadians with poor means select inferior dietary options. I love dairy and poultry products; however, I resent the dent they put in my budget.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-06 20:55:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  If Mr. Harper is going to be launching attacks, he needs to be doing so in a manner that actually hits the both of them.

This is actually really important.  While strategically attacking Mulcair does little for the CPC, by only attacking the Liberals and Justin, it's easy for them to come off as bullies that are picking on what is becoming the underdog in the race.  

Canadians like Justin.  They might not want him for PM, but he's a Canadian icon that voters aren't going to want to see dragged through the mud when he's already in 3rd place. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-06 18:18:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> My assumption is that potential conservative swing voters are only shared between the conservatives and the liberals.  Similarly, potential NDP swing voters are only shared between the NDP and the liberals. 

If the NDP continue to perform well in the polls, it will pull support from their shared swing voters with the Liberals.  This loss of support will discourage the conservative swing voters from voting Liberal and stick with the conservatives.

A strong NDP actually boosts the conservatives ability to aggregate their support in the election, because nobody wants to vote for a losing party, no matter how good their policies might look.  The green party is a good example of this (minus their fringe policy problems). </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-06 18:12:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Everything's a narrative... change is good, change is bad, one will win out over the other in the message wars.  

One thing I like about the premise of wagging the dog is that rather than wait around for rain and take credit for it, you manufacture a focus of attention for media and voters to change the conversation away from the fact that it's not raining. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-06 15:47:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> "You don't change horses midstream"

If you like political messaging, and satire, I recommend a movie from the 90s with Robert De Niro and Dustin Hoffman all about political messaging called [Wag the Dog](https://youtu.be/CNo0BicRM8k).

"Staying the course" could potentially turn into "We're turning the corner" if there's any economic improvement between now and the election. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-04 00:12:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> There were other mods of subs, I think /r/books for instance, who said they didn't even have a way to contact the authors that were slated to be doing AMAs, and no one told them Victoria had been canned...

Imagine if you were hosting Thomas Mulcair's AMA this week and Victoria had been the contact person on behalf of reddit, and then without any notice she was just gone.  

That's basically what happened to a lot of subs this week. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-03 05:12:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I have a small start-up doing R D to build a medical device. We just bought some materials from the states that were pricey, around $700. After the stuff arrived, my partner who handles the money pointed out it actually costed over a grand, because of the exchange rate. 

Those kinds of losses really add up when you're trying to make something before you run out of runway... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-03 05:02:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This really needs to happen, there are a startling number of cancers associated with HPV extending beyond just cervical cancer in women.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-26 20:03:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> There might be something wrong with those books... bed bugs for instance. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-25 23:16:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'd really like to see more riding equivalence.  There ought to be one riding for every 100k potential voters (or some appropriate fixed number).  

Maybe they could pie-slice urban areas for the riding boundaries so that we could still maintain some balance for rural and urban concerns.  However, [over 80% of Canadians live in urban areas vs. rural areas](http://www.statcan.gc.ca/tables-tableaux/sum-som/l01/cst01/demo62a-eng.htm), and it's ridiculous if the house of commons doesn't reflect that. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-25 03:40:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Have you considered simply giving up television?  I get by pretty well just with Netflix, and the only time I see a political ad is the odd time one pops up on YouTube. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-24 04:13:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I get that the LPC stalled announcing their policies to prevent giving the Conservatives ammunition for attack ads, but I can't help but feel like if they'd rolled them out periodically over the last 6 months they could have owned the message, controlled the conversation, and stayed ahead in the polls.

Right now, I feel like I'm in TO watching the maple leafs or something...

The LPC has SO MANY popular policy positions they could have announced. Announcing them all at once like this, unless you're a wonk, or a politics addict, it's probably just more noise than signal, and that won't overcome negative attack ads.

I don't know who's running strategy for the LPC, but they really don't seem to know what they're doing... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-23 17:10:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Not strictly Canadian politics, but I can't believe I'm living in a time when something with an overwhelming scientific consensus is treated like some arbitrary opinion open to snarky ridicule by random pundits. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Colby Cosh: Popes encyclical on climate change reads like the Unabomber Manifesto </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-23 17:03:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-22 18:51:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Admittedly better than soda pop though, no? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
