<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject6720</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-08 01:14:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I actually don't have the trademark yet, and I'm debating whether or not I should get one.  Here's what happened.  I was working on an online game with a friend for months and he kicked me out.  He said my ideas aren't technically worth any money, and that legally none of it is my IP even though many of the characters and game mechanics were conceptualized by me.  He said the only thing that I could have rights to is the name, but he said I don't even have rights to that since I don't have a trademark on the name.  I was basically screwed over, and now I'm trying to protect what I believe is mine. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Can another person use my trademark in this scenario? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-08 00:45:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [Maryland] If I have a registered trademark on the name of a potential online game, and Person B, who lives in the same state as me, uses that same name for an online game, is Person B allowed to do that? Please let me know. Thanks so much :) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-08 00:31:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> oh, i had no idea that was a thing.  Thanks so much! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Can another person use my trademark in this scenario? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-08 00:30:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [opinion] Why I think Bob Dylan is the best </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-07 06:17:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This was taken from this article: https://blugger.org/2017/05/06/my-analysis-of-bob-dylan/?frame-nonce=5cc5026a89

Like many artists throughout history, Bob Dylan had something to say about the world, and many of his folk songs are his responses to the ubiquitous change around him.  Often regarded as one of the greatest lyrical songwriters of the 20th century, Dylan creates long lasting works that resonate with audiences throughout time.  Though his musical style is derived from folk songs and ballads from decades ago, his words emanate from his heart.  The rhythmic style of the guitar strums add weight to each impactful lyric, and the results of this fusion are beautiful productions that have influenced so many writers in the last fifty years.  Dylans works are so well regarded that he won the 2016 Nobel Prize in Literature for his unparalleled addition to realm of music.  Though many parts of his life were shrouded in secrecy, Dylan remains a remarkable singer-songwriter of modern times, one who has captured the imagination of millions for nearly half a century of fame.  His wide body of work shows that passive observations and peaceful acts of resistance are the best ways to create change in society.

Bob Dylan was born Robert Allen Zimmerman in 1941 in Minnesota.  He spent most of his childhood listening to early country, blues, and rock and roll.  During his high school years, he performed covers of some of the most famous artists of the time including Elvis Presley.  After his high school, he enrolled in the University of Minnesota to study folk and rock and roll.  Thats when he figured that rock and roll lacked meaningful lyrics, and folk lacked the lightheartedness of rock.  Zimmerman believed that he could fill in the gaps, and he began to perform songs that he wrote at local coffee shops under the pseudonym Bob Dylan.  He got the last name Dylan from the name Dillon, which was the name of the poet Dillon Thomas.  He justified his name change by claiming that America is the land of the free.  This notion of a free land is what gave rise to Dylans lyrics as they were predominantly about freedom, peace, and prosperity.

After reaching a small level of popularity during his first year at college, Dylan dropped out to move to New York so that he could meet his idol, Woody Guthrie.  Guthrie was known for his numerous ballads about traditional and political ideologies, and Dylan was inspired by the idea of writing songs to send impactful messages.  After meeting Guthrie in 1961, Dylan started the discography that would change the face of music.  During the year of 1961, Dylan played at clubs throughout New York and received critical praise from famous publications such as The New York Times.  He became known for his ability to sing and play both the guitar and harmonica.

In 1962, Robert Allen Zimmerman legally changed his name to Robert Dylan.  This year was arguably one of his most productive years since this was when he wrote famous songs like Blowin in the Wind.  He also released his first album, which was appropriately called Bob Dylan.  Though the album itself didnt sell very well (it only sold 5000 copies in its first year), the product made enough to break even, which inspired Dylan to keep going forward.  Along with releasing his first album, Dylan signed his first management contract with Albert Grossman, who later became the manager of many other famous folk musicians.

In 1963, Dylan released his second album, which was titled The Freewheelin Bob Dylan.  Around this time, he became well known in the country for both his singing and songwriting skills.  Bob Dylan also became known for his protest songs, which blew up amidst political controversy.  Given his relevant songs pertaining to important matters around the world, Dylan began to establish himself as the musical voice of his generation.  He spoke specifically to his contemporaries and those younger than him as he believed if the world was to change, the future adults would be the ones to change it.  He knew what the people truly felt about important topics, and he spoke to each and every one of those people.  By this time, Robert Zimmerman was a shadow of the now famous Bob Dylan, which was really a costume.  In this sense, the concept of Bob Dylan will live forever since it isnt a physical, perishable object.  Zimmerman expresses himself through the notion of Dylan, and thats what makes Bob Dylan live beyond his own generation.

Dylan has proven through his body of work that passive resistance will almost be the solution to major problems.  Through his works like The Times They Are a Changin and Blowin in the Wind, Dylan has tried his best to promote peace.

Bob Dylans The Times They Are A Changin is a classic, timeless work of art that plays as an anthem for change.  Inspired by Irish and Scottish ballads, the universal, message-filled lyrics are coupled with great folk music in the background.  The song makes me think about how those who choose stay in the past must keep up because times are changing.


The song opens with a harmonica and guitar playing the melody.  Though this might not be what Dylan intended, I interpreted it as a patriotic tone on top the of the classic folk sounds. The first stanza perfectly sums up what the song is all about.  As Dylan asks the people of the world to admit that the waters around [them] have grown, he means that change has arrived.  He says that if people dont accept and embrace change, theyll drown in the past.  Its interesting to note that this was written in 1964 considering the tension between the past and the present.  At the time, the Civil Rights Movement was at its peak and anti-war sentiments in the midst of Cold War tensions were going strong.  I think Bob Dylan is trying to show that with all this call for change, those who wish to maintain the culture of the past will eventually fall because the new movements are growing at a fast rate.

The folk atmosphere provides a simple rhythm that Dylan repeats in the second stanza, but he shifts his attention from everyday people to writers and journalists.  He calls for those who prophesize with their pens to take careful note of change for when the times are changing, you never know what can happen.  Since the wheels still in spin, meaning that a lot change is still happening, Dylan explains that the loser now will be later to win so this is the time for journalists and writers to watch the world with sharper eyes.  This is a universal idea that applies to journalism, and we see it every day.  Surprising events happen all the time and modern journalists should try their best to foresee them since once they happen, time cannot be reversed.

The third stanza focuses on politicians, who are tasked with answering to the will of the people.  As Dylan points out, unfortunately, many senators and congressmen only work in their own best interests.  When the people demand change, Dylan points out that the congressmen cannot stand in the doorway or block up the hall.  Though I think the opening stanza is the best one, this one comes in a close second because of how truth-revealing it is.  Bob Dylan shows that the stalling politicians will ultimately be the ones who lose in the end because the demand for change (the raging battle outside as Dylan puts it) near the doors of Capitol building will eventually overpower even the strongest of politicians.

The last group of people that Dylan addresses consists of parents.  In the fourth stanza, he reminds parents that the children are the future.  Since times are changing, parents dont really have a say in criticizing what they dont understand.  He says that parents should not attempt to send their children on the path of the dusty, aging old road for their lives are unpaved.  Its the sons and daughters who must forge the new road, and if parents dont want to help, Dylan argues that they should get out.  This is Dylans stance on cultural change.  Its controversial due to the argument that parents want whats best for their children and sometimes their best is different from that of the children.  Though its difficult to see where the line is drawn, I would interpret Dylans lyrics as applicable to only the parents who dont want their children to make their own lives.  For that reason, I wholeheartedly agree with him.  Parents who hinder the decision making processes of their children really stand in the way of the future.  Every child has dreams and aspirations, and every time that a parent stands directly in the way of a dream, the future grows less bright.  I know its not a popular opinion among parents since many dreams are farfetched and risky, but true greatness often comes from taking risks.

The last stanza shows the universal and perpetual nature of change.  Dylan notes that the change of the present will soon be the past.  All the things he said earlier will soon apply to what we know as the present.  Its weird to think about life as this fast, linear movement of time, but it is.  Though Im young now, Ill be old soon and the thing that will keep me going is change.  If I dont embrace change at all stages of life, I too will sink like a stone.  Dylan poses this existential question of accepting change to everyone.

In my opinion, The Times They Are A Changin is the best Bob Dylan song, and its one of my favorite songs ever because of the messages that it conveys (which is funny since Im not a fan of folk music).  From its memorable melody to its universal lyrics, the song perfectly sums up why Bob Dylan wrote music.  Like many artists, he too had something to say about the world, and this song is his response to the ubiquitous change around him.

Bob Dylans 1962 song, Blowin in the Wind, stands as one of the artists greatest musical expressions.  From its opening line, Dylan weighs in on both the concept of maturity and some of the protest movements during the 1960s.  Like many of Dylans folk songs, the lyrics are supplemented with a simple acoustic guitar.  I personally think this is a good thing for this song since it adds more gravity to Dylans lyrics.


The first stanza starts out asking questions that Dylan was trying to figure out at the young, curious age of 21.  How many roads must a man walk down before you can call him a man?  When someone is 21, he/she questions the legitimacy of adolescence.  Am I an adolescent or an adult?  The common notion is that people become adults when they experience life enough to be well experienced.  Aside from the fact that this idea disturbs me, it definitely bothered Dylan.  Its easy to give that advice, but its difficult to point how much is enough.  The next question parallels the last by comparing an adolescent to a white dove trying to find a place to rest.  However, this question asks something a little deeper.  After doing some research about white doves, it turns out that the white dove is considered a symbol for peace.  In this sense, Dylan is actually hitting two birds with one stone (no pun intended) since hes also asking about the countless years it will take to achieve world peace.  Dylans attachment to peace is ultimately what won him the Nobel Prize in Literature in 2016.  This hinted question about peace leads into the next question asking the people how many times cannonballs must fly before they become banned.  Its the same idea as the last one, but its a little more apparent and concrete.  Then, he directs his attention to the listener and tells him/her that the answer is blowin in the wind.  I will talk about what this means further down in the analysis since its the overarching theme of the song.

The next stanza continues Dylans stream of questions with, How many years can a mountain exist before its washed into the sea.  I think this is a metaphor for ideas and legacy.  Much like how mountains can erode and become part of the sea over long periods of time, ideas and legacy can fade away after a person dies either figuratively or literally.  Literally speaking, when a person dies, memories of that person will fade until the person is nothing but a name on  a gravestone.  Figuratively, if a person changes who he/she is, memories of the past person will also fade away.  However, this question alludes to the notion that art transcends life and specifically time.  While the meaning of a work of art can change over time due to evolving interpretations, its physical aspect can in theory stay forever.  For Bob Dylan, his art will live on even after he is gone.  The next question asks about the number of years someone can exist before they can be free.  The simplest interpretation from this would be that Dylan sees a lack of freedom in many places around the world.  For example, the Civil Rights Movement can be seen as a protest against the dearth of true freedom for African Americans.  Dylan hopes that everyone can be free because only then can we achieve world peace, which is Dylans big hope for the future.  However, this question doesnt necessarily move on from the posthumous themes of the last one.  Even after some people die, theres still the idea that they didnt die in peace or that they died incomplete.  Many people can argue that performing someones last wishes or completing their unfinished duties will allow the deceased to rest in peace.  The final question of the stanza asks, How many times can a man turn his head pretending he just doesnt see.  These two lines express Dylans frustration with bystanders who just watch as others suffer.  There has been a long debate among many psychologists and historians regarding whether or not compassion is an inherent quality among humans.  If humans were inherently born compassionate, why is it that there are so many bystanders who dont do anything to help others since it would not be in their self-interest?  Dylan expresses his thoughts on compassion to show that we as social animals should work in the interest of each other so that we can achieve peace.  These thoughts are the hallmark of peaceful protest culture.

The first question of the last stanza is the one Im the least certain about.  I believe that Dylan is talking about the number of times that a man has ask a question before he finds the answer.  However, it could also have more literal meanings.  In the times leading up to 1962, the world saw gruesome wars that covered the sky with smoke.  In that regard, Dylan wonders how much time it will take until there isnt a war.  The next question goes back to the one about bystanders.  Dylan emphasizes that we as humans should take care of each other if we are to be happy.  The final question of the song targets the countless wars since the beginning of time that have killed countless individuals.  Dylan also questions those who killed in the name of God since the wars havent stopped and peace has not yet been achieved.  Those warmongering efforts in the name of God were ultimately pointless, and that if there is a God, He would be appalled by the violence and bloodshed done in His name.

I think the most important things about this song are not necessarily the questions that Dylan asks.  The real message that he conveys is that the answer is blowin in the wind, which means that the answers to all of lifes questions are anything but static.  The answers will move and flow with the passage of time just like a leaf does when it is blowin in the wind.  There is no definitive way to find the answers to lifes questions because there is no definitive answer.  This is why I think Dylans songs are fantastic.  They arent very long, but they speak volumes about relatable things like maturity and morality.

This notion sums up many of Bob Dylans works.  They are testaments to human nature.  Its no wonder that Dylan won the Nobel Prize in Literature in 2016.  The Dylan today is a remnant of the pasts Zimmerman, but thats what Bob emphasizes so clearly.  We humans forge our own path; names dont define us, but our actions do.  Over the last few decades, Bob Dylan has crafted numerous influential works of art that have stood the test of time and have entered musical history. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Mohit Puvvala - World New [Dance, EDM] </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-27 17:40:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> STAR WARS: THE LAST JEDI TRAILER BREAKDOWN </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-15 22:10:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Is Luke a Grey Jedi? The Last Jedi Trailer Breakdown </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-15 22:10:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Is Luke a Grey Jedi? The Last Jedi Trailer Breakdown </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-15 21:21:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-10 05:33:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hopefully there's a bright future ahead for everyone :) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-10 05:32:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> haha lol I failed that one </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Turned 18 Today </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-10 05:17:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Idk just wanted to put it out there :) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-02 17:24:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> ahahaha, what a story, DiskFelcore!  Yup, just changed it, thanks! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [Review] Why The Room is a Cinematic Masterpiece </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-02 04:52:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This review was taken from this link: https://blugger.org/2017/04/01/review-the-room/ 

The Room is a misunderstood cinematic masterpiece that deserves to be on every critics all time top 10 list.  Tommy Wiseau, the films writer, producer, director, and star, deserves the utmost praise for his magnificent role as Johnny, a banker who loves his fianc, Lisa.  This independent drama is the pinnacle of filmmaking as it challenges the audience with deep questions.  Very few movies have left me speechless (hence the small review).  The Room is so good that I literally cant think of anything on the level of praise that this film deserves.  Hands down, its the Citizen Kane of movies, period.

In this blessing from heaven, Johnny (Tommy Wiseau) lives with his fianc, Lisa (Juliette Daniel).  Right out of the gate, the two share an intimate love-making session that would make any 50 Shades of Grey fan drool.  However, Lisa believes that her love for Johnny is fading and that she is truly in love with Johnnys best friend, Mark (Greg Sestero).  As the film progresses, these three characters question their friendship and identity against the riveting backdrop of San Francisco.  Along with the leads is Denny, Johnnys and Lisas student neighbor whom Johnny financially supports.  Also, be prepared to bring footballs and spoons when you watch this movie  youll know why when you see it.

The first thing I noticed about the room was its wonderful and complex acting.  Every performance feels nuanced.  Lisas facial expressions alone tell a story, and I can really feel the frustration that she feels towards her life.  Greg Sesteros deceptive performance as Mark is wonderful to watch as well.  Philip Haldiman represents the universal teenager in a relatable way.  However, at the center of it all is Tommy Wiseaus distinct performance as Johnny.  His quirky subtleties are hard to catch on first glance, but this is what makes Johnny seem like an actual person.  This is a performance that extends beyond the screen and into our souls, asking us questions about relationships that we never thought wed ask.  There have been few times when characters transcend the movies that theyre in, and Johnny from The Room does just that.

This movie deserves an award for just sheer number of quotable lines.  Below are some lines that you might find yourself saying from time to time:

Oh hai, Mark.  Youre tearing me apart, Lisa!  Ha ha ha.  What a story, Mark.  It seems to me that youre the expert, Mark.  Anyway, hows your sex life?  You betrayed me! Youre not good. You, youre just a chicken. Chip-chip-chip-chip-cheep-cheep.  Hi, doggy.  If a lot of people love each other, the world would be a better place to live.

One of the main concerns about the movie is that it has subplots and certain plot points that dont go anywhere.  Thats where The Room is misunderstood.  The plot points and questions are left unanswered so you can fill in the gaps.  This is a film that involves the audience to the point of complete immersion.  The viewers tie themselves to the various characters in different ways such that each interpretation is unique.  For these reasons, The Room is definitely ahead of its time.  I mean, come on, this movie came out in 2003 and people still cant get on its level!  Id give it a few more years until critical perception of the movie will turn around.

If the movie wasnt good enough, it was so good, James Franco is making a movie (called The Disaster Artist) based on a book written by Greg Sestero about the making of The Room!  The Rooms influence can be seen in modern popular culture today.  Huge blockbusters are just ripoffs of The Room.  The new Star Wars, Marvel, and DC franchise movies all ripped off The Room so all the haters can just shut up.

Overall, I think 2003s The Room is a cinematic masterpiece on every level.  I dont have a single problem with it at all.  Ive never been this impressed by a single movie in my entire life, and I believe that every major film school in the country should use The Room as a perfect example of a perfect movie. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Why The Room is a Cinematic Masterpiece </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-02 00:07:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Review  Logan </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-11 01:17:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Review  Logan </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-08 23:31:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-23 02:25:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Just found it on amazon, and I figured I'll give it a read.  Thanks for the suggestion! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [Article] Explaining Arrival's Ending </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-22 23:06:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This post was taken from this blog post: https://blugger.org/2017/02/22/explaining-arrivals-ending/
In my review of Arrival, I said I thought it was a fantastic, thought-provoking movie. The best thing about it was its twist ending, which changed the audiences entire perspective of the film. I thought it would be nice to share my thoughts on what it all means.

Before I move any further, heres a spoiler warning in case you havent seen it and dont want to be told what happens. If you have seen Arrival, I have no idea how you stumbled upon this article, but okay, stuff happens. Anyways, this is your first and last spoiler warning.

Okay, now that thats out of the way, lets get into the nitty gritty.

The first thing that I would like to talk about is the Sapir-Whorf hypothesis. In the movie, the term is thrown around, and it really serves as the basis for Louises understanding of Heptopods. According to dictionary.com, the theory, developed by Edward Sapir and Benjamin Lee Whorf, states that the structure of a language determines or greatly influences the modes of thought and behavior characteristic of the culture in which it is spoken. Basically this means that since I speak English, I perceive the world in a unique way. The reason this connects with the movie is that as Louise spends more time uncovering the Heptopod language, she starts to see as they see. She begins to perceive time as they do. Ultimately, its this connection of language that ends up piecing the film together.
Louise realizes that the Heptopods do not perceive time as a linear thing. The past, present, and future all take place at the same time. When I first watched the movie, I thought the beginning was to set up Louises tragic past. I never thought that the film actually played it the other way around. The movie chronologically starts out with the arrival of the Heptopods as Louise is a linguistics professor at a university. She works on solving the language barrier while getting closer to Ian. The heptopods reveal to Louise the future, and Louise remembers how to prevent China from using its military force on the alien ships. China pulls back, and Louise sees how she will one day become a celebrated hero for creating the universal language, uniting all countries, and bringing about an era of peace. Back in the present, she and Ian get close. Eventually, they have a child named Hannah (who is introduced in the beginning of the film). I thought it was cool how she was named Hannah since its a palindrome, and it symbolizes the movie. The tragedy in this child is that Louise knows what will happen to her since she has seen the future through the Heptopod language. Since she knows about Hannahs heartbreaking death, she keeps this secret from Ian. When she finally tells him, he leaves her and his daughter. I might be missing a couple things, but this is how the movie is chronologically.

Its not just the future that Louise sees. In a single instant, her entire life from start to finish flashes by her. She has access to every detail, and could probably change the future (or at least I think so  the film doesnt talk about that). This idea poses the existential question: is it even worth knowing everything? I dont know about you guys, but after watching Arrival, I found myself thinking a lot about what I would do if I knew about the future and all of my future tragedies. Would I change the future or accept that those tragedies are just part of the journey of life? Louise supposedly chooses to accept her future as we see with her daughters future death. However, she understands more than everyone else that life is more than its individual aspects. Tragedy is only a part in understanding lifes true meaning, which varies depending on the person.

While Arrival is a sci-fi film about aliens, its more an ode to humanity. Director Denis Villeneuve explores the deeper questions about both individuals and their societies. In asking the question Why are they here, the light shines on humanity. Though different countries have differing opinions, a greater presence brings everyone together in the end, and humans finally realize that peace is the best option.

I know that this article is shorter than what I usually write, but I just thought I would get this off my head and onto the screen. Now I ask you, what do you think about Arrivals ending? Feel free to let me know by leaving a comment down below! Thanks :) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Explaining Arrivals Ending </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-22 18:58:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-22 16:55:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I just thought it would be nice to share my thoughts on it.  I got a comment on the review from someone who didn't understand it so maybe it helps :) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> My views on The Times They Are A Changin' </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-15 05:19:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> My views on Bob Dylan's The Times They Are A Changin' </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-15 05:04:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> My review of the Oscar nominated film, Arrival :) </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-15 01:42:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What Trumps Nominees Tell Us About His Administration </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-04 04:42:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-26 16:20:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Wow this is actually really harder than I thought it would be. u know what, Im gonna do it tomorrow - we have a free period tomorrow together </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-26 14:08:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Oh I don't actually have feelings for the guy, we both just like the girl lol I kinda see that I shouldn't have called it a "triangle" - do you think I should ask her now or on Valentine's Day? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-26 14:07:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Someone call Shyamalan cuz this is a twist he'll love :D </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-26 14:06:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thanks, I'm pretty motivated now :)  Do you think I should try to build some tension and ask her on Valentine's Day?  I know it's cheesy, but in my defense, I'm pretty good at performing in front of crowds - unfortunately more so than actual human interaction :( </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [17/m] I'm in a triangle with two friends and it's driving me insane, would love some advice :) </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-26 04:50:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So I've been friends with this girl I really like, and long story short, I really think I love her.  I know it sounds stupid af, but just hear me out.  I've never even tried to be in love because I'm so scared of a broken heart.  Then she came along, and we became friends.  We hang out a lot after school and text.  We even have the gold heart thing on Snapchat.  It sounds cringy, I know, just hang in there :D

On Snapchat, she sends me pictures where she clearly poses and takes the time to make them look good.  Some of my friends actually thinks we're dating, but we're not.  I say some because I think she likes another guy, and he happens to be my close friend.  While she acts like she likes me (she must just be really polite idk), she's more physical with him (he sits in her lap and sleeps on her shoulder).  I've also seen her drawings of him playing the piano (she's a really good artist).  He's a really good guy, and if there is a thing between those two, I would hate to be a jerk to either of them and get in the way.  We're both (the other guy and me) really good at the piano and we both play video games.  I guess I have more in common with her than he does cuz we (the girl and me) love to write and watch anime (the other guy doesn't do either).  All three of us are pretty weird though even though we're all well liked as people at school.

The problem is that I actually really like her.  I've never felt this way with anyone and I sometimes feel like I'm accidentally gonna blurt out "I love you."  This whole unofficial love triangle has been going on for months now, and it's driving me insane.  The one time I actually feel emotionally invested in someone, I know it's just a dead end because I have a long history of losing.  The other part of me wants to desperately win because I don't think I'll ever find someone quite as unique as her.  I might get close and I might find other unique people, but she's special.

Bottom line, I think I'm being led on, and she's going to eventually fall in love with him.  I'm just so freaking terrified by this because I know it's going to break my heart.  And isn't that why I never tried to get close with a girl before?

I have planned my final attempt.  If this doesn't win her heart, then I'm dropping it, and I'll deal with the sadness.  I wrote her a song that's not specifically addressed to her, but she'll realize at the end who I'm referring to.  I already booked a slot in the upcoming Valentine's Day assembly at school so I'm pretty set on doing this.

Other than that, do you think that I should just drop it?  If so, if you could give me some coping mechanisms to deal with the pain, that would be awesome.  Thanks, and you're the best :)

tl;dr I'm in a love triangle and it's driving me insane.  I want to succeed, but my low confidence tells me that I'm going to fail.  I feel really upset by this. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What Trumps Nominees Tell Us About His Administration </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-25 19:40:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What Trumps Nominees Tell Us About His Administration </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-25 15:11:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What Trump's Nominees Tell Us About His Administration </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-25 15:10:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-25 00:57:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yes.  yes they are </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> My Shadow </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-23 19:48:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I know what Im talking about when I say ghosts are real. To anyone who says he or she doesnt believe in the supernatural, your mind will be changed. The story I am about to tell you requires no pre-existing belief of the existence of ghosts. I only ask of your attention.

First, I should provide a little backstory of myself. I was born and raised the suburbs of my state (which I must not name to maintain my anonymity). The only experiences I had with any kind of supernatural being was in Halloween, and those were just kids my age dressing up as zombies or scary ghosts. So no, this isnt just something Ive always believed in. Hell, horror movies were my jam. Everything was going great until my family moved to a rural area, which was built in the 1800s. I know, this was the perfect horror setting.

From the moment I stepped into that house, I knew living there wasnt going to be easy at first. However, my parents insisted that the house was grand and deserved some respect. The grandeur of the house is apparent; the house was a mansion and it provided a lot of space. Apparently the place used to have a slave plantation, but it was torn down upon the previous owners request. I guess the place had since turned into a symbol that the wrongs would be undone, but that history would stay to haunt this place forever.

At the nights in my room, I had nightmares. I was just so used to being in my old room that as soon as I stepped in my own room, everything seemed so detached from the world. It was as if my room was otherworldly. Sure, the room was big and it had a great interior design, but the lights were a little bit faulty. Every time I tried to turn off the damn things, there was a delay, and every time I tried to turn on the lights, there was this creepy flicker. When the lights would turn on, I would think that I saw someone in the brief flicker who was revealed for a millisecond before disappearing. I didnt know what was happening and I thought I was just freaking out for no reason. Moreover, my brother didn't seem to notice anything when he walked into my room and my family was enjoying its spacious home. Though the lights were fixed, I was still afraid. Everyone was joyous except for me. Soon, I became paranoid about being in my own room. I began to contemplate that there was more to this house than I thought. At night, I felt alone in my room, but I did not feel truly alone. I felt there was something else, that maybe I wasnt imagining what I saw during those light flickers.

I still went to the same school, though, and I still had the same friends. My home would be different (and further away from my school), but I knew there wasnt much different outside of the house. I was wrong.

The paranoia of the house seeped into my daily life outside of my home. I kept looking over my shoulder to make sure no one was there. Even in school, I felt as if I was being watched. I wasnt one of those loner kids in school, the kinds you see in horror films. I was really just a regular guy who got scared by scary things. Think about it. If you thought you saw something in your new room on multiple occasions, wouldnt you feel like there is more to the story? I certainly did and it became a habit for me to check the house routinely.

That wasnt even the worst part. I started to imagine things, a result of my overthinking. I kept looking down at my shadow in the sunlight and imagined that another shadow would emerge behind that. The whole thing was driving me crazy.

The other shadow was harmless, though, and I knew even if there really was a shadow and I wasnt just imagining it that a simple shadow wouldnt be harmful. However, the shadow became more apparent on some occasions, mostly when I was alone.

I started to become more removed from my classmates as I had stopped talking with them after school. My grades in school started to drop and my parents warned me that I was walking through a downward spiral. They started to put me in tutoring facilities and places where I spent five hours a week on subjects I was normally pretty good at.

As the days went by, I noticed that I didnt have a second shadow anymore. I thought that things were getting better and that part of this had something do with my attention being diverted at the tutoring centers.

Yet, all that changed when my aunt and uncle were called over to check out the new house. They had two children  the older was my age and the younger was four at the time. They too loved the exterior and interior design, the spacious rooms, and the mansion like feel of the house. When I was washing my face (which I do when I am exhausted) on the second day that they were at the house, the left the bathroom door open. I looked in my mirror and saw my younger cousin walk in to say hello to me. I responded saying hello as well. As my eyes were closed, I continued to splash water on my face. Then my cousin said something I will never forget. She quietly asked, Whos that man in the mirror? My heart skipped a beat. I had no idea who she was talking about. When I looked back into the mirror, however, nothing was there except for my cousin and me.

I turned around and asked my cousin, What man? She responded, Never mind. I thought I saw a man. Its just you probably. You could probably say that my cousin was just imagining things, but I knew she saw something. Nevertheless, I decided that my cousin was probably referring to me in the mirror. After all, nothing unusual had come up in the past few weeks and I was beginning to let go of the problems that I had with this old mansion in the first place.

Nonetheless, one day, as I was walking through the school campus, I saw the second shadow again. I freaked out and tried to run away from the shadow. However, wherever I went, the shadow went. Something was different this time, though. The shadow started to perform actions. It was more visible and was clearly not the same as my own shadow. I couldnt stand this any longer.

I told my parents what I have been experiencing ever since the house was bought. I told them about the flickering lights, the shadow, and the all around creepiness of the house. They seemed to be oblivious to any of this! They treated this as an excuse for my falling grades. However, as I insisted that what I was saying was true, my father must have been persuaded somehow.

Though my grades were plummeting, I wasnt dumb. I knew I had to pay attention to others shadows. Maybe this thing was a scientific phenomenon, a way of lights doing their magic. After realizing that others shadows ONLY do things that mirror their owners, I came to the rather arrogant conclusion that my shadow wasnt of me. I know its only been one incident, but you have to see that I was an impulsive teenager (okay that made me cringe, but its true in retrospect). Its not that it did much that I didnt look for other possible solutions (I did), its just that I was starting to become a huge believer in the supernatural. Every once in awhile, my shadow split into two.

I was diagnosed with somewhat of a minor form of schizophrenia after I had declared to the school that I would jump off the building because the dark shadow chased me to the top. I had to deal with that, too. I couldnt get a job because of my condition and I kept attributing the dual shadows to my schizophrenia. Maybe I really had it. Maybe Im still crazy, but I dont know because later on, Ill tell you some absolutely batshit crazy stuff thats really going to end up asking the question to you.

I know I said some stuff about the job and thats after high school, but Im going to take it just a bit back in the timeline. After high school, I didnt go to college - there were too many people and I never did well with them. I was always pretty weird to them. Ive tried to pinpoint exactly what the problem was and put the blame on others, but I honestly just think I was me. Plus, people must have viewed me as a psychopath considering that my schizophrenia was announced in my junior year. All this made me feel a bit alone so after I moved out (luckily I was able to make enough money flipping burgers and writing blog posts during high school), I got a dog. He was honestly the best friend I ever had and I know thats something a lot of people say and I never had any other friends so I wouldnt have anything to compare with, but I knew he was the coolest buddy ever when I got him so I named him Buddy. There were times when I cried because I felt alone and Buddy was there to snuggle up with me and make me feel okay again. It sounds dark, but I would have been creamed by a car on so many occasions (I dont drive because of my condition, but the doctor said I might not be fully aware of my surroundings so even walking in front of cars is a problem). Buddy would bark and I would know that whatever problem I was in could be solved.

The best part about Buddy was that I never had any shadow problems. My belief in the supernatural slowly faded away.

A few weeks ago, Buddy died after two years of being with him. Ive overheard people talking about how their dog lived for over a decade, but come one, man, two years? I found his neck stuck in the front entrance to my apartment building as he whimpered in fear until he stopped breathing. I either didnt know what just happened or I couldnt accept it. Either way, I rushed him to the vet. The doctor attributed his death to a snapped neck. That fucking door closes on its own. I wish he went through the dog door like he always did, but everyone makes mistakes. I dont know what I was thinking after that, but I can tell you I felt like my heart was stolen for good. I couldnt go the lost and found and recover it - it was gone and stolen by the mastermind of thieves, Death herself. Even today, I picture his mind racing as he realizes the parts of the world hes leaving behind. Maybe I wasnt the best friend I could be, but god dammit this his death had me crying on his soft fur. He was my best Buddy. My mind went to dark places after that as I had often looked to the disorderly set of kitchen knives. Notice how the shadow hasnt come back yet? Well heres what happened yesterday.

My apartment without Buddy was quiet. After a few weeks, I got kind of used to being alone again. Every time I went to get groceries, I closed my eyes as I went near that front entrance. The small bloodstain from Buddys neck was all cleaned up, but my memory of it was lodged in my brain. I couldnt stand touching the door and feeling its old door handle. I fucking hate old, rusty brass. It reminded me of the kind in my old house, the one that caused me all that pain and put me in this shithole of a situation in the first place. After a few weeks, though, I figured that I had to move on. I couldnt just buy a new dog because that would make me forget my time with Buddy. I needed to just face the loss and be happy because its what Buddy would have wanted. He always wanted to make me feel comfortable.

It was time to take a good look at that door all the way downstairs. I needed to see every crease in that wooden door, feel the brass doorknob, hear the echoes of Buddys whimpers, and get it all out not only for my sake, but also for Buddys. I traveled downstairs. Slowly, I stepped down. At this point, I was reliving my final moments with buddy. I was reliving that fear in both my eyes and his. As I saw that door, time slowed down. I saw the pathetic excuse of a stained glass window. I heard my dog crying and pictured the tears running down his eyes as they were pouring down mine. Time slowed down even more. I remembered all my favorite memories with Buddy - all the time he saved me from my conflicted mentality. Time practically stopped when I crouched down and peered into the small chip in the wooden door that was the cause of my dog frantically resisting the automatic push of the door. Wait a second. Time. It would have taken a little while for him to go down there and he wouldnt go that far away from me. I figured he could get out of the door as that was open during the night, but how did he - how the fuck did he get in that situation.

Oh no. The doctor said one of the symptoms of schizophrenia was destructive behavior. I rushed back upstairs and blasted open the door with my arms so hard that the doorknob left a huge dent in the wall it smashed into. Sitting on the countertop next to my couch was the set of kitchen knives. If I had chased him downstairs, then how come whatever knife I used was put back in? I couldnt have chased my dog downstairs, watched him get stuck down there, and refused to help him even if I wasnt in control. I didnt need to be in control to know that I put my best buddy before me in every situation. Buddy and I were more than family. I checked each knife in the set to see if there was any with blood on it. I rolled my long sleeves up and saw that I had used the damn knife as I eerily observed my name sprawled across my forearm. At the end of my name was a question mark. As I picked at the hole from the dot in the question mark (the only mark that hadnt healed enough to become a scar), drips of blood dribbled down the side of my forearm. Did I scare Buddy enough that he ran away? Suddenly, I remembered.

I did both. I remember carving the letters into my hand at night and watching Buddy bark in shock and run downstairs. I remember myself taking the knife and walking down the staircase. I remember myself saying to my Buddy, Im supposed to be alone. The worst part was when I watched as Buddy ran through the dog door and I followed by pushing the door open and running outside with the knife in my hand. As I ran outside, Buddy ran back in. Confused by this, I tripped and fell. I guess Buddys friendly nature got to him as he barked and rushed to my rescue while the door started to close. I turned around and saw Buddy go halfway through the opening. Abruptly, a gust of wind forced the door to close on my only friend. I must have blacked out because I dont remember anything after that.

Now, as tears ran down my eyes, I had no other choice but to question everything I was. I rushed to the mirror and screamed at it. I cursed myself and asked the mirror why I was who I was before I looked down and cried into the sink. After I finally calmed down, I wiped my face and stared into the mirror as the final tears ran down my cheek.

This place was quiet. When I looked in the mirror, I saw what could only be described as my shadow, a second me. Isnt that what a shadow is, after all? The only difference was he was smiling.

This sick joke. All these years, I had been shoved aside by the doctors who told me I was wrong. I even thought I was wrong. It turns out I had been right all along.

You see, these things arent confined to old houses like the kinds you see in horror movies. A person didnt have to die in the general vicinity of the haunted area decades ago for the ghost to roam the lands. Thats what scares me. Some ghosts just want to hurt others. They just want to manipulate you into believing they dont exist and thats when they strike. The realm beyond our own can be a dark and fucked up place. They watch us with their eyes from below and take all the time they need before playing their cards. This ones final card was to show me that I fell for it, to prove to me that I could never win. As I saw that smile in the mirror, I knew my shadow had returned. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [Serious] Socially awkward guys of reddit, how did you ask our your crush? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-20 04:17:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-20 04:01:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I definitely respect dat opinion tho :) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-19 02:24:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Should it have been higher or lower in your opinion? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-17 13:26:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> thanks :) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-15 07:12:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That's awesome!  Feel free to let me know how it goes :D </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-14 06:29:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> true, thanks for reminding :) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Had to put Rogue One in my top 10 movies of 2016 list because it's fantastic! </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-14 06:29:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Had to put Zootopia and Finding Dory in my top 10 movies of 2016 since they were both fantastic! </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-14 06:15:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Had to put Civil War and Doctor Strange in my top 10 of the year since they're both fantastic! </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-14 05:14:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> My Top 10 Favorite Movies of 2016 </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-14 02:32:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-14 02:24:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> "Here's to the hearts that aaaache" </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-13 12:49:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> "Here's to the single males who went to see the movie aloooooooone" </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Review  FEZ </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-11 16:00:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Review  FEZ </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-11 14:38:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [Review] La La Land </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-09 05:50:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This review is taken from the link below:

https://blugger.org/2017/01/08/review-la-la-land/

La La Land is the best movie of 2016 in my opinion.  Heres why:

In 2016, I didnt give a single movie a 10/10 because to be a 10, a movie has to truly be something special.  The best movies have lasting impressions on viewers.  They make you go through emotions and get you to think about it way after youve seen it.  Damien Chazelle has crafted a brilliant, energetic, and amazing feel-good emotional journey in the form of La La Land.

First of all, Im not even the target audience of this film.  Im not a big fan of musicals even though I love The Sound of Music and Singin in the Rain.  However, those movies existed in an era in which musicals were the big thing, and now, musicals tend to feel dated.  Secondly, as a single male who went to go see the movie alone, I didnt think the movie would speak to me since most of my peers used this as a date movie.  Ive never really been a fan of romance movies because of how they tend to be predictable.  Im basically the opposite of the average person who would see this film.  I am elated to say that I do not regret any part of seeing this film alone.  Though many recent musicals are good, none of them top La La Land.  I would go so far as to say this is the best musical Ive seen ever.  Im really not kidding.

On paper, the plot seems pretty simple.  Sebastian, an aspiring jazz pianist played by Ryan Gosling, falls in love with Mia, an aspiring actress played by Emma Stone, against the backdrop of Hollywood.  While this sounds like a typical romance film, it features some of the best dialogue Ive seen in a while.  Because the characters speak with meaning, they become more lifelike even though the story is fictional.  For example, when Ryan Gosling explains to Emma Stone the reason why jazz is so fantastic, I started to view Sebastian as a person and not a character.  I was so invested in these two characters because of the great screenplay by Damien Chazelle and the amazing performances by both Ryan Gosling and Emma Stone.  Both Gosling and Stone give career best performances that really won me over.  These two people dont just deserve Oscar nominations; they deserve the award itself.  They created such a memorable on-screen duo that I really bought everything that they said.  There was not a moment of doubt that crossed my mind when it came to the authenticity of the characters, and thats mainly due to top-notch acting.

Though the acting is perfect, I would give major credit to Damien Chazelle for being able to do what he did.  Many of the scenes were done in one take with no editing.  The songs were mostly done in one entire take, Ryan Goslings piano scenes were done in one shot to show that it was actually he who was playing the piano and not a body double, and Emma Stones singing scenes were done in a single take to show that it was her actually singing.  Often times, films use editing for large scenes because its just really hard to do everything in one take and manage to keep the camera alive throughout the whole scene.  However, Chazelle was able to overcome these obstacles by probably practicing constantly.  Think about it: if one thing were to mess up, the whole scene would have to start over.  Chazelle needed to give everyone direction so no one would mess up, and he did it perfectly.  Each shot that was staged was brimming with color and fresh ideas.  The way he used color and lighting to convey emotions was something that a lot of films dont have.  Chazelles use of lighting added a sleek and modern flicker to an otherwise nostalgic work of art.  If you cant tell already, I think this guy deserves an Oscar for both screenplay and direction, and I hope that he gets it.

Since there wasnt much editing in the film, the movie needed to rely on great cinematography.  Many of the shots had great use of camera movements.  Each scene felt alive and I would be stupid not to give credit to the cinematographer, Linus Sandgren.  Honestly, I could not think of a dull moment in the entire film even though some scenes were slow.  In fact, those slow moments kept me glued to the screen anticipating what would happen next.  Also, the visuals of the film are much grander to see on the big screen.  Usually, I go to big budget blockbusters because thats where the big theatre screens shine.  However, La La Land works MUCH better in the theatre (technically I wouldnt know for sure since I havent seen it at home, but trust me).  This film looks phenomenal in the theaters since the big screen allowed me to appreciate every detail that was put into the film.

Since La La Land is a musical, the thing I was looking forward to the most was the music.  Every song actually added layers to the characters and had reasons to be there.  Most of the time, musicals have throwaway songs just for popcorn entertainment.  While these songs were immensely entertaining, they were seamlessly woven into the script.  The lyrics actually have meaning because they progress the story further and add more to the characters.  Composer Justin Hurwitz created gorgeous songs with varying emotional tones.  Right after I watched the film, I found the soundtrack on YouTube and just listened to the songs on my drive back home.  Though the songs feel natural in the movie, I could easily listen to them because they are so good.  Hurwitz also did the soundtrack for Whiplash, which was Chazelles last directorial effort (it was also my favorite movie of 2014).  Though all of them are equally fantastic, City of Stars was the only one that got a Golden Globe nomination.  In my opinion, all of the songs should have gotten one.  Its really difficult to chose one, but my favorite song in the whole film is Epilogue because it combines the best elements of all the other songs.

The last thing Im going to talk about before I do the whole overall thing has to do with the message that the film sends.  Though its a romance movie on paper, I viewed La La Land as a film about two people who just want to follow their dreams.  When Sebastian describes to Mia the reason that he loves jazz, he says that its all about clashing and compromise, and this is very exciting.  In retrospect, thats what pursuing dreams is all about.  Sometimes in life, you have to compromise to achieve greater things.  Sometimes differing ideas will clash, but the result is something beautiful.  In the end of the movie, when this message really comes to fruition (I dont want to spoil it), I was touched in the heart.  This message really resonated with me and I left the theatre feeling good as a person.

I could rave about this movie as much as I want, but unless you want 2000 words of me saying THIS IS FANTASTIC  GO SEE IT, I cant really say anything more without getting into spoilers.  Yes, I know this review is rather short, but thats only because the movie was just so great.  If I find that I have anything more to say, Ill definitely edit the article and add it in.  Other than that, I really cant say much more. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Review  La La Land </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-09 05:27:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-08 23:03:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thanks!  I feel like the last post made a lot of people angry and that led to some angry comments so I figured I'd fix it and repost. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-08 15:49:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Just saying, that movie was fantastic </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-08 15:07:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thanks :) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-08 14:57:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Okay, there it's changed.  Honestly, did that really affect the rest of the review?  Obviously I know it's an opinion - I'm pretty arrogant, but I'm not that arrogant.  Please feel free to let me know if the new first line is better.  Thanks! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Review  La La Land </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-08 14:47:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Mohit Puvvala - Tried to Make EDM and Failed Miserably [EDM, Dance] </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-02 21:37:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Mohit Puvvala -- 2016 New Years Eve [Dance, EDM, Skip to 1:40] (2016) </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-02 21:26:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Mohit Puvvala - 2016 New Years Eve [Dance, EDM] </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-02 01:02:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Smokey Mountains [OC] [1190  1192] </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-02 00:28:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [Serious] Guys, how did you handle being rejected by the girl of your dreams? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-22 04:32:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Review  Suicide Squad (and Extended Cut) </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-19 03:03:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
