<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject1493</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-09 08:06:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The first post is from a user added on the first night. He didnt speak english very well so he didnt really participate. I checked his post history at one point and he exclusively posted in /r/newsokur. Im guessing that post is him explaining to his friends what happened.

The next two are my posts. Night Mind is a youtuber I watch who specializes in investigating creepy stuff. He doesnt have the most active sub but i thought it was worth a shot to post it there. 

The /r/creepy thread is probably what got me purged since it got some moderate attention. I recommend checking the comments on that post. There are a few people whove had similar experiences to us. Theres at least a couple "purging" subs according to them.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-08 11:12:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Pretty sure they already tried that one. The farmers in tunnels won </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-07 00:32:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Feed them your carrot </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-06 23:22:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If it resonates with you then power to you my friend! Its your art after all :)

 I see what you were going for now that you mention it. I actually have similar experiences as a kid. Just curling up into a ball transfixed at some scary story. Too scared to do anything but stare.

Personally, I still think you could exaggerate that pose a little more. Really sell that hes transfixed by the story. But you know what that's so nitpicky at this point that im just gonna chalk it up to differences in approach lol

Your art is fantastic and nothing i said should detract from that!   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-06 22:53:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I really love this piece! The story is great, the atmoshpere is amazing. 

I have an extremely minor critique though. I would try to exagerate the kids reaction a bit more. Hes pretty static and boxy and really doesnt look like hes responding to the dad. 

 A story is told through action and reaction. Often reactions tell us more about the action then the action itself does. How the child reacts to the story the dad is telling is how your audience infers what the story is about. If he is excited we may infer its a happy story, if hes acting scared we'll more likely infer that its a scary story. 

Its very minor in the grand scheme of your work (i love all the little details in this piece) but i think keeping reaction in mind when trying to tell a story would go a long way!     </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-06 22:23:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Nicolas Cage is what artists refer to as an "Ideal Form"  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-06 22:05:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> T H I C C </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-06 22:00:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Pretty cliche but day-one DLC has always irked me. DLC in general usually feels like stuff that couldve been in the game from the start but at least they make it after the game is already out. With day-one DLC i dont really get what the excuse is to not have it in the game.    </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-06 19:24:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> https://youtu.be/m5RtlpXsl8k </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-06 19:00:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Probably way easier to meet someone and juggle school/career if you have the whole thing pre-arranged. I wonder if more non-indians would adopt this strategy if it were more accepted culturally in the west. I have a feeling some would but who really knows.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-06 07:11:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> They never think these rules could be turned on them. In their heads it will always be people they don't like who get silenced  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-06 07:03:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> At least he didn't drive home I guess </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-06 06:55:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> For to mkz litlte people  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-06 00:41:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> TIL Any white person who tans also thinks black skin is ugly/disgusting.



It scares me that that this isnt a  surprise anymore... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-06 00:37:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Ya get a load of this guy. Eating burgers with his hands like an animal. Who does that?   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-05 23:38:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I AM GROOT!


In all seriousness though, i like it. The monster was really creepy </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-05 23:30:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Suicide is badass! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-05 02:50:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So it has happened before. I thought there might be more out there. The mod on our sub hasnt given any rules of any kind or spoken to us at all. So i guess we can do whatever we want with it ahaha </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-05 02:25:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I checked some of the purged users and their accounts seem to be fine. Some of the other users were worried about that
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> I Was Added To A Private Self-Purging Subreddit </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-05 01:57:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm not sure if this is the right place for this. I find it creepy but not a lot has gone down. So far at least. Hopefully you guys find it creepy, or at least interesting. Any help figuring anything out would be greatly appreciated as well.

Story:
On Tuesday, May 2nd, around 12:00 am I recieved a message that i had become an approved poster on a subreddit called /r/vZEk9sCzqbi154p. The message: http://imgur.com/a/Gbyjq

Intrigued, i followed the link and it led me to a freshly made subreddit. There were only 4-5 posts on there total. Two of which were stickied posts from the admin, a user named /u/ApprenticeBot. The two stickied posts looked like this: http://imgur.com/a/2d6lP

I was more than curious at this point. Some of the later users likened it to the beginning of a horror movie and i definitely got that vibe too. Every user had a number from 1-25 flaired to their account. I was #19 in the beginning.

I commented on one of the posts and made my own trying to find out some more info. Only text posts are allowed and there are no rules to posting. Only a couple users were active. So i didn't really get any answers. I decided to check back later.

I check back in an hour and the stickied posts have changed: http://imgur.com/a/wBky7

There were 19 added and purged when i was approved. There were 13 after that purge. It looked like the remaining users list jumped from 6 to 12 as well.

A select few users continued making periodic posts. Mostly shitposting, speculating, and jokes. The stuff you expect to get when you give a bunch of random users control of a sub with no direction.

The third purge came an hour after the second. Sometime around the third purge I compiled my observations into this post: http://imgur.com/a/wazzm

Any user who posted as much as one comment is added to the remaining users list and survives the purges. Users who do not post anything are removed in an hour. New users are added at the same time as others are purged. This system ran like clockwork for 12 hours straight. The few active users and I kept glued to the screen. There were maybe 4-5 people making random posts and comments hoping not to be purged. Waiting to see what would happened when all 25 slots were taken up. Some examples of the posts: http://imgur.com/a/BXCTE

Well by around noon the next day we had our 25 users. I was now number #11. Users who are purged lose their spot and the remaining users get their numbers moved up to the next highest available slot. I waited anxiously until the next hour to see if we would finally learn what this is about. The time came and the current stickies were removed and replaced with one that read: http://imgur.com/a/L6hNM

So absolutely no answers. Great. These non-purges continued for another 12 hours. Each one the exact same message but still different posts. As the 24 hour mark inched closer i predicted there would be a purge of non-active users. 

Midnight came, marking 24 hours of the subs existence. And no change at all. The last sticky post just stayed up and continued to be up for 6+ hours. No other sticky had been up for over an hour up until now. Eventually the purge came, and it removed all users who hadn't posted in over 24 hours. I checked each of their accounts to verify.

Hourly purges began again for a little bit, recycling a lot of acounts. Right now it's acting a little weird, the list of purged users has been up for 6 hours, whereas a single new user was added two hours ago. I'm not sure what that means.

Basically thats all I know so far. The subs really quiet right now, nobodies quite sure what to do. I'm currently #4. Some users theorize that the sub is a sort of social experiment. One posited that this could be one of many such subreddits. I think it could just be somebody testing a bot of some sort. Either way nobody really knows why this sub exists.

If anyone out there has cryptographic experience, I'd really like to know if the title of the subreddit is just jibberish or if it could potentially have meaning.

I hope you guys found that intriguing. If you like this post i will provide updates if and when there are any. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> I was added to a hidden self-purging Subreddit </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-05 01:15:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm not sure if this is the right place for this. It's really more odd than creepy and not a whole lot has really gone down so far. However, I immediately thought of Night Mind when it first happened. Hopefully you guys at least find it interesting. And any help figuring anything out would be greatly appreciated. 

Story:

On Tuesday, May 2nd, around 12:00 am I recieved a message that i had become an approved poster on a subreddit called /r/vZEk9sCzqbi154p. The message: http://imgur.com/a/Gbyjq

Intrigued, i followed the link and it led me to a freshly made subreddit. There were only 4-5 posts on there total. Two of which were stickied posts from the admin, a user named /u/ApprenticeBot. The two stickied posts looked like this: http://imgur.com/a/2d6lP

I was more than curious at this point. Some of the later users likened it to the beginning of a horror movie and i definitely got that vibe too. Every user had a number from 1-25 flaired to their account. I was #19 in the beginning. 

I commented on one of the posts and made my own trying to find out some more info. Only text posts are allowed and there are no rules to posting. Only a couple users were active. So i didn't really get any answers. I decided to check back later. 

I check back in an hour and the stickied posts have changed: http://imgur.com/a/wBky7

There were 19 added and purged when i was approved. There were 13 after that purge. It looked like the remaining users list jumped from 6 to 12 as well. 

A select few users continued making periodic posts. Mostly shitposting, speculating, and jokes. The stuff you expect to get when you give a bunch of random users control of a sub with no direction.

The third purge came an hour after the second. Sometime around the third purge I compiled my observations into this post: http://imgur.com/a/wazzm

Any user who posted as much as one comment is added to the remaining users list and survives the purges. Users who do not post anything are removed in an hour. New users are added at the same time as others are purged. This system ran like clockwork for 12 hours straight. The few active users and I kept glued to the screen. There were maybe 4-5 people making random posts and comments hoping not to be purged. Waiting to see what would happened when all 25 slots were taken up. Some examples of the posts: http://imgur.com/a/BXCTE

Well by around noon the next day we had our 25 users. I was now number #11. Users who are purged lose their spot and the remaining users get their numbers moved up to the next highest available slot. I waited anxiously until the next hour to see if we would finally learn what this is about. The time came and the current stickies were removed and replaced with one that read: http://imgur.com/a/L6hNM

So absolutely no answers. Great. These non-purges continued for another 12 hours. Each one the exact same message but still different posts. As the 24 hour mark inched closer i predicted there would be a purge of non-active users. Midnight came, marking 24 hours of the subs existence. And no change at all. The last sticky post just stayed up and continued to be up for 6+ hours. No other sticky had been up for over an hour up until now. Eventually the purge came, and it removed all users who hadn't posted in over 24 hours. I checked each of their accounts to verify. 

Hourly purges began again for a little bit, recycling a lot of acounts. Right now it's acting a little weird, the list of purged users has been up for 6 hours, whereas a single new user was added two hours ago. I'm not sure what that means. 

Basically thats all I know so far. The subs really quiet right now, nobodies quite sure what to do. I'm currently #4. Some users theorize that the sub is a sort of social experiment. One posited that this could be one of many such subreddits. I think it could just be somebody testing a bot of some sort. Either way nobody really knows why this sub exists. 

If anyone out there has cryptographic experience, I'd really like to know if the title of the subreddit is just jibberish or if it could potentially have meaning. 

I hope you guys found that intriguing. If you like this post i will provide updates if and when there are any. 
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-04 05:29:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Huh, didnt know shaggy was into web development </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-03 23:30:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I re-did the superimposing line and oval exercises a few times. Definitely saw bit of an improvement.

Re-done exercises: http://imgur.com/a/ckJlx  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Lesson 1 Homework </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-03 06:05:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-30 21:47:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> He goes on to become Darth Vader, i really wouldn't be suprised if he was that powerful  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-29 22:56:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thank you. Could you please expand on the angles part? Im not quite sure i follow.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-29 17:17:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thank you! I couldnt figure out why it looked sort of odd lol. I changed up the shading based on your advice. I definitely think it looks better now 

http://m.imgur.com/uWLOFhM </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-29 06:55:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Bob Crews is my personal saviour  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Pretty new to art. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-29 06:18:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-22 02:27:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Place one of your thumbs on each side of the childs face roughly at the temple of the skull. Maintaining eye contact with the child, rub your thumbs first clockwise then counter-clockwise. Alternating every five minutes. You may make small whirring and wooshing noises as you do so but do not smile. This calms the child.     </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-21 08:33:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Holy shit i didnt know i needed this  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-21 06:29:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yep hes even got a clip of himself at the airport getting frisked. The clothes match up.  https://www.instagram.com/p/BS88LUKAqYr/    </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-20 23:08:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> He was literally just naming some basic film movements and concepts. Ive watched like 4 youtube videos on film and i could tell you that stuff   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-20 23:02:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Leeloo  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-18 22:08:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> IANAL but i believe they can be unrecorded and be admissible, its just hard to prove they happened. Both parties essentially have to agree that there was a verbal contract if it wasnt recorded. Verbal contracts also have to fulfill the same parameters of a written contract (consideration, length, terms of fufillment/unfufillment etc)   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-15 07:02:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This is why enemas are usually used for anal  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-14 20:35:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thats actually The Expendables 3 director Patrick Hughes. That picture was taken at the 2014 cannes film festival with him and some of the cast.

Heres a different angle of the picture: http://m.zimbio.com/pictures/TBWpA900z0Y/Expendables+3+Premiere+67th+Annual+Cannes/6iUVwvmA6Il/Sylvester+Stallone

Did make me think of Statham though. Hes got the same kind of look.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-14 17:51:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The intellectual heavyweight strikes again </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-13 17:49:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I know a guy like this too. Ive never personally seen his antics but i have a mutual friend who told me some stories and showed me some of the aftermath. Apparently, every weekend he would go out to bars and start shit with random people. Usually with bigger guys, often while piss drunk, and almost always for very little reason. Sometimes he would win, other times he would lose terribly. Hes been knocked out mulitiple times, hes broken teeth, he roped one of his friends into it who ended up suffering a pretty bad knockout. 

The guy wasnt dissuaded by any of the loses though. He couldnt help himself i guess. Anyway, he did his usual shit one weekend. Picked a fight with some dude over nothing. Except this time someone called the cops on him. 

Now perhaps your thinking that this was the wake up call he needed. Maybe this time he'll realize things had gone too far. Surely one would at least question themselves at this point. 

Nope. He tried to fight the cops and assaulted them. 

Hes got a few felonies hanging over his head now. Plus the cops didnt take too kindly to getting assaulted so he got fucked up as well. As far as i know he doesnt start as many fights now. So maybe it was what needed to happen unfortunately. I still dont think ill ever understand the thought proccess (or lack thereof) behind these people.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-13 17:28:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If they are like guitar cases then they are fairly form fitting. The edges of the case are touching the instrument and the cases lid comes down to rest on top of the fretboard. So im not sure how much extra padding you could fit in there to begin with as space is pretty limited by design. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-13 17:21:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Considering low-end student cellos can start at $2000 that sounds like a smart way to do it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-13 07:15:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Female infanticide, the killing of a new born female, has been a problem in India for centuries. The practice was outlawed during British rule but its apparently pretty ingrained in certain sub-cultures of India. So it still happens fairly frequently.

Source: https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Female_infanticide#India
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-13 07:02:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> "4th largest city in Pakistan" </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-12 04:34:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> She looks like a Dr. Seuss character  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-06 05:22:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> He probably meant "Peon", which would make more sense in context. Although, pion actually kind of works as well so who knows.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-06 04:35:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Perpetual defensiveness is a sign of a weak mind </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-04 08:25:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Honest question; Do you think his death would make you feel better?

Please dont take this the wrong way, im just curious is all. He sounds like an utter piece of shit either way.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-04 02:03:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I really loved how music was a central theme with cottonmouth  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-31 18:36:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Its a step down from pedophilia. Hebephiles are attracted to adolescents or children who have begun puberty  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-31 05:34:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> TINASHE WHERE YOU AT! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-30 23:28:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Dont call me a dick, buddy! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-29 21:28:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> She was also a minor at the time, the incidents were not reported to the police and no physical evidence exists by this point. It would be pretty hard to get a conviction out of this even if the statute of limitations wasnt up (which it might not be depending on the state this occured in). Even if she says she did it in her book, she can say she was lying or made it up for publicity, and it would be the prosecuters job to prove that the incident even took place.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-29 07:08:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> People who identified themselves as black make up 2.9% of the population or 15.1% of our visible minorities. South Asians are the largest minority group in Canada at 4.8% of the population and 25% of the visible minority population.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-24 18:00:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> A cop gave him the casing!? Ban police from schools! They are a bad influence! Did you know cops always have guns on them? What kind of message is that for our kids?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-24 17:51:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> "The valet service was terrible. I kept honking at your employees but they just honked back at me and flapped their wings in a derogatory manner. None of them tried to help me and I think one of them shit on my roof. 1/10 would not return"   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-24 17:45:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hold onto my carpentry tools im a going in! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-23 18:01:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> My mom and dad were both alcoholics. They met at AA actually and have both been totally sober for 25+ years each at this point. My mom is the best person i know and i cant even believe she used to be that way. 

My message i guess is that life hasnt given up on you. Regardless of where youve been its never too late to create something wonderful. I hope these 35 days leads you to a lifetime of happiness. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> I think I found Paul from an alternate universe </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-22 06:09:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-21 06:30:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I know they can replace certain parts of the skull with 3d printed implants. A youtuber i watch recently had a new forehead put in after a terrible bmx accident. His original frontal bone was removed surgically however, so it was a way more straight forward procdeure. No idea if they can do something similar here with that level of damage. There have also been fairly successful face transplants so that might be an option (http://www.dailymail.co.uk/health/article-2121185/Richard-Lee-Norris-face-transplant-Gun-accident-victim-given-amazing-operation-US-doctors.html) 

The least they could do would be to pinch the hole closed like the before picture in that article. Though, that seems easier said then done </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-21 06:03:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Good ol' NAMBLA logic </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-20 21:20:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I mean its not too far fetched for a 50 year old cocaine user to have a bad heart  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-20 18:07:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Not a doctor but i think youre right </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-20 00:49:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I believe this falls into the category of felony* murder. Basically felony* murder means you are responsible for any deaths that occur as the result of you commiting a crime. Doesn't matter if they are accidental, or if the person was involved or not. Intent doesn't actually play into it as far as i know, because its a technical charge separate to a regular murder charge.        </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-19 03:36:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> IIRC if you are the attacker with a knife you statistically have the same likelihood of getting stabbed as the victim you are attacking. Even if the other person is unarmed.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-16 04:26:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> TJ IS GARBAGE!


Cheers bud, Im watching the podcast too </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Trying to get past your parents without raising suspicion </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-16 04:23:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-15 15:38:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm fairly certain TJ has said in the past that he's in favour of legalizing and regulating all drugs. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-13 19:08:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> As long as women feel better who cares if they burn to death? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-13 18:54:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Very true the Fucked Up works on a gradient scale. You have to start with some softcore yuri or something and ease your way into Futas getting a urethral fisting. You can't go too deep too fast, much unlike Futa urethral fisting.      </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-26 22:01:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Should show him Crowder on the Joe Rogan podcast. They argue about weed and Crowder basically shuts down and starts accusing Joe of setting up his assistant with cherry picked sources to refute him... while they we're reading an article on Crowder's own website. It was a pretty embarrassing interaction. Joe isn't even some intellectual heavyweight but Crowder won't break from whatever established line of thinking he has so even simple scrutiny makes him fall on his face.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-23 18:31:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's not unusual to see my cry, I wanna die :(  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-23 18:24:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Young earth creationists have added up the various ages and dates in the bible and come to the conclusion that the earth is between 6,000 and 12,000 years old.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-23 08:42:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Je t'aime vous, JF! Always happy to hear that you're going to be on the show  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-21 19:12:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Heres a link to the podcast he was on if anyone wants to hear the full conversation. 

https://youtu.be/azC1nm85btY </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-18 07:52:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Damn man, are you sure you're allowed to post that here?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-18 07:40:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [This guy gets it](http://i.imgur.com/tyx9emw.gif) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-18 01:14:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yep


https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Kynodesme </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-18 00:49:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Well thats just getting two birds stoned at once  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-17 23:46:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> My nigga </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-17 23:22:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Traps or Futa? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-17 22:55:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I watched an interesting piece about alcohol smuggling in Nunavut from Vice (if I'm remembering right). The sale of alcohol is banned in a few communities up there and requires direct permission from a committee in others. So naturally people have taken to smuggling alcohol into these communities for profit. The demand coupled with the already high cost of getting goods makes it so cheap smuggled alcohol can sell for over $600 a bottle. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-17 17:38:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If im understanding correctly i think the problem he's getting at is that you need evidence of their intent. A rational person may think that but the bar for evidence is higher than that. He needs to prove that they didnt believe the jokes were anti-semitic even in context and intended to harm him. Something like witness testimony or written correspondence. 

IANAL so please correct me if I have it wrong.        </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-17 17:12:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Becoming a meme is next level marketing  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-16 22:43:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's from Rick and Morty. Great show btw, i highly recommend it if you're interested.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-16 20:35:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> How much do you know about The Gears War? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-15 07:42:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Gotta respect Obama on this one: 


For one thing, he said, "When I was a kid, I inhaled."

"That was the point," Obama told an audience of magazine editors.
 

Source: https://mobile.nytimes.com/2006/10/24/world/americas/24iht-dems.3272493.html </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-14 20:05:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Can confirm, OP is a cutie pie



Source: I am OP's mirror  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-11 10:42:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> OK now that is a proud ass animal. 

(0:59 for the lazy)   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-10 19:48:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> There's players that have been convicted of all sorts of crimes up to and including murder and they're still playing football. I really don't think anyone that matters will give a shit. The ability to play football tends to matter most to football teams </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-09 21:09:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Go on... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-09 19:16:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's has to be one of the sweetest things you can do for a pet. OP's definitely a good human and I think Jamie knows that  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-09 18:38:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Trump also favors Christian refugees in Syria, has plans to allow churches to back political candidates, and appointed someone who believes in private religious schools over public ones to head the department of education. So not a theocracy yet, but Trump and the GOP want to push it even further in that direction.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-09 17:53:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I thought this was an ironic post in /r/PCmasterrace at first, gave a little chuckle in that context  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-09 17:45:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> My step-brother has a bad habit of projecting like this. Hes morbidly obese, doesnt have the best personality, and doesnt take care of himself or dress well. So every good looking, fit, well dressed guy is automatically a douchebag asshole to him. Regardless of whether he knows them or not. Or if they're good people. His criteria is simply "look at him, he looks like an asshole" when all these guys have done is taken better care of themselves than he has. 

It's pretty sad because if a guy is doing better than you its time to take notes. Not try to cut him down to your standard. 
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-09 17:32:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Why is that different? If anything prison is the only true rape culture we have here in the west </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-09 08:18:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> George W Bush always seemed pretty energetic, especially when he was dodging shoes. He certainly seems to be doing better than Clinton right now just going on looks.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-08 22:38:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> We'd be happy to have you. Especially if you decide to stay! (seriously we could use some more doctors)  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
