<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject1395</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-10 05:52:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Ahah, that's groceries from a few days ago. [No bamboozle!](https://drive.google.com/open?id=0ByLTkA-eco-XbWJVX2tKMmgtdWM) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [Homemade] Beef Bulgogi </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-10 01:10:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-09 23:58:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Nice. I've messed around with a raspberry pi, and I used Ubuntu in college briefly so I didn't have to use Windows Vista. I'm a Windows guy too, but I mostly game, scrape and download random crap online, and organize the resulting chaos. 

I'd love to learn more about programming and maybe install Archlinux on my Chromebook. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-09 23:25:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Definitely! I actually just moved, so I only had the one knife available. But noted on the pith. I planned to use the lemon for an Aviation afterward, so no worries on wasting the lemon :) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-09 22:15:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Screw it I'm not watching the video then.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-09 22:08:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I feel similarly. I pick up so many projects that I never finish because I have few tech-minded friends. If you want to do a nerdy shit meet-up I'm down. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-09 18:34:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I agree. This sounds like the disfigured pipe-dream of a filthmonger. As a fellow filthmonger, I can confirm this project is not worth the time you put into it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-09 13:34:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This is incredible.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-09 13:09:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Very slow burn, but the book takes its time getting to a climax that you expect, but when it gets there it destroys you.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-09 13:03:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> But everybody loves a nice frothy martini! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-09 04:12:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> One word. Thundercougarfalconbird.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-09 02:01:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> 3 oz Junipero Gin

1 oz Alessio Vermouth Blanco

Stir with ice

Expel lemon oils from peel


Yes I know it's not dry vermouth. I wasn't really paying attention to my title </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Why did nobody ever tell me about this vermouth? Dry martini after a long day </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-09 01:57:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-08 18:51:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I definitely found myself missing the "mark as read" option. I like emails, texts, and notifications to be clean.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-08 17:32:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Don't forget the IO shield before you put in the mobo! Don't forget to connect the monitor to the gpu! Don't forget to flip the power switch on the psu! 

Ok now you're ready.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-08 17:19:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Definitely needs Q-Claw, Klobb, and the Moonraker </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-08 15:20:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I actually did a tech theatre major in college. I do AV/IT now, so it's kind of relevant. But yeah, I agree. You don't really age out unless it breaks you.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-08 14:11:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Similarly, Theatre: Learn some other skills.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-08 13:57:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If you liked Eragon, look into Naomi Novik's Temeraire series. It's really similar and much better. 
Otherwise, everyone on this sub can agree that Name of the Wind by Patrick Rothfuss is a great fantasy novel. Personally I'd also recommend The Gentlemen Bastard series. It's dark low fantasy, but it's incredible. Also anything by Brandon Sanderson.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-08 13:53:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> There is no universal color scheme. You'll need a multimeter to test continuity between the drivers and the cable. Generally you're probably looking at left, right, common ground, and two for mic/buttons.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-07 22:27:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> To be honest, I was in Italy a month ago and I looked for it. No luck. I'd love a spanish copy though, even if I have to find a less-than-legal way to acquire it.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-07 22:26:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> No dogs, but rent is $937 a month, and utilities are like $60 total monthly.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-07 19:10:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Ahhhh my tinnitus!  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-07 19:03:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So I was trying to find Spanish futurama to help reinforce my Spanish, but can't find it in other languages. Where did you find it in Italian?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Sublet in medford near tufts </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-07 05:18:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Looking for May-August 31st subletter for 1 Bedroom in Medford Apartment. We will prorate May, as we weren't able to find a sublet in time for May 1st. 

10 minute walk to Tufts. Right off Boston Ave, bus stop is 2 minute walk. 

Room is about 11'x15'? On the second floor off of the common area. Has one window, medium closet. Tons of storage space in the back of the house. Nice kitchen with full size fridge/stove/oven/dishwasher. 

Big common space. Second floor front porch. Free laundry in basement. Room for one car in the driveway. Three existing roommates (24-28 professionals), two on third floor, one on second floor. Really nice people. We're moving out because there isn't a lot of room for my girlfriend and I. I commute to Boston for work and it's about an hour by public transit - much faster by car. Close to lots of restaurants, Stop Shop/Trader Joes/Whole Foods, Davis Square (Red Line) and some nice places to walk/run/bike. Nice management company, very responsive. No first/last/security. Utilities are reasonable and split with roommates evenly. 

Let me know if you have any questions, want pictures or want a tour! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-07 05:14:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So she says holding the key to the start button didn't work. I'm not really familiar with the mechanics of how this works, but is the key RFID? Shouldn't it just be hard-coded in? I assume that if they can get the car's lights on, they can start it, but I really don't know, and I can't get down there to check it out.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> RAV4 Fob issue </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-07 05:04:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hi there. Quick question for you guys. 

My girlfriend's mother has a 2012 (I believe) RAV4, and the battery is dead. I only know as much as I have overheard over the phone, but apparently AAA can't jump the car, as you can't get it to start without the key fob. Well she has the fob, but evidently the fob's programming is only held in memory while the car has power. Or at least that is what AAA is telling her. I'm not nearby to look into it myself, but I'd like to see if we can save her a few hundred on the tow and reprogramming. 

My girlfriend found something online about reprogramming the fob with a series of -opening-the-door-turn-the-key-remove-the-key-etc. actions. Any truth in this? The tow is coming tomorrow afternoon I believe, so I'd love to know if we have other options. 

Thanks a lot for any help you can give! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-07 05:02:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Please tell me your bachelor party is a drunken hatchet fight.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-05 21:38:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Steelheart by Brandon Sanderson. It's about a world where people become superheroes, but become corrupted by power. The main character is out to kill all of the superheroes. Not entirely as dark as it sounds, and full of amazing humor.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-05 16:44:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I think a hacksaw and tap wrench is your best bet.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-05 14:44:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's hard not to resent my parents for perpetuating this though. Here I am doing IT with a Theatre BA. If I didn't owe $60,000 I'd be pretty well off instead of living paycheck to paycheck.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-04 23:16:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> How did I know that the top comment was going to be able Molex to Sata?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-04 17:01:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Man, I'll buy some of these some day. I have always wanted V-Modas. I even buy their cables for my other headphones ._. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-04 16:05:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I just don't get why anyone uses the app. If you can't figure out to pair BT without an app, just return the headphones.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-04 15:00:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> There's an exit out the back of the boss chamber that leads to No Mans Wharf </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-04 14:58:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You posted them with empty brackets. To a PC user that makes the links invisible. Either remove all brackets and parentheses or put something in the brackets (E.g. "Screenshot 1")

Edit: Ther u go bb </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-04 14:50:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I was thinking about this while watching Lobosjr do his randomized runs. /u/HotPocketRemix is it possible that enemies are formatted similarly to items? Could you shuffle all enemies in the game? 

Honestly I just want to see Lobosjr run into the Gaping Dragon on the buttresses in Anor Londo. 

P.S. Thanks for all your work! This is so cool and has led to hours of entertainment.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-03 18:49:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If you look on Wookiepedia there's a canon timeline </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-02 17:42:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> HDMI CEC is generally prettt fucky. If you are thinking of upgrading, I'd recommend matching the brand of your soundbar with the brand of your tv, and making sure it's a CEC enabled sound bar. The backup option is a harmony remote.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-02 14:51:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Well I guess my only reference is the render from the kickstarter, but I feel like they could have been a lot cleaner. The mold process they used may not have been the quality I was hoping for.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-02 13:50:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The models don't look as nice as I'd hoped :/

Honestly, I bought a 3D printer so I could make dark souls figurines, so I should get on that.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-02 13:47:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You neglected to mention the free popcorn in the title.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-02 13:45:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I've always wanted to try the hangover IV. I work in a hospital, so I have no excuse.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-01 22:01:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> They look super slick. This is the technology of the future.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-01 21:55:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The issue isn't whether they are as good as certified earmuffs, it's that most workplaces that are required to have you wear PPE will not let you use random earplugs that are "about as good". They require you to have the certification to use them at work.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-01 21:22:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I agree. His videos are for children.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-01 19:36:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Contains zero of the original ingredients.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-01 19:14:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> They cost three times as much as standard PPE and they aren't even NRR certified. They're garbage.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-01 18:17:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Makes me wish I had voted for him... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-01 16:48:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Definitely recommend the version off of Live After Death over the Powerslave studio recording! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-01 16:19:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Bring a torch into the first spider area if you're on SotFS. They are afraid of the torch. Maybe that might help? Just keep in mind, the boss is spiderish too.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-01 15:20:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm unsubscribing from /r/gadgets. This shit is stupid.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-01 14:08:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The saucers! They's a cra-shin! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-01 14:00:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The important question </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-28 21:58:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Any idea what the ticket gets you? Do you buy a ticket so you can get the privilege to buy drinks? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-28 18:07:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Glad to hear it! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-28 18:07:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's on youtube somewhere.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-28 17:15:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Someone did this with google, alexa and siri looping infinitely.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-28 12:43:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I feel like there's a specific halfling class that gives you this as a feature in pf or d d somewhere.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-27 02:37:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah 5 minutes each. And you'd think people would be smart enough not to afk in this game.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Looking for subletter in medford - 10 minutes from tufts - bedroom for rent $937 per month - free parking/laundry </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-26 22:41:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Looking for May 1st-August 31st subletter for 1 Bedroom in Medford Apartment. 
10 minute walk to Tufts. Right off Boston Ave, bus stop is 2 minute walk. 
Room is about 11'x15'? On the second floor off of the common area. Has one window, medium closet. 
Tons of storage space in the back of the house. Nice kitchen with full size fridge/stove/oven/dishwasher. Big common space. Second floor front porch. Free laundry in basement. 
Room for one car in the driveway. 
Three existing roommates (24-28 professionals), two on third floor, one on second floor. Really nice people. 
We're moving out because there isn't a lot of room for my girlfriend and I. 
I commute to Boston for work and it's about an hour by public transit - much faster by car. 
Close to lots of restaurants, Stop Shop/Trader Joes/Whole Foods, Davis Square (Red Line) and some nice places to walk/run/bike.
Nice management company, very responsive. No first/last/security. Utilities are reasonable and split with roommates evenly.
Let me know if you have any questions, want pictures or want a tour! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-26 21:30:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'll check when I get home! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-26 21:26:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Headphone users beware. Screeches like a harpy in all three videos.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-26 20:36:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I bought the drakeblood was considered trash because of multiple resistances? If it's actually good I'll totally start using it! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-26 20:30:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This is silly, but you could try something like [this](https://www.amazon.com/iSimple-Portable-Wireless-Smartphones-Bluetooth/dp/B00KPZN5UC) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-26 20:13:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Cool! If you end up with this cable, I personally use it with an Antlion Modmic and it's fantastic.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-26 19:39:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> While Audio-gd has one of the worst websites I've seen in years, the reviews look amazing. I'll definitely keep this one in mind. Thanks! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-26 19:28:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'll be honest, I could set aside $300 for a Schiit stack, but I'm a sucker for anodized aluminum. Have any recommendations in that range? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-26 19:10:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Been thinking about open backs recently. Screw it, I'm in. Anyone have an idea of whether these need an amp? At 62ohm I feel like it isn't a bad idea.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-26 18:50:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's got stiff mesh reinforcement, it's coiled in packaging instead of cinched into a tight bundle with twist-ties, its heavier and thicker, it has much nicer jacks on both ends. *Its $12* </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-26 18:45:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I assumed it would be horrible. It's not. Well done.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-26 18:31:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Congrats! I love my 598Cs. They're going to be my go to headphones until Massdrop ships my K7XX :)

Now every I see the 598Cs I recommend getting[ this replacement cable.](https://www.amazon.com/gp/aw/d/B00KAKBHKM/ref=yo_ii_img?ie=UTF8 psc=1) 

It's worth every penny. Enormous upgrade over the stock cable.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-26 18:22:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This is fantastic. I'd support rewriting class features for this.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-26 13:50:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Check your solder job. It's possible you're out of phase, or just a big clump of solder resisting current on one side.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-26 12:24:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Please tell me one of your PCs is just "Skeleton" </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-26 00:16:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This sounds like a basement mini fridge is your answer.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-25 22:06:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'd go with a chili paste variant like sambal or harissa  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-25 21:15:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Delete? Del-ete...? I don't think I know this word </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-25 21:09:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Transcode can be awkward if your server is weak. Plex can handle 4K, but I believe the only non-pc hardware that can play is back is an nvidia shield. I recommend looking into it on Plex's website.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-25 19:41:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> RAID! Backups! 

No data left behind.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-25 19:38:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Pipe and fitting is easy, but never cheap.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-25 16:28:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeh. Or you can use a NAS and run the server from something smaller than your computer. Or you can build a server. There are a ton of options.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-25 16:16:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Ralph's has a patio. That's all I need.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-25 16:08:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Space is cheap! Bestbuy has 8TB WD reds for $180 recently. Check /r/datahoarder </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-25 15:22:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Get Plex. Make your own Netflix. With blackjack. And hookers.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-25 11:49:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I definitely agree. I even joined the Facebook group, and it's possibly as bad. I get notifications every day and they're all shitty events, maybe two hang out posts a month.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-25 11:45:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Dalinar doing everything he does.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-24 20:43:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That hurt me.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-24 17:27:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Also basically you need to think of a cable as the wires inside the insulation. It's not just one rubber cord. If the whole cable is screwed up like that there's a problem with the wiring inside it. If you buy a nice cable that keeps those wires protected, it lasts way longer. The cable I linked has Kevlar mesh over is and aluminum terminations, so it's super beefy.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-24 12:47:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> "If you can't afford your bar tab, I *do* accept your everlasting soul instead of gold." </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-24 05:48:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's thicker, high quality and not cinched up in a bundle from the factory. Trust me, it's way better. It's a cheap price for such a nice cable.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-24 03:16:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That table must rattle the shit out of your poolside cocktail.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-24 02:52:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Try this cable. I have one and I love it. 

https://www.amazon.com/gp/product/B00KAKBHKM/ref=oh_aui_detailpage_o05_s01?ie=UTF8 psc=1 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-24 01:52:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The highest of fi </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-23 20:10:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Definitely my concern. Try plugging in a MacBook and you'll have worlds of trouble I bet.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-23 17:42:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That is ludicrously expensive.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-23 04:40:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I think Kelly Square is beautiful in its own right. And I can only think of two fatalities there! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-22 03:39:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Not what you're looking for, but look up Steelheart. You might like it.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-22 02:37:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> 1/4" drive.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-21 23:39:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Beelzebub's Bok Choy </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Be careful what you say! </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-21 23:24:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yesterday I was on a bus and I noticed a girl wearing AKG K7XXs. 

I was SO CLOSE to saying "Nice cans". 

Dodged a huge bullet there. 
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Room for sublet near Tufts in Medford </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-21 02:29:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Looking for May 1st-August 31st subletter for 1 Bedroom in Medford Apartment. 
10 minute walk to Tufts. Right off Boston Ave, bus stop is 2 minute walk. 
Room is about 11'x15'? On the second floor off of the common area. Has one window, medium closet. 
Tons of storage space in the back of the house. Nice kitchen with full size fridge/stove/oven/dishwasher. Big common space. Second floor front porch. Free laundry in basement. 
Room for one car in the driveway. 
Three existing roommates (24-28 professionals), two on third floor, one on second floor. Really nice people. 
We're moving out because there isn't a lot of room for my girlfriend and I. 
I commute to Boston for work and it's about an hour by public transit - much faster by car. 
Close to lots of restaurants, Stop Shop/Trader Joes/Whole Foods, Davis Square (Red Line) and some nice places to walk/run/bike.
Nice management company, very responsive. No first/last/security. Utilities are reasonable and split with roommates evenly.
Let me know if you have any questions, want pictures or want a tour! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-20 22:34:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Macro mech keypads show up on Massdrop occasionally too. 

1. https://www.massdrop.com/buy/max-falcon-8-programmable-macropad-kit

2. https://www.massdrop.com/buy/staryu-mini-macro-pad

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-20 03:19:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Today I got on my bus to go to work and he drove me to Midir </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-20 02:18:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Oh jeez, I bought a guppy and the knife detent broke. Didn't notice until I reached into my pocket and stabbed myself. Piece of shit.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-19 20:44:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's a bit wonky sometimes, but I love it.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-19 20:19:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Went US to Italy a few weeks ago. Slow but no issues otherwise.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-19 19:10:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I felt ripped off when the raid boss after the campaign was literally just the final campaign boss again. And 2k Australia should have paid some non-Australian voice actors.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-19 15:07:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm a bit of a hypocrite since I carry a Leatherman (Sidekick - Wave got stolen on a job site), but really a multi-tool is just a bunch of shitty tools bolted together. 

You should have almost zero reason to use it when you're at home or anywhere near real tools.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-19 14:34:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The Sun Tzu guys were my favorite.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-19 14:33:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> He was my favorite part of that show. "His head is off. This usually leads to death. I'm a doctor."  

Looking back, my heavy consumption of Bacardi 151 while watching this show may have something to do with it.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-19 12:28:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That's just resting corgi face. This is fine. Stupid title.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-18 21:49:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That was actually super cool. Though whoever did the editing and put the BUMP tststse BUMP tststse BUMP drum track over EVERY car's name should be fired.

Out of a cannon.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
