<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject1780</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-10 04:57:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Enlighten me! I have only ever been able to guess at how many submissions you guys see in a day. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-10 03:52:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It boils down to preference, honestly.

On one hand, it would be easier to build a following if every thing is under one name. On the other, you can add to immersion by using other accounts.

As far as real name vs. pen name, it just depends on what feels good to you. I use a pen name because my real name is hard enough to pronounce, let alone try to sell books with. 

Do what feels right! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-09 21:46:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It absolutely is enforced. But you're looking at a team of like *maybe* ten people combing through dozens (if not more) stories per day. Unfortunately, they can't catch 'em all. 

There's the report button that we're all encouraged to use to notify them when something slips through the cracks. Like my great granddad always used to say:

"Mods ain't gods." </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-09 11:34:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I said biiiiiiiiiiittttcccchhhhhh.

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-09 11:33:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Biiiiiiiiiiittttcccchhhhhh. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-09 11:32:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Like pretty much every artist ever. This is the right answer! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Wordless </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-09 04:12:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> She never spoke. 

Never.

Not to a man,

at least.

I tried my luck 

when I saw her

singing 

at the bar down the street.

We locked eyes during 

"Can't Stop Believing"

and I thought we had a moment.

I was met with

stiff opposition

and a stiff drink

in my face. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-08 19:27:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Which actor pitrayed James Bond in a way that you found most favorable? Also, when are we going to tell them about the engagement? Stop hiding me! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-08 19:24:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Nah, wasn't me. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-08 14:16:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Mikey is a nickname that my grandma used to call me since part of my first name is Micheal (not a typo). Knutson (kuh-newt-son) was her maiden name. It's essentially a tribute.    </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-08 14:02:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> I always did fancy me a Butterfree </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-08 03:11:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> From day one, I knew my boy was gonna be special. When we had got home from the hospital he done reaffirmed my beliefs. Like a true parasite, he ate the host he came from. Left a few bones but I ain't never been one to complain. Plus, she was more than enough to fatten him up and keep him occupied fer a while. 

Ya see, newborns need to be loaded up on nutrients. Alla them carbohydrits and such. Well, the doctor told me that at least. Said something about his arms and legs need the energy to "distend" or something like that. I don't know. I like how he's been crawling around all cute like. 

Wasn't really ever a problem with my boy until he got a bit hungry. He started to eat my kitty cats and I gotta be honest, it rightfully pissed me off. I yelled at him and he hid under the couch for a couple of days. I was so mad, I didn't even bother looking til early this morning. 

Boy, I wish I would have looked sooner.

Damn boy wrecked my whole couch! There's a bunch of fuckin sticky strings and spit under there like a goddamn tent! Upholstery ain't cheap! When I saw that I lost my cool temper. I shook the couch hard as I could muster. Grabbed it by one arm and tried lift in it up to scare him out. Jumped on it. Kicked it. Sprayed it with febreeze. 

Til I heard a light screech that made me dizzy. I looked under and I cracked his little hiding spot open. It's got a pretty purple light coming out of it. It's so pretty in fact that I ain't even mad no more. I might even go find him something to nibble on. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-07 21:47:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Borrasca.

Always Borrasca. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Oahu </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-06 17:28:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The coconut sunset glazed my body. 

I became a new person that day. 

The warm red became white

and I left home for the night.

All of my filth had been washed away. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-06 17:22:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I heard they're getting the Pothole Maze. Each contestant is given a tiny car that they have to navigate through a twenty foot stretch of various sized holes. All while air horns blow at them to mimic other cars.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Ain't Never Heard a Man Scream Like This Man Before </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-05 16:59:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> He's never been late before

today. Punctual is

his motive for living.

We sent a driver to his house.

1141 Poilnee Lane. 

The house with the green door.

It was open.

Stanley was open

with a black mass standing

next to him.

The video cut to static.

Never heard a man scream like

this man before. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Jingle Jangle </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-05 14:51:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I drink coffee to get through my day. Like those who drink alcohol to get through lonely nights. The main differences between myself and an alcoholic are as follows:

I drink coffee to hear voices. 

They drink beer to stop them.

I'm aware it's a broad assumption that people drink to stop voices. Does your brain not create monologue for every thing you do? Those poor decisions can be drowned with the right cocktail blend. 

I can't hear them. I wake up without motivation. Caffeine boosts my adrenaline. Kicking my ass, saying:

"Keep running."

They won't find me before 17. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-05 14:30:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> **Team:** Phalluses Shaped Like Slugs or Slugs Shaped Like Phalluses, Either Way We're Slippery and Slimey

**Title:** I'm open to suggestions

---

I've never quite understood why people feel the need to crowd around someone after an incident. They don't know the victim and typically don't even care about their well-being. Is it bragging rights? Being able to say you were there when that beautiful, young woman fell two stories from a balcony to the pavement must qualify people for a higher status quo, I guess.

I was across the street sitting on the patio at Starbucks when the commotion began. An older gentleman began shouting for help as he ran to the side of a motionless blonde woman who was trying to dye her hair red. On cue, the ants began trickling in to capture any piece of the sweetness that they could. 

"She must have fallen right off!" The old man exclaimed as he wheezed, out of breath from the excitement. 

I glanced up at the balcony. It was void of the vultures that typically stare from above when someone "falls." I took a sip of my decaf and went back to the article on my phone. 

"Suicide." I murmured to myself with a chuckle, " Horrible height to do it from. Completely inefficient." 

"Are you a fucking *asshole* or something?" A woman berated, slamming her hand down on the table in front of me. 

"I'm just saying it isn't an effective way to get the job done." I shrugged and looked at the scene. "See, she's already moving again." 

The woman smacked my coffee to the ground and marched off, presumably to go uphold justice somewhere she could be more successful. After assessing the damage to my loafers, I glanced again to the crowd that was paralyzed by discombobulation. The blonde was standing and brushing herself off. I couldn't make out her words but it appeared she was letting them know she was okay. Our eyes met.

She immediately abandoned her entourage, casually strolling towards me. When she got to the sidewalk outside of the patio barricade my heart fluttered. Despite being in the middle of a poor dye job, she was the most elegant creature I had ever seen.

"Hey. So I'm having a really rough day. Do you want to go get beers or something?" Her voice was soothing in ways I can't begin to explain.

"Absolutely." I couldn't say no to those legs.     </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-05 13:50:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I think my favorite was 2007 or 2008. Whatever year they toured with Pepper and the Wailers for the first time. Maybe 2006? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-04 19:35:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Generally, I'm hyper critical of people who only come on reddit to advertise and don't actually participate in the communities they hope to gain the attention of.

*However,* despite being cranky today I decided to check out snippets of videos on YouTube. 

Not bad. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-04 11:28:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Beard, chest hair...whateva! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> About these Pledge updates </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-04 06:22:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Is it just me or do they suck?

I remember the updates for Stereolithic being so much better. I honestly don't even bother checking them right away most of the time. I really don't even know why I bothered preordering. I can't say I'm any more excited for the album than I was when they announced it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-04 05:01:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Oh you mean my smash hit *STEAL THIS STORY* that is in my featured selection of the r/nosleepinterviews sidebar? (luh u /u/poppy_moonray 3) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> You Make Life Seem Hard </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-03 19:20:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Isn't it all just pointless

to ponder?

I wouldn't be bothered

with any sort of heartache.

Great.

I'm the selfish asshole

you hate under your breath

because 

I didn't clean my plate. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-02 16:32:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Damn, son.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-02 14:46:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Haha I could totally do my entire hit album! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> YouTube sounds like an order a caveman would give </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-02 12:11:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> How would everyone feel about watching a vlog of a young man's journey into writing?

I've been sitting on this idea for a bit and now that I'm getting close to the point of doing something with it, I wanted to see what my brothers, sisters, and whatever /u/AsForClass is, think about it. 

That's...uh...that's it. I don't have anything else. Just wanna start a YouTube channel to document my thoughts and stuff. Yup. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> May 2017  r/TheDirty31 </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-02 11:59:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Rain Delays </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-02 07:59:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> "Emma, could you phone my wife and tell her I'm going to be late today? I'm going to take the bus."

It was a peculiar request. Harold had a mobile phone, a swell car, and it was a particularly bad day for public transport with the rain. Still, Emma obliged as a good secretary does.

"You let him go!? Why!? How long ago did he leave?" Harold's wife was frantic. That morning, she had discovered his manuscript on the desktop. She knew he was a writer. She also knew this wasn't one of his stories.

*Dear Ashlyn,*

*Don't blame yourself...* </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-02 01:26:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> **Team:** Phalluses Shaped Like Slugs or Slugs Shaped Like Phalluses, Either Way We're Slippery and Slimey

**Title:** TBD

**Order:**

/u/subject1780        
/u/EtTuTortilla         
/u/ThisIsTheSignal           
/u/kanjay101         
/u/ahilgen         

We're writing a vampire story kiddos, better hold onto your respective gender's genitalia!        </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-01 19:21:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Excited to be back ;) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-01 13:02:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yessir. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Mikey Knuston </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-01 07:20:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [Reddit](http://reddit.com/r/subject1780) | [Twitter](http://twitter.com/knutsonwrites) | [Facebook](http://facebook.com/knutsonwrites) 

May 1st: [Too Long, Too Late](https://www.reddit.com/r/shortscarystories/comments/68k7dh/too_long_too_late) - r/shortscarystories

May 2nd: [Rain Delays](https://www.reddit.com/r/DrabbleRousers/comments/68rfd0/rain_delays) - r/DrabbleRousers

May 3rd: [You Make Life Seem Hard](https://www.reddit.com/r/youpoetried/comments/691r3z/you_make_life_seem_hard) - r/youpoetried

**May 4th:** [Ain't Never Heard a Man Scream Like This Man Before](https://www.reddit.com/r/shortscarystories/comments/69f6n3/aint_never_heard_a_man_scream_like_this_man_before) - r/shortscarystories

May 5th: [Jingle Jangle](https://www.reddit.com/r/DrabbleRousers/comments/69eh1c/jingle_jangle) - r/DrabbleRousers

May 6th: [Oahu](https://www.reddit.com/r/youpoetried/comments/69lqyb/oahu) - r/youpoetried

May 7th: [I always did fancy me a Butterfree](https://www.reddit.com/r/shortscarystories/comments/69v232/i_always_did_fancy_me_a_butterfree) - r/shortscarystories

May 8th: [Wordless](https://www.reddit.com/r/youpoetried/comments/6a2neq/wordless) - r/youpoetried

May 9th: [My Shadow Has Eyes](https://www.reddit.com/r/nosleep/comments/6abysg/my_shadow_has_eyes) - r/nosleep </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Too Long, Too Late  r/shortscarystories </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-01 07:16:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Too Long, Too Late </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-01 07:15:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You stopped coming around. Why? Are you still holding a grudge against me for eating your dog?

Come on, man. Don't be petty.

We both know it was a clean kill. You laid him down on top of the altar and we both held the handle as it pierced his neck. Exactly as the book instructed. It wasn't my fault you decided to burn the body. Cooked meat is cooked meat.

You used to visit me. Twice a week more regularly than an old man on a prune diet. Is one meal really enough to stop a bond like ours?

It was *him* wasn't it? 

Did he visit you, too? Leaning in doorways. Sitting in the good chair. Casually murmuring under his breath how you need to act first. You always had to be first. Well, I won't be last. I'm coming for you. 

It worked, and I'm back. I'm not going to kill you back - that would be petty. I want to become you. Occupy your mind and ruin your life. Then you can kill us both next time. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-01 06:30:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Good luck, homeslice!!  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-01 04:47:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> With the frequency of their posting, I'm not surprised by that at all. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-01 04:38:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Fucked him so hard he ain't walk right for a week! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-01 02:50:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Was it Ty Notts? (Totally kidding he would *never* steal multiple stories from regular contributors on r/nosleep and then blame us when he got caught)

You can file a DMCA claim against the offending YouTube channel. They're quite responsive and helpful in these situations. My issues were resolved in less than a few days. 

As far as stopping it, it'll never happen. Even if you never published works online and only stuck to print publishing someone, somewhere will read your book and steal the idea. Erasing your nosleep catalog isn't the way to go. It's a headache, but fortunately these things can easily be dealt with once discovered. No worries! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-01 01:10:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [Hotlink.](https://m.imgur.com/gallery/WcOas)  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-30 15:18:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That was a fun, quick read. Thanks! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-30 15:14:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Cheeky. I like it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-30 15:13:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Oh boy. My mom had no serious restrictions when I was growing up, so she let me watch a lot of stuff most little kids couldn't. I say that because I'm certain I saw a lot more prior to this, but my first memorable horror movie was *Friday the 13th.* That lake scene at the end fucked me up for yeeeaaaarrrrssssss. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-27 22:41:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm excited to have you on my team again! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-27 21:09:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Actually, that's a valid point. If you're not into the gradual burn then its a waste of time. I haven't found any great indie/underground horror from the US lately that I haven't seen before. If you have any suggestions I'm all ears! I'd love to find some new shit. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-27 17:22:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Absolutely. Actually, I almost posted a similar thread last night about how American horror specifically is trite these days.

Like, I still get scared - don't get me wrong. It takes *a lot* to get me there, though. I'm in the same boat as Elias. Video games are generally the only thing that can truly set me off. It's something about being immersed into a world where you're in control and those things are, in a way, happening directly to you. 

Also, horror in non-American cultures is way better. Side note.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-27 04:29:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> A lot (see: 100%) of my stories contain elements from my life. I guess you could say quite close? Except for the killings. I haven't killed *nearly* as many people in real life. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-26 23:34:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Even the stupidity?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-26 19:01:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Depends on how long you've been gone. I'd recommend sorting through top posts. A lot of the all time posts have changed in the last six months due to new writers and the new upvote algorithm. 

Off the top of my head..

/u/Hayong is new and a lovely contributor.

/u/iia, of course.

/u/A10A10A10A10 has earned a spot in my heart, even though I have zero clue if the user name is spelled that way.

There's also the *Dared My Best Friend* series by /u/Harrison_Prince.

Um.

Infected Town **finally** finished up. 

That's all I've got. Admittedly, I've been reading way less than I should be.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-26 18:55:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Being a writer does it for me. Once you cross that line, verisimilitude isn't a factor when you read r/nosleep. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-26 14:55:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I feel like I only ever promote myself on these...but:

I tried to blend the two together with this story [about clowns.](https://redd.it/565abv)  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-25 08:43:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> ~~It might have a lot to do with the recent rule change that now allows that to be in stories.~~ Rape is a tough subject to write about, and I agree it's often done incorrectly (I'm pretty sure I skimmed it in my most recent story, honestly). It's something that I'm sure will pass, as do all other fads you might see on the sub.

**Edit:** Was wrong. Don't listen to me!
  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-25 02:32:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Bond. James, Bond. Has been portrayed by many actors over the course of history. Who do you feel is your favorite? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-24 23:40:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hi. I would like to formally request to lead a team of vigilantes across the country on various United Airlines flights to uphold the rights of middle America. 

Or like, captain a team. Yeah. That's what I meant. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-24 16:07:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [I wrote this one.](https://www.reddit.com/r/libraryofshadows/comments/5ckuyq/robots_need_less_than_three_noir_contest/) Maybe it'll work for you? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-22 18:44:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I have nothing productive to add to this at the moment. I just got a good giggle out your friend not being able to read *Borrasca* because he's a movie guy. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-21 20:42:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> But I'm your favorite weirdo, right?? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-21 20:24:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Try r/subject1780. I heard that dude just kills a bunch of people and doesn't really delve into paranormal too often. I've met him a few times also and he's gorgeous. So. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-19 03:08:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's because your character didn't actually *do* anything. There's no action or event that takes place. Stories here have to have that. You have a solid intro, it just needs more added on! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-19 01:16:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's hard to answer that because what scares someone is completely subjective. I will say that I've personally read (and written) stories here that *just* barely fit into the typical horror category and not had an issue. The biggest focus should be having a complete story for each piece.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-18 22:01:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Every part has to have an element of horror and be a complete chain of events. Unfortunately, parts just for character development would be considered against the rules. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-18 19:26:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Dammit, I blinked. Can we do it again? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-16 03:05:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> fellow writers

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-16 02:59:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I find it odd that you're wasting your time trolling a writing community. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-16 02:53:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Can we do it naked? Just for fun. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-16 02:51:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> He chose to make a grammatical for artistic effect, duh. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-16 02:48:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hey man, if you sell the Checclist for millions of dollars I'll eat a live chicken.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-16 02:46:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Ayyyyyyy </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-16 02:41:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So, you're a troll right? Guys? This guy has to be yanking our chains. 

Or it's Tommy Wiseau. 

Maybe we just don't *understand* "the Checclist." </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-16 02:33:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Lol. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-15 19:21:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Write what you want to write. Simple as that. I've had *maybe* five or six stories that broke 500 upvotes out of the dozens that I've written for r/nosleep.

It's all about what you want. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-15 05:03:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'll be sure not to blink so I don't miss it! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-15 03:23:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> :) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-15 02:10:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I've had those same thoughts. It's rough losing a parent at a young age. I'm very sorry for your loss. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-15 02:09:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thank you, that's very sweet of you to say! Fortunately enough, this was in the past and I've since graduated (albeit barely). I'm still considering the benefits of college. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-15 02:08:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Amen. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-15 02:08:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> At the time, I believed that. However, /u/awesome_e is right. Rape is rape and is not acceptable in any circumstance. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-15 00:05:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I can respect your opinion. It's hard to understand things you haven't experienced. No harm done. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-14 23:04:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You sound just like my teachers and parents. Thanks. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-14 22:13:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> He raped me. I didn't see it that way at the time, but Jonah showed me the truth. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-14 21:15:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Why is that? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-14 21:11:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's been an interesting life. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Thank You for Calling Me "Fat"  r/nosleep </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-14 21:10:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Thank You for Calling Me "Fat" </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-14 21:03:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It started with a razor blade. The stereotypical stainless-steel trapezoid that only rusts if you let the blood sit too long. I stole it from my father's workshop. 

My father picked me up from school that day after the principal called to inform him of my "grandiose hysterical behavior" - I believe that was the exact quote. I was inconsolable. A wreck. A hot mess. A twelve year old who shouldn't have been carrying the emotional burden that I was. When he came into the principal's office it became clear to me that I was alone. Mrs. Rollins, for being a rather voluptuous black woman in an all white town, should have had some empathy. The townsfolk didn't want a "nigger" there just like the girls in my class didn't want...me...learning alongside them.

"Mr. Halls, your daughter has been causing an *excessive* disturbance lately. Do you have any idea what has gotten into her?" Rollins quickly blurted out, as if she was afraid her cholesterol was finally catching up with her.

"David." He replied.

"I'm sorry?"

"Name's David. Mr. Halls is some guy in Ohio that I've never met." My dad shot me a sly wink as he frowned to try hiding his grin.

"*Mr. Halls.* Ellie has been disrupting her class almost daily since sessions began this term." She stood up and threw her hands down on her desk. "Do *you* know what's going on with her?"

My father, a calm man by nature, stood straight up and slammed his hands onto Mrs. Rollins desk, mimicking her. 

"No." He said softly. That was the first time I laughed since school started.

"This is not a joke!" Rollins erupted, and my father stopped hiding his smile. 

"You're right, Donna. It isn't. My wife and I are paying you nine-*thousand* dollars a year for our daughter to attend this school. Do you know why we pay that, Donna?" His cheeriness began to fade. "We're paying that so Ellie here can get a good education at a good school around good people so she can grow up and have a good life. Are you following my theme here?" 

She nodded and returned to her chair.

"Good. We don't pay you nine-*thousand* dollars for our daughter to come home every single day in tears because some snotty little bitches hate that she eats more than a carrot stick for dinner."

"It is **not** appropriate to talk about children that way!" She popped up and slammed her hands onto her desk again, this time knocking over a pile of papers.

"You're right," my dad sat down and crossed his arms, "it isn't. No one should be talking about any child that way. Why do these girls get to call my daughter fat, Mrs. Rollins?"

I can't recall much of the meeting after that. I think hearing my father, my hero, acknowledging that I had a weight problem made me suppress the rest. That's what my therapist said, at least.

The clearest memory I have after that meeting is stealing the blade from dad's yellow toolkit while I sat in his shop waiting for him to finish a desk. He had so many that I was confident he would have no idea he was missing it. We went home that evening and my mother had dinner ready for us. Meatloaf, mashed potatoes, and carrots. I ran to my room in a fluster of "grandiose hysterical behavior." No one followed.

I expected the first cut to hurt. My hands were shaking as I tried to hold the blade steady while my insides seeped out from behind it. The second cut came with greater ease. Whether that was from the loss of blood or the willingness to die I can't say. I wanted to keep going until the end, but as foolish as it was, I freaked out when the blood starting pooling on the carpet. My mother would kill me for leaving a stain in her house. I wanted sympathy...someone to care. Not chastise me. I stopped. The blood didn't. 

I panicked and shouted for help as loud as I possibly could. I didn't realize how unprepared I was to die. 

Mr. McKinney was the nicest person I think I have ever met in my life. He wasn't like any of my teachers, bosses, or *typical* therapists. For five years on Tuesdays and Fridays I *mattered.* McKinney understood me and my struggles. In fact, he was like me. He was made fun of in school because no one wanted him there. Girls didn't breathe in his direction and boys spared no expense reminding him of what he was. That's why he became a therapist - to help kids who were dealing with what he what went through. I loved that man. I always will. 

On my first visit after turning seventeen we experimented with a new form of therapy that McKinney created. The first step was hypnosis. Not put-you-in-a-trance style, but rather a light, drug induced state of lucidity. While in this calm state, he would attempt physical stimulation to manifest activity in my dream state. For the first few sessions, he would perform various pokes and rubs on my feet to see if I would make myself run while lucid. We then moved onto my thighs, where he would tickle the insides with his fingers to make me kick. He'd massage my shoulders and kiss my neck to get me to look in a particular direction. Mr. McKinney would fuck me because he was a monster. I loved every second of it. We had a real connection, and to this day he's truly the only man besides my father that I loved. 

My second attempt was not long after I told my parents about the relationship Mr. McKinney and I were having. I pleaded and pleaded with them not to do anything. "We're in love!" was my stump phrase when they would use their word for us. I tried explaining that I wanted it. I wanted him. Rape is only rape if it wasn't consensual. 

It didn't matter.

Within a short month of being arrested, McKinney lost his office and his entire career. As we were waiting in the courtroom for the first of many trials to begin my father collapsed onto the cold, marble floors. Dead on arrival. There was no hope for resuscitation, according to the paramedics. It didn't stop me from trying CPR until I had to be physically restrained. 

The hospital held me overnight due to my "grandiose hysterical behavior." I believe the official listing for my stay was due to a mental breakdown which, looking back on things now, was a horribly mild diagnosis considering my mental state. After my nurse left my mother and I with discharge papers, I ripped the pen from my mom's hand and shoved in into my neck as far as I could until my world went white.

I didn't see anything for those two minutes of being legally deceased. I only heard a voice - a child's voice. He told me his name was Jonah and that we were best friends now. Jonah said he would help me get through the hard times. 

Jonah wasn't real, as far as I know. Five years after we first met, I'm now quite confident of that. He was a figment of my imagination that manifested itself during a time of peak stress. He did, however, give me the confidence to make it through my last year of school after my father died. 

My second round of senior year started in September, a couple weeks after the rest of the kids started. My new therapist believed that all of the hustle and bustle of kids getting acclimated to their classes would be too stressful for me. I also had to have my teachers sign off that I attended every class, and then turn my sheet into the principal's office at the end of each day where my mother would meet me and take me home. I was a prisoner living under a disguise they called freedom. 

My grand return to school started with homeroom, where all of my life-long "friends" also happened to be. A failed subtle attempt at keeping tabs on me. They could have at least found actual friends of mine. Instead, the class was filled with boys only looked at me like a freak and girls who moved on from making fun of my appearance to reminding me of how I killed my dad by being a whore. 

I didn't make it to my next class. 

Jonah came to me while I was sleeping that night. He wiped my tears and handed me a slip of paper - the address of one Isabella DeSantis, also known as the girl who lead the bitches that made me how I was. Jonah told me how we could handle it. I disagreed, but he was just as persuasive as he was persistent.

Together, Jonah and I walked to her house. I slid in through a window and he followed close behind. We explored the house until we found her bedroom, all white with stupid gold decorations. She was a diva, alright. As I stood over her, looking down at the source of my years of self-hatred I lost my confidence. I wept and backed away. I couldn't go through with it. Jonah became angry at my flaking. He took the razor blade from my hand and slit both of her wrists while holding his hand over her mouth. She only struggled for a couple of minutes, thankfully. I went home with Jonah and he held me while I slept soundly for the first time in years.

I haven't seen Jonah since I fell asleep that night, but I know he's still watching me. This morning I found an address and a date in my planner. The release date of Jim McKinney, and the return of my best friend. 

10/18/17. 

I'll see you soon.

[Love,](http://reddit.com/r/subject1780)

Ellie </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-13 09:57:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Ugh. Damn werewolves. Always mauling people and such. What an inconvenience! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-13 09:51:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That thing from Alien that occassionally pops out of people's stomachs.

Or cancer. Fuck cancer. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-12 16:25:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Huh. I now have this insatiable urge to write a story that starts with K and X. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-11 22:05:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm hoping for like a Summer of Love vibe. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-11 16:36:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> My biggest piece of advice would be to work on fluidity. A lot of your adjective heavy sentences come across almost list like, as if you're just retelling bullet points from your notes. That also applies to the action in your story. It just has a stoic, list feeling to it.

Instead of listing, you could try adding in descriptions to action. Or coattailing descriptions onto other sentences. 

*We walked down the tunnel. It was dark and damp, with noises that would unsettle most.*

To

*We walked down the dark, damp tunnel that was echoing with unsettling noises.*

For example. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-11 01:43:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Your favorite James Bond incarnation. Who is it? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-11 01:42:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Nick, is that you?! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-10 20:12:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm skeptical about a couple of these, mostly "Days of '88." I'll still give everything a fair shot though. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-09 04:01:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Leave him for me. It's the only solution. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-08 23:47:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Borrasca.

Always Borrasca. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Health Anxiety Triggers </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-08 20:03:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I want to talk about what sets us off, worrying we're going to pass out and die right on the spot. 

For me, it's basically any abnormalities. Today, however, I entered my password wrong twice at work and had a panic attack because I thought my confusion was me having a small stroke. 100% irrational, but here I am sitting in the bathroom creating this thread.

So, what irrational things like the spark for you guys and gals? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-08 15:50:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I must have misunderstood the OP's question. That's way more reasonable. Although I will stick with the fact that anyone I write who is fucked up will be equally fucked up regardless of sexual orientation. 

Also, TIL. I'm admittedly not up-to-date on all of the specifics of LBGTQ, so thanks for teaching me something! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-08 15:47:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> All of mine...

*sighs* </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-08 01:25:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> ...nah. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-08 01:16:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> First off, I appreciate how you're handling this thread. I definitely thought you were going to come across as unnecessarily hostile about the subject. Thank you for not :)

To answer your question, I tend to write a decent amount of stories based on people being disturbed. Paranormal just isn't my thing (for writing - fucking love ghost stuff). If I were to exclude anyone on the LBGTQ spectrum solely for being under it, why would I not exclude heterosexual people as well? I would essentially be labeling straight people as the only ones who can be mentally disturbed. That just isn't fair. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-07 21:04:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> ...nah. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-07 21:01:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> ...nah. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-06 03:44:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [I don't know why this is the only imgur gif I could find for this.](http://m.imgur.com/gallery/YOzEaoZ) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-06 02:59:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Don't really want to make it tough. I just wanna tell you that I had enough. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-06 02:55:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Oops! I'm not even sure how that happened. Nice catch! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-06 02:52:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It might sound crazy but it ain't no lie! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-06 02:47:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Never *want* to leave? Oh boy. They didn't tell you, did they? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-06 02:39:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Like the King said, future isn't necessarily believable. However, you *can* make it work depending on how you set the premise. If it were to be a dream that someone had, for example. Or a person under hypnosis. Fortune teller. Pensieve.

There's ways to work around the rules, just gotta be willing to explore a bit! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-06 02:34:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hmm...a grin that is far too wide? Perhaps with too many teeth...? I'm not familiar. Maybe /u/vainercupidOOC could help me out with that one.

In all seriousness though, tropes are hard to avoid. To be ~~ab~~original these days is almost impossible. Writing is essentially just taking a common trope and refreshing it with a new spin. Unfortunately, not every one can make it work and you'll tend to notice it a lot more because of that. When done well, you'd have no idea.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-06 02:22:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Congrats! I'll definitely be picking up a copy! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-05 15:50:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Having my heart broken too many times got me into all sorts of horrors. But there's a pill for everything these days! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-05 06:28:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> But I'm your favorite shitfuck, *right?* </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-05 06:28:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I don't because I'm not a dick. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-03 22:36:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'll kill you all, bathe in your blood, and cuddlefuck your organs. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-01 18:20:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I think /u/feyedharkonnen put it best when he said that writing works better than a shotgun.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-01 14:54:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It feels like a Nick Hexum Quintet song played by 311. I dig it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-31 17:19:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> /u/IrrationalFearsHost, I choose you! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-31 15:37:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You said "shit" thirteen times in five paragraphs. I'm not sure if I want to yell at you or shake your hand for that.

So, as for your question, you definitely should look into fleshing this out a bit. The claustrophobic aspect of being stuck in the sewer while his suit fills could use a lot more detail. Also, maybe some more backstory as to how or why he can change bodies when he dies. You can definitely add some strong paranormal elements to this with that. I won't suggest any more endings because I think cymoril hit that perfectly. You could possibly frame this from the get-go about how he hates his *current* life and wants a new one. Idk. This is good though! 

In short, you've got a strong skeleton that just needs some flesh and scary shit.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-30 22:31:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> But I need to keep my hand strength up so I can write! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-30 22:31:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-30 15:41:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Stan? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-30 14:06:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Sucking. I need to learn how to not. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-30 05:48:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm not talking to you. We're fighting. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-30 05:47:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I try! I'm by no means an expert editor or anything, but I like to think I can help people make a sufficient r/nosleep post! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-30 05:46:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> *Just* your writing?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-30 00:40:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Nah. The journey of discovery is what makes...ah fuck it. You win this one, Dick King. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Wait, there's a workshop for NoSleep writers?! </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-29 23:27:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Did you guys know this? Because I sure did. That's where I started. Go on. Check my post history. 

...

Good? Or did you get stuck on the r/ladybonersgw submissions?

Anywho. It's fallen behind. Like, a lot. After talking briefly (as in she never replied) to my favorite piece of poop, /u/poppy_moonray, I realized that I want to get back into editing and mentoring new writers for our community. So I'm going to go back there. If you're reading this and you need help or want advice, I'll be there. Within 24 hours guaranteed or your money back....or within a reasonable amount of time, at least.

If anyone wants to join me, I'll be waiting (balls deep in /u/decomprosed). </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-29 16:59:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Like, yes and no. Personally, I like reading stories told in that format. However, I can understand that they're overdone more than found footage horror movies. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
