<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject3775</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-10 03:08:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Pedro runs for class president. Doesn't get a single vote. Gets deported </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-09 17:25:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The story comes off as completely ridiculous, and it is. The thing is, if you look around the country, there are hundreds of "local" organizations and weird lawsuits that turn out to be funded by the likes of the Heartland institute and similar conservative PACS/think tanks. An example are "beach rights" and "fishing rights" groups who are opposed to things like public access to the water or the regulation of fishing stocks for the public/common good. In the case of Berkeley for example, why are inflamatory conservative speakers so keen on talking there? It's not like the local population is receptive. They are instead studied provocations. They want to go to Berkeley, because they know they can get a knee jerk reaction from the fringe left/anarchists which will make the whole leftist political movement look bad in the eyes of the right leaning base. I may be reading too much into this guys motivations, but if you read the article, all the witnesses say he seemed to be genuinely not offended, even on the point of the black santa. Now it has changed. Why? Does he  really expect a payout? Doubtful.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-09 17:17:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You're just mad about all those archaic features of the constitution. A modern democracy wouldn't have something as stupid as the electoral college.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-09 17:11:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If the hat fits, then wear it </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-09 16:42:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Half tongue in cheek. There is evidence of archaic human living in caves along the sea coast in South Africa ~200K BP, but the main thrust of my comment was part of the now discredited aquatic ape theory that we evolved from earlier primate/hominin ancestors that took up living in a coastal environment. According to theory, coastal living lead to both the loss of body hair and high protein seafood diet fueled the evolution of a larger brain </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-09 16:31:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This has the ring of something that has been promoted as deliberate provocation by a conservative group (a euphemism) to try to undermine the credibility of valid discrimination claims. It is on par with Milo Y or Ann Coulter scheduling to speak at historically left wing universities like UC Berkley and UC Davis --i.e. he doesn't really expect to win the lawsuit. What he wants is to inflame the radical fringe who will respond violently to the concept of a white man filing a discrimination complaint as a black man. The underlying intent is try to establish that african americans are a privileged, and un-deserving of that privilege, class (Not my opinion, just my analysis of the agenda behind these antics). 

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-09 03:06:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I thought it was because we were a coastal species eating high protein shellfish
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-09 03:05:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Wang Corporation when the founder insisted his son be name CEO </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-08 21:14:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So, most of your analysis appears to be based on a rocky planet model (no real surprise there), but the question itself appears to be driving toward another question: Is there plate tectonics underneath Europa or Ganymede's oceans? How would the presence of high pressure ice VI, VII, VIII, IX, etc between the liquid water and the rocky mantle affect the propensity for plate tectonics, especially with the lighter metals contributions expected for the rocky core </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-08 20:23:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Somebody with an evolutionary or other biology background, I'm interested in the concept that humans have fire as an energy source because we cook our food. Is this generally accepted in ecological models for food webs including humans? Is the energy input into cooking food part of the overall caloric content that drives human metabolism as compared to say other primates who don't cook their food?
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The energy expansions of evolution </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-08 17:05:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-05 02:38:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> As a teen, we used to jump off intracoastal waterway bridges, in those days, rail to water was about 55 feet. If you didn't hit just right, you were in serious pain. Some guys dislocated their shoulders simply from having their arm out from their side instead of flush against the body. Same for flat feet instead of pointed toes. This guy looks like he hit on his ass. He got a serious enema, and almost certainly was spouting shit and possibly blood out his ass from all the water that shot up his rectum </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-01 16:57:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I got that story from an astronomer who studies blackholes and gravitational waves. While you have one version of naked blackholes ejected from the merged galaxy, of the ones that have been found, several are near galaxies that still have their central blackhole, hence the "fanciful" story  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-01 16:41:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Long live the Sahara Sea!
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-01 15:55:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The scenario envisioned here is for a three way galaxy merger. When andromeda and the Milky Way merge in a few billion years, the two black holes will eventually end up orbiting each other in a shrinking spiral leading to merger. If in the meantime another galaxy collided with the merged galaxy, a third johnny come lately black hole would join the dance. However, with the head start, the first are like to merge before the third one gets tightly bound. If the third one is close enough when the first two merge, it might be similarly launched by the gravitation wave of the merger. One question might well be, are there any black holes from the galaxies already eaten and merged with the Milky Way still floating free and not yet descended into close orbit with our own supermassive black hole ? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-01 15:44:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Recent reports of methane bubbles rising to surface off the us pacific and Atlantic coasts suggest deep water temperatures may be rising enough to destabilize extensive methane clathrate deposits. The thinking is this could release a huge methane pulse into the atmosphere that would cause a huge jump in warming which destabilize more clathrate etc. How real is this threat? Is any part of your research focused on validating clathrate stability and out gazing volumes? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-29 18:27:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> there really was a project called "Dreamland" having to do with realtime control of USAF satellites. Always thought it was a pretty stupid name. Also always thought Archer team knew about the project </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-27 23:54:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Barney Miller, Brownies Episode! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-27 22:00:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Unlicensed body modifications like rooster combs and wattles; and reptilian scale skin/claws </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-27 20:06:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Even better, have the message on one of those changeable smart highway signs, linked to camera that reads license plates, looks up registered owner, and substitutes in the names of the drivers coming up to the sign </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-27 20:03:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Is there some kind of ordinance that says everyone must walk backwards in the park? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-26 14:37:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The line weights are another accurate portrayal of physics as the curved surface of the glass and different refractive index at the water glass and glass air interface causes a lensing effect, essentially making the glass a magnifying lens. Hence, the thicker line weight reflects the magnified view of the straw thickness as compared to the view of the same straw through the air </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-26 01:45:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hammers and vacuums, seems like there should be other service items but damned if I can think of any. Chocolate toilet brush maybe </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-25 16:14:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This is like police racism. As analog, to westerners, all asians are just asians;  but in each of the different asian countries there is a tendency to have a view of the relative superiority/inferiority of each different country.  Police have a similar view. City police may look down on the wildlife enforcement rangers, but in the end; they both of the power of arrest and authority to use force without legal repercussions if their use of force is considered within policy. When it isn't, it is rare for the repercussions to be anything other than "they need to obtain training to understand when it's not ok to beat/shoot/kill someone".  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-24 16:09:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> There are an awful lot of men that still appear to be on the forward section of the hull as it explodes. I would say you see quite a number of them actually killed in this clip. In addition, it appear you can see at least one, maybe several bodies that are throw high into the air and silhouetted against the explosion as they fall back into the sea.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-24 15:26:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Before I looked at the comments at all, I wondered whether the sunspots on the current sun would match. Not disappointed https://imgur.com/gallery/1ifZa </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Receding water stains looks like a topographic chart </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-24 02:50:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-24 02:45:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Bigus Dickus Undercover </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-21 19:48:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> As someone from the beach areas where the oil came ashore, I can tell you there are still oil sheens that appear out of the sands along the water line on occasions. Kids digging in the sand will hit a layer of discolored sand, 2-3 feet down and after sitting in the sun, there is a definite chemical smell from the sand. The spill residues are known to contain polycyclic aromatic hydrocarbons from both the crude oil and the spill dispersants used on it in great quantities. PAH compounds are known to cause cancer, especially when infants/young children are exposed to them. When those kids playing on the beach get cancer in 8-12 years from now, will those costs be added to the damage totals? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-21 14:05:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Numeraptor already includes the additional raptor found in the result, making poweraptor unnecessary  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-21 14:01:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Einstein's early work on relavity was inspired by his observations of rocks, bottles and cans thrown from moving train windows while commuting to and from his patent office job. This appears to suggest his greatest work was inspired by what were essentially pranks. Are there any other examples of works in physics that were discovered through mischievous activities? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-19 21:01:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Did you cut down that tree to recover it? (not judging, just looked like it wasn't going to be an easy climb) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-19 18:34:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> By combining such a large number of spectra.. found that diffuse hydrogen gas engulfs the entire galaxy, which would account for a large part of the galaxy's baryonic mass.  

Just prior to this abbreviated passage, the article discusses the missing mass problem and how it gave rise to the theory of dark matter. This passage appears to be suggesting a least a portion of galaxies' dark matter halos could simply be neutral hydrogen gas. However, it never quantifies "a large part of the galaxy's baryonic mass". Are there any theories that dark matter is simply neutral gas surrounding galaxies? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-19 16:50:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Gas Rock Lodging </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-19 15:04:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> FTFY: Bajan Lizard  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-19 02:47:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Total gonzo </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-13 20:33:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> From at least one frozen mammoth's stomach contents, they've found that mammoths ate a type of plant called a forb. Buttercup flowers are an example of a forb. From what I've read, they're not very common up in the tundra latitudes today. There are tree species such as osage orange and pawpaw whose fruit seems adapted to be eaten spread by large herbivore animals, ones that are absent in the ecosystem today. The relative rarity of these trees total suggests that they were part of an ecoweb that is now missing its keystone species. Perhaps the mammoth is that keystone species, and their restoration would bring changes to the tundra or boreal forests the way the restoration of wolves to yellowstone created major changes in the vegetation and landscape. Or, the mammoths could just die out again, because some other element of the overall ecoweb in which they lived is also extinct. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-13 20:03:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Do a 3-d surface chart where each chart is displaced in the Z-axis, like this 
https://www.mathworks.com/matlabcentral/mlc-downloads/downloads/submissions/24368/versions/4/screenshot.jpg   

or this  

https://i.stack.imgur.com/0pJEr.png </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-12 17:05:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That's no gecko, it's a [maserati lizard](http://www.carlogos.org/logo/Maserati-logo-black-1920x1080.png) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-12 17:03:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Clearly an japanese mythical creature that will be used to base a new pokemon type  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-12 16:58:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> FTFY: Widdershins   
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-11 20:36:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That was a very important text message </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-11 18:21:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Ah, caught by the poster on the file cabinet and the whiteboard on the wall behind </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-11 14:11:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Adding to the question - many media articles refer to the incident relative to United Airlines Contract of Carriage (CoC) Rule 25, which has instances where passengers may be denied boarding. However, the contract definitions section doesn't have any definition of boarding. Lacking a contract definition, it seems this term is subject to english interpretation. Hence my question - if he was already allowed onto the plane with a seat assignment, hasn't he already boarded and all rules for denying boarding are out the door? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> If the United Airlines passenger was already onboard the aircraft, why does the media and airline keep referring to their actions as "denied boarding"? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-11 14:08:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-10 22:11:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Think of the other opportunities. Hippo meat is supposed to be delicious. I've actually tried whale in iceland and thought it was interesting. Mammoth, giant ground sloth maybe even some dinosaurs. The variations could get really interesting. Mammoth McNuggets has a nice ring to it, , as long as you had Mulan szechuan sauce to dip it in.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-10 16:33:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> A co-worker from several years back had a hand that was similarly missing a finger, including all the bones in the hand associated with the finger. However, in his hand the missing finger appeared to be the ring finger rather than the pinky. The difference being, in this hand, the ring finger actually appears to be longer than the middle finger, and is completely parallel to the middle finger. In my friend's hand, the last finger was shorter and was angled out, like the pinky is on normal hand. That would also seem to be due to some terminating process in limb/finger growing process that appears to be missing in this case.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-10 14:54:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Object very strongly to the certainty in this posting title, even if the authors themselves claimed it. Ever since the Miller-Urey experiment, there have been competing theories for the origin of life energy sources. These have ranged from lighting in the Atmosphere envisioned by Miller-Urey, Sun's UV radiation and more recently the chemical energy from hydrogen sulfide in underwater "black smoker" hot springs. It is good to see new work in this area, but a more appropriate title would be "New Evidence for solar radiation energy source in life's origin"  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-08 02:09:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  suffered a minor wound to his lower body  

Shot his tiny little dick off

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-05 18:51:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Where is the center of gravity on empty Falcon 9 stages? I see these landing on drone ships and think of the heaving decks of ships I've been on in moderate seas. Winds too. The ships are described as "Drones", implying there isn't anyone on board, but I have to believe it would be really advisable for these rockets to be chained down to the deck before the ship heads back to port. Does SpaceX send somebody onboard to do so or is the ship completely autonomous?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-05 01:56:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That's what he said </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-04 22:25:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The tops of mountains on Venus appear much brighter in the Mariner 10 radar images of the planet. This effect was later determined to be due to a form of "snow": compounds of metals like lead are vaporized in the heat of the lower altitudes, but the mountain tops are cool enough to cause them condense on the rocks at the high summits.   

https://www.seeker.com/the-metallic-snow-capped-mountains-of-venus-1767586407.html </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-30 18:45:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I worked on sonar systems for the USN fast attack subs during the 1980s. At the time the sonars were being enhanced for operations under the polar ice cap. Narratives at the time talked about the need to navigate through huge 3D mazes of multi-year ice that intruded hundreds of feet underwater like giant underwater ice forests. How has the loss of so much multi-year ice in the arctic ocean affected the underwater ice environment? Do the under-ice geographies/topologies of the under-ice environment of the 1980' still exist to any extent? How has their reduction changed the underwater ecosystems? Are there species that depended on those environments for development?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-30 03:57:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I just read an article tonight about sand grains on titan behaving like dipping your cat in packing peanuts. This is too weird </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-28 18:52:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Reading the title and looking at the thumbnail, I was sure this was going to be a freaky scrotum tattoo 
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-27 21:41:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> My aunt has been doing genealogy research and discovered Calvin Coolidge was related - 2nd cousin to my great-great-grandmother or some super distant connection. Never the less, this revelation makes me exceedingly proud  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-27 20:03:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> For some reason, this gate kind of creeps me out. I get the impression of tortured frogs or strange, long legged little men </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-27 19:38:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Geez, isn't there anybody in their 50's on this thread. Three words: Colonscopy Preparation Moviprep. You drink that shit, don't get further than 10 feet from a toilet. It'll come out like a firehose, and keep coming until you'd swear you were shitting meals from the future.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-27 17:55:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Isn't the argument for fire and EMT workers to be issued guns one that basically extends to any government or government sanctioned job workers to be issued guns. If Fire/EMT get guns, why not, oh, let's say, the Comcast guy who comes to hook up your cable? Also all the assholes at the DMV who take their sweetass time hour and after hour issuing licenses, registration, etc. Seems like there are plenty of stressed people out there who have the potential to start shooting up the DMV. And what about those safety patrol kids who stop traffic so the other kids can cross the street. Shouldn't they have guns? You never know when some asshole parent, late for work while dropping off their own kid is going to try to run them down. I'll bet they'd feel a lot safer if they had a gun to blow away those parents. 

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-26 17:15:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It typically takes me 2-3 restarts to get the app to connect with the gps connected and the landscape filling in. First try usually gets baby blue screen with buddy window icon and pokeball blank/white </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-14 22:27:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So, I'll have to look at the article but wanted to point out this theory was supposedly disproved by another team that went around to the sites that original theory publishers claimed had sediments with meteor traces. They found the supposedly simultaneous metals rich layers at the sites were in fact far apart in age. https://www.sciencedaily.com/releases/2014/05/140513113605.htm  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-14 18:04:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah, and maybe a monkey will fly out of my ass </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-13 20:57:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Huh! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-10 21:27:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Fuck the giants </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-10 19:33:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What are the colors? Is there a standard color coding for classification of different subreddits that I should already be aware of? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-10 15:19:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> When asked if it's the policy of the Wilmington Police Department to instruct citizens that it is illegal to film traffic stops, Thompson said, "it is not.". 

This is the wrong question or at least a follow up should have been asked and gotten an answer on record: "was the officers' instruction to turn off the video a lawful order?".   

Police are given wide latitude for their actions after a civilian fails to obey a "lawful order". Whether something is or is not policy in the department, establishing that the order was not lawful would make all their subsequent actions subject to scrutiny for criminality </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-10 14:32:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Toad hat for scale, demonstrates size of dog </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-10 12:39:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Pilots have revenue goals.  
Not enough heavy drinkers onboard?  
Turn the heat down to drive blanket rentals! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-08 21:02:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If you ever read any of Edgar Rice Borough's "Pelucidor" novels, you'd want to believe in a hollow Earth too. Who wouldn't want to travel to land where beautiful women riding mammoth's are just waiting for you to come save them </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-07 21:32:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It is actually one of those scientific mysteries that no one completely knows the answer on --ie we don't really know what gives rise to Earth's magnetic field. Clearly rotation of the planet is a part of it, but it is not complete answer, since looky looky, Mercury has one and doesn't rotate.   

--Source, I'm paraphrasing a cocktail party conversation with a researcher who works on determining the physics giving rise to the Earth and other planet's magnetic fields  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-07 21:24:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This article/study? seems to be predicated solely on the longer rotation time of Mars. If you look at some of the evidence they're citing, it seems like they're forgetting about the actual causes of jetlage  

In mice, a misalignment between internal timekeeping cues and external cues creates a host of problems  

Except on Mars, the external cues --ie the low sun at sunrise and sunset -- will be aligned with a longer clock. Yeah, you'd be jetlagged if you kept to a clock running on Earth's 24 hour day. But if your clock was set to run synchronized with Mars' 24 hours + 37 minute day, the internal clock and the external cues will remain in synchronization </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-02 20:47:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Whoa, The_Donald still exists?   

Thank you Huffman for letting me block groups from r/all. So glad not to have to see the shit they boosted to the top with their bot voting.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-28 13:31:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Do you even know what hyperbole means?   

Sure, it's like a really fat tree..you know..girthy  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-28 01:33:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Read your post as "slave plantain".  

I wanted a banana for scale </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-26 16:03:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Recently watched a sea lion trying to slap a big fish on the surface while fighting off a flock of gulls trying to steal it. Right in the middle of the fight a bald eagle swooped in and stole the fish right out of the sea lion's mouth. Gull fleeing this scene makes me believe a similar situation was going on here </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-22 16:02:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Solar panels are not without environmental impact. They are essentially building roofs that are impervious surface area, increasing rain runoff and soil erosion

There is a dairy and turkey farm near my home which has covered its barns and created sunshade areas for the animals covered in solar panels. In another area, a private school with significant land holdings has fenced off several fields and turned them into solar farms. This same school operates an entertainment facility (ropes course) with still more property used for parking.  

The point here - setting good arable land aside for a solar farm is not a great use for the land. We have a huge amount of land that is already covered with structures or could have structures built on it that allows dual purpose use as solar farm as well as other use, --ie like building  shade covers for a parking lot that is also a solar panel farm, or building sunshades for animals on a farm.  Simply setting aside good land for use as a solar farm is not that much different from building a self storage facility. Yeah, you can make some money but you're not doing the best for the land or the environment 

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-22 01:29:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Cheese me up before you go go, ain't anyone gonna know know </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-21 18:45:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Liquid helium is required to induce ordinary superconductivity in the static magnetic field coils of the MRI. With the discovery of higher temperature superconductors a few years back there was work on building MRI magnetic coils using these materials and then cooling them with liquid nitrogen instead of liquid helium. My recollect of somewhat laymanized papers in the medical imaging press at the time was that the magnetic fields produced from high temperature superconductors were not as uniform as those produced from true superconducting coils. As a result, the prototype MRIs they were testing had to make software corrections to the images produced that reversed the effect of the non-uniformities in the static magnetic field. A lot of imaging professionals pooh poohed these machines saying a radiologist review the images from them would never be able to tell whether something in the image was a true anatomical feature or an artifact introduced into the images from the software corrections. Bottomline, the new devices didn't really catch on but it suggests if liquid helium did become increasingly scarce, there might be alternatives.  Regarding the statement that helium comes from natural gas production, until recently this was true, but only in the fields of north and west texas. In recent years a gas field elsewhere in the world, I think it was in China, was found to be a significant new source of helium, relieving concerns about a world wide shortage of helium as the texas fields became depleted.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-20 01:37:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> A neighbor believes eating corn is bad for you because it is "all full of genes". I think she probably means GMO corn will kill you, but at this point I'm afraid to ask her to explain  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-17 17:00:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If you ever took typing class, back when there still were typewriters, you would have typed page after page of that sentence </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-17 16:02:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Not a nanny cam per se but close enough. Worked with a guy who was a young techie. He'd installed one of the remote control home systems / Internet of Things when they were pretty much a new thing. He was newly married and his wife had moved into his house. We were on an installation assignment in California, often working late. He'd open up the remote control an look at his wife reading on the couch in the living room. Then he's start fucking with her, turning on and off different lights around the house. She looked scared and turned to look at the camera, flipped him off and screamed damn you! stop that shit or I'm moving out! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-16 21:07:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Smash bottles over someone's head.   

They're not knocked out and waking up just fine later. 
Most likely they're dead or permanently brain damaged.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-15 22:24:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Apparently you're unaware of the quote from the original article included in your comment. I quote your quote verbatum   
 
Hijacking to mention for those who don't know: It is misleading that the article states:
This week, the path toward **animal-free meat** grew slightly clearer in a paper published in the journal Nature. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-15 17:23:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Unstated in all of this is the arabic script symbol carved in his sidewall. What do you want to bet the real issue is that someone finds it profane? What is it by the way?   

--------EDIT---------  
Thanks to the suggestion from u/coffee_o

Help us r/Translator, you're our only hope!
Please look at photo in OP. 
what is the meaning of that mysterious symbol?  
-------EDIT-----------  
The mystery deepens. The cryptic symbol on his head is....   

The number 3!!!  
But what does it mean?  

Is it homage to Dale Earnhardt?  

Babe Ruth?  

Or is it perhaps, a crusader conspiracy to introduce the concept of the Trinity (babe of the matrix)?  

Why too, is this thread locked? Have the religious police grown suspicious of the uproar?



 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-15 13:54:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's the tucanator! I'll be back, for your fruit loops! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-15 13:50:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Your rocket, it's so....girthy  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-14 17:10:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The quote in your comments specifically referenced animal free meat. Sure, not your words, but for some reason you included it, hence my comment

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-14 16:12:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So, as the parent of a vegetarian child, at least a portion of the vegetarian community ain't buying the "animal-free" label. If you take cells from a live animal, culture them into meat and then offer it as food, sure no animals were killed, but it's still animal meat
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-14 16:00:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What are the effects of oxalic acid treatments (vaporized) on bees. Recently started using to treat my hive after massive population loss to varoa. First year worked great, 2nd year my hive is empty after the holidays, no dead bees, just empty. It's making me wonder if the oxalic acid made the hive somewhere the bees didn't want to be.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-13 16:56:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Clearly the crash and subsequent fire can ultimately be blamed on a piece of debris in the roadway that fell off the airliner that took off from the street shortly before Rocketship Tesla attempted its own takeoff
  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-07 20:46:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Amex was a charge card until sometime in the mid 1990s or early 2000's when they stopped being able to make the business model work compared the credit card.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-06 21:09:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So, in the UK "on grounds of diminished responsibility" is the legal equivalent of "innocent for reasons of insanity" in the USA? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-06 21:07:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  42 Wallaby Way, Sydney

According to google maps, there is no 42 Wallaby Way in Sydney. There are however, locations for 42 Wallaby Close, 42 Wallaby Trail, 42 Wallaby Circuit and 42 Wallaby Grove. All of Sydney, New South Wales, Oz </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-06 21:00:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I see you've played knifey spoony before </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-06 20:58:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Fannies, don't forget fannies, ya cunt
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-02 21:57:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Wait, wait ... isn't there a statement from the nope police union spokesman about how his completely legal actions have been misrepresented by a hostile liberal press and an out of control prosecutor? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-02 00:11:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The ice tea was gelatinous </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-02 00:01:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> On an island somewhere, a crowd of old sock men are living out their lives with wide mouth Tupperware containers who ran away from the wide-ass husband lids </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-30 07:00:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Landfills from the early to mid 20th century are already natural gas sources. In some locations this gas is actually trapped and gathered for use/consumption. Where it is exploited commercially, the gas well operator gets an depletion deduction on the income from the gas extraction, same as a natural gas well operator would. In other locations the gas may simply be gathered and flared off to prevent methane leakage into the atmosphere. If you've ever been to Caesar Chavez park on the Berkeley Marina waterfront and noticed the big metal pipe sticking out of the ground, that is the chimney for the gas flare. The park was built on an old landfill. Early in the morning you can see the heat shimmer from the exhaust gases coming out of the chimney  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-29 10:59:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I have a 1922 $10 bill I got in change at a sailing club frequented by a lot of older people. Where yours says "Will pay to the bearer Five Dollars", mine says "Redeemable in gold at any federal reserve bank". Now a days, 10 dollars in gold would be pretty hard see I think </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-28 17:20:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That morally straight Ken Starr, he sure maintained his strict moral standards when it came to football players. No stone left unturned  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-28 15:48:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The Japanese hayabusa probe was much much earlier than Rosetta. Their lander craft failed but the main spacecraft, never designed to land, was maneuvered to a touchdown and managed to get some dust into a closeable compartment that was returned to earth </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-28 04:26:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Life in the 1970s </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-27 18:51:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It is a nice bit data you've collected. However, I feel the imagery you've used with the statistics to be a bit misleading. Most of the early firsts were hard landings and did not successfully return any imaging of the surface. Showing surface images from later successful soft landings creates the impression these images  were from the original event  --e.g. Russian Mars 2 lander crashed, sent no images. Russian Mars 3 lander landed, sent one unrecognizable/garbled  [image](https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/4/46/Mars_3_Image.png)  before going silent. Picture shown appears to be from Spirit or Opportunity rover. First good/recognizable images returned from Mars came from USA [Viking Lander](http://sen.com/thumbs/1024x576/img/145424924071721454250396.jpg) in 1976. Similar objection to Russian Luna picture. Not clear what mission the picture is from, but suspect one of the Apollo missions. [First image returned from surface of the moon](https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/e/e9/Luna_9_moon_surface_image.gif) was from Russian Luna 9. All Venus surface images have come from Russian probes but like the moon probes, the first several crashed. [First images from Venus surface](http://mentallandscape.com/C_Venera09.jpg) were from Venera 9, from 1975, much later than the 1966 date of the Venera 2 1966 crash </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-26 17:56:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> An ingrown hair in my nose that tunneled completely through my nostril, turned into a pimple and came out on the outside of my nose when the pimple popped </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-26 17:44:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I was surprised The_Donald wasn't higher in the rankings than it was, but then remembered, they've developed their terminology for profane and insulting comments from cuck to libtard and snowflake. I wonder how sentiment analysis handles this community specific language development </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-25 17:28:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Looking at her photo, my gaydar says no one would be surprised that she is a lesbian. The issue here is the clinician identifying it as a medical condition with the clear implication that it has some relevance to actual health issues she might be experiencing.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-20 18:49:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The thing that I've noticed about these ads are that the wording has changed. They used to be MIT grads. Then it changed, they became "Boston grads". Now they're just math grads. I want to know if MIT and BU have been filing injunctions against everquote for brand dilution or false claims </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-19 21:50:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> 4 oz could still make a decent molotov cocktail </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-17 21:54:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> why would you assume that defines its death? Jupiter and the outer planets will still orbit. Maybe the heat in the outer solar system will enable new life to evolve on the moons of jupiter or saturn, assuming it hasn't done so already? And, when the red giant collapses down to a white dwarf, why would it be dead then? There will still be energy being radiated? When the white dwarf collapses into a cold cinder (neutron star? Not sure if the sun is going there or not?) Is the solar system dead if planets are still orbiting around the cold dim remnant? When we're talking solar systems, what defines death? Is it when all movement ceases or sometime sooner, when the last living cell in the solar system dies away? What about those water bears that were released into orbit and are floating, desiccated and cold, waiting for the water and warmth to revive them?   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Do countries allowing international flights to over fly their territory charge the airlines for passage? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-17 17:19:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-16 23:18:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Both parties indicate the incident occurred at the end of an angry " exchange. You don't give a "playful" poke to end an angry confrontation. It was done in anger and to demonstrate power. I'm sure the man sincerely believed he could get away with it. That was in fact the meaning of his comment about not having to be politically correct. It will be interesting to see how many more trumpistas who have felt empowered in this heated political season will need to learn that their actions really are against the law even if they don't agree with the law

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-16 19:10:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Seriously, what is that sensor?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-16 15:44:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'd definitely donate if I could get a T-shirt shipped to me </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-16 15:32:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Rosie Palm will work the recovery tent </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-16 15:29:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm definitely going to be working bortokal into my next fruit related conversation </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-16 15:08:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah, that was the point of the probe. There's not a lot about it and I think it was considered disappointing because of the failure to see some of the expected variations. They concluded later that the probe passed into one of the clear zones between major cloud zones and so did not encounter all of the different cloud layers they expected to get data on. They did record 330 mph winds blowing it sideways though, about 25% higher velocities than expected  

http://www2.jpl.nasa.gov/sl9/gll38.html
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-16 03:40:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> In most areas they swim up to heads of bayous where fresh water creeks empty into the salt. In the keys, those places are more brackish than fresh but is enough reduced in salt they can drink it </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-16 02:19:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Look up the probe the Galileo spacecraft dropped into Jupiter when it first arrived. It descended 97 miles below the cloud tops before being crushed by increasing pressure of the atmosphere </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
