<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject3642</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-10 03:55:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> When the fingers are tiny like they were when Dawn was a baby, you just need to break the skin and pop the bones at the joint. Surprisingly little force. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-10 00:08:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This administration continues to leave wreckage in its wake. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-09 23:21:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Because I loved her so much :) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Dawn </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-09 19:25:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Dawn </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-09 19:25:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Dawn is my little sister. When I was 11 and she was just a tiny baby, I hurt her really badly. I didnt know what I did was going to cause so much trouble. I just wanted to do something nice. Something that would make us happy. 

My parents made me go away for a long time. I didnt understand why everyone was so angry. I missed my sister terribly. Even worse, I felt betrayed by the people Id expected to understand me. 

After six years of hospitalization, I got to see her again. My parents had passed away in a car accident while I was gone and I went to live with my aunt and uncle. Both were psychologists. Both understood the problem I apparently had. Still, they believed Id learned to cope with it over the course of my rehabilitation. And they were right. I would never hurt anyone again. The mere thought of it was abhorrent.

Dawn had no memory of me. Under the watchful eyes of my aunt and uncle, I was reintroduced to her life and I got to discover the wonderful person shed become. She was even more perfect than Id remembered. As I stared at her, I wondered if I would have the same inclination to hurt her thatd gotten me in so much trouble six years ago. 

I studied her body: her small feet; her narrow shoulders; the way her thin arms terminated at her hands. God, her hands. But I didnt feel anything other than happiness. No, I wouldnt hurt Dawn. Not again. My aunt and uncle beamed when I kissed those little hands.

The first morning I was back, I woke up and went downstairs. My aunt was cleaning mud off the floor. Muddy footprints had covered the hallway and kitchen and had gone halfway up the stairs. Dawn, whod gotten up before me, was getting a stern talking-to. Despite her protestations and claims of innocence, my aunt was having none of it. Dawn wasnt to go outside before the rest of the house had gotten up. It was dangerous and, well, we could see it was messy. So no more. Dawn just looked sad. I didnt know what to say. I felt a little flicker of hope.

Over the next two weeks, those muddy footprints showed up three more times. The first two times Dawn was yelled at. The third time was met with a spanking. I cried out to my uncle and begged him not to hurt her. I said it wasnt her fault. In response, my uncle just carried Dawn to one of the footprints, put her foot next to it, and showed me. It was the exact same thing. My flicker of hope became a bonfire.

That night, I heard giggling outside the door to my bedroom. High-pitched, girlish giggles. My heart pounded in my chest. I closed my eyes and listened while I thought about tiny muddy footprints and my lips pressing against Dawns hands. Those silly, kissable little hands.

In the morning, Dawn was getting spanked again. There was more mud on the floor. This time there were handprints, too. While my uncle disciplined her, I began screaming at him those arent Dawns handprints! Look at them! Theyre not! Theyre not! In a haze of desperation and sadness about the unfair treatment of my sister, I burst out of the house and ran. 

I ran for what felt like hours; arms pumping, lungs burning, feet slapping the wet forest soil. Finally, I got to where I wanted to be: about a mile away from our old house - the house Id been taken from six years ago. Beneath the cluster of oak trees thatd grown even taller since the last time Id been shaded by them, were ten, gaping holes in the dirt. The bonfire of hope Id been stoking erupted into pyroclastic explosion of joy.

It had worked.

The forest blurred around me as I ran back to my aunt and uncles house. As I grew near, I thought I heard yelling. With each stride closing the distance, the yelling gave way to quiet. My last few steps were in silence.

I opened the backdoor and tried to take it all in. The beaten, mangled bodies of my aunt and uncle were in the corner of the kitchen. The floor was covered in mud and blood and decorated with countless footprints. Dawn was in the middle of the room, beaming. And the others were there, too.

When Dawn was born, I loved her so much it hurt. I wanted to be around her all the time. I would hover as my mom would bathe her and help as my dad would change her diapers. I refused to sleep in my own room. Even if she had to go for a checkup, Id beg my parents to let me go with them. I couldnt bear to have her out of my sight.

After a while, my parents had to have a talk with me. They felt my connection to my sister was unhealthy. They were happy that I cared for her so much, but they worried Id grown codependent. I wasnt allowed to be with her 24/7.

I was devastated.

One afternoon, when Mom was in the shower and Dad was at work, I was watching Dawn in her crib. She smiled and gurgled and waved her tiny hands at me. I kissed them. I kissed each little finger. Right then, I knew I could solve the problem of not seeing her as often as I wanted.

Dawn screamed as I bit off each of her perfect fingers. It didnt take long. I felt terrible as I did it, but I knew it would be worthwhile in the end. I ran as fast as I could into the forest and buried them. They were never found.

Six years later, as I stood in the kitchen of my deceased aunt and uncle, I studied Dawns young face. She seemed confused by what was going on, but she was happy to see me. A safe, familiar face. She reached out to hug me, her fingerless hands clutching my back. Everyone else smiled. Ten Dawns, seeded from her little fingers so many years ago, joined in the embrace. My plan had worked. It took six years of my life, but it was worth it in the end. I would never have to be away from my [sister again.](http://unsettlingstories.com)


 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-09 04:56:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Cut him some slack; Russian is his first language.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-09 04:10:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [Been there!](https://www.reddit.com/r/WTF/comments/2ziimu/i_guess_he_really_likes_ants/cpj8mcs/?context=3 st=j2gx5nsi sh=e220b901) :D </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-09 00:17:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Um that's my friend don't be mean </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-08 23:56:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> ;) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-08 23:55:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Haha it doesn't count sometimes like if it's drool or blood. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-08 23:54:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Um, everything. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-08 23:54:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I know lol </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-08 23:54:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Scenes from the life of ya girl MADISONNNN! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-08 23:54:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> My Storyyyyyy! aren't I pretty!! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-08 23:54:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Haha you can't pronounce it with only one tongue lol </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-08 23:53:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Lol Gaykev is still such an r-word tard it isn't even funny lmao </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-08 23:50:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> She's so brave and strong lol </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-08 23:44:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Lol death isn't the end. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-08 22:36:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Omg why are you sorry? Katniss has so much to look forward to! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-08 22:35:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I know right lol </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-08 22:21:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Um isn't it obvious Katniss grew next to my brain and the Hierophant is making her into new brains and lots of other great things. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-08 21:49:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> OMG I GET THAT REFERENCE </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-08 21:38:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> OMG we're going to do so so much! Especially now that Gaykev is going to be back and normalish. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-08 21:38:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Oh yeah haha I think Black God had one of those as a pet once. They're so cute! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-08 21:33:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Um what lol don't be racist. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-08 21:31:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I can't believe you've done this. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-08 21:31:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You know that's what I thought at first! But no, there's SO LITTLE pasta in my baby. She's all like worms and tentacles and stuff plus she's dead so there's that lol </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-08 21:16:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Haha nice just wait 5 years and I can show them to you lol. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-08 20:40:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Lol guys I'm really pretty if you upvote this you can see my boobs. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-08 20:36:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Haha I know right? The Hierophant is always full of surprises! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-08 20:19:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Haha you sound poor. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-08 19:58:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That's a good idea but I need there to be more Katniss left after the Fermentation. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-08 19:54:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Um it's perfect because it talks about how I was freaking out like oh my god Katniss are you okay but the Hierophant just said shes dead Madison and I was just like oh, okay but like shes still my baby and stuff and we can do things with her now that she isnt stuck to life anymore right and the Hierophant was like yeah thats what weve been waiting all this time for. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-08 19:51:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Omg right? It's so good and yes I tried it but it tasted so weird, like it was made out of a baby or something lol. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-08 19:50:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I never do that lol </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-08 19:48:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> OMG totally! I'm always the best in my class in English. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-08 19:48:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> STOP! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-08 19:46:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Haha I love smores code. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-08 19:41:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Testing is this thing on hahaha jk no offense. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-08 19:38:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm serious like why are you here and why do you get to be at the top? That's really unfair to all the people in here who are saying how good my story is. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-08 19:37:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's so quiet in here I bet people are like speechless. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-08 19:30:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> How to change a comment to make it look like someone else wrote it </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-08 19:30:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah you seem really nice and smart! I loved your story. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-08 19:26:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Um people should like this story more it's about me. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-08 19:21:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Can you, like, leave me alone unless you have fettuccine? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Guys I think my baby just died lol </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-08 19:14:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Guys I think my baby just died lol </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-08 19:13:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> HI GUYS ITS YA GIRL MADISON! AND GUESS WHAT?! I HAD MY BABYYYYYYYY! AND SHE DIIIIIIIIIED! Well, I think she did. Not really sure yet. Maybe you can help me!! (Probs not though because almost all of you are like r-word tarded haha)

So remember my [dumb sister Gina](https://www.reddit.com/r/nosleep/comments/4ho869/um_can_any_of_you_guys_tell_me_whats_wrong_with/?st=ivbamqdh sh=d65e3411) and then [my gross brother](https://www.reddit.com/r/nosleep/comments/5c2xzz/ok_now_my_brother_is_all_messed_up_and_gross_lol/?st=j2gdwat0 sh=d1bc1025) and my [sad story about not finding a boyfriend](https://www.reddit.com/r/nosleep/comments/5i4e1h/omg_guys_why_is_it_so_hard_to_find_a_boyfriend/?st=j2gdwond sh=bc301b6e) and then [learning Im not a virgin anymore](https://www.reddit.com/r/nosleep/comments/5myi34/haha_guys_my_parents_think_im_a_virgin_but_im/?st=ixqad0ed sh=2e1a5ff7) and then [why I was sad](https://www.reddit.com/r/nosleep/comments/5qiij8/guuuuuuuuuuuuuys_im_saaaaaaaaaaaaad/?st=j2gdxlgy sh=d74eddb8)? Wow thats a lot to know! But you should know it if you dont because Im like awesome lol. MADISON!

Yeeeeeeah so like I was having headaches and I mind-told Gaykev back at home and he was like uuuuuuuuuuuugggflflflflf so I regular-told the school nurse and she had me go home. Mom picked me up and then had to go back to work, so she left me there alone. Then, like, I started to bleed out my eyes lol it was hilarious kinda like I was crying blood but I wasnt crying because I was watching the nice black man on TV with all the funny answers to questions but yeahhhh blood! Out my eyes!

I thought it was a little weird if I do say so myself (I love saying if I do say so myself it makes me sound so sophisticated if I do say so myself lol) so I called the Hierophant and he came over like RIGHT AWAY and made it seem like a BIG DEAL. I dont see what the big deal was. I love Katniss but if she died it wouldnt be that big a deal I guess babies die all the time. Especially around me lololol shhhhhhh.

Annnnnywayyyyyyyy the Hierophant had me lie down and he said stuff like chanting about bodies in bodies and bodies of bodies and Black God and all that then everything got SUPER BLURRY I swear it was like Gaykev was drooling in my eyes again but he was chained up out back so I know it couldnt have been him but like it was still warm and drooly but like DROOLY ENERGY you know? I bet you know.

I felt a ton of pressure behind my eyes like Katniss was kicking again but then it started to itch a LOT and the Hierophant reached down and took his finger and like pushed my eye allllllllll the way to the side and it hurt a lot but then there was this sucking noise and with my other eye I saw him pulling something that looked like clumps of fettuccine out. Guys guys guys guys guys. I gotta tell you something: I LOVE FETTUCCINE.

So like you have to expect when I love something as much as I love fettuccine Im gonna talk about it when I see it so when the Hierophant was pulling out the fettuccine I kept telling him how much I love fettuccine and that fettucine is my favorite and asking him if hed share the fettuccine with Katniss while hes in there and whether or not he was interested in eating the fettuccine with me and can you believe it? He told me to be quiet! I was so super surprised because he never told me anything like that before and I was just trying to communicate - like communication is GOOD for people but no he thought his work was more important so he just kept pulling and pulling the stuff out.

I guess I went to sleep because when I woke up he was still there and still pulling and he was like Im almost done Madison and I was like good because I cant wait to eat fettuccine and then he finally said Madison that isnt fettuccine and I was like what are you talking about it looks like fettuccine and he said shh so I did but I still thought about fettuccine.

Like AN HOUR LATER he was all done and he let me sit up. On the floor near the couch was a big ol pile of stuff that looked a h*ck of a lot like fettuccine but I guess I could tell it wasnt even though I still wanted some. It was really clumpy and stringy and smelled pretty bad and I was like did Katniss make that and the Hierophant just said Madison that is Katniss.

GUYS I WAS SO SHOCKED. Like, Id expected a baby-baby. Not a weird wormy fettuccine baby. It took me a second and I stared at the Hierophant thinking he was making some kind of joke but he just kept chanting stuff over the pile of not-fettuccine and it hit me. Guys. IT WAS KATNISS! My little girl! 

Well I got off the couch and hugged the pile of Katniss fettuccine and it kinda like wriggled and sighed and right then I felt what all new moms must feel when they hold their baby for the first time, like oh my God.

So like we snuggled for a little while and Katniss crawled around in my hair and stuff and I tried to like stick my boob in her a couple times in case she was hungry but she didnt seem interested which was fine because like I thought it was weird to have my boob out in the living room lol. But yeah the Hierophant said one last then then Katniss STOPPED MOVING GUYS.

I was freaking out like oh my god Katniss are you okay but the Hierophant just said shes dead Madison and I was just like oh, okay but like shes still my baby and stuff and we can do things with her now that she isnt stuck to life anymore right and the Hierophant was like yeah thats what weve been waiting all this time for.

So AWESOME, right? I had my baby, my baby died, and now all the great stuff can finally start. The Hierophant is leading Gaykev into the living room and starting to stuff pieces of Katniss back into his dumb brainless head lol I love ya Gaykev and you know I think hes actually getting smarter as more Katniss gets stuffed in there?

Right before he left, the Hierophant chained Gaykev up again and took some Katniss and swallowed her. Bodies in bodies, he said to me as he left. Bodies of bodies!! I yelled back. Lol I dont know what any of it means but it sounds cool and I think a lot of fun stuff is gonna happen. I sure hope its fettuccine [if I do say so myself.](http://unsettlingstories.com)




 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-08 17:40:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> "subject3642" was the default name of my Night Elf rogue when I first started playing WoW about 10 years ago. Super creative. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-08 17:36:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Frasier mad lib?

Poppy (*verb, -ed*) the (*adjective*) (*noun*) of Niles while Maris watched, (*adverb*) (*verb, -ing*). </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-08 05:37:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Goodnight! :D </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-06 17:12:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The picture behind him. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> A Warning To Women With IUDs </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-05 19:27:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> A Warning To Women With IUDs </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-05 19:24:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Im a doctor working in Hong Kong. I dont want to cause any undue alarm, but after what Ive seen here, I think its important to say something. From what we can tell, contaminated IUDs, manufactured in India, have been shipped overseas. Most went to India and China, but a few thousand ended up in the US and Europe as well.

To begin with, these IUDs have a very high failure rate. They were cheaply manufactured and the copper core is easily fragmented. This means the devices effectiveness drops from above 99% to as low as 60%, depending on the level of damage.

For those who dont know, becoming pregnant while an IUD is still inserted is highly dangerous to both the fetus and the mother. If you believe youve become pregnant while implanted with an IUD, see your doctor immediately. Your life may be at stake.

Theres something else about these IUDs, too. Something I wouldnt have believed if I hadnt seen it with my own eyes.

A few nights ago, there were two pregnant women from the same village brought to the hospital. They were experiencing severe pain and bloating. The initial exams showed they had both been fitted with IUDs and were in their early first trimesters. What shocked us was what we saw on the sonograms.

The fetuses were dramatically larger than they should have been at the first trimester. They were also hideously deformed. It was hard to make out details, but the heads appeared to be hydrocephalic and the hands and legs were equally swollen. Further, they moved swiftly and abruptly, causing enormous pain for the poor mothers.

It took some time to get the medical records for both women, but when we did, it turned out they had the same type of IUDs. Someone on our team worked on contacting the manufacturer while the rest of us tended to the women.

One was worse off than the other. Shortly after being admitted, she began producing a foamy, yellow discharge that was quite noxious and corrosive both to her skin and the bedding. In normal circumstances, such complications would lead to an automatic D C, but considering the size of the fetus, a Cesarean was performed.

I was not on the team who performed the Cesarean, but I saw the aftermath. I heard it.

I still hear it.

The mother died during the procedure. It turned out the discharge was the amniotic fluid mixed the corrosive residue of the IUD as it decayed. In any other situation, this would have killed the fetus as well. But this is not an ordinary fetus.

Right now, as I type this, the second woman has been sedated. I think its for the best. When she began hearing the hideous, keening howls which as of this moment still echo throughout the hallways of this hospital, she realized immediately she had something similar inside her. She was stopped before she could throw herself down the stairs.

The deformed infant, which grows larger by the day inside the now-otherwise-vacant NICU, confounded every expert in both our hospital, as well as the specialists who have been brought in to see it. Confounded, that was, until today. 

Today we received information about the manufacturers of the IUDs. Then it all made terrible, terrible sense.

To the women who are reading this, if your IUD was manufactured between 2010 and 2016, seek help. If youve experienced an inordinate amount of bleeding immediately after the insertion of your IUD, seek help. If youve experienced any unusual discharge at any time following the insertion of your IUD, seek help. All these may be signs that you have one of the contaminated devices. The earliest ones are just beginning to break down. Its all starting.

After Lin got off the phone with someone who knew about the manufacturer, she told me what shed learned. All I could do was stare in disbelief.

The manufacturer of those IUDs was shut down late last year by the Indian government for environmental contamination. When their medical device business had slowed, they began accepting raw materials from unregulated, uninspected, and unlicensed sources. Sources that disposed of chemical waste. Sources that disposed of nuclear waste. Yes, you heard me right. 

These IUDs contain recycled heavy metals and nuclear isotopes. 

I can still hear the mutated fetus screaming with such intense power that I fear our windows will shatter. Even now, I see the belly of the other woman seething with something terrible inside. It wants to get out. And I know these arent the only two.

Please, if you feel you may have been affected, seek help. As I said, this is only[ just starting.](http://unsettlingstories.com) 


 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-04 21:30:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Jesus Christ that's funny  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Heather's Phases </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-04 19:26:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Heather's Phases </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-04 19:24:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> For as long as Id known Heather, she was into her beauty treatments. Manicures, pedicures, makeovers, all that stuff. I dont even know the words for half of them. Whatever they were, they helped her feel better. Shed always had body issues.

When we first started dating, I noticed she wore an inordinate amount of makeup. It wasnt really my thing, but hell, if it made her happy then who was I to judge? She wasnt a big fan of eating, either. Whenever we went out, shed get a salad or a small piece of chicken or fish. Never anything good like burgers or steaks. It was obvious she didnt want to put any weight on.

We dated for a few years, then I proposed. She said yes. Our wedding was gorgeous, and afterward, we settled into marital bliss.

For a while.

As Heather got older, she grew even more concerned about her appearance. She was 40 when I convinced her to see a therapist. I knew she was depressed; I hoped a professional would provide her with the help she needed. 

Heather saw him for a while, tried a couple medications, then gave it all up. She said nothing worked. That whole time, she barely ate and painted herself with all sorts of expensive products to try and regain the glow shed had when she was younger.

She began looking at alternative medicine online. Stuff on websites that were barely written in English, let alone containing coherent, informative sentences. The online beauty communities raved about certain treatments: some for hair, some for nails, some for skin, some for teeth. Heather ordered it all. And it was expensive. We felt the strain on our budget as she poured more and more of our savings into these products.

I was at a loss. I knew Heather was sick. Id spoken with her mom about it, but there wasnt much she was willing to do. Im pretty sure Heather got a lot of her body issues from her, anyway. All I could do was sit back and watch, even though I did everything I could to comfort her and assure her that she was beautiful.

She was truly beautiful. Of course shed grown older. We both had. Everyone does. But she still could turn heads, and did quite often. Still, she wasnt convinced. It wasnt enough.

One Sunday in April, Heather came to bed crying about the little pouch of fat on her belly. Old lady skin, she called it. I studied her stomach. There was indeed a small amount of fat there. But nothing abnormal. It was something pretty much all women have. Knowing I couldnt tell her otherwise, I just suggested that she use the cucumber skin-tightening lotion she liked so much and that maybe shed feel better in the morning. Heather took my suggestion as a tacit acknowledgement that she looked awful. She screamed and wept and left me in the bedroom.

It wasnt the first time such a scenario had happened. I let her go.

When I came downstairs in the morning, it looked like Heather had been on the computer all night. She was calm, though, which I took as a good sign. I kissed her good morning and went to make some breakfast. 

She joined me in the kitchen and we chatted and even laughed over coffee and cereal before I had to leave for work.

When I came home, Heather was still in a good mood. I asked her how her day had gone, and she told me shed spent it reading and cleaning the house. I looked around. The house really did look great.

We ate dinner and talked. She told me she had some new stuff coming in the mail. Stuff thatd be there the next day. I nodded and didnt ask what. I knew it had to be more makeup or lotion. It always was.

Sure enough, the next day, Heather received a package with some weird writing on it. Definitely not English. Not Chinese or Japanese, either. Maybe Thai? Arabic? Didnt really matter. Id checked the credit card account online and saw it was $150. I wasnt too happy.

After dinner and a movie, Heather took a shower and spent quite a while in the bathroom. She came out eventually, stark naked, and covered from head to toe in a sheen of oily film.

Another new moisturizer,? I asked.

Actually no, she replied. This is for weight loss.

I got worried. Heather was always taking diet pills and fat burners and all that crap, but Id never heard of a weight loss product that you smeared on yourself like a lotion.

Is it safe,? I wondered aloud.

Of course, Heather answered. I dont think theyd be selling it online if it wasnt.

I started to say something and stopped myself. There was no point. At least the stuff smelled good.

Days went by and Heather religiously slathered herself with the product every night. Whatever it was, it didnt seem to be doing her any harm. Her mood was good and it might have been my imagination, but her appetite had actually increased. She even split a rack of ribs with me one night. I gotta tell you, nothings sexier than a woman eating a rack of ribs.

When we got home that night, Heather performed her usual shower, shave, and slather ritual. It did look like shed lost weight. Not a lot - not an unhealthy amount - but still some. She still looked gorgeous. I noticed the lotion smelled different that night. I asked about it.

Its a three-phase product, Heather replied. You use the first one for a week, the second one for five days, and the third one for one night. I just started the second one.

Okay, I answered. I supposed I couldve asked more about it, but her mood had been so high for the last week that I didnt want to discourage her. Besides, I was scheduled to go on a business trip in the morning and wouldnt be back for six days. I had a lot on my mind.

The next day, I kissed Heather goodbye and headed to the airport. It was a long, turbulent flight to London, and once I texted Heather that Id arrived safely, I took a taxi to the hotel and slept for 12 hours. Next on the schedule was meeting after meeting after meeting. It sucked, to be honest. 

I skyped with Heather a few times while I was gone, and every time I did, it seemed like shed be eating something. One day it was a burger. Another time it was a bowl of fettucine alfredo. Later it was a bag of chips. All stuff she wouldve *never* gone for before starting that weight loss plan.

On the last day I was in London, as we skyped and Heather ate out of a Ben and Jerrys container, I asked how the weight loss was going.

Its amazing!, she squealed, and lifted her shirt. I was dumbfounded. It looked like shed lost 20 pounds since Id left. Heather was never fat, but she always carried a little extra weight around her middle. Nothing any doctor would consider excessive and something pretty much any guy would prefer, just to be able to hold onto. But it was all gone. 

Are you sure you want to go through with that third phase of the lotion?, I asked. You look amazing as it is.

A cloud of disappointment crossed Heathers face. Just one more day, she said. I want to see it through. Besides, Ive been so damn hungry lately that Im worried Ill balloon up if I stop. 

I didnt have anything to say to that. If Id been eating like she apparently had, I wouldve put on ten pounds in the first day or two.

We said our goodbyes and I went to sleep. 

I arrived back home very late the following night. Heather was asleep, so I undressed in the dark and crept into bed. I could smell the new lotion on her. 

About twenty minutes after Id passed out, I felt Heathers hands on me. Rubbing. Groping. Id been quite a while since wed had anything even *resembling* sex, so I was ready right away. We rolled around for a little while, the slipperiness of her lotion adding a delicious, frictionless element to the mix.

She pulled herself on top of me and I felt her biting my lips and neck and ears before she whispered, I need to taste you and crawled down the bed. The ravenousness shed exhibited on our skype chats was nothing compared to the voraciousness she showed in the following minutes. I was helpless to do anything other than run my hands over her slippery back and thighs, and I marvelled at how thin shed gotten since the last time Id felt her.

Before long, I knew I had to stop her, so I pulled her up and kissed her mouth. She rode me as I felt the smooth slickness of her back and chest and butt; so much oily wetness and heat and hunger - I couldnt help myself. I lost myself in the moment.

When I finally regained a semblance of wherewithal, Heather was still on top of me. Still riding. I knew shed orgasmed at least twice, but she wouldnt let up. I was starting to get uncomfortable. Her silhouette in the dark room was so much slighter than it had been over the years wed been together. She looked like a new person. She felt like a new person. 

As she ground against me and mewled with mindless pleasure, I stared at her shape. In the dark, I couldnt make out details. But gradually, a cloud that had been occluding the moon moved away and I could see more. Just enough to realize something was very, very wrong.

I wrenched my arm backward and slapped the light switch near the nightstand. I screamed.

Heather still sat on top of me, grinding back and forth. Her skin was bright red and streaked with veins. 

No. It wasnt her skin. It was what had been behind her skin. The flesh was melting off her body. We were in a pool of it; greasy and pink and so terribly warm. Heather was sucking her thumb as she writhed against me, and I watched in horror as she pulled her finger from her mouth, peeled back the thumbnail, and dragged her front teeth across the meat on its underside. 

Im so hungry, she gasped. It feels so good to eat again.

Heather, stop!, I shouted, and went to push her off.

My hand passed right through the meat of her shoulder and I felt the bones dislocate. Rather than scream with pain, Heather groaned with hideous pleasure. She took her free hand and pinched her left nipple. It came off between her thumb and forefinger.

Panic overtook my desire to save my wife. I bucked my hips to get Heather away from me. It worked. I was able to get off the bed. Heather fell forward. As I scrambled for the phone to call 911, she turned on her side toward me. She was bleeding badly from her thighs; my push appeared to have caused major damage.

The dispatcher answered and I babbled while Heather studied me, her eyelids drooping before falling onto the bed like fleshy moths wings.

The 911 operator was saying something, but I couldnt hear what it was. Heather was talking to me. Her voice was weak.

Did...did I do a bad job Max? Do you not want me anymore? Am I ugl --

The word was cut off when her lower jaw fell from her face. Her tongue lolled before also dropping onto the sheets. Her eyes darted back and forth a few times, and then she was still.

I stared at the remains of Heather on our bed. Sirens pulsed in the distance. 

Youre not ugly, sweetheart, I whispered to her, tears cascading down my cheeks. Youll never be [ugly to me.](http://unsettlingstories.com) 











 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-04 00:52:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thank you so much. I appreciate the heads up :) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-04 00:49:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Shit, did they get one of mine? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-03 23:37:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I named her Pezzie because she's like a little Pez dispenser. She's so cute omg. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-03 21:02:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> She's even sweeter :) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-03 20:48:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Omg thank you! She's so nice and hasn't cried once! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What To Expect When I'm Expecting </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-03 19:30:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What To Expect When I'm Expecting </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-03 19:24:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> As I sit here and hold my baby, I cant help but think back about how difficult my life was before she was in it. But things are so much better now. She was worth everything. Every little bit.

When youre expecting, the hardest part is the wait. You cant tell anyone for the first few months, just in case something terrible happens. Thats a lot to worry about, you know? After 12 weeks, you can break the news. In my case, though, I didnt. I was worried what people would think.

I wasnt married. I didnt have a job. I knew people would say that a baby would be irresponsible. But I wanted a baby. I needed one. The companionship would be so important - especially after Bobby left. The bastard.

A while earlier, I learned that the one friend I had, Katrina, was pregnant. She was overjoyed and glowing. Her life was perfect; a husband, a house, a career. Why she wanted to be my friend didnt make much sense to me, but I guess having grown up together really meant something to her. She told me about her baby the day she found out. Bad luck if youre superstitious. She wasnt, though. I was so happy for her.

Days turned into weeks, weeks turned into months. Katrina was huge at eight months and wore clothing to show it off. I didnt want to show off anything. I wore baggy clothes and didnt like going out in public. I told a few family members Id be having a baby and the reaction was what Id feared: anger, disappointment, contempt. I never told Katrina. In fact, I made myself scarce. She hardly noticed. Must have been nice to have so much positivity in your life that you can forget your best friend.

I called Katrina a few weeks later and asked if she wanted to meet me for lunch. I was delighted when she told me she did. I prepared sandwiches and iced tea and waited for her to arrive. An hour later, she did. We sat and ate and talked about baby things. She told me shed just had a checkup and everything was going great. I expressed my happiness for her. And then, finally, did I let her in on my secret: I was going to have a baby of my own.

To say Katrina was surprised was an understatement. 

Oh my God, Julie, thats incredible! Our kids can grow up together and be best friends just like us! When are you due?

I grinned back and just said, any moment now.

A look of confusion flashed across Katrinas face, but her smile remained. But youre so tiny! How is that pos--

The smile was still there when I lunged.

A few minutes later, I was freeing my baby from where Katrina had kept her. She was so warm and perfect. In my excitement, Id sliced Katrina too deeply and my baby had a bad cut on her neck. It was fine as long as I kept a hand on the top of her head to stop her from looking up at the ceiling all the time. No worries. She was still there and she was mine. Finally mine. And even more beautiful than Id [expected.](http://unsettlingstories.com)

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-03 01:12:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Fast forward to three hours later and she's sitting on the toilet with her legs straight out and pulling the towel rack off the wall while trying to endure a post-Arby's shit. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-03 00:30:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> :D </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-02 21:42:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thanks! :D </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-02 18:40:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> My preciouses.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-02 04:39:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thanks, Ken M.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-01 23:39:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You're doing a great job! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-01 21:00:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> These just keep getting better. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-28 19:32:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Got explicit permission to repost after it was removed for a title issue, but thanks for complaining. I'm sure you're a very good hall monitor :) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-28 01:49:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> :) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> I'm sure this has nothing to do with anything. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-28 01:32:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-25 22:41:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> :D </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-24 19:47:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thank you! :D </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-24 19:27:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Guys we just had to evacuate the hospital for some reason. I don't know if Jerry's okay or not and the doctors or police won't say anything. I'll get back to you tomorrow. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Jerry's Mouth </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-24 18:12:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Jerry's Mouth </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-24 18:11:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> **April 2nd, 2017**
 
Either Im going to kill my husband for lying or whatevers growing in his mouth will do it for me. God only knows what that slut gave him on the night he didnt come home, but Ill be damned if Ill let him go to the doctor for it. The last thing our family needs is the nurses down at that clinic talking about how Jerrys been fucking around on me again. Ive got leftover penicillin from the infection he gave me two years ago. He can have that.

Listen, I know I sound cruel, but Jerrys on thin ice. Two weeks ago, he claimed he was coming home from the bar and all of a sudden he woke up in the woods 15 hours later. His truck was in a ditch on the side of the road. I called bullshit immediately. Heres what I know had to have happened: he was drunk, he picked up some chick at The Rooster, and they went into the woods to fuck. And now he caught something. Again.

Last time this happened - when he swore itd never happen again, mind you - it took a good long time for me to forgive him. He begged for another chance, so I gave it to him. But now Im fed up. Im not going to divorce him, but this is the last straw. He can sleep on the couch for the next 30 years for all I care.

And thats where hes been. On the couch.

Heres the issue: he does have something wrong with his mouth. That little slut he was with mustve given him something awful because the glands under his tongue are swollen pretty badly. He doesnt seem to be in much pain, but he slurs when he talks.

Im thinking I might cave and let him go to the clinic the next county over, but hes only been taking the penicillin for a few days. I think that stuff can take weeks to finally kick in, so hell have to suck it up. A little penance for thinking with his dick.

**April 6th, 2017**

Jerrys mouth is nasty. The swelling started to go down but the color under his tongue looks bad. Its bright red and the veins are really prominent. His breath could kill a horse, too. The guys at his job are making fun of him for catching something; he doesnt even try to defend himself about it anymore.

I almost feel bad for him when I hear all the tossing and turning on the couch while Im trying to sleep. Hes had some terrible nightmares since that night. Must be all the guilt. Well, he should feel guilty. God knows he wouldve given me what he got if I didnt realize hed been gone all night. He wouldve just rolled on top of me like everything was alright and wed both be in the same situation. No thank you!

**April 9th, 2017**

Something popped under Jerrys tongue overnight and theres yellow slime all over our pretty couch. He said hes very sorry and spent the morning trying to clean it off, but something tells me well be getting a new sofa before the year is out. 

The left side under his tongue isnt swollen anymore and Jerrys thinking about lancing the other side tonight, but now all he does is complain that the roof of his mouth is starting to hurt. I dont even want to think about what he did with that girl that night.

**April 10th, 2017**

I woke up to the sound of Jerry screaming. I ran downstairs and found him, stark naked, staring out the sliding glass doors that lead to the backyard. There was a terrible mess all over the floor and couch. The other area of swelling under his tongue mustve popped either by itself or with help from him, because there was that yellow stuff everywhere and it was mixed with blood. 

Ill admit, this was the first time I was actually worried about him. It wasnt the blood or the goo, but it was how he kept screaming even after I turned the light on and how he just stared out that door. To make matters worse, hed fingerpainted these things all over the glass. They looked like they could have been people, but the proportions were all off. I dont think Id ever been scared of a stick figure until right then.

I went over and unlocked the liquor cabinet and poured him a big drink. He took it from me and started to calm down after a few sips. It was the first drink I let him have since that night he didnt come home. I think he mustve had a beer or two after work in between now and then, but I havent seen him even buzzed. Hes been trying to be a good boy. Its gonna take more than that.
  
**April 12th, 2017**

I guess the penicillin did the job because the swelling in his mouth is all gone but he still says the roof hurts. Hes talking normally now and after that little scare last night, he slept like a baby. Good thing hes off work today - he got to sleep in.

We even watched a movie together after dinner. I could see his mouth moving as he poked his tongue around inside. Yuck.


**April 24th, 2017**  

Something really terrifying happened last night. Im trying to convince myself it was a nightmare but now Im here in the hospital waiting to hear whether or not my husband will be okay. I was sleeping and this super bright light started shining outside. Jerry started hollering right away and I jumped out of bed, but everything felt slow, like I was still asleep and trying to walk through deep water. Jerry screamed and screamed. As hard as I tried to move, everything took forever. By the time I got to the top of the stairs, I thought I saw shadows moving along the walls. Weird shapes and figures that reminded me of those things Jerry drew on the window that morning. None of it made sense.

Jerrys screams got drowned out by a loud, low humming that made the windows rattle. I got really dizzy and felt like I was going to fall, but when I tried to steady myself I realized I couldnt move at all. I was pinned in a standing position at the top of the steps. 

The low sound stopped and Jerrys shrieking filled my ears again. It sounded different this time. Muffled. The lights stopped and I regained control of my body. I stumbled down the stairs toward my husband, took one look at him, and called 911.

Ever since I arrived at the hospital with him, Ive been trembling. Whenever I blink, I still see it moving in his mouth. Writhing. Trying to get out.

[Will be continued.](http://unsettlingstories.com)







 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> BuzzFeed discovers truth. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-24 16:27:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-23 05:29:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thank you for remembering it :) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-23 05:11:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> He's far more handsome. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-22 01:23:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Here's a little number I like to call "[Soft Teeth](https://www.reddit.com/r/nosleep/comments/4gj0g4/soft_teeth/?st=izexzhwf sh=47df33e3)." </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-22 00:11:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> My uncle used to drag his feet across the carpet in slippers and give me a shock and then treat me with this method. It worked too because I *always* gasped. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-21 20:34:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Not sure, but it's pulsating and has little legs sticking out like one of my usual zits, so I'm pretty sure it's just that. :) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-21 18:44:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I've never wanted to feel thick, pulpy orange juice coat the back of my throat more than I do right now. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-21 18:31:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [Some might think I took this because a profile shot is more dramatic. I'm actually trying to hide a zit the size of a small breast on the other side of my face.](http://i.imgur.com/HEiBepo.jpg) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-21 18:28:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Whhhooooa, we're halfway there! Whhhhooooa, we have oranges that look like diiiicks! :D </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-21 00:16:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Man, you can't just copy and paste generic nonsense. You gotta write something that actually fits the content. Jeez. Kids these days. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-20 22:17:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Gneiss one.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-20 00:18:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Poor snek just wanted to get warm and got a tire bump instead :( </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-18 18:35:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Cross-platform fun, baby! :D </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Hanging out in the middle of Tumblr's "romance" tag. Again. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-18 18:09:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Hanging out in the middle of the "romance" tag. Again. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-18 18:05:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-18 02:31:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Today was ok. Tired af.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-17 03:27:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thank you   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-16 04:58:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Or the white stuff that fills the androids in my kind of movies. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-14 16:15:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> There wasn't a dry dick throughout the whole Potsdam Conference.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-13 02:57:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> 3 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-13 02:35:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I stared into the void and the void spasmed back. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-13 01:59:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I didn't know they were x-raying my mouth. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-13 01:40:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Another x-ray machine looking back at you. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-13 01:02:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hahahaha gotcha motherfucker :D </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-12 16:33:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Much appreciated! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-12 15:56:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thanks! :D </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-12 04:43:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> A couple, but I think they were joking.

I hope they were joking.

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-12 03:10:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Haha, thanks. Yes, I'd be surprised if this wasn't referencing [my story.](https://www.reddit.com/r/nosleep/comments/5iibin/its_hard_to_clean_blood_out_of_the_crotch_of_a/?st=j1ea42xt sh=63253d4c) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-11 20:35:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That looks so cool - I love that cover.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Shadows on the Wall </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-11 16:21:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Shadows on the Wall </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-11 16:21:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Growing up, I was convinced Id be abducted by aliens. I lived in constant, sleep-deprived fear as every strange shadow and every reflection of light on the wall signified the beginning of what I knew would be my end. 

Logic told me the shadows were just piles of dirty clothes or my coat rack; that the reflections were just from passing cars on the street below. But logic fails in the face of terror. If it werent for my older brother, Jason, with whom I shared the bedroom, there was a very real chance I wouldve lost my mind.

I remember my 13th birthday with the same detached sense of helpless violation as a victim of sexual assault. The day itself had been fine. Pleasant, even. My parents, who were always caring and supportive, did their best to make sure my birthday was enjoyable. They knew I was stressed. They knew I was anxious. Id never told them why, though. Only Jason knew, and he promised to keep it a secret.

After the festivities, I went up to my room to play video games. I had two hours to play before lights-out. Jason sat on his immaculately-made bed, which was in stark contrast to my messy one, and watched, offering pointers as I died over and over.

Two hours went by quickly, and Dad came in to say it was time to go to sleep. He sat next to Jason on the bed and let me know he was proud of me; how Id been brave despite having a hard time and that things would get better. He wished me a happy birthday and kissed me goodnight, switching off the light on his way out of the room.

For a little while, I felt pretty good. Like I said, I never told my parents exactly what had been bothering me. Theyd ask every so often, but they wouldnt pry. They could tell I was struggling. I heard them cleaning up downstairs, comforted by the fact they were still awake and alert. With a sense of security I hadnt felt in a long time, I drifted off to sleep.

After a couple hours, I woke up and glanced at the clock. 11:26. I closed my eyes again. Before I could drift off to sleep, though, I noticed something. The room smelled bad. It wasnt a scent I could identify in the slightest - it was heavy and medicinal, but organic, too. Strange. Alien.

My eyelids lifted to the sight something shuffling toward my bed. I tried to shout and bolt away, but nothing worked. No movement, no sound. Only my eyes could receive my commands, and they stared, bulging out of my skull, as thing stood over my supine body.

I knew itd finally come to me; this was the day Id anticipated and dreaded for years. I tried to make out the features on its face. All I could pick up on was hideousness. Deformity. A head with its upper-left quadrant missing. A mouth with no lower mandible and a shriveled tongue lolling down to its skinny neck.

Robbie, it gurgled.

It knew my name. It had been studying me and it knew my name.

No more me, Robbie. No more me. Time to grow up.

Its head came down and touched my forehead with the remains of its upper lip. As it tilted, maggots tumbled out of the cratered skull and landed on my face. They squirmed and tumbled onto my pillow. I felt them writhing against my ears and the sides of my neck.

Ill miss you.

It turned and walked toward Jasons bed. I tried over and over to scream as panic suffused the entirety of my being; the dark world around me blurred and I knew I was going to pass out. I knew I was going to fail my brother and not be able to warn him before the creature reached him. Before I lost consciousness - before I passed into a dreamless morass of black - I hated myself for being so useless. For being so weak.

My mothers shrill, panicked shriek catapulted me back into reality. The room was bright. It was morning. Mom stood over Jasons bed wailing and sobbing and I heard Dad thundering across the hall from their bedroom. He burst into the room and immediately saw what Mom did. I watched his knees tremble, as if he were about to fall.

I didnt move. Everything from the night was coming back and I knew - I was certain - Jason was dead. My big brother was gone. The certainty was overwhelming and searing tears of leaked down my cheeks onto the pillow. Something wriggled against my neck. I gasped and leapt to my feet.

Everything went slowly for the next few minutes.

I turned and saw the ring of maggots around my head print on the pillow. Dad was crossing the room to take me in his arms when he saw the bugs on my pillow and in my hair and whispered, oh my God. He picked me up. He hadnt done that in years.

I rode out of the room in his strong arms. Dont look at your brothers bed, he ordered. I couldnt help myself. I looked as we exited. One glance was all I needed.

Jasons body was on the bed. He was wearing a stained and dirt-encrusted blue suit. Oh no, I thought to myself, as I took in his injuries: the torn lower mandible. The caved-in skull. The desiccated, green-gray skin that was mostly gone.

Moms wracking sobs had escalated to hysterical screaming. As Dad and I rounded the corner and headed downstairs, we heard her shouting, how did you come back? Why are you here? Who did this?

Dad whispered in my ear as we walked. Its okay sweetheart. Its okay. We dont know who did it, but its going to be all right. Its not your brother anymore. Its just the body he doesnt need. Hes still in heaven, okay? Hes still in heaven.

I started to shake and Dads voice cracked with emotion as he spoke those last words. Hes in heaven. It sounded horribly, horribly familiar. I closed my eyes and saw a coffin. I saw my parents standing next to it, sobbing. I saw a large, framed picture of Jason and a room full of friends and family.

But I also saw the toys I was playing with. And I saw Jason sitting next to me. We played while everyone else cried. He grinned and said, Dont be upset, Robbie. Ill be here to help while you grow up. You dont have to feel sad.

My aunt, Lindsay, came up to me and stood in the exact same spot where Jason was sitting. I remember thinking it was strange she could do that, and then she knelt down and said, hes in heaven before walking back to my cousins and uncle. Jason winked at my confused face, then we kept playing with our toys.

Jason died, I whispered to Dad.

He nodded and I watched as he eyed the muddy footprints from the back door which led up the down the hall and up the stairs to my room.

You were probably too young to remember, but he loved you so, so much.

I thought back to all the fun wed had in our room over the years, all leading up to the video games on my 13th birthday the night before.

Youre the same age he was now, Dad said, and tears freely flowed down into his beard. Youre all grown up.

Something from the previous night buzzed in my ear. No more me, Robbie. No more me. Time to grow up.

And then it clicked. And my screams joined those of my mother in a [terrible, dissonant chorus.](http://unsettlingstories.com) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-11 16:21:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thank you! Good choices :) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-11 05:53:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This truly is my legacy. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-11 05:28:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> D O N G B O Y E </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-11 00:20:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I assure you, such great literature is effortless to me. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-11 00:15:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> :D </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-11 00:12:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Who the fuck do you think you are? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-11 00:11:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That's so true but then you can't have water balloon fights with the condoms after :( The neighborhood kids would be so disappointed. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-11 00:00:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Entomologist here!

Flies are known for their superior grip strength, which is why they're collected by less technologically-developed cultures in order to hold together surgical incisions and mechanical parts. The hard part is convincing them to stay that way because they're often anxious to get back to their families.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-10 23:16:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Happened to my cousin once. He was jerking off really hard and his buddy came over and was like hey can I help and my cousin was like hell yeah buddy let's do this. So they were jerking him off then all of a sudden he blew a load like a god damn howitzer and his buddy was like damn, that's nothing like breaking your arm when arm wrestling and my cousin was like don't touch me I'm not gay. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-10 21:46:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It wasn't like she was reading a novel. It was "novel reading"
 - she had a novel way of reading books that involved shoving 800 detached snail eyes into her vagina and then stuffing page after page of the book up there until the library caught her. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-10 19:51:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> *A salty delight.*

*Put your nose into my mouth.*

*Now blow, baby. Blow.* </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-10 16:36:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Suck my diiiiiiiiick I'm a buuuuuuuuus. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-09 00:09:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Been busy :( </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-08 05:27:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I love you too baby  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-08 04:24:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The very same! :D </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-08 01:18:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> And I'm just sitting here thinking about eating all their hair. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-08 00:28:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm telling you, you haven't gotten jerked off until you've had your hog tugged by someone with triphalangeal thumb syndrome. I knew this chick named Betsy who had hilarious thumbs like this; even if you were blindfolded, you would know right away if those were her hands on your cock.

She'd go up and down and it'd feel so good. I swear, it'd take all my concentration not to dump a load on those long-ass thumbs right away. But I'd keep my composure and she'd keep going - up and down and around and around. She'd spit, she'd change direction, and she'd even talk dirty. She was one filthy girl.

At the end of it all, when she was looking for a Dunkin Donuts napkin to wipe herself off, I'd make small talk. I'd talk about the weather, the stock market, and even politics. She didn't want to say much. She was always concerned about getting a ride home. Apparently it's really hard to hitchhike when people driving by think you're just pointing in the same direction they're going. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-08 00:11:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> No that's ball juice. I'm an expert. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-07 23:57:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I knew I liked you. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-07 23:53:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> My entry level taco eating begins at 3 tacos. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-07 23:25:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Fun fact: this was based on a train suicide I saw at the New Brunswick, NJ train station about 15 years ago! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-07 23:24:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I did some research; it looked a LOT like [one of these](https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=Ap8Ts6lv_k0) only way bigger. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The Incident at the Train Station </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-07 23:02:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The Incident at the Train Station </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-07 23:01:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Jan and I got there seconds after it happened. People were still shouting with surprise and dismay. The body lay in tatters on the tracks.

Oh God, Jan whispered. That poor man.

What happened? I asked the guy next to me.

Suicide, the guy said. He hopped off the platform right when the train was coming by.

Christ, I muttered. I wondered what our options were. Thered obviously be a delay while the police and paramedics attended to the scene. From the looks of it, Jan and I were going to be late for our friends wedding in New York that evening; people were already scooping up the remaining taxis to take to their destinations. It looked like wed be stuck there for a while.

There was a Dunkin Donuts on the platform and I suggested to Jan that we go in and wait until everything was cleaned up. She agreed.

I sipped coffee while Jan picked at a bagel without eating it. The police had just arrived. They draped the mans torso and head with a cloth, but his legs were still uncovered. They were about 10 and 15 feet from the torso, respectively. Whatever blood there was had been soaked up by the gravel between the tracks. Still, there were spatters on the platform and nearby structures, including the window of the Dunkin Donuts. An employee went out a couple minutes later and wiped it off.

I watched the cleanup on the tracks and Jan texted our other wedding-bound friends. She mumbled something about not being in the mood to see a bunch of happy people after having to look at a dead body. I wasnt paying much attention to her, though. I was staring at the cloth covering the dead mans torso.

It had moved.

At first, I thought it was just the wind. It wasnt. It obviously wasnt. Just one small location on the cloth was jutting upward and then pulling back. From the looks of it, no one else had noticed.

Then a cop did. 

Hey, he shouted to one of the guys from the coroners office, who was working on collecting one of the legs.

Jan, look at the cloth covering the guy, I instructed. She looked up.

The coroner glanced at the cop, who was pointing at the cloth. The coroner frowned.

The cloth jerked up hard and the coroner placed the leg back down on the tracks. I watched his mouth form the words, what the fuck?

He walked to the cloth and pulled it off. He was standing between me and the torso, but he backed away quickly after and I saw what he did. What the fuck?, I mimicked.

A thin, wiry thing was flopping back and forth out of a hole in the dead mans back. Someone who looked like a boss yelled to get away, and everyone on the tracks hopped back onto the platform. 

The thing flapped and writhed against the mans bloody back. Jan was pleading with me to leave, but I couldnt tear my eyes away. More and more of it poured out of the mans body. Three feet. Five feet. Ten. Twenty. It slapped against the tracks and gravel as if it were being electrocuted; more and more and more ejected itself from the corpse until it was free.

Two of the cops had their guns pointed at it, but their boss was yelling at them not to fire. A guy from Dunkin Donuts was recording the whole thing was his phone. Jan was green and huffing and puffing the way she does right when shes about to throw up.

The creature on the tracks looked like it was trying to move away from the body, but it almost seemed to be tangled up in itself. It writhed for another minute, then jerked three or four times, then lay still.

Tentatively, one of the cops approached it, gun drawn. The thing didnt move much. It twitched a little, but if my guess was any good, I wouldve said it was dead. The boss on the platform said something to the cop, who got closer. He kicked the worm. It flopped flaccidly against the tip of his shoe. In the glare of the setting sun, I watched a wet patch appear on his shoe. It might have just been the light, but i couldve sworn I saw that wet patch crawl up to his sock.

The coroner came over with a much bigger cloth, which he threw over the thing. Another order from the boss, then the cops began to clear everyone from the platform. We were asked to leave the Dunkin Donuts.

Jan pestered me to have an Uber bring us from New Brunswick to the wedding in New York, and $200 later, we were at the wedding. And that was that.

I didnt read anything about the creature on the tracks in the paper, although I did see something about the suicide. Just a normal guy named Juan Cordero, apparently. Nothing remarkable.

The one thing I did find remarkable, though, was what I read in the paper a few months later. Its why Im writing this in the first place. When I was going through the paper last week, I saw a story about a police officer whod committed suicide on the steps of the police station a couple days earlier. Apparently thered been a pretty big disturbance after, but the paper didnt give any details. 

I didnt recognize the cops name, but the picture was familiar. It was the same one whod kicked the worm thing and had gotten the stuff on his shoe. As for the disturbance after, I can only guess. But itd be a [pretty good guess.](http://unsettlingstories.com)
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-07 22:22:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I appreciate you. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-07 21:32:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I would literally suck a void's dick. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-07 21:26:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> "Gone wrong" is an incredibly offensive label for a gift like that. I'd make a tiny incision and suck the delicious fluid from that man's swollen scrotum and kiss him while it dribbles down the front of our shirts. Why don't you think about the joy other people experience from this sort of thing before calling it wrong? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> A Weekend of Red Clouds and Hazmat Suits </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-06 00:50:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Last weekend, we werent allowed to leave our home. Hazmat-suited men were everywhere and kept insisting it was for our own safety. They wouldnt give us a hint about what was going on.

Being right across the street, I stayed glued to my front window. It was fascinating at first. Then interesting. Then tedious. Still, I felt like I had to keep watching. There was something going on in there and I needed to know what. Nothing on television gave any indication something was wrong. Our cell phones had no service. It was as if the signals were being blocked.

Toward the end of the first day, Id started to feel a surprising amount of apprehension. My wife, too. It felt as if we were about to receive terrible news, despite not having any reason to.

Another hour passed as we moped around the front room, frequently glancing toward the window at the commotion across the street.

Around 8pm, the sound started. It was low but intense. We felt it in our stomachs and teeth. Everything in the house rattled. A portrait of Lucy and me on our wedding day fell off the wall, shattering the glass frame. Our dog, Pupper, yelped from his hiding place under the sofa.

Outside, hazmat-suited people poured from the neighbors house. They huddled behind the trucks parked alongside the property line and waited. 

The sound intensified. I could feel my teeth throbbing in their sockets and Pupper ran around in circles, barking and panicking. A vile smell filled the room. It had not been produced by any of us.

A red, miasmal cloud seeped from the doors and windows of the house across the street. I felt panic rising in my chest and instinctively brought my shirt up to cover my nose and mouth. My wife did the same. I picked up Pupper and carried him into the upstairs bathroom and placed him in the tub. It was his favorite place whenever he was scared, but I also hoped hed be safer. The house shook like it had been hit by a truck. More objets fell from walls and cabinets.

Back downstairs, Lucy yelled, you have to see this! I galloped down the steps and pressed my face against the window.

A massive crack had formed in my neighbors front yard. I couldnt tell how deep it was from where I was standing, but from the way the hazmat guys approached it, I got the impression it was very deep indeed.

Beside me, Lucy slumped over. Before any concern or alarm could register, everything went dark.

Hours passed without either of us seeing or feeling anything.

Lucy was the first to wake up and the sound of her throwing up roused me soon after. I felt okay before opening my eyes, but the moment I did I felt overwhelming nausea. My head spun. The room spun. Everything spun. I slammed my hands over my eyes and the dizziness went away.

Close your eyes, I yelled to Lucy. Upstairs, I heard Pupper retching and whimpering. 

Lucy sobbed and stumbled around blindly as I narrowed my eyes into slits and tried to see what lay behind the front window. There were shapes I recognized. The orange, hazmat-suited men walked around the crevasse and in and out of the neighbors house.

The red mist that had poured from the windows and doors appeared to have congealed and fallen on the lawn and bushes and street. The men walked through it with some difficulty, as if it were tacky. The smell was still there, but less powerful. 

All this was glimpsed through narrowed, bleary eyes. Nothing was sharp. Nothing was focused. Any attempt to properly resolve anything beyond the distance of my nose resulted in another bout of acute nausea. Behind my confusion - behind my churning stomach and roiling bowels - lurked a profound, primal fear. It was a feeling that there was something outside our home that didnt want to be seen. 

Pupper cried from the room above us and Lucy crawled on her hands and knees up the stairs to try to comfort him. Outside, I heard shouting. Without thinking, I widened my eyes and tried to look. An astonishing wave of sickness swept through me and I collapsed to the ground, cradling my knees to my chest, as my stomach contents drooled from my mouth.

The shouts became frantic, but I was too weak to move. Colors shimmered before my eyelid-cloaked eyes and I yelled to Lucy and Pupper to stay upstairs. Lucy said okay. The floor vibrated as men outside screamed. The nausea returned even with my eyes shut and I gasped at the ferocity of it. A hideous, droning buzz filled the air. Again, my consciousness left me.

When I woke up, it was still light out. I shouted up to Lucy, and she muttered something. I heard her and Pupper starting to move around in the bathroom. With a great deal of trepidation, I opened my eyes. Nothing happened. I felt fine.

I lifted myself to my feet and looked around. The house was a mess - it looked as if there had been an earthquake. Books and magazines and dishes and glasses were strewn everywhere. Cold air poured out of the broken front window.

I looked outside and didnt quite understand what I was seeing at first. The gash in the ground had closed and now resembled an ugly scar. But my neighbors house was gone. Simply gone. The street and yard were still covered in the unidentifiable, red substance.

Not a single person in a hazmat suit could be seen.

I checked my phone. For the first time all weekend, it had service. To my disbelief, it was already Monday. Whatever had happened on Sunday morning had knocked us out for 24 hours. I dialed 911. The operator told me, very pleasantly, that they had received calls from my neighbors and emergency services were on their way.

That part was true. The police, fire department, and ambulances arrived shortly after my call.

We were told on Tuesday that there had been a chemical spill. That a truck had taken a detour down our street and had, inexplicably, leaked. The substance reacted with something the house and exploded and thankfully Mr. Davidson wasnt home or else he would have been killed. I knew it was bullshit. All of us did. But we had no evidence to prove it was anything else.

The spill had been all but cleaned up by Wednesday. Lucy and I did our best to clean the house up and repair the damages. We still feel lingering effects of whatever had made us so sick. That smell still sits in the air as a reminder of what happened, whatever it was. We want to forget it all.

Its not easy, though.

Its not just the smell. Its the memories. Its the missing house. Its our poor Pupper, who hasnt been the same since. Its lots of things.

But most of all, its the people whove showed up at night. People Ive never seen before. People who, until theyre physically threatened with violence by one of the neighbors, wont get out of the road or lawn across the street. People who congregate in circles and chant and yelp in dim candlelight. People who spend the hours dragging their tongues across the areas thatd been covered in the [red slime](http://unsettlingstories.com).




 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-05 20:50:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So stories that were deleted under the old rules can be reposted now? Or will they be removed as reposts? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-05 03:25:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> My life would be complete. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-05 00:01:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [This one?](https://unsettlingstories.com/twentyyears/) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-04 23:07:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah I fucked that up. Wasn't paying attention. Too busy sucking spider dick. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-04 23:03:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thank you so much! :) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-04 22:31:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> 100% </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-04 22:06:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Much appreciated! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-04 21:08:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thanks so much! (They're all stories written by me.) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-04 21:05:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> :D </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-04 03:56:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> () </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-04 03:47:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thank you! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-04 03:46:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You have some audacity to claim spiders don't have dicks. What is it that I've been sucking? What is it that I've swallowed? You dare to say what I'm doing isn't real, yet I don't think I've seen a single scratch around your mouth made by legs twitching in excitement and pleasure.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-04 03:26:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yes 3 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-04 03:21:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [My PM box is ready to accept.](https://unsettlingstories.com/2016/09/15/licks-from-a-bear/) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-04 03:13:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [How about another one?](https://unsettlingstories.com/2016/12/05/trees-of-eyes/) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-04 03:11:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Have you ever even sucked a spider dick? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-04 03:11:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [Done.](https://unsettlingstories.com/newhampshirediary/) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-04 02:59:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You're right. I'll fix that. Thanks. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-04 02:02:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Excellent :) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-04 01:05:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> :D </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-04 00:20:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I think everyone knows by now that the easiest way to get a huntsman spider to stop coming in your house is to flip it over and suck its dick. 

Hear me out.

Carry a spatula around and when you see one, flip it onto its back. They're surprisingly docile once they're in that position. Then, all you need to do is gently press on its abdomen to retract its penis. It will be small; approximately the size of a thin pencil eraser. Use the tip of your tongue to manipulate it to full erection, then suck with your lips until it ejaculates; usually 30-45 minutes later. If you don't feel the rush of semen, you will know by its legs scratching playfully at your face when it gets oversensitive afterwards.

The main trick is not to swallow the spider semen. Trust me, I know it will be tempting. But no, pick up the spider and let him outside, then drool its ejaculate material near the entrances to your house. Spiders are highly promiscuous, and its semen mixed with your saliva will signal him to move on to another house. Spiders do NOT like to get their dick sucked by the same person twice. 
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-03 04:17:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> He's got outside in early April dick.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-30 18:48:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah, keeps the brain limber to fire out some smut at a moment's notice. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-30 18:21:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You know, I think I am :) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-30 17:19:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Lift it from its bed not only so you can hear the sexy "thfffft" sound but because clear liquid will come out that looks just like the alien drool. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-30 17:14:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Those ridges are the best! All you need to do is find someone to hook their top front teeth under one of the ridges and pull back! Just have them apply some pressure from the bottom with their tongue and the whooooole thing will just slough off, no problem. 

If you look right where the nail meets the toe, there's some discoloration. That's where the flavor pocket is hidden. After the nail's off, get them to suck the juice out of that pocket. If you're lucky and they're not super selfish, they'll kiss you while it's still in their mouth. There's really nothing like a sticky toenail juice kiss. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-30 14:09:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> :D </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-30 03:07:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Some have a left. It depends which hemisphere they're in. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-29 23:06:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You should respect their beautiful culture. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-29 21:03:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yep, doesn't bother me. I'm having fun :) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-29 21:01:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You guys are the best :) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-29 21:01:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> :D </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-29 20:56:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This was the second advertisement for the product. The first was poorly received, as it was just a picture of a frowning woman squatting over a bottle with the tagline "blast some bleach up ya cunt." </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-29 20:24:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So's my mouth. What. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-29 19:22:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Okay. I'm fucking pumped. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-29 18:43:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Oh, my apologies. It's from the British Museum of Natural History. Third floor on the left. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-29 18:42:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> OP did say it was warm. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-29 18:32:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Haven't you wanted to fuck a centenarian without her graham-cracker hips splintering every time you thrust? Now's your chance to get the next-best thing. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-29 18:31:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> No, but I appreciate his seminal work on epididymal blockages. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-29 18:06:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I was referring to the video clip linked by the OP. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-29 17:53:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I know a lot of people think this is a joke because it's fake, but there is a culture in South America that cultivates blemishes like this for certain culinary purposes.

One of the tricks is to keep the area well oiled; adolescents will collect their facial oils using specific, spongy leaves and then squeeze the oil into a communal jug. Nightly, that oil will be applied to the facial area of the person who will be contributing their blemish.

Once the blemish, usually a pimple or abscess, is grown, a village elder will perform a ceremonial squeezing onto a slab of maize bread. That bread will be consumed by pregnant women to, according to tribal lore, increase the likelihood of them birthing a male child.

If there aren't any pregnant women, the squeezing product will be distributed among the men of the tribe by the elder, who sucks the product from the blemish and drools it into the mouths of the virile tribesmen.

I love cultural anthropology.

*Edit: guys, just because it's a cultural practice you disagree with doesn't mean you have a right to downvote it. That's intolerance.* </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-28 19:28:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The only thing worse than that is how they used to cure it in the old days. Human saliva is remarkably potent as a disinfectant, so they'd have someone, usually someone from a lower class, drag his top teeth around the edges of the wound to collect whatever is growing there. 

From that point, the chosen person would keep what he collected in his mouth, milk his salivary glands, and mix together the pus and skin and saliva until a paste was formed. Once the consistency was right, he'd carefully drool the mix around the wound and allow it to sit and disinfect. 

They'd repeat the process between 12 and 30 times an hour until the wound was free of infection. I've gone to numerous hospitals to volunteer, since I know old remedies like leeches and stuff are coming back. They haven't been interested in my methods, though. They're never interested :( </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-28 17:36:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> "I'll trade you 12 roses for one salmon orchid." </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-28 16:17:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Poor snek :( </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-28 01:41:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I just beelined back to the top of the page to look while thinking "I don't care about dicks." Well color me surprised, I apparently do. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-27 19:24:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Everything about that family is just fucking cancer. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-27 16:01:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So instead of having a Squirtle up your asshole you've graduated to a full-blown Blastoise. I respect that. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-27 15:45:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I don't see why he wouldn't. I still have the same kinks that I had 16 years ago. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-27 15:39:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'll make sure it's nice and drooly for when you crawl in with me after dinner. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-27 15:36:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I still appreciate you for trying, Dad. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-27 15:19:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> "Bleeding back-passage?" Does this writer compose bad erotic fiction on the side? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-27 14:50:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> My buddy Schlomo used to let us drink it right from the tap. He'd just tilt his head to the left or to the right and we'd all lap it up as it came out. Nice guy. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-27 14:34:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That's absolutely incredible! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-27 04:30:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Bront.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-27 03:40:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm more of a [Burger Queen.](https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=SlTk0NzOF9s) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-27 03:39:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You're welcome :) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-27 02:40:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's definitely still going on. You will find any future updates on /r/subject3642 and [UnsettlingStories.com](http://unsettlingstories.co).  :) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-26 15:41:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Good grief.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-25 16:29:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> :) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-24 21:51:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hear, hear. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-24 21:43:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Couldn't even pass it with a Republican majority. What a complete, utter loser.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-24 19:57:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I've always wanted to suck one of those like it was a dick. Not in a dirty or inappropriate way, mind you. More like an act of love or compassion. I'd know I was doing a good job when those little feelers scraped against my tonsils, almost like they were begging me to go on. I'd run my hand over its length and stroke as my tongue worked up a sheen of saliva over its surface.

After a little while, I'd feel it start to squirm and twitch. It's mouth would open against the back of my throat and all the feelers would get vibrate really quickly, then stiffen, as if it were orgasming.

Of course, it wouldn't be, because it had just died from not being in the water for the length of the blowjob. But I still think, somewhere deep inside, it was happy that's how it all had to end. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-24 17:21:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> When he opens his mouth you can see SpongeBob watching TV. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
