<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject577</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-17 06:18:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Turn the apparatus completely over, the bottom is flat. Easy :) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-10 22:42:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Nope, she didn't edit it. You just totally misread it and/or are looking for a convenient "out" </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-10 22:41:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> No she didn't. There's no "*" </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-10 04:34:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Haha hahahaha the irony </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-09 14:00:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yes, but she's 20.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-08 20:31:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> /r/2meirl4meirl </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-08 20:24:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Again, reading comprehension. The start of the context is [here](https://www.reddit.com/r/SubredditDrama/comments/645phg/moderators_discover_that_reddit_is_brutal_when/dfzwvvi/), which is what /u/literallydontcaree didn't understand.

The part I don't get is why people seek **community on an online forum** in the first place.

Really, this isn't so hard. Either you can't comprehend what you've wrote, or you can't make your own thought process clear to others. Either way, the onus is on you, and I'm not going to hold your hand through your own thought process anymore. Good luck buddy! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-08 19:44:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The start of the context was you talking about subs generally, i.e. "The part I don't get is why people seek **community on an online forum** [general] in the first place." You don't get to jump context mid-conversation and then claim "oh, oh, the context!"

And no, you said explicitly, absolutely, definitely, exactly, precisely:

I don't get why anyone would seek community on something as silly as an online forum.

That's a direct quote. An exact quote. An explicit quote. I understand that your explicit quote was "general," because I have basic reading comprehension. You moved from your explicitly general quote to an explicitly explicit situation in an effort to avoid a_dissident_is_here's critique. I'm sorry if you can't comprehend what you've typed. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-08 19:18:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The sub isn't about a hobby

But other subs are. You explicitly said 

 I don't get why anyone would seek community on something as silly as an online forum.

/u/a_dissident_is_here was talking about subs *in general,* like you were in your previous comments. Backpedaling about "the sub" (SRD? NIM?) not being about a hobby doesn't negate his points, and still shows your lack of awareness. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-08 18:50:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> No no, not you. The OP </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-08 17:33:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> And then, of course, we'd be fine if you died </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-08 17:26:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The dude's hiding vote counts now, lol </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-08 17:22:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hahahahaha oh my God you're hiding vote counts now to obfuscate how hard you're getting fucked. 

Hahahaha </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-07 18:40:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That's fair.

The same Claudia Goldin you quote says in the article

Does that mean that women are receiving lower pay for equal work?  That is possibly the case in certain places, but by and large **its not that, its something else.**

Further down

Some of the best studies that we have of the gender pay gap, following individuals longitudinally, show that when they show up right out of college, or out of law school, or after they get their M.B.A.  all the studies that we have indicate that wages are pretty similar then. So if men were better bargainers, they would have been better right then. And it doesnt look as if theyre better bargainers to a degree that shows up as a very large number.  **But further down the pike in their lives, by 10-15 years out, we see very large differences in their pay**. But we also see large differences in where they are, in their job titles, and a lot of that occurs a year or two after a kid is born, and it occurs for women and not for men. **If anything, men tend to work somewhat harder.** And I know that there are many who have done many experiments on the fact that women dont necessarily like competition as much as men do  they value temporal flexibility, men value income growth  that there are various differences. But in terms of bargaining and competition it doesnt look like its showing up that much at the very beginning.

The woman will then begin to make  if shes the one who did this  she will make considerably less than the man.  And a lot of what we see  not all of it  but **a lot of what we see is this choice to go into occupations that have less expensive temporal flexibility, that allow individuals to do their work on their own time.**

Further, you say "the gender pay gap still persists even within the same indurstries."

But Goldin says 

So, the ones that have the smallest difference between male and female earnings with these corrections are the technology occupations and the science occupations and the health occupations where there is a small degree of self-employment  as is true today for, for example, pharmacists.

And that the largest differences are in "the corporate, the financial sectors, also law, and the health occupations in which there is a high fraction of ownership."

It's *really* simplistic to say that women earn 0.73 on the dollar to men. On the whole, it's true, but case-by-case it often is not. 

And when it is true, it is a self-inflicted choice *by the woman* to take the job with more flexible hours, less stress, etc.

What do you want in our legal system? The ability to force employers to pay the same amount to women even if they take the easier hours and do less work?

Secondly freakonomics is incredibly guilty of cherry picking their data

that is such a lazy reply. At least give me some references, don't just throw it out there with no context. Freakonomics here quotes **the same** person that you did from the nytimes. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-07 17:44:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I think you're being unnecessarily simplistic about the pay gap. 

http://freakonomics.com/podcast/the-true-story-of-the-gender-pay-gap-a-new-freakonomics-radio-podcast/

Re: men and control over the development of the foetus, that's the point. They have no control, and can't be expected to have control in the near future. They are at a strict disadvantage. Women have more privilege than men here.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-06 17:47:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If we got single payer, there would be no need for an insurer. 

What is your idea on how to handle people who simply cannot afford healthcare? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-31 03:40:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> There are more? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-20 13:12:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Oh, sure! I haven't gotten the fetters, you're right. Hadn't made that connection, thank you :) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-20 11:37:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I play Holy and I've gotten the lashers on Botanist.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-19 22:16:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Comment comment </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-12 18:44:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  There's amble raid-wide damage

Very small nitpick, it's "ample," not amble.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-12 16:11:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Me too thanks </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-12 13:10:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> http://i.imgur.com/iXCOOIf.jpg </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-12 12:59:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> http://i.imgur.com/EuIPBtY.jpg </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-11 19:44:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> T H A N K

H

A

N

K </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-11 16:10:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> T H I R S T Y B O Y

H

I

R

S

T

Y

B

O

Y  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-09 04:44:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Lol 15? That's awfully optimistic. Try five days.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-09 04:37:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> People still visit the chive? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-08 17:57:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Why does it matter? Could be any reason. Maybe she was that hairy, she seems to lack self introspection. Maybe her not-so-hairy legs were prickly. Maybe she missed a spot last time she shaved. Maybe he misinterpreted the feel of dry skin as "hairy". Maybe *gasp* his preferences changed. 

She's still definitely overreacting.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-08 17:25:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Everything s your choice. 

Why does the i on is have an accent? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-08 17:21:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Wow, you're going for a huge racist extreme?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-08 17:19:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's not the same. Long hair is not something deemed by society to be shameful and disgusting (for no rational reason). Men are not ridiculed for having long hair 

Seriously? What's the first thing people say to folks going job hunting, or meeting the SO's parents, or going to a wedding? Get a haircut. I work in one of the best hospitals in the world, I see *incredibly* few male doctors and nurses with long hair. Short hair is preferred and long hair is definitely stigmatized.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-08 17:14:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Why are you insisting that shaving is saved for special nights, as if it's some blanket rule that everyone follows? Are you telling people they "need" to not prefer shaved legs? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-08 17:12:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> "We've" set precedences? From this post, it sounds like her demanding that he only speak in a way that she approves of.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-08 17:11:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Maybe when he said "don't take this the wrong way," he knew that you could get "irrationally angry" and upset. You say other places that "we've" been working on "his" wording of certain things. 

I wonder what this same encounter would sound like from his side.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-08 17:05:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Wait, it's okay for her to say "need to brush your teeth"? What about "his body, his choice"?

Also, what about him shaving his face? Haircut? Trimming his nails? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-08 15:22:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Seeing as we're getting her side only, in the best possible light for her, I still don't think his words count like "policing." Was he angry? Insistent? Demanding? I don't think so, I bet it was more like if your breath stinks, and your SO says "you need to brush your teeth." It's a nudge, a suggestion, a request. Not policing.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-08 14:25:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Absolutely. Why do people feel the need to police what their SO says to such a huge degree? Nobody is perfect. My wife sleeps through her alarm, leaves the sponge in the sink, is too anxious and worried about some things, and doesn't put away her clothes. But she's still my wife and I love her to bits!

There's a huge amount of kneejerk overreaction in this whole thread. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-08 14:22:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Honestly, you policing so heavily what he says and how he says it, and *then* flying off the handle being "uncharacteristically furious" and "so angry" is a much bigger problem than him lacking a little tact.

You need to do some introspection. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-08 14:19:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You should just move on. Was it a "need to" like "You **need** to do this, otherwise..." or was it like you saying "Hey, bf, you look/smell/feel unkempt, you need to (get a haircut)/(shave your face)/(throw that shirt out)/(trim your nails)/(brush your teeth)/(etc)?"

I really doubt it's the former, since you've alluded to him being not perfectly tactful in the past.

You're overreacting, and after you're done complaining on /r/relationships, you need to move on. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-08 14:16:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You've never told your boyfriend "Hey, you're looking a little unkempt, you need to (get a haircut)/(shave your face)/(throw that shirt out)/(trim your nails)/(brush your teeth)?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-08 14:13:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Definitely overreacting. If it's been a few weeks since I've had a haircut, I look super shaggy and my neck is a mess. My wife will let me know, "Hey, you need to get a haircut."

Is it a commandment? Is she being a rude jerk? No! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-08 14:06:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Nothing negative? That sounds potentially really unhealthy, imo. It's almost like putting you on a pedestal and treating you like you can do no wrong. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-08 14:04:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> A lot of people use antiperspirant, so hair isn't as important.

Moreover, if you have less or no hair, you use *way less* deodorant, and it lasts a lot longer.

I'm a dude, and I shave my armpits. Highly recommend. It's not "fucking ignorance," ffs, it's a preference.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-07 21:12:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Like "enough" </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-01 19:15:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> "Obama set the tone for his presidency when he said "Republicans need to understand that elections have consequences. And I won."

He spent his first four years brow beating Republicans and passing the ACA. The Republicans never forgot that. 

Anything you see now is the Democrats getting a taste of their own medicine. "

and

"Which was in response to how the democrats treated us from 08'-'10. And it can go on and on. We need to mend bridges because those in power have an obligation to the entire nation not just their individual constituency, regardless of how things have been down in the past."

and

"In part, that's because the use of the filibuster has increased dramatically. Invocation of cloture was at a peak under Obama because use of the filibuster was at a peak by the GOP minority in the Senate in Obama's first term."

I mean, this is in just part of the top thread.

Republicans were asses to Obama for eight years. Astoundingly obstructionist, voting "no" on things they would have historically supported, trying everything they could to make him a 1-term (lol to that) President. The GOP is *so shocked* that the Democrats were rude to Trump. The incredible short-term memory being shown by **both** parties is just unbelievable.


And now, of course, you're trying to hide behind Biden's precedent! Do you even basely understand how your two points conflict?

"Being the bigger person is not to be so principled that you get taken advantage of in politics." </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-01 19:08:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Right, and I agree. 

However, the GOP is now seeing the consequences of trying to make Obama a "one-term President," including ridiculing him and trying to block almost literally everything Obama tried to do.

Are Democrats in the right here? Of course not. Were the Republicans in the right for the last 8 years? Of course not. But to suddenly be surprised, "Oh, no, the opposition party treats the President like garbage! How un-American! They should compromise!" is just absurd. Both parties know what they're doing. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-01 18:31:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I mean, you know we were talking about how the opposing party treats the President, right?

Or are you saying that by being completely obstructionist and passing few bills that the Democrats will control Congress and the presidency? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-01 18:24:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Are you telling me that you are incapable of seeing the hypocrisy shown by some conservatives in this thread? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-01 18:09:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Like conservatives, here in this thread, based on the last 8 years? Pot, meet kettle </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-01 16:15:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I would love that weakaura, I have a hard time keeping up with my judgements. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-22 22:29:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Gearing question:

I have 4 legendaries. Prydaz, Sephuz, Uther's Stride, and Aggramar's stride.

Since I can only pick two, which would be preferred? Right now I use Sephuz and and Prydaz, because I tend to abuse LoTM and the shield absorbs that.

I feel like I'm missing out on the Int gains from the other two, though. Thoughts? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-22 22:28:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Gearing question:

I have 4 legendaries. Prydaz, Sephuz, Uther's Stride, and Aggramar's stride.

Since I can only pick two, which would be preferred? Right now I use Sephuz and and Prydaz, because I tend to abuse LoTM and the shield absorbs that.

I feel like I'm missing out on the Int gains from the other two, though. Thoughts? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-13 20:54:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You're making the decision *for* him. 

You're married, you're a partnership, you're a team. You are one functioning unit.

You need to communicate, and make the decision **with** him. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-09 05:34:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> 668 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-02 02:55:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This is pretty fucking ironic, seeing as /r/T_D deletes submissions and block users that aren't lock-step with Trump. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-26 21:29:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Blood tests take about 2 minutes.

Huge simplification. Some assays are that short, others have multiple hour-long incubation periods. Or if we're talking micro, occasionally WEEKS to get answers. 

This is also ignoring the fact that reference labs can take a long time to get results back, due to backlog or only running the test once or twice a week.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-01 13:27:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Clavicles aren't shoulder blades, scapulas are.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-25 15:58:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hey there person who posts to a public page that anyone can reply to! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-25 15:49:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Then don't do it. This is not a difficult concept.

At the very least, fucking ask them. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-25 15:40:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> but your responses have been rude and I'd appreciate if you could be a bite more polite/respectful. 

I bet people you bite who don't like it or want it feel the same way. Grow up. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-25 15:40:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Mmm yeah, because they're my SO, and they've given me consent. It's not a hard concept. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-25 15:35:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> People break their SO's personal space for physical affection all the time.

**WITH CONSENT**. Fuck, BDSM and rape play is okay, WITH CONSENT. You're just going out and biting whoever the fuck you want.

and do my best to not do it again. 

When I was 14-15, I would tease my brother to the point of tears. Want to know the last time I teased him? When I was 15. Because it's the right thing to do. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-25 15:33:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Doesn't fucking matter. It's like when a young girl complains that a boy is teasing her or hitting her or something. "Oh, he just likes you and doesn't know how to show it!" Bullshit.

Do you bite your parents? Uncles? Grandparents? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-25 15:32:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Mmm, no, I mean all touching. I don't go around hugging other people, or patting them on the back, or "playfully punching them."

 I don't do it to be mean or hurtful, and have stopped

Is this a recent thing? Or

I may bite someone maybe once every two months </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
