<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject7316</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-03 20:18:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Arslan and Mark: Thanks for the great questions everyone! This was a fun discussion. 
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-03 20:16:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Arslan: Interesting hypothesis. There is some evidence that nose width increase has led to a decrease in the volume of the maxillary sinuses (Source: Butaric 2015 http://onlinelibrary.wiley.com/doi/10.1002/ar.23182/abstract). Whether this variation explains differences in risk of sinusities is unclear but worth pursuing! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-03 20:07:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Arslan: I don't think anyone has rigorously tested this but it is thought that people in warmer climates tend to be taller with longer limbs and people in colder climates tend to be stockier. The longer body and limbs tends to dissipate heat more effectively while the stockier bodies tend to keep heat in. This pattern is known as Allen's rule and is thought to be due to adaptation to temperature.
https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Allen%27s_rule </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-03 20:03:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Mark: Very true. Populations are the scale in which evolution happens and they often can show dramatic changes in 5,000 years or less. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-03 20:01:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Mark: This is true for persons whose ancestors from Northern Europe and some part of Africa. "most of us" if you are speaking for the human species are still lactose intolerant. The LCT gene is the gene that affects the persistence of lactase phenotype allowing some adult humans to metabolize milk sugar and several mutations have occurred in this gene all quite recently as you indicate.    </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-03 20:01:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Arslan: Interesting hypothesis. Not sure if someone has looked at this but I bet it would be difficult to test.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-03 19:58:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Arslan: This is an important question. There are two answers:

1. Studying human evolution and adaptation helps us understand how genetic disease arise, what genes are underlying their risk, and how the risk might be different for different people. This information could be helpful in narrowing down the cause of the symptoms of someone who walks into a clinic and perhaps even in treating them. 

2. Basic science is the raw material on which applied science, such as medicine progresses. Faraday used to perform 'magic tricks' with electricity before he knew that it would be essential to our way of living today.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-03 19:50:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Arslan: There are several papers out, which have identified several genes for nose shape. More are likely to be in the works. Some good examples:

1. http://journals.plos.org/plosgenetics/article?id=10.1371/journal.pgen.1002932

2. https://www.nature.com/articles/ncomms11616

3. http://journals.plos.org/plosone/article?id=10.1371/journal.pone.0176566

4. http://journals.plos.org/plosgenetics/article?id=10.1371/journal.pgen.1006149

5. http://journals.plos.org/plosgenetics/article?id=10.1371/journal.pgen.1004224 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-03 19:45:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Mark: Very few of these are currently known. Probably the biggest problem has been how to quantify a trait as complex as the face. Some good groups are working on this and we will know more in the near future. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-03 19:44:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Arslan: Humans don't have a lot of differences among groups even for traits such as skin pigmentation and facial shape, even though it 'seems' like there might be. Even the differences observed in these traits are an exception rather then the rule. They are likely different because they are exposed to the environment or are important for social interactions, both of which can be different in different geographic regions. Other traits are much less different between groups. So far there is not a lot of evidence supporting large differences in the brain among human groups.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-03 19:40:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Arslan: Good question. Actually, we believe nose shape is just like skin pigmentation in this respect. It is controlled by many genes and tends to 'average out' in kids of parents of different ancestries.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-03 19:38:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Mark: Granted darker skin protects from too much UVR. Lighter skin is also adaptive in facilitating the production of greater amounts of vitamin D. Sexual selection could move skin color in either direction. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-03 19:35:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Mark: Penn State! Good question. Clearly we are reshapping our genetics with our environmental technologies, and have been for hundreds of thousands of years. Clothes probably helped bring about loss of fur for example (more efficient sweating was very likely made possible only on losing fur as well). Environmental and medical technologies should be expected to slow the rate of ecological selection as a force shaping our evolution.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-03 19:35:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Arslan: Selection isn't just about killing off the 'less-fit'. It's about relative fitness. Suppose person A and person B lived up to the same age, but person A had way more kids who survived in future generations than person B. This would make person A more fit in the strict evolutionary sense, even though they both lived up to the same age
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-03 19:30:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Arslan: We did not look at this trait specifically so we don't know yet. :) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-03 19:29:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Mark: Thanks for your interest.
1) We don't have a clear way to compare sexual and ecological selection pressures. One reason we expect sexual selection has helped shape the nose, in addition to climate-driven ecological selection, is the high level of sex difference observed in nose traits. Sexual dimorphism is most easily explained as sexual selection.
2) Among the groups we studied, the South Asian and European populations were the most similar pair of similar to one another due mostly to a recent separation of the ancestral populations and migration (gene flow) since.
3) It would be very nice to study desert-adapted populations as well as cold-adapted and altitude-adapted groups. More to your question, I'd expect desert-adapted populations would be better served by noses that facilitate substantial convective humidification of inspired air.
4) I think these conclusions are pretty solid and the populations use represent a nice sample of human diversity. Clearly, there are many more human populations and these can and should be analyzed to better understand the forces shaping the nose as well as to help us identify the underlying genes affecting nose shape and how these genes have evolved.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-03 19:23:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Arslan: Human variation is continuous, which means we exist on a spectrum. Some have broad noses, some have narrow noses and some in between. We also observe the same trend on a genetic level. It is not possible to draw a line somewhere to separate people into disparate groups on any biological level just like there's no way to separate black and white on a grayscale. 
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-03 19:15:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Mark: We can also expect that sexual selection will have a stronger role in the future evolution of the human species than it has had in the past and stronger than ecological selection or genetic drift. Selection (either sexual or natural) can change frequencies and traits very quickly, on the order of 5,000 years.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-03 19:14:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Arslan: Some people have already answered this question in the replies. While there are some forces of evolution (e.g. selection), which can lead to predictable changes over time, many other forces, such as genetic drift which is quite powerful in humans, are very unpredictable. Depending on the relative strength of each of these, evolution can be quite unpredictable. Movement of people across the globe and genetic admixture makes this even more complicated.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-03 19:11:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Mark: "Populations" are groups of people who more often select mates within the group as opposed to from other groups. Some people use "race" to mean this, but it's a word that has too many meanings to use in terms of human genetic variation.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-03 19:08:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Mark: Good question. Admixed populations are what we call groups who show ancestry from populations that were separated until recent migration events brought them together again. These populations can be especially useful for studying the genetic and environmental factors that affect traits and disease risks that vary across the parental populations. A number of skin color genes have been identified using admixture mapping, the technical name for using this recent admixture to identify the location of genes affecting the population differences. We've only done one initial analysis of facial variation in admixed populations, which was also published in PLoS Genetics in 2014. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-03 19:06:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Arslan: First of all, great question. I understand what you mean but the term race is indeed complex and has little biological basis. It is helpful to use terms like genetic ancestry or simply ancestry. 

Yes, when performing this kind of study, taking into account the ancestry of the people under study is important. When looking at whether nose shape might have evolved because of climate-related selection pressures, we focused only on people whose ancestry was mostly from only one of the four populations: W. African, S. Asian, N. European, E. Asian. We did this because we wanted to restrict more signals of recent admixture (mixing of people with different ancestries), which can cloud older signals such as those of adaptation to climate. We determined the ancestry of individuals in our study based on their DNA sequence.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> PLOS Science Wednesday: Hi reddit, were Arslan and Mark and our PLOS Genetics study shows differences in human nose shape may have evolved due to local adaptation to climate  Ask Us Anything! </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-03 13:57:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hi Reddit,
 
My name is Arslan Zaidi and I am a postdoctoral scholar at Penn State University. My broad research interests revolve around studying the ultimate (evolutionary) and proximate (developmental) causes of human variation.
 
My name is Mark Shriver and I am a professor of Anthropology at Penn State University. I am interested in studying the evolution of complex traits such as skin pigmentation and facial shape in humans, and in identifying the genetic determinants of these complex phenotypes.
 
We recently published a paper titled [Investigating the Case of Human Nose Shape and Climate Adaptation]( http://journals.plos.org/plosgenetics/article?id=10.1371/journal.pgen.1006616 utm_source=reddit utm_medium=ama utm_campaign=reddit-ama-0503) in the March issue of [PLOS Genetics](http://journals.plos.org/plosgenetics). We were broadly interested in how and why facial shape has evolved in humans in our recent history and wanted to focus on one long-standing hypothesis: that differences in nose shape in humans have evolved due to adaptation to climate. We found support for two things: i) nostril width and nose width seem to be evolving faster across populations than expected under genetic drift alone (read: due to divergent selection), and ii) these differences may be driven, at least partly, by local adaptation to temperature and humidity
 
**We will be answering your questions at 1pm ET. Ask Us Anything!**
 
You can follow us on [@A_A_Zaidi](http://www.twitter.com/A_A_Zaidi) and [@alljustatoms](http://www.twitter.com/alljustatoms). You can also follow Arslans blog on [genewiz.wordpress.com](https://genewiz.wordpress.com/) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-26 20:29:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Steph: Absolutely. First of all, I often say that art and science are being kept apart against their will. This is reinforced by common neuromyths like "Left Brain/Right Brain" suggesting that creativity/art and logic/science are somehow independent. Aside from this being completely false from an evidence-perspective, the popularity of this idea speaks to how our culture categorizes different ways of knowing - which is a problem. This is where the STEAM (Science, Technology, Engineering, *Art*, and Mathematics) movement is trying to make a difference. In my experience with March for Science, STEAM has been an important emphasis. We had science illustrators, art installations, musicians, filmmakers, etc. at the SF March. Essentially, artists showing up for science. Though it may be idealistic, I think we should be shooting for a world where scientists feel compelled to show up for a March for Art as well, and I think incorporating STEAM into our messaging is a good starting point. P.s. today happens to be "Science Creates" Day in our Week of Action! Check it out: www.marchforscience.com

As to your second point about the impact of stereotype threat on children's interest in STEM, I think there are a lot of moving parts. First of all, we have to change the messaging and break the stereotypes. Unfortunately, a lot of this comes from pop culture. We have to make sure the people we cast and the characters that children see representing scientists are diverse and representative of the full population. Additionally, there is a lot of research suggesting that women and underrepresented minorities tend to show early interest in science but then drop off. To me, this says we have work to do to ensure that science as an institution is welcoming and listening to people of all backgrounds who may currently feel excluded, unheard, or unsupported. Science, as an institution, reflects the biases of society, so we have to be intentional about doing better. Everyone benefits from a rich pool of diverse scientists at the wheel. 

Most of that is my personal take, but I will say I feel like the March for Science takes these ideas seriously. In SF we worked extremely hard to be proactive about the voices and partners we shared our platform with and how we were using our influence. A common misconception is that these are peripheral - even "distracting" - issues, but they're not. They're core to making science something that truly is for everyone. And, perhaps indirectly, that's really the goal. That's how we get everyone to support science: we work towards a science that is serving everyone. These issues can't be solved passively, and I'm very proud of the choices SF made to support evidence-based policy, equity, and STEAM, with each building up rather than detracting from the other. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-26 20:29:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Valorie (DC): Thanks for participating in the AMA, Kal, and great q! This was, by far, the most challenging and inspiring thing, I've ever done. What started as a few independent conversations in social media platforms in January quickly grew into a global movement with hundreds of thousands of active supporters! Much of the organizing involved working together with lots of people across time zones, almost all of us total strangers with varying backgrounds and skillsets and day jobs and personal obligations to boot! It was a truly extraordinary feat to coordinate, and I tip my hat to everyone involved and all the people who organized/continue to organize grassroots campaigns! Now we are working in conjunction (partnering organization representatives, satellite organizers, and the feedback from marchers) to maintain and grow the global network and infrastructure to keep championing science for the common good. 

Selection on public statements and AMAs vary, depending on availability (as we have all been passion project volunteers!), relevancy (role in organization), and other factors. It has surely been a gargantuan and galvanizing experience being involved in this. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-26 20:07:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Steph: Absolutely - I get it. When I was in graduate school, I started an outreach program in our lab. We organized field trips for students to learn from my PI, tour the MRI, and get some selfies with real brains (which once led to me having to answer an 8 year old's question: "Was this in someone's head once? Are they OK? O_O).

It was a huge challenge and it's a problem that there is not well developed infrastructure to support these sorts of programs more broadly. Scientists need to do their part, but we also need to support liaisons who know how to run these sorts of programs. There are currently very few jobs for the "in-betweeners" as my old lab called me. 

The People's Science does have a science communication/training wing. We recently went to UC Davis, for example, where we spoke to a wonderful group of scientists called "Science Says" about these sorts of issues and best practices. 

I think training is helpful, but institutional support is just as important. Many researchers I've worked with over the years feel that doing outreach work is at lease somewhat at odds with their career plans; that the culture of science isn't currently conducive to prioritizing these efforts. We have to find a way to change that. I think that March for Science has a great opportunity here to scale and implement support programs in Satellite locations. My hope is that your local Satellite would have a program in place or work with a local partner organization that had such a program so that the role of the scientists is to show up, talk, listen, and do their part... rather than playing the part of the organizer. Then, educational organizations like The People's Science and ComSciCon and League of Extraordinary Scientists can all contribute to providing resources to fill in the educational gaps for such programs. It's going to have to be a team effort.

For resources and a selection of research articles on science communication and outreach more broadly, check out our ongoing list: www.shareyourscience.org. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-26 20:02:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Valorie (DC): That hour flew by! Thank you to everyone for submitting questions and comments, and I look forward to hearing from you again in the future. What the marches around the world demonstrated on April 22 was a historic moment. Now let's keep working together to make it a historic MOVEMENT. 

#KeepMarching,
Valorie </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-26 19:56:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Valorie (DC): Thanks for your question, Ludovico. I just want to assure you that nobody was hired to misrepresent the MFS mission, which I reiterate here: The March for Science champions robustly funded and publicly communicated science as a pillar of human freedom and prosperity. We unite as a diverse, nonpartisan group to call for science that upholds the common good and for political leaders and policy makers to enact evidence based policies in the public interest (https://www.marchforscience.com/mission/).

That being said, with hundreds of thousands of people participating in marches in over 600 locations on April 22, and the many more paying attention on traditional and social media, there are many, many voices about how science impacts diverse individuals and communities. These are important, ongoing conversations, and change begins from local to global. I urge people to stay engaged locally, to participate in our Week of Action (with many actions being globally applicable), and to stay involved in these crucial dialogues about how the science communities and general public can keep working together and listening to each other to champion and improve how science serves (or can better serve) us all. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-26 19:54:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Steph: Speaking from SF perspective specifically here. Yes, absolutely. I don't think I've ever learned so much about myself in such a short period of time. Every day was a new challenge. As a grassroots movement, we were defining our goals, defining our roles, developing partnerships, fundraising, and juggling tasks that I'd never heard of three months ago... all while trying to figure out how best to work with a team of people we'd never met before. We were pulled together and forward simply by our commitment to speak up for equitable evidence-based policy. 

Now that we have space to breathe and reflect, our next steps in SF are to identify what went well, what gaps there were in our knowledge and skills, and what structure/programs we need to move forward, including strategies for effectively communicating our core goals and messages. It was definitely a crash course in a lot of things that were never on my to-learn list, but I'm very excited to channel those lessons into long-term impact. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-26 19:46:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Valorie (DC): The MFS global movement demonstrated that science has no borders; the urgency and the desire to express solidarity in championing and improving the role of science in society went beyond the US borders. Of course, specific issues at each place and country were clear as well, and we can't deny the current sociopolitical climate in the US, and how that affects geopolitics. At the same time, we are strongly committed to being and remaining nonpartisan. After all, that's one of the core issues we marched for -- to keep partisan politics out of science. Acknowledging and voicing support and actively engaging to ensure that science continues to be a strong priority in our lives and societies absolutely delves into the political -- but does not and should not be partisan. That science helps us prolong and save lives, enables us to monitor for air and water and food quality, for improving national security, for giving us tools to build a better future -- those are not and should not be partisan, despite how much other people may want to paint them in that light. Science improves and can better improve all our lives, and all our communities. 

I understand your hesitancy in joining one of the Marches, but I urge you to reconsider involvement. The only way to be heard is to speak up. Have your voice join the voices around the world that proclaim: we champion science that serves the common good! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-26 19:41:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Steph: In many ways, this is *the* question. How do we make sure science is not branded as "belonging" to any given party so that it can be celebrated and utilized equally by all? I think it's a complex question with many possible answers, some of which March for Science can address directly and others that require a broader societal shift. I've heard many stories of conservative scientists feeling isolated by their peers, for example, so inclusivity has to start from within the culture of science itself. That's the long game. 

Speaking specifically from SF's perspective in the short-term, we have plans to produce stories that focus on a given socioscientific issue that's often presented as a partisan issue. We're currently developing a program that partners with groups that typically see the issue differently, telling the stories and backgrounds of both sides, and facilitating dialogue. We also hope to shed light on the stories of those who break the stereotype of the "typical" scientist, whether religiously, politically or otherwise. Our hope is that by respecting, featuring, and encouraging informed dialogue across perspectives or profiles, we can take one step closer to breaking down some of these perceived barriers. This won't play out the same way everywhere, so it's important that individual Satellites tailor their initiatives to their local communities.

Of course, no single program is going to fix these problems, but my hope is that this movement will have inspired enough efforts that, if coordinated, we're able to move in a better direction. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-26 19:35:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Valorie (DC): Thanks for your questions! April 22 was just the start. Now we #keepmarching for sustained, coordinated science advocacy! One of the first steps toward that is our Week of Action: https://satellites.marchforscience.com/, where we highlight daily themes, impacts, educational and advocacy components for participants to engage in and share! We will continue working on co-developed and original initiatives in the future, in collaboration with partnering organizations and the thousands of satellite organizers and marchers around the world. Throughout the past few months, we have been communicating with and listening to these groups, via email, phone, social media, and other platforms. Our mission and identity stays the same -- championing nonpartisan science for the common good. 

The success of any grassroots campaign like this one, and the OWS movement, can be measured in several ways. I don't think previous movements 'failed' so much as there are short- and long-term scales and goals at which to gauge success. The turnouts on April 22 with over 600 locations around the globe participating in solidarity to champion science and its role in society was a success. Moving forward, it will take more time to see how those efforts lead to concrete changes. But already, we are seeing so much local engagement happening with people initiating their own science clubs at schools, pledging to become more consistent voters, starting or joining science meet-ups and get-togethers (such as participating in the taste of science festival or Get Out the Science), hosting science teach-ins, and more. Truly, it is incredible. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-26 19:27:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Valorie (DC): Hi Firedrops, thanks for being a Boston organizer! Having urged my colleagues to organize the local Albuquerque one, I know how much work that entailed -- so thank you! Steph (SF) fielded a lot of your q here already. As she mentioned, we have been working to gather and synthesize feedback from all organizers, including global representatives, as well as from the hundreds of partnering organizations. What is clear is that many are remaining committed stakeholders, who want to keep working together to have a unified and coordinated science outreach and advocacy platform together. April 22 was just the beginning; now, the movement continues! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-26 19:18:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Valorie (DC): DC had tens of thousands attend, as many as 100k+ (although this was reported informally by production staff and not independently verified). I can solidly state it was more than the 10k reported in various media outlets :) Many satellite marches are still reporting crowd estimates, and we look forward to providing an overall # when we receive the data!

SF, LA, NYC, Chicago, Seattle had large turnouts as well! Equally amazing were the smaller but important turnouts in the middle of the country, abroad, and even under water (Wake Atoll divers!)! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-26 19:16:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Steph: Great question. Satellites were an incredible resource to one another throughout the planning process. There was a lot of resource sharing and collaborative problem solving that I think set the tone for what needs to happen next. If the goal is to build a unified network moving forward, it has to start with maintaining the lines of communication between Satellites and building effective bidirectional lines of communication between Satellites and national. 

The beginnings of this is in the works. A couple of weeks ago, Satellites were sent an overview of possible future plans and invited to provide feedback, both about what they think the organization should become and what role they think the Satellites should play within it. The next step is synthesizing and folding in that feedback as a post-March organizational structure is finalized. Our goal in soliciting feedback from as many groups as possible is to champion a collective vision that strikes the balance between supporting Satellites to make the decisions that best fit their local community and providing sufficient infrastructure for this to become a sustainable organization. 

On a personal note, I believe that it's the incredible network of Satellites that gives this movement a chance to have a serious impact - so a critical part of this process is taking the time to hear what they need to move forward. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-26 19:15:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Valorie (DC): Thank you so much! It was a joy to see the crowd in DC from the mainstage, despite the rain, and to see all the supporters and marchers on the street after the rally! We are definitely discussing this being an annual event and will know more after discussion with satellite organizers and partnering organizations. In the meantime, please continue to encourage engagement on our Week of Action: http://p2a.co/3BfL3J9, which features highlighted daily impact actions, a postcard initiative running all week for people to send support statements to representatives from global to local levels, and supplementary actions co-developed or originated by our partner organizations! NCSE also has a science teach-in toolkit publicly available as a helpful starting resource to hold informal science teach-ins anywhere any time! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-26 19:10:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Valorie (DC): I think what we witnessed on April 22 was hundreds of thousands of people around the world demonstrating their desire to have science and scientists play a more active role in improving and strengthening the role of science in society and policy. Many of the marchers are science enthusiasts and advocates, and marching together with people embedded in science communities displayed a commitment to working together to champion and improve how science serves all our communities. We heard the message loud and clear -- people want to see more scientists out there, and more scientists felt empowered to do that! 

Emphasizing the role that science plays to undergird our economies, to prolong and save lives, to ensure we have clean air and safe food and water, to bolster national defense -- that is nonpartisan no matter which way people cut it. Speaking to people's values -- what matters in day to day lives -- is crucial. The MFS movement is aspirational, not negative. After all, the brand of science is HOPE, and science enables us with the best tools to reduce inherent human biases, to address our modern problems, and to help us build the better futures we envision. We must keep working hard from local to global to not only relay this message, but to demonstrate it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-26 19:03:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Valorie (DC): The global March for Science movement kicked off with more than 600 marches around the world in celebration and defense of science in society and policy.  But those marches were just the beginning! Now, the real work begins. On Sunday, we rebooted our website to highlight a Week of Action that keeps building on the momentum from April 22 into sustained, coordinated science advocacy impacts: http://marchforscience.com/. We must #keepmarching to channel the energy and momentum from the march into a series of focused and connected actions demonstrating our support for science and science-based policy, and to communicate how science serves or can better serve our communities.  

In addition to the daily messages, impact actions, and education links, threading through the whole week is a postcard initiative, where we urge participants to send an e-postcard expressing support for science/March for Science/free inquiry/critical thinking/local issues. It kicked off yesterday http://p2a.co/3BfL3J9 with a letter to the President of the UN General Assembly and continues going from global to local representatives! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-26 18:59:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Sara K, PLOS official: Kristen was the MFS SF organizer. She had to pull out of the AMA due to a schedule conflict with her day job. Stephanie of the MFS SF team was already attending the AMA and will be representing MFS SF on Kristen's behalf.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-26 18:51:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hi everybody! I'm Valorie, one of the MFS Co-chairs. I'm just getting my coffee ready and looking forward to diving into the great q's and comments here in a few minutes! Thank you to Reddit and PLOS for coordinating and hosting this AMA!
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> PLOS Science Wednesday: Hi reddit, we're Kristen, Stephanie and Valorie. We organized the March for Science events in DC and San Francisco. We're taking your questions on what's coming next -- Ask Us Anything! </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-26 14:12:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Update: We just learned Kristen, MFSSF lead organizer, will not be joining this AMA. Stephanie will be representing MFSSF in this forum. 

Hi Reddit,

My name is Valorie Aquino, and I am a PhD Candidate in Anthropology at the University of New Mexico. My research reconstructs and compares original, high-resolution archaeological and paleoclimatological records to better understand the articulation of climate volatility and politics in the ancient Maya world. I am an organizer with the [March for Science DC](https://satellites.marchforscience.com/), where my role is Co-chair.
My name is Stephanie Fine Sasse and I am Co-Founder   Creative Director at [The People's Science](http://thepeoplesscience.org/#home). My work focuses on improving the relationship between science, society, and the individual through educational technology, informal learning, and interactive STEAM experiences. I am also an organizer with the March for Science SF, where my role is Chair of the Partners   Programming committees. I also supported the national team in their Week of Action and initial post-March development.


With over 600 satellite marches worldwide, there's no doubt that March for Science was an incredible moment. Now the question on everyone's mind is how we can turn that moment into a movement. That's no easy feat, but I can't tell you how excited I am that we have this chance to try.

You can follow us on Twitter: 

Stephanie [@thescientish](http://www.twitter.com/thescientish).

March for Science SF [@sciencemarchSF](https://twitter.com/ScienceMarchSF)

March for Science DC [@sciencemarchDC](https://twitter.com/ScienceMarchDC) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-19 20:03:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Author SM: id love to see your source for what you state above.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-19 20:02:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Author GP: we captured over 95%  of incoming freshman so this is certainly a representative study. Infractions occur on and off campus  and offenders are not routinely tested for alcohol or drugs, so it's hard to answer your second question </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-19 19:57:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Author GP:  we actually address that in the discussion section of the paper.  It's possible that users develop tolerance,  or that they  tried to adapt to cognitive effects of substances by taking easier courses,  or that they drop out of college. We think we eliminated the last possibility  but not the other two. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-19 19:55:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  author GP: this is an important question,, but  virtually everybody in our study was age 18 when we began  enrolling them, so no way to answer that in our sample </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-19 19:54:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Author GP:  if you can find us funding, we  would be more than happy to try to do that.. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-19 19:53:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Author GP: yes we studied both of those things using anxiety and depression questionnaires and  the MINI psychiatric diagnostic interview to address that </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-19 19:50:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Author GP :  we did  perform structural and functional MRI on a subsample  of our students  (450 at baseline) with two-year follow-up,  so we are examining that and have a few publications out already </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-19 19:47:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Author GP:  we followed our students over  multiple semesters for 24 months,and consumption patterns  were generally pretty steady </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-19 19:46:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Author GP: if you're anxious  at baseline, consumption is related to performance in an inverted  U-shaped curve </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-19 19:45:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Author GP:Not in our study sample.  The base rate of schizophrenia is only 1%, so we're underpowered to detect that in our subjects. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-19 19:44:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Author GP: we administered all subjects  extremely detailed neurocognitive measures (both paper and pencil and  computer-based), as well as personality assessments and measures of impulsivity  in multiple domains </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-19 19:42:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Author SM: Note we never make conclusions based on MJ alone all we can infer is that when MJ and alcohol are used together it could be detrimental for academic performance.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-19 19:42:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Author GP: we leafleted campus and made announcements and classes, and succeeded in getting over 95%  participation. The survey was thousands of questions in multiple domains, so it's hard to summarize  succinctly.
We rewarded subjects for participation by paying them small amounts of money, and entered subjects who responded promptly into a monthly raffle for e.g. iPad. When subjects didn't respond they received multiple  email reminders..  We also  tried to boost subject retention by sending subjects birthday cards and  later updates on  study data that would not alter their  responses. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-19 19:37:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Author GP:  yes that's an inherent problem with these sorts of self-report studies.. Short of  weighing the drug and assaying the amount of THC in each sample there's no way to have a truly  valid answer  to your question. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-19 19:36:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Author GP:there were too few of these subjects to do a meaningful follow-up on </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-19 19:32:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Author SM: I dont think this has been directly examined in humans but there have been animal studies that point to heavy binging being more detrimental to cognitive function compared to consistent regular drinking. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-19 19:31:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Author GP: useful question we made an attempt to look at this, as well as the inherent difficulty of particular courses,  and found it extremely difficult to come up with any standard measures for these. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-19 19:29:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Author GP: important question   I don't think students  willfully take tests/exams  when acutely intoxicated, but there will certainly be residual effects ( hangovers, cognitive fuzziness) that last a variable amount of time depending on use patterns </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-19 19:23:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Author GP:the freshman and the different substance use groups started with  non-different GPAs.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-19 19:19:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Author SM: there might be a variety of variables to consider that moderate causality, many of which have been discussed above. given that alcohol and marijuana have a direct impact on brain function and structure, we are working on methods to show direct moderating effects of brain physiology that mediates substance use and GPA.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-19 19:18:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Author GP: we summarized use patterns across each separate semester in order to characterize subjects </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-19 19:17:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Author GP: obviously it's unethical to choose a random group of subjects  and dose some with  variable amounts of alcohol and cannabis and others with placebo, but that doesn't mean a study that is not directly measuring cause  is not useful. Think about epidemiologic studies showing correlational relationships between cigarette smoking and lung cancer  as an example. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-19 19:15:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Author SM: No we did not but that would be an interesting thing to look at given that we already might have access that information. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-19 19:15:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Author GP:  Good point.  Most students "mature out" of heavy substance use  by the time they leave college; those who don't tend to be more likely to have later substance use problems.  We weren't funded to do a follow-up study, although we  would love to do  so, and  it's remarkably hard to keep in touch with  a large representative subsample of participants besides. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-19 19:13:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Author GP:  yes we  had explicit measures of anxiety, depression and overall psychiatric diagnosis </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-19 19:11:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Author GP:  we looked across the board, so if there were benefits on memory, brain function etc. we would've detected them </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-19 19:09:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Author SM: Please see my response to this question above </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-19 19:09:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Author GP: students who moderated substance use on average saw their GPAs start to climb again, so hang in there </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-19 19:04:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Author GP: yes,  we screened specifically for ADHD, levels of depressive and anxiety symptoms and traits as well as  using the MINI brief psychiatric screen </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-19 19:02:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Author SM: Possible given the recent changes with MJ regulations. However what i can say that our data was consistent with data that was captured and reported almost 15 years ago. Please see my above comment for the reference.

One thing i would note here as we did in the paper was that this was a convenience sampling of only two local colleges (although incoming students are selected nationwide). It could be entirely possible that if we did a more nationwide representative sampling we might be able to capture this key group thats missing in the current study. Having said that the data that we report here is very consistent with the harvard school study published in 2001 where 17000 students nationwide were ascertained and they found only .0003% of their sample to to consume marijuana alone with no alcohol.

http://www.alcoholpolicymd.com/pdf/williams_alcoholmjnov2001_final.pdf
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-19 18:59:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Author SM: Yes i agree this would be an important element as well. However from what i recall prior studies have shown (atleast with alcohol) that use is directly related to less time studying and more time socializing. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-19 18:54:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Author SM: One thing i would note here as we did in the paper was that this was a convenience sampling of only two local colleges (although incoming students are selected nationwide). It could be entirely possible that if we did a more nationwide representative sampling we might be able to capture this key group thats missing in the current study. 
Having said that the data that we report here is very consistent with the harvard school study published in 2001 where 17000 students nationwide were ascertained and they found only .0003% of their sample to to consume marijuana alone with no alcohol. 

http://www.alcoholpolicymd.com/pdf/williams_alcoholmjnov2001_final.pdf


 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-19 18:53:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Author GP: Thank you </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-19 18:52:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Author GP: Well, we might have predicted independent substance effects. But heavy drinking alone had almost no effect on grades </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-19 18:51:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Author GP: If they were there in our population, we would've found them. And yes, it was a surprise to us. I remember lots of people in the 60s and 70s who smoked marijuana and totally disdained alcohol use. As in  "I would never use alcohol.....  It's a drug". </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-19 18:45:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Author GP:  check out the Dunedin New Zealand epidemiologic study; their measures of subjects over multiple years  tried to answer those questions </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-19 18:44:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Author GP: Yes, we used to secure anonymized website, so subjects would have minimal reason to not report  truthfully </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-19 18:42:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Author GP: Connecticut is currently debating  legalization of recreational cannabis, so we may have a chance to examine that as you say. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-19 18:35:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Author GP- I think that's a sensible idea  for future study.  We have collaborators in Colorado, and have discussed doing something like that with them, so this may happen at some point. There's a lot of discussion among cannabis researchers about how to quantify the  "standard joint"  so hopefully consensus will come about soon.. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-19 18:31:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Author GP- we have detailed measures of personality and separately of impulsivity, so we can certainly look at that in more detail.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-19 18:27:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Study author GP. It's hard to obtain accurate estimates of how much time students are  actually spending studying outside of class.  Even if you know the actual amount of time, it's hard to correct for the amount of "study time" actually spent  on social media, spacing out or playing solitaire.. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-19 17:53:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Author GP:We looked very carefully across 2 demographically different  campuses and still found almost nobody who used cannabis heavily but did not also consume moderate to high amounts of alcohol. And as the paper makes clear we captured over 95% of possible subjects so, if the low alcohol/high marijuana subjects  actually existed  we would've found them. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-19 17:48:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Author GP: While it's easy to estimate quantity/frequency for alcohol because there are standard quantity units; with marijuana people buy different strengths of cannabis from different sources and inhale different hard-to-estimate amounts, in part because people share joints of different sizes/bongs/vaporizer bags so that  there is no "standard marijuana unit" that's equivalent to a standard alcoholic drink. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-19 17:42:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> substance use during the experiment was collected in the same way during the first two years of college  using a secure online site with a structured monthly survey; there was no equivalent way to estimate substance use in an analogous manner for our subjects prior to starting college there's too much retrospective  bias  and lack of validity. And after the 24 months of the survey was up, we did not  continue to follow subjects.. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-19 17:08:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Author SM: Unfortunately no, but i do 100% agree, this would have been a very interesting variable to capture and perhaps control for. In terms of this study being done in high school seniors, i wouldnt be very surprised if we saw a similar outcome as to what we see here. 

There was a recent report that showed both alcohol and MJ were associated with greater academic delinquencies and unpreparedness in middle-high school students

http://onlinelibrary.wiley.com/doi/10.1111/add.13442/abstract </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-19 16:48:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yes i do, but i feel that would be our best shot at attempting to answer this question post-hoc given the data at hand. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-19 16:10:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Author SM: Hello - Thanks for the question. What you say is absolutely possible, however as we explicitly indicate in our paper, the analysis that we did just wasn't geared towards examining any causality. We tried to somewhat alleviate effects of intermediate variables by controlling for baseline measured personality and emotional traits. However to properly investigate what you allude to requires a causal modelling analysis such as SEM etc. We plan on doing this in the near future at least on the baseline variables to see what the data shows us. Again this is just the tip of the iceberg, much more to come in the future years! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> PLOS Science Wednesday: Hi Reddit, were Shashwath and Godfrey and we assessed how the use of alcohol and marijuana impacted college students academic performance over the long-term  Ask Us Anything! </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-19 13:17:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hi Reddit,

My name is Shashwath Meda and I am a Senior Clinical Research Associate at Olin Neuropsychiatry, Hartford Hospital/Institute of Living. I am also joined by Dr. Godfrey Pearlson who is the Director of Olin Neuropsychiatry and a Professor of Psychiatry at Yale University. A primary component of our research here at the center focuses on studying the effects of substance use on brain cognition and function.

We recently published a study titled [Longitudinal influence of alcohol and marijuana use on academic performance in college students](http://journals.plos.org/plosone/article?id=10.1371/journal.pone.0172213 utm_source=reddit utm_medium=ama utm_campaign=reddit-ama-0417) in [PLOS ONE](http://journals.plos.org/plosone). In this study, we evaluated the combined effects of alcohol and marijuana on academic GPA in 1142 freshman college students who were followed up longitudinally over a two-year time period. During this period, each month we collected data on their alcohol and marijuana use patterns while in college through a secure self-report website. In analyzing these data, we identified three substance-use groups, **a)** a group that used either no or very low amounts of both alcohol and marijuana, **b)** students that used no/low marijuana but medium-high amounts of alcohol and **c)** students that consumed medium-high quantities of both substances. Interestingly, we found almost no one that consumed no-low alcohol but high amounts of marijuana.

Our findings show that despite students having the same pre-baseline academic achievement as measured using the SAT scores, at the end of incoming semester those who heavily used either alcohol or alcohol+MJ had a significantly lower GPA compared to those who abstained or had very little of it. We also noticed that students who consumed fairly large quantities of alcohol alone (very little MJ) did not have a consistent decrease in GPA across the two-year period (we only noticed a significant decrease in GPA for the incoming semester). Finally, **our follow up analysis suggested that those who moderated drug use over the period of the study could recover and perform better academically**.

We will be answering your questions at 1pm ET -- Ask Anything! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-12 21:06:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If it came straight from permafrost, there's a chance it has DNA good enough to be sequenced.  If it was buried outside the arctic chances are slim.  Most mammoth sequencing is happening at UCSC, the Swedish Museums of Natural History, and formerly at Penn State.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-12 21:04:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> They have!! Two neanderthals have been sequenced to high coverage.  This is how they know Neanderthals and humans interbred.  It also helped people trace their migrations out of Europe as separate events. 

I have other work on genome structure changes in Neanderthals, which was an interesting project to work on.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-12 21:02:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Woolly mammoths could not eat trees. Their teeth are flat with shallow ridges that ground up grasses, similar to Savannah elephants. This is one of the factors that contributed to their extinction.  As forests grew up over the Siberian grasslands, the mammoths struggled to find food.  Combined with human predation, their numbers dwindled.  Mastodons have a completely different tooth structure, with sharper points.  Their name even means nipple toothed.  Mastodons (and possibly Columbian mammoths) could eat twigs and bark, but woolly mammoths could not. 

Wrangel Island is an unusual habitat. It does not have grasslands, but scrubby bushes.  The island gets hit periodically with arctic cyclones.  These storms rip up trees and prevent them from growing on the island.  The cyclones make Wrangel Island a harsh environment to live in, but in the end they may be one reason why the mammoths could persist on the island even after the mainland populations were extinct.  
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-12 20:11:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The sequence data is completely incompatible with this hypothesis for mammoth origins. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-12 20:05:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> George Church has proposed using an artifical uterus to incubate the transgenic elephant/mammoth.  I will be interested to see what he comes  up with.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-12 20:03:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's difficult to say what the exact effects might be using gene sequences alone, but any of these are possible.   Better research on urinary proteins and olfactory receptors in elephants might help us figure out more detailed answers.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-12 20:02:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> There are two mutations in a gene called FoxQ1.  One chromosome has a frameshift mutation-- an extra site gets put in and it messes up formation of the protein completely.  The other chromosome has a huge deletion that takes out the entire gene. 

That gene causes a satin coat in mice, and it's involved in fur formation in other mammals. So long as the gene acts the same way in mammoths that it does in lots of other mammals, the mammoth would have a very shiny coat.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-12 20:01:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The outer guard hairs were very long and stiff to keep out the cold.  Underneath were a much softer fur.  I have some, along with mammoth ivory on my book shelf.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-12 19:59:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Mutations appear at random over time.  Bad mutations are removed from populations as long as the population size is very large.  When population sizes are small, chance plays a bigger role.  Mutations that might be out competed are tolerated in small populations.  This leads to an accumulation of bad mutations in the genome.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-12 19:57:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Any of these could be true.  It could be that selective pressures changed-- predators weren't found on the island, the plant composition was different, perhaps there was less sexual selection.  It could equally be true that breaking olfactory receptors just isn't that bad.  It's not as if the mammoth drops dead when one olfactory receptor is broken. So it falls within the neutral threshold and the mutations start to accumulate.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-12 19:53:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I've wanted to work on mammoths since Kindergarten.  I had heard about arctic explorers who found mammoths frozen in ice sheets with fur still on them.  To me it seemed like the closest you could get to having a time machine.  We could still see what these animals looked like even tens of thousands of years after they had died off.  

When Love Dalen's lab published these mammoth sequences, I downloaded them the same day.  It was exciting to get to work on mammoths, but even more exciting when I saw what looked like a genomic meltdown.  It's probably one of the more fun projects I've worked on.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-12 19:51:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Mammoths went back and forth from the mainland to the island when glaciers covered the Siberia and sea levels were higher.  The mammoths became isolated on the island as sea levels rose.  There's some debate about the exact timing but we know that by 12,000 years the mammoths were only on the island.  

There's some debate about how far the mammoths could swim in the arctic, and also about how think the ice sheets were in winter vs summer months.  By 12,000 years ago the channel between Wrangel Island and the mainland was too wide for them to cross.   Thankfully it kept the humans away for a long time as well.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-12 19:47:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> A two-ton wombat with a long nose with opposable appendages at the end.

My coauthor would probably want me to point out that they have nothing to do with wombats.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-12 19:46:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Humans reached Wrangel island around the same time mammoths went extinct there.  We don't have direct evidence of hunting, but it's awfully coincidental. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-12 19:45:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Some people have hoped to find evidence of mutations accumulating especially in small groups of archaic humans.  So far, no one has found a signal as strong as what we saw in mammoths.  The mammoths were a very extreme case with a 43 fold change in population size and they were isolated for thousands of years.  There might be less extreme cases in humans that could be found with more individuals and more complete theories, but nothing has come up yet.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-12 19:43:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> There are several different mammoth species.  Woolly mammoths are one. There were also Steppe Mammoths, Columbian mammoths, Southern Mammoths.  There were a few subspecies or groups on islands as well-- Wrangel Island, St Paul's Island, Channel Island and Crete.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-12 19:42:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Bottlenecks are a different phenomenon.  They happen when a population goes from being very large to being very small. Just by chance, you could have a mutation go from very low frequency to higher frequency because it was found in one of the 10 who survived.  

There was likely some kind of bottleneck in the island invasion, but we don't have evidence that it was very strong.  It also could not cause the massive signal of bad mutations that accumulated in the Wrangel Island mammoth's DNA.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-12 19:40:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> We would expect that a population, once brought back to large population size, would purge some of the bad mutations.  There is a nice paper with this theory from Balick et al. (link below).  This purging will take a VERY long time.   

With the large deletions that we studied it will be even more difficult to undo the damage.  Once a gene is completely deleted, how do you get it back?  Most of my research is on new gene formation.  It is much more difficult to get new beneficial genes than it is to repair a single letter change in the DNA.  There could be other compensatory mutations, but that's difficult to guarantee.  

http://journals.plos.org/plosgenetics/article?id=10.1371/journal.pgen.1005436 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-12 19:36:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Transposable elements are selfish genetic elements that live in the genomes of most eukaryotes.  They copy themselves like viruses, even if it causes harm to the host.  There is constant conflict over evolutionary time.  TEs will proliferate and cause bad mutations, the cell will come up with a repressor to keep the TE quiet, and then the TE will mutate again to proliferate.  It's a genetic arms race that leads to some pretty exciting biology. 

If you've read Dawkins' the selfish gene, this exactly the type of dynamic he is talking about.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-12 19:34:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Woolly mammoths are closely related to Asian elephants, and African elephants are more distant relatives.   We mapped all the mammoth DNA onto the African elephant Loxodonta africana genome.  The two are a surprisingly good match.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-12 19:32:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Generally scientists like data. We like keeping data once we have it.  It helps us understand the world around us and make informed decisions.  

The ethics guidelines established by the NIH for biomedical research state that destroying data (before or after publication) should always be investigated.  No matter what the policy is on environmental protection, destroying the data that informs policy decisions is wrong. 

There was a great story about a hack-a-thon at Berkeley that saved large sections of EPA data.  I was glad to see that.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-12 19:29:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The best case that I know of for similar genetic meltdown is in the foxes on the Channel Islands.  They found that there were lots of amino acid changes accumulating in the foxes on the island, which has had a similarly small population for a very long time.   We would be very interested in following up on the foxes to see whether they have a similar excess of other classes of mutations, and how good the fit is with mathematical models of genomic meltdown.

Other people are starting to sequence other endangered animals (yes, like Cheetahs).  I will be very interested to see what comes of it.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-12 19:26:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> We aren't particularly hopeful of finding an in tact nucleus for direct DNA transfer.  Even the best preserved cells will have a lot of DNA damage which might produce negative effects.  There was an attempt to clone an extinct Ibex this way.  The offspring lived for 7 minutes.  

Elephants are extremely intelligent and social animals.  They are also threatened in the wild.  One would want to have a serious look at the implications of cloning or genetic engineering in an elephant before the experiment was done.  Fortunately every institution has an ethics board that governs these types of experiments.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
