<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject2952</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-10 16:35:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah its definitely not Zulu but I can see how you'd get there.

I'm almost certain it was an American unit holding the hill, so English voice acting. 

IIRC the enemies had a desert yellow uniform and I vaguely remember an emblem or a star on their helmets/hats.

I don't remember a great deal, hence why its so hard to find. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-10 15:19:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Just had a look and I don't think it's this either. Thanks for replying </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-10 15:19:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I've just watched a clip and I don't think its this one. Thanks for the help </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Can anyone help me find this movie? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-10 15:05:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I've been trying to find this movie for a while now but I can't remember what its called for the life of me.


What I know/think;

- War movie (Unsure of whether WW2, Vietnam or Korea)
- Produced in the US
- American Army in the pacific theater (Unsure if the adversaries are Vietnamese/Chinese/Japanese/Korean)
- They spend a lot of the movie holding a hill against the enemy
- I remember them blowing up some bridges also
- A relatively old film - I would say made between the 50'   70's
- I remember the landscape in the movie being quite sparse
- IIRC it was a color movie 


Any help appreciated! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-08 12:28:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> PS4 player here.

I'd love for my Xbox brothers to get this additional content.

Console Exclusives shouldn't be a thing IMHO </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-09 13:12:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This doesn't work as well anymore, much better going to Archons Forge to be honest </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-16 13:20:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Looks like Kirito's sword from SAO, nice! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-07 17:50:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Legend. Did not know this, I shall start taking those packages now </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-07 17:49:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> No problem. I had done 5 of the 10 heroic strike before noticing... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-07 16:24:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Not yet, It wasn't working for me just a day or two ago. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-12 12:04:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yes! To be honest i was sold on Destiny on the FPSMMORPG title that was given originally.

Something akin to Final Fantasy XIV would be amazing. minus the monthly subscription. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-10 17:27:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I know she used to but I went over to her yesterday and she didn't have it? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
