<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject9073</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-10 17:20:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> And the soil behind the DQ was the only safe place?

I didn't fail to understand anything. I just don't like it as much as you. That's all. I was thinking a cave or something would have been safer. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-10 17:18:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I really liked the movie. I wasn't criticizing the film for not following science or our physics... I was just trying to break down the story in simple terms for my fianc that I realized how nutty the main storyline isespecially for people not "in the loop" so to speak.

Understand, when it comes to hard sci-fi and comic book lore, my fianc is a total layman. So ideas and concepts that comic book   sci-fi Fans readily understand and accept are not exactly intuitive for her.

Upon further reflection... The character of Ego (in the film) seems VERY emotionally immature for a being that is millions of years old. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-10 17:13:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You had to fill in a lot of blanks that the film didn't. But your explanation is good. Still... Fuckin Dairy Queen?

You also forgot about the McGuffin where throwaway character Mantis is able to put the entire planet to sleep. That was kinda weak. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-10 17:08:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It is crazy!

I was talking to a friend of mine who writes fantasy... It's amazing how the modern cinema audience has changed. Fantasy is almost mainstream, and the "deep" comic book stuff is showing up more often.

I don't think a character like EGO would have even been accepted by film audiences 15 years ago. But now... We've been primed and we're more open to the concepts.

It is a good time. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-10 17:03:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Pretty strange. Nothing said by anybody in this thread should merit a downvote. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> I realized that Guardians of the Galaxy 2 has an absolutely absurd plot when I tried explaining it to my Fianc... </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-10 13:47:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> After watching GOTG2, my Fianc admitted thatalthough she liked the movieshe didnt really understand what was going on at any given minute with the plot. And, to be honest If you dont have a background in Sci-Fi or Comics You might not intuitively follow the story of GOTG2. So when we got home, I explained it to her in brief

Kurt Russell is a giant, humanoid brain whoafter years of solitudegot lonely being the only celestial and created an entire planet around himself, then converted into human form to study life elsewhere, at which time he became disappointed with all existing life and started sowing tiny plant bits of himself on various life-sustaining Worldswhile simultaneously romancing and impregnating a variety of different females (?) throughout the Galaxy so that at a later point in time he can befriend and join forces with one of his own celestial bastard children, hopefully be able to gain said bastards trust so he can lure them back to his planet/body, gauge their genetic strength, and if they prove capable, convince them in a few days time to help him eradicate all life everywhere through the destructive force of planetary Ego blobs.

It was at this point that I realizedalthough I still really like it Its fucking absurd.

They even dust off the old Death Star trick Ego is super-smart and all powerful, but he left himself vulnerable to attack by a small creature with a bomb. Fuck. Off.

**RANT MODE ACTIVATED:** AND, Im sorry but Behind the fuckin Dairy Queen? Really? Thats where you hid your planet-killing Blob-Flower?? Really, motherfucker??? How about, pick a REMOTE spot on the planetlike, oh I dont knowANT-FUCKING-ARTICA to plant your shit so some little kid doesnt run behind the DQ and stomp on it. But apparently in movieland, the small area of trees behind the local DQ remains undisturbed for 30+ years. If that was an Austin DQ, they would have leveled those trees and built condos behind that Dairy Queen in the late fucking 90s. **RANT MODE DEACTIVATED**

I still liked it. A lot. Its a testament to the strength of the characters and the comedy that we can all overlook the ridiculous plot line. Because it is ridiculous. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-10 13:36:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> SIDE BAR: How in the fuck have ALL of the comments by everybody in this thread been downvoted?

The TOP COMMENT by aced411 had almost 15 points yesterday and has been down voted to 6. Are these Crackle users who are downvoting him??

I had 6 points on my comment where I'm just asking other people's opinions... Nobody replied, but I've been down voted to 1.

What the fuck? There should be no downvoting of anybody here... We're having a very civil discussion.

This is why I fucking hate reddit and why I'm considering calling it quits. I get tons of Karma for fucking bullshit posts and comments, but when I try to engage in an actual exchange of information, I get downvoted. Fuck of, reddit. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Nobody gives a shit about the current time in Oklahoma, Google. Get your head out of your ass. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-10 03:16:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-09 23:17:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Start running the electricity and water NON-FUCKING-STOP right now. Run those bills up as high as you can get them. If you're not on the bill, it's 100% his responsibility.

File a Police Report regarding him breaking into your phone. If nothing else it could be considered harassment.

Report him to the ASPCA or Humane Society for Animal Cruelty. Make sure this is officially documented, because it could impact any future acts on his part.

And now the big one... Who is on the lease? Is it a house or Apartment? If possible, get the fuck out of that place. Give him ZERO money.

Does he have a criminal record of any kind? Like anything? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-09 23:06:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This is interesting.

Haven't heard of Tubi until now. But I might give it a try.

How does everybody else feel about the CEO's comment?

I happen to think he might be right. Yes, I can save money by cutting the cord and paying for a subscription. But if I can get premium, quality content for free, that's even better.

And if I only have to suffer through 5 min of commercial content every 30 minutes (which is about 2.5 minutes less than Cable and Broadcast), then it's not really a big deal for me.

I will saywatching commercials during movies would annoy me. How does that work, Tubi Subscribers? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-09 15:18:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Did I swear too much? I think I swore too much. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Enough is enough... All you Roman Reigns Fuckboys need to shut your mouths. RR sucks. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-09 15:14:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-08 19:53:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Late to the game, but I'll say it anyway

This film has faded into obscurity for a reason. It sucks.

It's a brilliant concept. But the execution was awful. And BTW... McConaughey was a huge star by the time this got made. Butler and Bale were up-and-comers. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-05 03:25:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I refuse to "lol" this on principle. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-05 02:54:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Didn't even bother to change the headline.

WTF, reddit? Why can't reposters be flagged and banned? Mods are banning people for everything nowadays. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> When your bullshit re-post ends up right next to the original... </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-05 02:53:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-05 00:40:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Play the rumor game back on them.

Enlist some of your straight male friends (like at least 5 or 6) to tell as many people as possible that the 4 Hoes in question all caught Hep C from sleeping with the same guy. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-01 00:21:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> ^ very clever </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-27 15:47:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Funny... I had WWE Network for about 6 months. It wasn't that I couldn't afford it, it was that I just wasn't watching it. It's really just a lack of time for me. NXT actually looks like a lot of fun. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-26 21:36:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Takeover Dallas?? My man... I barely have time to finish Raw and Smackdown every week, let alone any PPVs. I JUST finished watching Wrestlemania for Christ sake.

I'm glad you can watch the Takeovers, but for us regular fans, WWE needs to step their DEBUT and BRANDING game up. Most of us don't know who this guys is, or why he's wearing the stupid mouth guard and rolling around, posing like Madonna doing finger dances. It just looks weird and unwarranted if you don't know anything about the guy.

Yada yada... Finn Balor paid off. I'm sure Nakamura is fine. I'll just have to wait until they let him wrestle to see what the hype is all about.

If it ends up being Emily to Emilina type hype, I will be so fucking annoyed. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-26 21:29:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This is not aimed at you personally... I understand how NXT works. UH BUT...

Hearing somebody tell me"You should be watching NXT"is kind of like when I don't understand something in a Marvel movie and some Nerd says"Well, did you read the Comic Book??"

No. I don't read comic books. I prefer films. So I expect Filmmakers to do their goddamn job and tell me the whole storyIN THE CONTEXT OF THEIR FILM. I don't expect to have to do homework to understand the backstory of a movie.

Same with Raw or Smackdown. Don't just put Roman Reigns in the ring and TELL people he's the Big Dog. Make him earn that shit. Make people realize it for themselves.

And don't drop Shinsuke Nakamura on a bunch of unsuspecting fans who haven't invested time in NXT (because they don't haver the time to invest) and maybe give us a video bio or something. Or maybe have him win a few matches in grandiose style before you send him out rolling and writhing to some shitty violin music.

We shouldn't have to look up a wrestler on google. They should DEBUT him/her properly so we realize it for ourselves. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-26 21:19:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thank you. You pretty much summed up my problem.

I have a life. A full time job, friends, a Fianc... Ain't nobody got time for NXT. I'm sure it's the shit. I used to love Minor League Baseball. But I just don't have time. So I kind of wish WWE would do a better job of educating people who only tune in for Raw, Smackdown and some of the PPVs. Even Finn Balorwho I now lovewas a little too flamboyant when he debuted in the big show. I was like... "Jesus, who is this guy?". Nakamura is like that times a hundred. Unless he's the BEST WRESTLER IN HISTORY, I think he should dial it back for fuck sake. He's writhing all over the mat and shit like a freak. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Um... Shinsuke Nakamura. What the fuck am I missing? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-26 11:34:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Based on the ridiculous flamboyance of his entrance, I was expecting something special.

Not so much. Am I missing something?? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-25 00:24:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> How about... Report him to the police. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-23 06:52:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I would never recommend committing any crime, of course, but in a fantasy alternate reality...

If you know where he drinks, then in theory, you know where he'll be drunk. Drunk people are vulnerable as fuck. Period.

Gather some of your boys together, wait for him to walk out into the parking lot and have a nice, four on one chat with the man. Once he has been "laid down to sleep", remove his keys, phone and wallet from his pockets. Keep any cash for gas and expenses (duh), then drop his keys, phone and wallet into a fucking sewer.

If this guy really did what you say he did, then fuck him. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-18 15:56:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Very cool!

You should post a link to just the vector file so people can steal it!! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-17 20:20:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's a... Kit Kan't.

FUCKING ZINGER!!! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-12 18:18:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thank you! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-12 16:20:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Somebody find a link so we can all buy one of these!! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-12 15:48:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Not that I don't believe you... But I can't confirm this information.

There is nothing on the Austin Animal Center website that verifies they are allowing free adoptions.

Can anybody verify this?

Note: I want to post this on our Office Slack, but I want to make sure it's true. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-12 15:19:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That's what I'm screaming!

It was great though. The more I think about it, they should do crap like this every week. I want more! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-11 22:52:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> LOLOL... What's kind of funny, is when I wrote that comment, I wasn't actually thinking about the Ambulance flip at allwhich was the most absurd and entertaining part.

I laughed like a little girl for about 5 minutes when Stroman chucked the Gurney off of the loading ramp. It was CLEARLY an insert clip, and it was pretty obvious after they cut back to live footagethe spot where they positioned RR was nowhere near where the gurney landed.

I fucking loved all of it. Every second. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-11 20:43:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> As much as I loved watching it...

Anybody else laugh hysterically at how fake it all was?

I mean... Even by pro-wrestling standards... Just fake as hell. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-30 18:02:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That's awesome. Drawing is one of my favorite hobbies. Great activity for mentally withdrawing from the World and relieving any stress.

Keep it up! Can't wait to see what your illustrations look like in the future. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-30 16:01:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The Usos sucked with paint.

The Usos suck without paint. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-30 15:39:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> How old are you?

How long have your been drawing?

I think this is good. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-21 20:19:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Ultimate...

Fucking...

Warrior. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-21 17:37:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Was it not two different cave women??

I might have to go back and rewatch now. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-21 17:18:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It doesn't even have to connect to the present day story... I just really want to know what the hell happened to Cave Baby.

I'd like to think he/she made it. She was raised by Other Cave Woman and lived to be old and prosperous. For a cave person. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-21 15:51:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [David Warner](http://1.bp.blogspot.com/-37iUNin8RgM/VlDZK5HS68I/AAAAAAAAPEE/qP0TpVnFN1w/s1600/Timeabove%2Binterview.jpg) in [Time Bandits](https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Time_Bandits)! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-21 15:27:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I wish they would give him the full Jenny Jones and give him a Haircut and Beard Trim.

Mick Foley looked pretty god when they did it to him. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-21 14:57:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I want to know what happens to the Cave Baby. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-21 14:56:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Why is Xavier woods a god to all gamers now?

What am I missing? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-16 21:31:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Pretty sure the correct answer to this question is...

Human Centipede. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-16 19:47:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> "something something something... WORSE THAN YOU CAN POSSIBLY IMAGINE."

NO... It's hardly ever as bad as the worse thing I can imagine.

Maybe my imagination is just that bad. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-15 20:55:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I think 'International Assassin' (S2 EP8) might be my favorite episode so far. It's just such a departurepun intended!

But as far as character moments; 'Lens' (S2 EP6) is so freaking good. When Nora gives Erika the DSD Questionnaire... I was GLUED to the screen.

Funny... I binged S2 in one day. And just reminiscing right now I realized that I completely forgot about the awesome prologue to the first episode of S2with the Cave Woman. I forgot all about her! I hope we see the continuation of that story also. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-15 20:04:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  This is pretty much exactly how I felt at the end of S2.

Only 1 short month until S3! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-15 18:58:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Weikels. It's the jam! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-14 17:19:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Why are you friends with these two?

In this case, I would say the best revenge would be to ghost them. Stop talking to them completely and cut them out of your life.

Anything you would do would seem petty, and probably go to prove the point that you are a bully/asshole.

Based on the way you describe both of them, it doesn't sound like you have a lot of respect for either oneso don't waste your time.

Ghost those motherfuckers and start living life. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-10 15:24:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Most recently...

[Enemy](https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Enemy_(2013_film) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-10 15:13:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Contact the Power Company and impersonate him.

Tell them you (your friend) is leaving the Country on an extended sabbatical and that you need the power disconnected.

You can also advertise a Gang Bang on like Craigslist with his address. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-10 15:02:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Can we get an ELI5 on this? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-09 21:30:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You tracked him down on FB... So you know his name?

If that's the case, then you should probably phish as much personal information about him as possible.

Then locate his property (home or car) and do about $240 worth of damage. This is $80 actual damages x 3 for punitive measures. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-09 16:07:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This is a small step for Reddit, but a giant leap for Redditkind. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-23 22:18:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Honestly... Burger King.

It feels like they stopped giving an actual fuck years ago. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-23 21:15:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I know that it isn't the satisfying answer you're looking for, but I will echo the other responses here and saydon't watch it for the explanation. Watch if for the characters.

When I finished the first season, I was not happy. But then the marvelous second season completely turned things around, and even made me look at S1 differently.

Without over-selling it, this is easily one of my favorite shows of all time, containing some of the most riveting, character based interactions I've ever seen on TV or in Film.

I was was initially very frustrated when the creators said they would never reveal what happened. But once I was sucked into the show, it didn't matter anymore. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-22 22:10:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'll get tired of it eventually. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-22 21:16:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The Usos are somehow worse than Fetch.

It's tough, because I want to applaud them for ditching the stupid PAINT thing, but they just suck. And I'm not being a hater. There just isn't any appeal there... They weren't good Baby-Faces. They aren't good Heals. Their wrestling isn't good or badit just is. And their mic skillz suuuuuuuuuuuuuck.

LikeEnzo is a pretty shitty wrestler, but I'll listen to him say "Cuppa Haters" all day long because it makes me laugh. Same thing with New Day... As separate parts, they were all very average; but as New Day, they have that 'it' thing that entertains people. The Usos just don't have 'it'. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-22 18:12:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> lol... ANYTHING is better than the face paint. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-22 18:05:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> How did he fuck you over? This is necessary information before supplying a response. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-22 17:02:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I had to change the channel.

The WWE should stop trying to make the Usos happen. They're not going to happen.

EDIT: Down-vote it all you want... The Usos suck. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-22 14:26:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Dredd was good, but fuckinHobo With A Shotgun? Really?? That movie fucking sucked. You just shot your credibility. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-21 15:22:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I agree. Especially when compared to Hacksaw or War Zone. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-21 14:45:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Zing! You got a Tuesday lol out of me.

It's funny, because it's true. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> DEADPOOL   LOGAN are receiving praise for their Hard-R violence... Just want to remind everybody that THIS MARVEL MOVIE existsand it's fucking awesome! </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-21 14:42:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-20 23:08:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Sure it was. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-20 23:07:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Uh huh. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-20 16:38:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The Phoenix Lights

https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Phoenix_Lights

It 100% DID happen... The only question iswhat was it? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-19 15:46:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I feels like this song should have more than 132K views.

It's a pretty good song. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The Stepkids - Sweet Salvation [Psychedelic Soul] </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-19 15:42:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-17 19:13:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I agree with this suggestion from Jimbabwe.

You look kind of rodentine when you smile. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Some quick advice for Kellyanne Conwaysince she CLEARLY hasn't figured it out for herself... </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-15 19:49:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Stealing this from myself and re-posting herebecause I just discovered this sub! Have you Ticonderoga fans seen John Wick 2?? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-14 21:31:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-14 01:53:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Oh sorry... I deleted the image, Bitch Tits.

I posted it in the Eternity Club if you want to try to steal it again. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-10 15:43:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This should be a movie. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-10 02:42:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> AHHH HAAAA! You got schooled, bitch! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-09 23:27:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Obviously nobody gives a fuck because you're a dooooooooooooooooork. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-09 20:29:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> username checks out </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-09 14:41:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Holy shit, that's a good idea. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-09 00:20:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thank you!

lol... I saw the gif. I just didn't know what I was watching. It looked cool. But I had no idea exactly what was happening. Posts like this make me think I'm not Minecrafting hard enough.

I have zero experience with concrete. I didn't even know what powder concrete was. I still don't actually. Which leads me to my next question...

What is powder concrete? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-09 00:02:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Somebody tell me what's so cool!

I wanna know too!! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Help Me Get Revenge On An Christian Who Complained to the President Of My Company About My "Red Devil" Google Profile Pic! </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-08 22:06:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm employed at a company that woks with Schools around the country. My Google Profile picture is that of a funny Red Devil.

Today I sent an email the Office manager of a notoriously intolerant Christian School... When I say intolerant, I meanthey won't accept openly gay students, etc.

Anyway... She emailed the President of my company (who I happen to share an office with) and asked him to address the matter of my devil picture, saying that it was unprofessional. In other words... I'm a Christian and I'm offended by the image of a Red Devilso you should make him change it.

I wasn't forced... But it was suggested that I change my Google Profile pic. So I did.

Even though I'm not in trouble and everybody in my officeincluding The Presidentgot a good chuckle over it... I can't help but still be annoyed. SO...

Fuck this Christian Bitch! How do I get my revenge?? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Can we make TAPPER FACE (aka "Come The Fuck On") a new thing? Because honestly.. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-08 18:01:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> How can my Office set up a private Yelp for our Employees to use? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-08 15:46:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-07 15:02:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Absolutely... And I think the writers chose the exact right TYPE of humor to use in S2not to mentionthey picked some very choice moments to employ it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-07 15:01:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Have no choice to agree... It's the old Empire Strikes Back argument

It's become very trendy to claim Empire is the best Star Wars film, but without A New Hope, and the groundwork laid out for the story and characters, Empire wouldn't be anywhere near as effective. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-07 14:59:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Maybe that's the lynch-pin for me... I really appreciated the use of humor in S2. Like when Kevin tells the guy he won't sing because it's "fucking stupid". That was brilliant. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-07 14:58:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Honestly... BY that standardthere's no doubt Season 1 was effective, because I really was impacted emotionally by each episode. I wasn't kidding when I said I was gloomy. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-07 05:51:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I agree.

I'm just hoping The Leftovers has a better end than LOST. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-07 05:48:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If it's Austin, shouldn't it be called the Jaywalking Dead? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Kinda hated S1... But S2 REALLY turned things around! </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-06 22:00:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Just Binged S2... Wow. I meanholy guacamole. That was 10 SOLID episodes of greatness.

But it was such a "departure" ( pun intended) from S1or at least it was to me.

S1 was slow and depressing. At the end of every episode I was more gloomy than before.

But S2 really turned the whole experience around for me, and now I can't wait for S3. I don't give a shit if anything ever gets explained... This is good stuff.

Am I the only one? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-05 18:31:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah... I saw Ramsey's thing. I do love Ramsey... But I'm not sure I'd subscribe.

I like the GIF format for quickly explaining and running through a recipe. But there always seems to be 1 or 2 egregious errors in every tasty clip. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-05 17:56:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hey, u/pizzalovingkinglove this response.

Serious Question: why don't some 5 star chefs get together and start their own gif cooking channel?? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-05 17:45:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> There is a pretty big difference between showing a preference and being racist.

I prefer Blondes. That doesn't make me a Brunettist. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-03 22:08:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I love u/DrWankalot! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-31 19:49:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> All he needs is some practice on the mic and I think he could start hitting home runs. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-31 19:49:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I didn't really like him UNTIL that moment... I couldn't get a read on his character. He was just another dark bad ass guy.

But right after he tossed Strowman, he seemed to almost come out of his shell and get AMPED.

I liked it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Royal Rumble [spoiler] - "CORBIN ELIMINATES..." </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-30 23:57:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> ...STROWMAN!!"

Finally! Baron Corbin showed a little spunk. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-27 03:17:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You're already winning my vote for World Leader. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-26 16:40:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> UUUUUUUUUUUUPvote! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-26 14:27:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So they can easily set up my monthly subscription and take my payment online, but in order to cancel I have to call?

Here's the best part... When you call, theyof coursehit you with the full-court sales press, and try to get you to reconsider, then they offer you half off. Then they put you on hold for 2 minutes while they "process" the cancellation... What a joke.

Yeah. Ill never be resubscribing.

And P.S., New York Times, remember those hundreds of layoffs/buyouts you had back in April? Yeahthis is why youll eventually die out. Because youre assholes.

EDIT: Anybody who IS subscribing to the Times and wants to save 50%... Just call and cancel. By the end of the call you'll have saved half your money. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Here's how to quickly and easily cancel your subscription Fuck you, New York Times! </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-26 14:26:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-25 22:02:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Women do love the man. My fianc will watch any match with him or Dean Ambrose. And she hates wrestling. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
