<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject2022</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-10 07:46:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Speak for yourself. I love him so much I want to sleep with him . </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-10 06:08:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Jesus. Didn't think of getting a room at a motel? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Sometimes I think what if Geralt suddenly got the urge to hammer Ciri? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-09 09:09:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I know this is a weird one to ask but technically they're not related by blood so I could definitely see Geralt getting a boner and Ciri helping with that fucking boner lol. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Do you honestly believe that Better Call Saul is better than Breaking Bad? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-09 07:41:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I've heard a lot of people voicing this opinion and I want to get a general sense of how this sub feels. Personally I think Breaking Bad is better, but I really love BCS too. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-08 23:34:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Haven't read it myself, but it looks like it's well liked by the fans.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-08 22:04:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Pick one: Under the Dome, The Long Walk, Salems Lot </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-08 21:43:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> And that's completely fine. I wish more people understood that.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> I'm sorry, but IMO Bryan Fuller is 100% a hack. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-08 21:38:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Dude is all dress up and no substance. Check out Hannibal and American Gods. He likes to dress stuff up, but if you peek behind the curtain you'll see that there's nothing there. Really, can you tell me something interesting about the storytelling in Hannibal? I mean, yes, the score was incredible, the cinematography, the acting, even the dialogue seemed sophisticated. But as a whole, did Hannibal even tell a *good* story? Idk, there's just something about his work that doesn't seem ... genuine? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> In your opinion, which non-erotica author writes the best sex scene? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-08 21:07:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> My favor is Stephen Kings IT gangbang, and other memorable mentions include certain sex scenes in ASOIAF, the Magicians, and Big Little Lies . although I gotta say, The First Law series have funny sex scenes, in that they're awkward and kind of real, what with the awkward grunting and the like. One that stands out happens in book 2 and it was hilarious. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-08 20:04:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I have a tiny dick </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [SPOILERS] Can well all agree that this is hands down the best scene in The Witcher 3? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-08 19:33:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-07 19:03:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I agree. I'm just curious if anyone else used (or still uses) Facebook as a show criticism outlet.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-07 04:59:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Lmao you're getting fucked in the ass now aren't you.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The man in black fled across the desert, and the gunslinger followed </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-06 20:53:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-06 20:46:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I haven't even started writing it lol.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-06 20:22:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's 1978. Three men are dispatched on the shores of Cuba. Their mission: assassinate Fidel Castro. But what these three men don't know is that their mission will take an unlikely turn when Jason Hertz, the leader, gets involved with Castro's mistress, which brings a whole world of complications to their mission.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> I actually disagree with most of you. Here's why. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-06 17:49:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-05 22:35:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Imagine I was Stephen King. Would take his work and so stain it?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Final monologue by the villian in my novel. Watcha think? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-05 22:25:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-04 17:38:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Shhh. Just sit back and enjoy the ride.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-04 08:18:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> My dick is so small it looks like a vagina. With teeth.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [META] How to play like an adult. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-04 07:50:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Sit here beside me. Grab the controller. See that? That's people in the lobby. *Actual people*. 

What are you doing man? Don't say that. Those are actual people with actual feelings. Don't say that. 
Don't vote to kick you stupid asshole idiot. 

Ok, dude, what are you doing. Don't team kill. It makes you a total asshole who probably likes dick. Oh ,and by the way, you shouldn't go around treating people like that. I don't man, you never know.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-03 23:30:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I like /r/books better.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Is Red Sparrow by Jason Matthews worth reading? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-03 23:24:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-03 21:53:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The Sopranos ever Ozymandias level? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Better Call Saul has reached Ozymandias heights of drama level IMO. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-03 21:27:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This latest episode has proved that it continues to surpass breaking bad in every way. The characters are better, the show is funnier and the plot is actually kinda better.. guys, this is the next Ozymandias right here 
. I love it </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-02 22:14:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's a sex question  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-02 22:09:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Well I used to words like "hotel" and "chuck".  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What would you do if Vince Gillian sent you a DM asking you to meet him so he can chuck you? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-02 22:00:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-02 07:19:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I gotta ask, what's your second favorite?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> How fucking big do you ?m </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-28 01:34:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-26 22:38:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> But bro what if he drank gasoline before dying /s </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-26 09:11:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hi ;) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-26 00:52:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Or she went there to have a good time? She's not in the KGB you know </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-25 15:11:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'll leave an excellent review for you just in case you are in fact a real person

Cringe.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Taboo Is Sexy, And If You Don't Get A Boner While Watching The Show, There's Something Wrong With You. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-25 09:35:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The writers , directors producers know how to arouse you whats amazing is that Taboo rarely has any sex stuff in the first few episodes, and even the entire series doesn't have that much sex at all. Taboo's arousal mainly cums from the imagination, from the tense atmosphere that borders on erotic on some parts and gritty gruesome on others. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-25 09:21:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You have a healthy brain. Can't you guess?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-25 09:13:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Xbox Live must find ways to be inreactive.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-25 08:35:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That's it? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-25 08:35:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Ok </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-24 10:28:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's not a fantasy.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> My dad is asking me to perform ***** in order for me to get an Gears 4. Is it worth it? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-24 10:16:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> I want to be in a TV show. What do I have to do? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-23 09:54:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I have done impressions videos they're really good and honestly I feel like I'm a good actor. I act all the time even though I'm sad I act cheerful and happy and when I'm angry I act cool and people believe me when I lie. So, how does one enter the showbiz? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The intro sequence for The Night Of is one the best at setting the tone </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-23 02:21:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-23 00:58:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> you sink to their level of unprofessionalism, why would someone hire you in the real world. 

quit college </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Looking for something similar to The Missing/The Killing/ True Detective </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-22 20:32:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If it's closer to The Missing the better. Basically a good mystery book with fleshed out characters and a good mystery at the center. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-22 08:20:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Secret service will be just outside.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> If Donald Trump offers you 2mil for you to cover his mouth with your hand and jerk his cock until he cums, would you do it? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-22 08:13:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-22 08:11:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Post another one  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-22 02:55:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Or in Russia. The Walking Dead in Moscow would have been awesome  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-21 20:55:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Because daddy keeps fucking teenage sluts behind mommy's back. She doesn't like that.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-21 18:32:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> How is that a good thing? Do you think that type of crowd will watch this show? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Confessions from a teamkiller. (xpost from /r/xboxone) </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-21 04:24:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> First off, let me say that I *do not* do it on Ranked. Only casual. That said, teamkilling is one of those things that never gets old, even after 500 hours spent in the game. It's not like I always do it. But, let say that if I play 15 casual games in a day, in at least 5 of those I will mess with my teammates. I like having fun with it, like taking some health and acting like it wasn't me, or pretending to have bad aim during the prep phase while shooting drones. And don't think of me as a toxic player- i am not. In fact, i am a really good teammate when i feel like it. It's just that sometimes I like teamkilling. 


It is fun. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-21 02:30:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Dude just after reading this comment my xbox one went up in flames...wtf.. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Confessions from a Rainbow Six Siege teamkiller. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-21 02:27:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> On Xbox One Exclusives. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-20 21:28:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Microsoft's strategy for Xbox has changed in a way which makes high-profile (and high-cost) exclusive software less justifiable within the company. That's especially true of high-profile games that won't be on Windows 10 as well as Xbox One; one of the ways in which the Xbox division has secured its future within Microsoft in the wake of the company's reorganisation under CEO Satya Nadella is by positioning itself as a key part of the Windows 10 ecosystem.curious as I am about howHalo Wars 2will turn out,Crackdown 3is another title that seems to have gotten lost on the way to release, as weve heard nearly nothing about it in ages. Im not sure who exactly is terribly excited aboutState of Decay 2, when another Microsoft exclusive zombie game,Dead Rising 4, barely made a splash in 2016. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> There have been some complaints that this current season of The Americans is way too slow. What do you think? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-20 17:58:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Personally I still love it. That's exactly why this show is one of my favorites. They treat each plot line carefully, they flesh everything out as much as possible and they always go for a route that is both realistic and unpredictable. That's why this show has always had strong writing. Do I believe this season is perhaps a little slower than usual?  Yes. But I also really enjoy each episode and have faith that the writers know what they're doing. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Have you guys heard about this show tHe WiRe? Looks pretty good. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-20 09:16:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Do you think about cum every time you brush your teeth? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-19 22:55:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-19 22:42:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I've watched Malcolm in the Middle at least seven times, I'm not sick of it I'm just sick of *only* it.


Millennials, amirite? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-19 19:39:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> No, playing the Joker didnt drive Heath Ledger to his unfortunate and tragic death </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-19 09:28:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> No other has fans more invested right now than The Walking Dead. How can you honestly say that when the show has more than proven it can be amazing?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-19 09:26:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Write consistent characters that have convictions and inherent traits that define their decisions and actions? Not so much. 

How can you say that when, every time a major character dies, there are hundreds upon of hundreds of reaction videos on Youtube. People CARE about these characters. 
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Let's take The Walking Dead for example. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-19 08:18:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The writing of the plot is very strong. Shows how to introduce characters. How to expand and build a world. Incredible world building in fact. The show gets a lot of crap, but I just think that we can learn a lot from it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> My sister has the weirdest television habits. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-17 20:04:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If she discovers a show that she likes she watches it more than once. She did it with Parenthood and now with 13 Reasons Why. She literally finished the show last week and is already watching it again. Like...really? Couldn't pick up something else? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> If I invite you to a party, join. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-17 07:44:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Thinking about raping one of my main characters. Thoughts? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-17 07:01:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Why did King Kong get killed? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-16 22:18:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-16 21:06:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Let me guess you've been watching To Catch A Predator  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> How the hell do you write about the underworld if you've never experienced that kind of life? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-16 20:16:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I love crime fiction- some of my favorite books and shows: Mystic River, Breaking Bad, Gomorrah, The Missing, American Crime and American Crime Story, Justified, and so on. But...how...I mean, a lot of times these type of shows have counsel from professionals, a lot of times the writers had first hand experience in that kind of life (see: The Americans, ex-CIA) 

So how does one bloke even get that kind of stuff right? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [S3 Spoilers] Was that a nod to the movie Crank? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-17 19:25:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That episode where Dewey Crowe must collect money because that nurse removed his kidneys reminded me of Crank. The music, the camera work, the race against time factor, it was really like the movie. It's honestly one of my favorite moments from Justified, I love how writes try new things and keep the show fresh and interesting. I also liked the twist that he still had his kidneys lol. Any thoughts? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [Critique] Prologue of my future BEST-SELLER </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-13 07:08:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> She was screaming before the cock even slid inside mushy mush. Frantic sex ensued. 

"Oh! Oh! Oh! Oh! Oh!" The midget girl squaled. 

"Jesus Christ shut the fuck up. And do you have to squeal like a pig?"

Off to one side, a clown was getting swarmed by exactly seventy monkeys, each one intent on pulling down his trousers and stick dicks or fingers through the hapless man's asshole. Tears ran down makeup ruined by tears. 

The giant reached down and grasped the midget's right leg. A savage heave sent the hapless creature flying into outer space. 

The moon, watching all this with haunted eyes, opened an incredibly large maw and sent vomit that was actually semen tumbling down to wash the earth below and these creatures that had no decency at all. 

A continent away, east, a king sat on his throne, getting a blowjob by his 27th son, but let us skip this horrid scene for now, and go further east, where a huge dragon was chained on a vast clearing. Every night, the villagers from the village close to the dragon set out in a procession to molest the poor creature and its exposed genitals. We should skip this too and go *further* east, inside a mountain carved into the likeness of a pair of breasts with a raging penis sticking out in the middle. The legend went that a god so obsessed with the naughty carved it himself. 

Inside the mountain, things were happening. 

Things that could change the world. Bring normality to the world outside. And who wanted normality in a world you didn't have to look long for getting your dick sucked? Or chopped off. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-05 23:56:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Great. Before I read, are there spoilers for later books? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Is this series a tragedy? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-05 23:14:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I've read a couple of times on the Internet about Erikson being compared to Shakespeare. As someone who's still on his 1st read, yes, I know there is tragedy, but almost every book of the main series I've read so far, while tragic, also has moments of light and (some, however slim) happiness. 

But tragedies almost always end...well, tragic. But Erikson juggles so many characters that the end of his books can have some sad stuff but also moments of hope. Thoughts? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-03 01:06:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I can't wait for the moment I open my copy of The Winds of Winter, and then A Dream of Spring 

Should we tell him? I think we should tell him.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-29 22:03:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Sadly, Hitler  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-27 20:47:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> ^(^hey, ^at ^least ^i'm ^contributing ^something ^at ^least...what ^are ^you ^doing ^for ^the ^series?)  


Is buying and reading not enough? 


 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-19 09:38:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Dude, run! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> They talking mad shit bout us </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-17 11:17:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-16 02:10:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I think the relationship between Hannibal and Will is definitely gay, but not in the way you think. In other words, they don't turn each other on via their cocks, they turn each on in their brains.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-15 04:31:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> No. Instead, you touch yourself for your mother.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-15 03:51:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Because you touch yourself.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
