<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject16</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-08 17:35:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Sure she could do some low-level crimes like theft or maybe paying somebody to do shady stuff. But I do not really see how she could engage in high-level corruption without bringing anything of worth to the table in terms of political power (basically her only asset all over the years)? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-08 17:18:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Great comment. How about an argument why I am wrong?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-08 17:01:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If you want to know more about this Mercer guy. Here is a recent profile. Very illuminating:

http://www.newyorker.com/magazine/2017/03/27/the-reclusive-hedge-fund-tycoon-behind-the-trump-presidency

Sadly the article we are commenting on is very low on details.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-08 16:58:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Eichenwald loses his cool way too much. They are still Americans. No need to wish them bad things. Just get rid of the people resonsible for this shitty bill to make overall life better for everyone.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Anti-protest bills would 'attack right to speak out' under Donald Trump </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-08 16:55:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-08 16:53:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The way it is written wikileaks does not indicate the methods at all. Collecting information about the views of a candidate on the US can be done in multiple ways. This could be nefarious if they did shit like breaking into their house to read their documents, but could be completely harmless if they just gathered whatever they said publicly on their view towards the USA. No way to know from this press release.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-08 16:46:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Man, there sure are a lot of Trump bots posting easily debunked shit about Hillary at the moment. I wonder what they want divert attention from? Something about to come out?

This webpage is some low-effort shit. It has zero evidence on it. 
You can read about it on the fucking wikipedia page.
https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Clinton_Foundation


Also this is kind of funny:
What are they selling?

She lost? So she wields zero political power at the moment? What the hell are people who donate to her charity supposed to be buying? What are the people donating to Bill Gates charity buying? 
She might be doing into shady shit, but lost all relevance when losing the election. She literally can not do anything bad because she has no power.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-08 16:38:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The espionage order for "Non Ruling Political Parties and Candidates Strategic Election Plans" which targeted Francois Holland, Marine Le Pen and other opposition figures requires obtaining opposition parties' strategies for the election; information on internal party dynamics and rising leaders; efforts to influence and implement political decisions; support from local government officials, government elites or business elites; **views of the United States**; efforts to reach out to other countries, including Germany, U.K., Libya, Israel, Palestine, Syria   Cote d'Ivoire; as well as information about party and candidate funding.

Okay finding out what happens in other countries before it is written in the newspapers is kind of the CIAs mission? 
This is among the least nefarious things an intelligence agency can do. 

Unless I misunderstand the content of this press release from February? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-08 16:22:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Psychology

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-08 16:07:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [This research tested whether support for the killing of animals serves a terror management function. In five studies, death primes caused participants to support the killing of animals more than control primes, unless the participants self-esteem had been elevated (Study 4). This effect was not moderated by gender, preexisting attitudes toward killing animals or animal rights, perceived humananimal similarity, religiosity, political orientation, or by the degree to which the killing was justified. Support for killing animals after subliminal death primes was also associated with an increased sense of power and invulnerability (Study 5). Implications and future directions are discussed.](http://journals.sagepub.com/doi/abs/10.1177/0146167217697092) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Fear of Death Affects Human Attitudes Toward Animal Life </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-08 16:06:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-08 15:01:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> NYT report on a five-day convention of the Multidisciplinary Association for Psychedelic Studies (MAPS):

Rather than rock stars, scientists from schools like Johns Hopkins and N.Y.U. were the main attraction, bringing evidence to the medical case for psychedelics like psilocybin (the active ingredient in magic mushrooms) to assuage end-of-life anxiety, to help deepen meditation practices, to search for the shared underpinnings of spiritual life, and  in a new study  to explore a possible treatment for severe depression.

Over 50 years later, the advocates gathered here believe that psychedelic drugs, from LSD to magic mushrooms to MDMA (also known as Ecstasy or Molly), are taking a place in mainstream life. We are not the counterculture, said Rick Doblin, the executive director of MAPS, we are the culture.

The 3,000 or so attendees were a striking mix of ages and types: academics in blazers side by side with a demographic more typically associated with Burning Man than with carpeted conference rooms at the Marriott. They were united by a fierce attachment to the belief that psychedelic drugs, far from being a recreational diversion, have the potential to enlighten, cure illness and change the way people relate to one another and our planet.

So exactly why are we witnessing what many are calling a renaissance in psychedelic drugs now, when theyve been around so long?

There are many theories, including that Big Pharmas solutions to mental illness are not satisfactory to everyone; that the internet is helping to spread knowledge about the power and potential of these drugs; that ayahuasca  the tree-bark tea administered by shamans  has become so popular in certain enclaves in the United States that its helping revive interest in other psychedelics; or simply that baby boomers who discovered the wonders of LSD in the 60s are now facing death, and looking, again, for ways to get in touch with their spirituality.

Reporting probably can not get more descriptive and unbiased as this. No more moral panic at all in credible MSM reporting.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Molly at the Marriott: Inside America's Premier Psychedelics Conference </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-08 14:56:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Do Democrats Need to Tweet More Like Trump? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-08 14:48:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-08 14:46:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The Trump administration ratcheted up the pressure on Senate Republicans on Sunday to solve the policy problems in the House of Representatives' bill repealing Obamacare, urging the upper chamber to improve the bill even while defending its most controversial elements.

The White House dismissed those concerns. Mulvaney said the White House expects the bill to change so much that any score of the House bill would be essentially irrelevant. And Priebus said the administration didnt buy the earlier report that estimated the bill could lead to 24 million fewer people having insurance.

Everyone instantly isnt going to come off insurance, Priebus said. Thats the old bill, thats before the amendments were put in. And its also before the Senate takes the bill and makes it even better. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-08 14:39:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  As I step off the train in Roquefort, southern France, I sniff the air appreciatively. It's so good to be out of the Paris bubble, meeting some authentic French people to answer the biggest question in European politics: why did so many people vote for Emmanuel Macron? Was it a lack of economic anxiety, or a lack of racism?

Either way, their concerns deserve to be heard. Some might find them unpalatable, but history has taught us that repressing such views only makes them more virulent. It might not be pleasant to hear them, it might offend our sensibilities, but we have to share our towns and cities with pragmatic centrists, so we must strive to understand them. Too often, during this French presidential cycle, an out-of-touch media elite has failed to understand these people, connected to the political process, broadly trusting of the mainstream media, and what has driven them to vote for a liberal, globalising ex-banker who wants to deregulate the economy.

This is quite well written.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Deep in Macron Country. We must now confront an uncomfortable question. Why did so many French people vote for Emmanuel Macron? Was it a lack of economic anxiety, or a lack of racism? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-08 14:38:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-08 14:25:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Could make a list, but bullet points without the explanations won't tell you much. Rather interesting article I believe.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> 7 psychological concepts that explain the Trump era of politics </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-08 14:24:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Therapists and principals say teens shouldn't watch 13 Reasons Why. We think they're wrong. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-08 14:22:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-07 19:21:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Taken together, findings suggest that alcohol is an effective analgesic that delivers clinically-relevant reductions in ratings of pain intensity

I read that pain is a complex construct that includes huge psychological aspects (reason for placebo) and I would speculate that alcohol makes people care less about the nociceptic input they get? So the nervous signal might not be dampened but the interpretation of it changes in a positive way when you are drunk. This may apply to all kinds of pain and may be the reason why drugs are so successful despite huge attempts to curb their use.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-05 11:22:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Might be a ceiling effect. Maybe the men in the study could not possibly get more horny towards women? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-05 11:15:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> **Submission Statement**

Article about the tension between reactionary philosophy and classical conservative philosophy that has been amplified by Trump and his followers by the leading intellectual conservative publication. Rather abstract in its arguments, but I found it very illuminating.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Conservatisms Intellectual Divide: Classical Liberals vs. Reactionaries </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-05 11:12:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-03 14:51:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Das war auch der Topkommentar in ungefhr allen Threads hier. Und die BILD schreibt was die Leute hren wollen. Die simplen Assoziationen, dass sich die Leute denken knnen: "jo klar das war auch mein erster Gedanke." Jeder der Spiel gezockt hatte musste diesen Gedanken loslassen. 

Oder sind fr dich die Leute die das in den entsprechenden Threads geschrieben haben auch fiese Menschen die nur die armen Computerspieler verfolgen wollen? Da muss man sich schon arg verfolgt fhlen, wenn man das als Beispiel ranzieht. 

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-03 14:47:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Da wird man immer noch bld angeguckt, wenn man zugibt, core gamer zu sein.

Vielleicht solltest du nicht 'core gamer' sagen? 

Fr mich hrt sich das alles nach Strohmnnern an. Kein Mensch stresst sich mehr weil iwer Videospiele spielt.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-03 12:15:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It is some of the best writing out there. The choice of topics may be sometimes elitist (e.g. art stuff), but contrary to other publications whenever they write about something you know a bit about, you realize they know what they are doing and they produce insightful articles.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-02 10:10:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> A recent New Yorker article layed out in detail how the Mercers bought Trump and made him President. Extremely informative. Explains a lot of Trump's 'policies'.

http://www.newyorker.com/magazine/2017/03/27/the-reclusive-hedge-fund-tycoon-behind-the-trump-presidency </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-01 17:49:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Former White House press secretary Ari Fleischer told The Hill in a recent interview that he advocates not showing daily presidential press briefings on live television, arguing "that would cool things down" and lead to less posturing for the cameras.
"I think that would cool things down and calm things down a little bit, and be more old fashioned in the conveyance of information," Fleischer explained. "As opposed to two sides posturing and fighting on air."

On the one hand this statement is probably not false. People put on a show when the cameras are on. On the other hand the Trump administration is so full of liars that there needs to physical evidence every time they say something so that they can not weasel out afterwards.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-01 16:19:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> They really try to avoid him doing interviews, but I guess he wanted to boast about the greatness of his first 100 days. 

They cannot lock him into the cupboard. From time to time he will have to speak to the press.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-28 10:44:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  no hard work

So like Trump who golfs all the time because thinking about things like healthcare is [too complicated](https://www.theguardian.com/us-news/video/2017/feb/27/trump-healthcare-complicated-budget-video) and who is so clueless that he thought [the presidency would be easier than his previous work](http://www.reuters.com/article/us-usa-trump-100days-idUSKBN17U0CA)?

You are arguing a straw man. People in here are angry that Trump does not work. He did not bring a single job back. All he does is empty talk. He is a millionaire Reality TV star. He did not do any hard work his whole life. He has absolutely no qualifications for the job. And nothing in his previous life suggests he has any empathy for hard-working people. 
So I am at a loss why you would defend him.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-28 10:31:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Title does not tell you much, but they interviewed him and this is a great, insightful piece about his first 100 days. 

Some nuggets:
He addressed the idea that his senior aides werent getting along. He called out their names and, one by one, they walked in, each surprised to see reporters in the roomchief of staff Reince Priebus, then chief strategist Steve Bannon, and eventually senior adviser Jared Kushner. The team gets along really, really well, he said.


-

More than 200 of Trumps campaign promises are scribbled in marker on a whiteboard in Steve Bannons West Wing office, which he calls his war room. Other pledges are printed and taped beneath a poster that says: Make America Great Again.

-

In Kushners office, just steps away, theres no Make America Great Again memorabilia. Instead, the whiteboard lists deadlines for bipartisan projects in his newly-founded Office of American Innovation on infrastructure and veterans affairs. Kushner often talks about the presidency like its a business, describing it privately as entrepreneurial and in beta mode. He often doesnt mind when Trump flip-flops, if its in the service of striking a deal.

-

As Trump is beginning to better understand the challengesand the limitsof the presidency, his aides are understanding better how to manage perhaps the most improvisational and free-wheeling president in history. If youre an adviser to him, your job is to help him at the margins, said one Trump confidante. To talk him out of doing crazy things.

-

But theyre learning. One key development: White House aides have figured out that its best not to present Trump with too many competing options when it comes to matters of policy or strategy. Instead, the way to win Trump over, they say, is to present him a single preferred course of action and then walk him through what the outcome could be  and especially how it will play in the press.

-

Of late, some Republican National Committee members have become deeply concerned about Priebus, who was party chairman before joining Trumps team. Priebus, who is distrusted by some rival White House factions and lacks the control previous chiefs of staff have had, has privately complained about the profound frustrations of the job.


-

Since taking office, Trump has 16 times tagged Fox and Friends, the networks morning show, in his tweets, and countless other times weighed in on whatever they were talking about on air. After Democratic Rep. Elijah Cummings went on Morning Joe and asked the president to call him, Trump did. After Republican Rep. Dana Rohrabacher defended Trump in an early Saturday morning Fox News hit, Trump called him moments later, inviting him to an Oval Office meeting. And after news segments, Trump will sometimes call his own advisers to discuss what he saw.

No slight is too small to ignore. West Wing staffers have even fumed about news coverage of the Easter Egg Roll. First, it was that Trumps White House wouldnt be smart enough to pull it off. Then, it was that no one would be there. And after the Easter Egg Roll went off without a hitch, no one wanted to give us any credit, said one senior administration official.

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Trump's First 100 Days: The education of Donald Trump </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-28 10:31:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-28 10:23:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> ["I loved my previous life. I had so many things going," Trump told Reuters in an interview. "This is more work than in my previous life. I thought it would be easier."](http://www.reuters.com/article/us-usa-trump-100days-idUSKBN17U0CA)

How is this a different meaning? 

Also you are wrong. They did not take it from different sentences.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-28 10:21:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This is a pretty short article that everyone should read. It leads to constant headshaking. 

I am still amazed this guy managed to become the President of the USA. 

He misses driving, feels as if he is in a cocoon, and is surprised how hard his new job is.

President Donald Trump on Thursday reflected on his first 100 days in office with a wistful look at his life before the White House.

"I loved my previous life. I had so many things going," Trump told Reuters in an interview. "This is more work than in my previous life. I thought it would be easier."

A wealthy businessman from New York, Trump assumed public office for the first time when he entered the White House on Jan. 20 after he defeated former Secretary of State Hillary Clinton in an upset.

More than five months after his victory and two days shy of the 100-day mark of his presidency, the election is still on Trump's mind. Midway through a discussion about Chinese President Xi Jinping, the president paused to hand out copies of what he said were the latest figures from the 2016 electoral map.

"Here, you can take that, that's the final map of the numbers," the Republican president said from his desk in the Oval Office, handing out maps of the United States with areas he won marked in red. "Its pretty good, right? The red is obviously us."

He had copies for each of the three Reuters reporters in the room.

Trump, who said he was accustomed to not having privacy in his "old life," expressed surprise at how little he had now. And he made clear he was still getting used to having 24-hour Secret Service protection and its accompanying constraints.

"You're really into your own little cocoon, because you have such massive protection that you really can't go anywhere," he said.

When the president leaves the White House, it is usually in a limousine or an SUV.

He said he missed being behind the wheel himself.

"I like to drive," he said. "I can't drive any more."

Many things about Trump have not changed from the wheeler-dealer executive and former celebrity reality show host who ran his empire from the 26th floor of Trump Tower in New York and worked the phones incessantly.

He frequently turns to outside friends and former business colleagues for advice and positive reinforcement. Senior aides say they are resigned to it.

The president has been at loggerheads with many news organizations since his election campaign and decided not to attend the White House Correspondents' Dinner in Washington on Saturday because he felt he had been treated unfairly by the media.

"I would come next year, absolutely," Trump said when asked whether he would attend in the future.
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-28 10:13:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Although the specifics of what constitutes a better life vary from generation to generation, one constant is that children expect to do betteror at least to have a good chance at doing betterthan their parents. Chetty et al. show that this dream did come true for children born in the middle of the 20th century, but only for half of children born in 1984 (see the Policy Forum by Katz and Krueger).


Additional discussion here:
http://science.sciencemag.org/content/356/6336/382

I think papers in Science can be accessed by anyone after a free registration. Or use sci-hub.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
