<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject4921</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> A special sugar modification of Yes Associated Protein (YAP) is essential for liver tumorigenesis that is associated with high glucose levels. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-10 06:28:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-09 07:24:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Trout, Donaldson, taillon, Brantley, Matz, .....this shit does not end.  And here I thought I had a semi solid team to start the year.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-09 06:57:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Man, all I did was just hit the 'X' button to stop loading the page before the paywall popped up and it worked.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-08 00:59:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yup.  Don't mind trailers, but get fucking rid of the ads that are not for upcoming features.  People are paying insane amounts of money per ticket. We don't need ads taking up time.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-08 00:17:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Drinkery or Steampunk Alley </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-08 00:14:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Like I said, 'ethically controversial'....I in no way claimed it was either right or wrong. 

FWIW, overall, I believe Hopkins is a great benefit to the city and society, even though it is flawed sometimes.  No institution is perfect, and it isn't always easy to tell what is ethically correct when doing an experiment.  Hindsight is always 20/20.  Hopkins is pretty much the only entity in the city that's actively investing in neighborhoods even though their plans aren't always perfect.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-07 23:39:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Remember when ubaldo Jimenez had an insane half of a season?  People are still buying Into him because of that.  Story is the same. Just because a guy has a crazy half of season doesn't mean anything over the long run.  Baseball is a cruel game, eventually everyone comes crashing back to what will truly be their average production.  Story is just the offensive version of Ubaldo.  There's always danger of buying into a player with virtually 0 track record over multiple years. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-07 22:33:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Multiple DLs this week and now lost an additional 3 starts from losing this game.  Fuck this week. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-07 07:16:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's all over Eastern MD.  There are maniacs on the road in the city, on 83, on 695, 95, all around the beltway in DC....MD is really, really bad.  And I've lived in a lot of different states on the Eastern seaboard.  MD by far and away is the worst.  Not just bad driving, but dangerously aggressive and vindictive.  MD people need to chill the fuck out while driving.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-07 07:07:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Reasons for hate:

--they own HUGE swaths of the city and don't pay tax

--they pay many of their workers low wages

--ethically controversial medical studies involving minorities, people from other poorer countries

--Buying up property and kicking out poorer/long time residents in minority neighborhoods or making it unaffordable for them after they fix up the area.  

Reasons for love:

--provide jobs with reasonably good benefits to a looooooooot of people

--many Nobel Prize winners and laureates.  Some of THE single greatest minds on the planet are housed at Hopkins

--The US wouldn't have won WWII w/o hopkins and APL:  see the proximity fuze

--Fixing up large portions of the city, trying to get their employees to move into Baltimore (who'll end up being decent tax payers)

--Positive community programs, e.g. underprivileged high school kids from Baltimore schools can go to Hopkins (one of the top universities in the world) for completely free

--Some of the best physicians and medicine in the world </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-07 04:06:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Taillon, Trout, Donaldson.....when the  does this stop? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-06 18:35:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I think the counter argument is that is that using names simply 'sticks'.  Med school students use the same technique to memorize inordinate amount of information using names, poems, or word play that have 0 related to the science involved.  Some chemical transformations have multiple steps, so I'm not sure what exactly you'd descriptively call those transformations in a concise manner.  Some palladium, ruthenium, etc. catalyzed reactions have extremely complex catalysts or mechanisms, so how do you descriptively name them using less than 200 letters? Everyone doing organic knows, however, what exactly you mean when you say ' Hoffman rearrangement' for example. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> A move towards using 'unnamed' reactions in chemistry? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-06 11:22:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So while at the NIH this discussion came up with a very, very high level and famous scientist there who talked about how at one university they've come up with idea that reactions in chemistry will no longer be taught according to the names of the scientists who discovered it.  For example, no names will be used to describe reactions like 'Diels-Alder', 'Suzuki couplings', 'Sonagashira', etc.  They'll instead be called  things along the lines of 'electrophilic addition to xyz...' etc. etc. The reason being that all of the reactions learned in organic 101 are named after men and that they didn't want to discourage women in science.  Someone eventually quipped, 'but what are we supposed to call Michaelis-Menten kinetics then?'

How do the labrats feel about this one?  Just curious.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-06 10:11:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I try to avoid the areas where they're most likely going to be, although it doesn't always work because sometimes they surprisingly pop up in new locations.  I almost never drive down President Street if I don't have to. 

I've had them hit my car multiple times and cuss me out for being a 'mother fucking faggot' because my automatic windshield wipers came on once they started spraying, which they did NOT take kindly to, assuming I was the one doing it on purpose to shoo them away.  

This was during the summer. My windows were completely rolled up.  My only interaction with them was waving no incessantly (without ANY verbal contact at all).

 I'm not sure how I see that I was in anyway disrespectful at all or wasn't 'treating them like a human being' or was being a thinly veiled racist by simply waving no.  In what society do you live in where older people have to walk on eggshells about trying not to be 'disrespectful' to youth like teenagers?  There are window washers at the end of 83.  There are window washers at President/Lombard.  There are window washers at North Ave./Maryland.  There are window washers sometimes on Central/Baltimore.  There over a dozen panhandlers on MLK/Lombard/at the end of 83 and various other parts of downtown.  Am I supposed to give all of these people money?  And when I don't want to that means I'm a racist?  I've lived in this city for years; sometimes I simply get annoyed for being constantly hounded for money and it has nothing to do with being a racist, it is the fact that I'm constantly being nagged nearly 7 days a week nearly all year, every year for money, and when I refuse I get cussed out and get called a 'faggot'.  I'm not even rich, nor do I drive a fancy car.  

 If these kids are so enterprising, give them a space and funds to startup a car wash somewhere near downtown.  Make them learn useful business skills starting a legitimate business.  Hell, there is a completely lack of any car washes close to the center of the city--they'd make a killing doing legitimate work. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-05 00:25:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm not really a fan of parts and labor (dine in) but they made a really good sandwich the one time I went. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-04 06:26:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Literally perfect.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-04 04:39:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Didn't you read the link?  The NIH's own investigation shows that the idea that super labs are more productive the more money you dump into them is dubious.  

People in this thread also talk about how a super lab has to blow $60k on an instrument they don't even really want, only because they have a use it or lose situation.  I'd argue $60k would be better spent on a small lab that's going to actually investigate a new hypothesis rather than buy a super lab a fancy machine that is just going to collect dust. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-03 18:08:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Alconox </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-03 16:46:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> About time.  Mid career scientists get screwed hard.  In super labs, students in training can go an entire year without seeing the PI in charge and are governed by a whole bunch of post-docs while the PI is going on tour throughout the world trying to drum up funds for any one of their dozen startup companies or is giving talks in order to maintain being famous and in the spotlight.  


EDIT:  I also found this quite eye opening:  "While implementation of a GSI limit is estimated to affect only about 6 percent of NIH-funded investigators, we expect that, depending on the details of the implementation, it would free up about 1,600 new awards to broaden the pool of investigators conducting NIH research and improve the stability of the enterprise."

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-03 16:37:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> https://www.reddit.com/r/fantasybaseball/comments/68axij/what_is_the_worst_move_youve_made_thus_far/


Yikes.  

I actually didn't make that move on a whim though, it took me 2 days to think over and make that mistake. The reason why I fell for that mistake was because Judge never hit more than 20 HRs in lower ball and it wasn't clear if he had a starting job at the time; meanwhile pundits were saying DeShields Jr. was a lock for the gig and 50 SBs. 

You have to understand our league though.  LMs constantly try to pull off the [Sweeney plan](http://deadspin.com/5789399/the-epic-story-of-a-new-jersey-prosecutor-who-stole-my-idea-and-made-fantasy-baseball-history) in order to pull off asymmetric wins vs. teams that are better.  I already had tons of power on my team with Trout, Machado, Donaldson, Myers, and HanRam so I decdided to pull the trigger and drop Judge for DeShields Jr. because I didn't want anyone trying to out steal me.  

Yes, a mistake for sure.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-03 05:36:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> nothing thai about it but it looks good.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Phosphorylation of inositol using a phosphoramidite </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-03 02:53:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I found a beautiful reaction from a 1988 tetrahedron paper where they phosphorylate inositol using a dibenzyl diisopropyl phosphoramidite with tetrazole in DCM.  2 hours later they add mCPBA.  
I tried this and it works like no other.  Before I was trying to copy JOC procedures where they were heating carbohydrates in phosphoric acid.....what a mess that was. 


So how does the phosphoramidite reaction work?   I do a lot of chemistry but don't have a doctorate level understanding, so I don't always understand some synthetic transformations and why they work.  In the end I most care about the biochemistry but it would be nice to know how that amidite reaction works and why it works so beautifully. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-03 02:40:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Meh I always BS with them. They tell me about their families, vacation, etc.  Heh, I told them where I was going to a conference once and they were very familiar with the location/city and they gave me an AWESOME recommendation for both a small botique hotel and restaurant. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-03 02:36:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Lol, I actually really love the manual ones.... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-02 16:04:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Ahhhh the dreaded oblique.  Can't tell you how many times I've had a player injure their oblique from a 'violent sneeze'.  I know it has happened more than once to me.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-02 15:56:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That was such a stupid era of hockey though.  Goalies would routinely have  3.00 GAA and still be considered 'good'.  No way would Gretzky score more than 140-150 pts in his prime this day in age.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-02 05:12:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The key would be to genetically engineer a bacteria or something with the a similar acting enzyme as what's found in bugs and have it produce something useful like ethanol instead.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-02 04:59:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Union 
Waverly
Blue Pit

One of my favorite mini bar crawls.  


Honestly, Baltimore is small enough you can afford to Uber anywhere.  You could do a brewery/distillery tour/tasting:

Baltimore Whiskey Co.

Waverly

Union

Heavy Seas

Peabody Heights

Monument City

Sagamore

Diamondback

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-01 15:55:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm liberal leaning and this sounds like a mess.  You want $15 hr wages, want more funding for schools, want to fight against racism/sexism/homophobia, change immigration.....

Well which is it?  This is why the Dems continue to get smoked in the election polls.  Liberals have no clear agenda.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-01 14:40:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Touche.  I think I had about 5 beers when I wrote that, heh.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-01 03:32:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Why the fuck do any players have any say when it comes to shit like this? Sorry man, your're not the one paying $230 million for your stupid ass, so YES YOU WILL GET THE MRI.  The staff should literally tell Thor to stfu and get the MRI which will only take 20 minutes.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-01 03:29:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So basically the only player to do it in the history of the league. None of those stupid old time records count before the modern era of baseball.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-30 21:55:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thor is a dumbass.  Literally just get the MRI. It is non invasive and doesn't take long at all.  Shit, those things cost thousands of dollars for regular folks. I'd get one just for shits and giggles if I could since they're so expensive. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-30 19:37:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Protein precipitation. You can do modified bligh dyer extraction or something like an Acetone/ acetonitrile precipitation to remove protein.  Personally I would try the bligh dyer method first and then analyze the aqeuous extract. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-30 03:09:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Anyone.  That place can be a total shit show (but entertaining).   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What is the worst move you've made thus far? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-29 20:39:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Ok, I'll admit I made the egregious error of dropping Aaron Judge for Delino DeShields before the season began when experts were saying DeShields would have a full time job.  I didn't want people beating me in steals because I have plenty of power.  I was also convinced by chatter on this sub that talked about how Judge never hit a huge amount of HRs in the minors, his strike out rate, and how it is hard to project.  Damn, I'm never going to live that move down.  And Judge was a 22nd round keeper. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-29 04:36:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Lame.  All those trades were fair.  Any trade that is not collusion should be allowed. Period.  Time to leave.  Vetoing trades is the worst thing ever invented.  Only the LM should be allowed to block a trade and they should only do it if there's cheating going on.  That's it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-29 04:23:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Their new place is an attractive space.  Definitely a place to go to watch an Os or Ravens game and stay away from an obnoxious crowd. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-28 15:13:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Wake the fuck up Machado.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-28 14:41:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It went from $12 smoothies before to an uber specialized hobby shop.  Will anything ever make it there?   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-28 14:40:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Steve Aoki in town for it.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-28 01:42:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The human body is simply not made to throw a ball that hard, that many times, and for a long period of time.  I don't care if your 6'10" and 300 lbs, there's a Hugh probability that your arm or shoulder will give out.  

Teams should stop emphasizing power characteristics such as fastball velocity and tell their staff to concentrate more on consistency, placement, deception in delivery, ball rotation, and movement. Top out fastballs at 92 mph.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-27 15:09:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Heh, glycobiologist here.  

It wasn't until the 80s that we discovered a direct link between cellular consumption of glucose and direct modification of protein physiology.  We now know of direct links between glucose and all sorts of things like regulation of gene expression, epigenetics, and modification of almost every single cell signaling pathway.  Post-translational modification via sugars is sort of like the dark matter that is hiding in the cell and something people still haven't heard of too much.  Here's an overview of abstracts and free articles:

http://journal.frontiersin.org/article/10.3389/fendo.2014.00221/full

http://jcb.rupress.org/content/208/7/869

http://www.cell.com/trends/endocrinology-metabolism/abstract/S1043-2760(13)00033-7

https://www.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/labs/articles/22522719/

http://www.nature.com/nchembio/journal/v4/n2/full/nchembio.68.html

https://www.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/pubmed/11522386

http://www.jbc.org/content/289/50/34472.full.pdf

https://www.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/pubmed/20466550

http://www.fasebj.org/content/28/1_Supplement/608.4

https://www.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/pmc/articles/PMC3985334/

https://www.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/pubmed/22128088

https://www.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/pmc/articles/PMC2919351/ </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-27 14:41:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> OK, this is where I frequent where mostly 0 tourists go:  Clavel, Mayuree Thai Tavern, Venice Tavern, Waverly, Peabody Heights, Union Brewery, Koco's Pub (crabcakes), Blue Pitt BBQ, Wicked Sisters, Of Love and Regret, Bar Liquorice, 1157, De Klein Duivel (mentioned already), Wet City, Walt's Inn, Cardinal Tavern, Mount Vernon Market Place, Hoehn's (would stop here it's almost 100 years old and is truly Baltimore), Charmery, Sunday Farmer's Market under the JFX (if you're still around) and get a Black Sauce biscuit sandwich (get there early before they sell out) .  

Most of those are watering holes, you guys have pretty much everything in NYC to eat.  I'm also biased--I absolutely hate going out in main Fell's Point, Canton Square, or Federal Hill.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-27 14:33:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I like how they fry it, but agree that it needs seasoning.  Salt and some stronger spices in the batter.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-27 14:32:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Good story.  Hopefully they can turn it into something lucrative after building a customer base.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-27 06:23:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> One if my most fav. of all time was Croatia.  Fly into Zagreb and rent a car. Travel down the coast and end in Dubrovnik.  The entire country is absolutely stunning. Tons of towns and cities with a Medieval feel where you can get lost in all sorts of small alleyways and find an awesome cafe, restaurant or bar.   If you have time get on a boat and go out to some of the islands.

If that is too much for a last minute vacation, then doing something like the Pacific Northwest on up to Vancouver is pleasant.  It's beautiful up there. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Rancid and Iggy Pop - No Fun [Rock] </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-27 06:03:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-27 04:29:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> . Dogwood used to be there and served excellent food but it closed.  I think reviewers were overly harsh on Le Garage on Yelp, because we always liked the food and cocktails.  There were simply too many snooty Hampden hipsters destroying it.  

Location seems cursed.  Both Dogwood and Le Garage were kind of dark and mellow inside.  If the concept is going to be changed make it very bright and open.  Hampden doesn't have too much of that. 


 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-26 15:24:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Also forgot to mention Barfly's.  A little underrated hole in the wall that makes good pizza if you like the thicker Matthew's type of pizza.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-26 15:17:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The funniest part is that liberals go to see Milo and Coulter in droves *because* they want to be outraged.  

I mean if you want those kinds of people to disappear, stop giving them an audience to spew to.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-26 15:14:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Have you ever been a victim of crime, specifically one committed with a  deadly weapon? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-26 15:08:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I've been robbed before and had a gun pointed in my face.  

I can tell you at that moment in time I wish I had the ability to do something more than just nothing except praying that this guy isn't going to shoot me in the face over $8 in my wallet and a POS phone that's 5 years old.  

Does carry and conceal prevent crime on a macro scale?  Debatable.  But does macroscale trend matter to you when you're sitting there with someone pointing a gun in your face?  Why do we put anti-lock braking systems in cars when they have close to 0 net effect on fatal car crashes?  

https://crashstats.nhtsa.dot.gov/Api/Public/ViewPublication/811182


That's because you want at least the safety option of not having your brakes seize up/your car skidding when you need it.  
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-26 15:02:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Too much competition, plus the owners used to be assholes to a degree (they had an obnoxious set of rules on their website before).  Maybe ownership has changed since then, but there's simply way, way too many places to compete with, plus parking is horrendous in Mt. Vernon. Would pick Paulie Gee's, Birroteca, Rads, Isabella's, or Our House before thinking about Iggie's.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-25 21:09:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You look into CTAB precipitation at all?   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-25 15:28:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Ahhhh NBA Jam.  You kids won't remember how awesome it was when you could shatter that backboard.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-24 23:06:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It happens.  Start a new line.  Skin cells could flake off, you drop some hair into it, you sneezed/coughed outside of the hood yet droplets got inside....who knows.  You do cell culture long enough you're bound to contaminate at least one culture.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-24 03:14:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's so dumb.  PURE THC is literally 100% legal and sold everyday by pharmacists.  But oh god, grow it in plant form the world explodes:

http://www.webmd.com/drugs/2/drug-9308/marinol-oral/details

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-24 03:05:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> There's a stigma?  Shit, I go all of the time because many days I have off hours when everyone else is at work or my wife is at work.  

I actually prefer going to the movies alone during the early afternoon.  

My dad is a huge movie buff and has gone to the cinemas nearly every week for the past 40 years.  He worked the midnight to 8 AM shift and goes to the movies by himself nearly 100% of the time.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-24 03:04:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Probably for rapidity in this case.  And what does it matter?  A perfect score is a perfect score no matter how you bowl.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Bowling a perfect game in only 90 seconds (new world record) </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-24 01:44:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-23 18:04:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hanley.......You're killing me brosef  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-23 17:59:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yes. If this is another elbow surgery he'll be out for the year and then on a conservative program for a year after that.  He will already be in his 30s at that point with not much upside.  And that's only if he still has a job 2 years from now.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-23 02:32:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Career could be ending soon.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-22 21:39:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Good lord, Byron Buxton looks truly *awful*.  How did the scouts get it so wrong on him?  He's going to be out of the league for good very soon if he doesn't start to right the ship.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-22 21:16:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Glycobiologist/chemical biologist. 

More than happy to talk to about sugars, sugar chemistry, and sugar biology all day long!   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-22 20:30:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Lying....ok, because it is everyday someone posts on a forum like Reddit with the name Sialic Acid.  

Uncle Tom....OK.  I know reddit skews younger, I think many in their 20s still haven't had a lot of experience doing things like dealing with all of the politics that come while working in places like institutions of higher learning, doing something like pitching a business plan, or pitching your idea for a new project to the board running your discovery program in an industry like biotech.  

You simply never win over people when you try to use blunt force.  I've learned my lesson through many failures.  What scientists are good at--science.  What they're terrible at--politics (whether in academia, industry, or government) and policy making.  If you want to convince people to vote for administrations with strong environmentally focused platforms, who are committed to funding institutions like the NIH, or who'll support things like stem cell research, then you need to convince the public using more finesse than what's going on in DC today.  Example, if scientists are so concerned about this topic, why aren't they going out to Kansas, Nebraska, Ohio, etc. and doing simple things like town hall meetings to have friendly Q and A sessions on climate change?  Describe to people in HARD and REAL ECONOMIC terms how climate change will affect their ability to farm corn and earn a living in the future. 


 It's always the economy that will drive the vote.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-22 20:25:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> And you're the reason why science fails at policy making.  

You're done 'trying not to the hurt the feelings of **blue collar idiots**'.  

Congrats, you just pulled a Hillary and lost the vote.  It doesn't matter if you're a scientist, blue collar Jim in Nebraska still has the same voting power as you do and you just convinced him not to vote for science.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-22 20:14:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Machado too. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-22 18:58:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Ok, a dumbass who has committed over 20 years to science as a professional.  You are literally admitting that this whole charade is political.  That in of itself is anti-science. 

This is nothing more than a liberal march.  I'm a liberal too on many issues, but all this march is doing is alienating the very types of people science should be trying to convince that things like climate change are real.  

Guess what this whole debacle is going to do?  A whole bunch of nothing.  Guess what scientists should really be doing?  Listening to people who don't think climate change is real and trying to explain to them why they may be wrong in a non-condescending manner.  This march won't do anything to accomplish the more IMPORTANT goal of actually trying to influence the vote.  

As I've gotten older I've learned the hard way that getting what you want requires you to have much more tact and finesse rather than doing something like this where you're basically telling half the voters 'You're a stupid anti-science supporter!' or 'You're wrong! I'm right because I'm a scientist!'.    

This whole thing will be viewed as yet again another condescending attack from the liberal elitists who think they're above the blue collar man in middle America.  Call me crazy if I think scientists should use more tact.... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-22 18:36:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Scientist here.  Science and its practitioners should be apolitical.  Let's be honest here, this march is filled with people who only want to surround themselves with the same liberal echo chamber that is pervasive in the academic setting.....i.e. this is REALLY a partisan march with an anti-Trump agenda. This is bad for science. 


And before you get upset, I'm no Trump voter at all.  If you want to protest Trump, do it under a different brand. People are completely overreacting. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-22 18:19:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> No, i've never seen that product in these parts, but make it yourself?  What, vodka + heavy cream, sugar, vanilla and 1 min with a blender? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-22 10:59:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> PngaseF </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-22 10:55:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Many places let you separate based on aqueous, non-halogenated, and halogenated waste.


Never use any type of plastic for organics. It's actually cringe worthy when I see biologists trying to pipette out reagents and organic solvents using things like serological pipettes.  Not only can you contaminate the bottle of solvents, you can contaminate your biology.  Use glass for anything that's organic unless it is something crazy like HF.  

Use glass pipettes with a bulb to measure out volumes in a 10ml graduated cylinder.  For larger volumes like 10ml, 25ml etc.  if you need to be very accurate, use analytical glassware like a volumetric flask or glass  volumetric pipettes.

In general, even if you don't do chemistry, the rule of thumb is NO when it comes to plastic + any organic solvent.  It would behoove biologists to do that:

http://www.nature.com/news/2008/081209/full/news.2008.1291.html
   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-22 00:30:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> People have to move out and pay for new housing. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-20 14:20:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Who cares.  If he can go twice per week and pitch 3-4 ip everytime and rack up 1.5-2 k/ip that's the equivalent of a valuable starter that'll help your ratios and counting stats. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-20 06:38:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> As a Machado owner...........please fucking end April.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-20 06:34:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hope more teams do this in real life so we can finally get rid of the entire category of the save all together.  put in the best damn RP for the situation, regardless of some mythical assigned duty to pitch only at the end of the game.  I hope every team employs 4-5 'closers' in the future so that we can all completely ignore such a stupid category.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-20 04:04:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You know this dude has his own reddit account and loves to talk to the public right?


u/TheMrTrashWheel

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-19 06:58:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Nah, our little guy ALWAYS flops and shows his belly to us as soon as we get home from work AND loves it rubbed. 

https://vid.me/HbET

Maybe he's just a weirdo.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-19 06:44:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> No way.  Brach could literally be a top 5-10 closer if he gets the job.  And forearm injuries are notoriously ominous for long DL stints.  You don't drop a solid guy that has the job locked down for a guess. 

Kelley hasn't been THAT great this season overall either.  The nats could make a trade or a move for a closer later.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-19 06:40:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I just pray I get to see a player have a 1.000 slg for the entire season.  


Who doesn't like a big pile of beef? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-19 06:32:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Nathan. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-19 04:59:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I dunno.  I'd hold Treinen for just a bit longer.  Pick up Kelley too if you have the space.  

http://www.federalbaseball.com/2017/4/18/15206438/washington-nationals-closer-blake-treinen-growing-pains

You just might have to wait out the shit storm for the kid to get over whatever mental block is causing him to choke.  The higher brass went w/ Treinen for a reason, they probably don't want an egg on their face, at least not yet.  Relievers began Monday this week with a 4.10 ERA, compared to a 3.76 ERA in April of last season. Many of them are potential playoff contenders; the Rangers, Mariners and Cubs have all endured blown saves.  Don't forget, we're talking about people and not just commodities here.  Teams do want their players to develop and will be more patient than fantasy players.  



LOL, watch this shit show get our ol' boy Nathan his job back.  
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-19 04:43:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Dusty put in Kelley in a massive jam.  


That means you need to pick up Glover probably.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-19 04:38:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Alright Nats went to Kelley.  Does that mean he's higher up the closer chain than Glover? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-19 04:36:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Have Treinen and Scherz.  Don't fuck me sideways and blow both the save and the win Treinen.  Fuck face.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-19 04:27:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Old.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Any idea of who'd crack the LAD rotation next if Ryu keeps stinking up the joint? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-19 04:25:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Alex wood or is it Urias time?   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> TIL that during the course of normal operations submarines build up 'magnetic signatures' due to the Earth's magnetic field that make them more vulnerable to detection. The Navy 'deperms' subs regularly to make them magnetically silent again. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-19 03:39:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-19 00:49:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> La Food Marketa.  Dylan's.  Rachel's new American.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-18 23:48:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If you're 100% it isn't due to degradation ( you can even overload inhibitor) then your antibody is shite.  Just get a new one from a reliable vendor.  Not worth wasting more time. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> TIL that getting bit by the Lone Star Tick can possibly make you violently allergic to meat for the rest of your life. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-18 20:21:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-17 18:44:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> "Brandon Grimes, now 31, was charged in the killing of Chesley's father. Grimes had been arrested 17 times, including twice for handgun possession before Troy Chesley's killing, but was convicted only six times, for nonviolent offenses.

The case prompted outrage from police officials and politicians, who expressed frustration over issues that persist 10 years later: easy access to guns and repeat offenders."


Yowza </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-17 18:31:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Stop sucking Snell.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Any useful site where you can find the probability of players stealing a base against a pitcher starting the next day or find who's allowed the most stolen bases for an upcoming starter? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-16 04:55:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Need to attempt a spot start to catch my opponent in SBs to either tie him in that category or beat him in it in order to tie or win the week.  Wondering what I can do in order to maximize my odds.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-15 20:31:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Is now the perfect time to buy low on Quintana from frustrated owners? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-14 19:17:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Dickey </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> TIL we were able to figure out that heart cells can indeed renew themselves because baby boomers were born during the cold war when nuclear bomb testing was intense, allowing scientists to radioactive carbon date heart cells. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-14 07:53:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-14 06:53:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Jesus christ, the baby boomers are fucking insane.  Amazing how they learned NOTHING growing up during the cold war.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-14 03:59:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> of course, the only year I spend a 1st rd pick on this guy.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-14 03:35:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Seriously, why don't they ever warn you about late fees?  How the hell are you supposed to know if you owe if you're never notified?  Sometimes I do worry that I have some toll I forgot about a long time ago after driving on say the ICC and that the MTA never contacted me about it yet will come back years later with huge fines.  I don't have an EZ pass either.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Highway of Death during Desert Storm. NSFW </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-14 03:16:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Any slim chance Reed keeps job even when Familia comes back? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-13 14:42:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> He's been quite reliable as a closer thus far.  Is there better than a 25% chance, let's say, that he keeps the job...I.e. he's not an immediate dump in the near future?


Edit:. Stupid phone autocorrect typo. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-13 14:36:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Separating close diastereomers. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-12 18:44:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Damn, wasted a weekly move on Bush.  Wake up and less than 24h later he has shoulder problems now.  I'm staying completely away from this hot garbage of a bullpen.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-12 14:52:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> $40-60k.  Sorry, biology and biomedical sciences have shit for pay.  

Do not give in as best as you can for a low salary.  Your first salary is often the most important, because if you give up $10k now, it might take you 10 years to get to the salary that you should have originally gotten if you just bargained harder.  There are always other employers and different industries if you're willing to branch out and motivate yourself to network.  Wait until you find an employer that is willing to pay you what you think you're worth.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-12 14:46:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You still agreed to the terms and conditions when you bought the ticket.  

Not that I like United though.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-12 06:47:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Best brunch: Mayuree Thai Tavern.  I know...Thai for brunch right? But they are amazing.  Their potatoes with a slight Thai flair are AMAZING and their french toast with pandan sauce is not only 100% unique and creative, it is delicious.  Their purveyors are also the same exact ones a ton of those fancy overpriced places in harbor east use, so the ingredients are higher quality.  The bartender there also makes some of the best and most creative cocktails in the city.  You gotta try the 5 Scotts drink which creatively uses 5 spice and his out of this world ginger tamarind sangria, both of which he invented.  Best brunch. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Antique 121 Year Old Dunk Tank Mouse Trap In Action </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-10 05:20:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-10 03:03:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Despite how vehemently self-cutters will argue, you can almost *always* tell when someone cuts their own hair at home.  The lines around their ears and the back of their head always look messed up or aren't neat.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-10 02:14:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I just worry it'll zap his power. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-09 20:15:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> 5x5 obp league.

C: Perez

1b: hanram

2b: zobrist, j. Ramirez

SS: Machado

3b: Donaldson

OF: Brantley, Myers, trout

UTIL: j. Turner, moncada, kipnis

Sp: scherzer, Snell, Norris, Cole, taillon, Ryu, wright

Rp: melancon, treinen, Ramos, Reed.

This team is getting its ass kicked. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-08 23:18:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> UV should be more than good enough for serotonin . Simple HPLC should work like butter.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-08 23:02:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> 1000x?   I know you said you checked a dozen times, but it highly sounds like you're missing a dilution calculation somewhere.  Mg to ug or ml to ul somewhere or vice versa. Could be in you Elisa calcs.

If I absolutely had to pick between the two, hplc is the absolute gold standard. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> FC Dallas under-15 boys squad beat the U.S. Women's National Team in a scrimmage </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-08 17:56:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-08 17:48:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Probably just some extremely polluted water way.  A tire with the bones of a dead bird or other animal around it.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-08 17:28:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Heh it's worth a shot.  File for $900 million and hope that Warner pays you $10k-20k to go away.  Why not?   Even $5k would be sweet.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-07 06:07:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Don't.  Unless they have OF/1b eligibility and get over 400 ABs.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-07 04:41:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> How long until owners start to get frustrated and/or bail on T. Turner? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-06 04:01:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Kershaw will have the best season of his entire career and one for the history books.  Gets Cy and MVP.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-06 03:13:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Ask your co-workers? 

http://www.baltimoresun.com/news/maryland/baltimore-city/bs-md-ci-schools-legislative-audit-20121006-story.html

They all seem to have their greasy hands in the honeypot and then have the gall to cry that there is a 'funding crisis'.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-06 00:15:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The school system is completely inept.  Didn't they 'lose' something like 1000 computers?   They also have had horrible problems before  of unauthorized staff changing  payroll hours that have cost millions of dollars in 'overtime' to be paid.  The school system accountants are so inept that even the busing companies have been rippinng off the system, as evidenced by the fact that the school system was charged fees based on THE SAME EXACT mileage for several months in a row.....Or something along those lines (iirc).  Wouldn't doubt at all if some admin in the school system have a 'friend' who owns or runs the bus company. There are so many criminal elements in and around the Baltimore City school system that it is basically a mafia of people all with their hands in the taxpayer honeypot.  When everyone in the system steals a little bit here and there it quickly adds up to millions of dollars 'lost' leading to a 'budget crisis'. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Can r/migraine help me out with my project? How much would you be willing to pay for new CGRP therapies? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-04 08:00:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> First time doing a stock pitch. All competitors in a new class of drug looks extremely similar in terms of clinical results/efficacy. Any other ways to predict who will win or capture a larger share of the market? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-04 06:55:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm looking at CGRP antibodies and am analyzing TEVA.  Teva's, Lilly's, Amgen's and Alder's therapies all look very similar in terms of efficacy for treating migraines.  What other factors must be looked at to see how one company could differentiate themselves?  Something like access to distribution channels?  Costs of production?  How will one company dominate this sector if all of their treatments look the same? Or will they just equally share it?  

Sorry if these are novice questions, this is my first time attempting at stock pitch.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-04 06:41:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Nah, nothing like mai tai.  Will be honest--some of the ones in house DO contain sugar, but they're not crap like Mai Tais, Whiskey Sours etc which contain gross amounts of sugar.  They have a Thai Side Car which is delish.  Andy also experiments with using fish sauce, thai chilis, 5 spice (what you use in stuff like pa lo), drinks made with Mehkong etc. for some of his drinks. He also is quite good at making classic cocktails and has been trying to learn a lot about them.   

Mayuree is definitely NOT a lounge/fancy place at all though (just a warning in case that's what you're looking for).     </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-04 04:09:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Of Love and Regret

Blue Pit

1157

Magdalena

Wicked Sisters

Wit and Wisdom

Cardinal Tavern

Grand Cru

Barfly's

Rachel's New American

Mayuree Thai Tavern


Our favorite on that list is Mayuree (relative to the price). Andy behind the bar is always whipping up something new and does  cocktails (some with a Thai flair) you won't find anywhere else in Baltimore. And it is never super duper crowded. Highly recommend their 5 spice cocktail which he invented and perfected.  And make sure you pair one of their drinks w/ their taro custard dessert, which is amazing--and it's another thing that you won't find anywhere else in Baltimore and is in fact hard to find just about anywhere else in the west.  
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-03 14:53:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yup, same here.  1 hour ahead then is normal.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-03 06:28:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> impressive performance  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-03 03:16:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Melancon blowing 100% of his career save opportunities in a Giants uniform. I dunno how much longer he is going to have the job at that rate. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-03 02:09:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> $80 for gas+electric in a 1 bedroom 1 ba apartment with shite for insulation during the spring and early summer.  Where. I need ac and heat during the summer and winter, respectively, about $110-160 (higher if it is a bad month, obviously). </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-03 00:12:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This one again??? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-02 20:42:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Gabriela Szabo:

https://www.google.com/search?q=gabriela+szabo source=lnms tbm=isch sa=X ved=0ahUKEwjmtoO7tobTAhVl4YMKHRqfDvoQ_AUIBigB biw=1536 bih=755

YES PLEASE.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-02 20:42:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> And how well did that work for 'ya over the past 8 years for a guy like Nolasco? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-02 19:17:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> He's done.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Somebody had to eat all of those poisonous mushrooms, berries, and other plants for people to figure out what was safe to eat. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-01 18:45:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Woe to the guy who thought they could eat a death cap 'shroom after cooking or the first person who accidentally tried destroying angels.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-01 18:42:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> How much do these go for by the lbs in the store?  People actually eat these things?  Not afraid of getting poisoned?  Who is an expert with an actual degree?   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-01 18:30:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I did read the post.  

No to NOlasco.  You can split hairs all you want, and yes, I read that you've already addressed that he has never, ever lived up to Saber potential.  Half a season w/ LAA isn't impressive after blowing chunks his entire career.  No.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-01 05:50:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Trea Turner at 3 overall.  I remember when Anthony Rendon went early in the 2nd too based off of one year's worth of work.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-01 05:46:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> No, never, EVER again.  

Nolasco was SUPPOSED to 'right the ship' and 'regress to the norm' because he was and seems to still be a darling for SABER nerds based on his peripherals.  Guess what? We've been waiting for Nolasco to show up since 2009 based on his peripherals, based on his ball park, based on his 'bad luck'.  At some point the excuses have to end, some pitchers never live up to what 'their peripherals suggest'.  FIP will always be a fake number in fantasy, the numbers that will always count in the end no matter what for fantasy are ERA and WHIP.     </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-31 15:52:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Happy hour loop at Union Brewery, Waverly and then Blue Pit.  

If you like plants and flowers and that sort of stuff, B Willow just opened up in Remington.  I'm not a huge plant guy, but I thought it was awesome.  You can build your own terrarium, even an aquatic one, and then head over to R House for a bite.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-31 05:26:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yet we have public funds to put towards[ $750 million dollar football stadiums](http://oak.247sports.com/Bolt/Owner-of-NHLs-Vegas-franchise-criticizes-Raiders-stadium-deal-52059928), profits from which will be privately owned.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
