<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject2140</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-10 04:24:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> No and thats not what anyone is predicting so fuck off with your strawman bullshit.  I am turning off inbox replies as i am not wasting anymore time with someone as clueless and ignorant as you.  pm = block. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Sessions to Toughen Rules on Prosecuting Drug Crimes </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-10 04:04:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-10 02:20:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You ignore everything i post no matter what.  Your pathetic, also i do not believe you.  You don't post any evidence ever.  I will be ignoring any further shitty evidence void posts from you.  If you have something worthwhile to contribute fine, but i don't think you do. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Condoleezza Rice on Kim Jong Un: He is smart </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-10 02:01:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-10 01:53:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Absolutely agree with you. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-10 01:51:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> "Opponents of unpopular president Nicols Maduro plan on using a new tactic dubbed the poopootov cocktail to ward off security forces" </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> 'They have gas; we have excrement': Venezuela protests take a dirty turn </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-10 01:41:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-10 01:36:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Im 95% sure it is part of one.  This is basically stating the obvious. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-10 01:34:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thats because the real reason for his firing is the Russia investigation. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Project to map human brain from womb to birth releases stunning images </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-10 01:33:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> James Comey fired: Democrat leader Chuck Schumer calls for special prosecutor to probe Trump's Russia ties </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-10 01:23:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> U.S. regulator's 'throttling' lawsuit against AT T to be reheard: court </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-10 01:14:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Clinton aides react to Comey firing with concern, not joy </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-10 01:12:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-10 00:08:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Time for a special prosecutor. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-10 00:08:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Good god we need a special prosecutor right now. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-09 23:37:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Its junk science just because you said so?  You also said it was hotter in the 40s then it is now which is clearly not true.  Sorry im not moving my stance i have done and seen plenty of research and global warming is still clearly real.  For example during the university level geology courses i have taken have have been vastly helpful in understanding the history of our planet including carbon and temperature data, which of course makes it clear that we are in a completely unseen level of raising temperature due to human activity.  While these were not classes directly focusing on global warming they did talk about things like glaciers which are clearly in retreat today and how we can date rocks to a time period and that is a useful record for climates.  Learning things about rocks that formed years before any records would be kept and before people existed are one of the single most crucial things in learning about the climates of the past.  That is actually just the tip of the iceberg as to classes or research i have done.  None it made me come to the conclusion that global warming was fake in fact it only strengthened my belief in man made global warming and its evidence.  

As to the rest of your post

"Even if you were to come up with save the environment, what energy source will you use? How will prevent monopolies from existing?"

Even nuclear power is way more safe then coal and fossil fuels, yes its not perfect but they do produce an absolutely crazy amount of energy.   All you need to do is ensure its secure and safe.  The mining and pollution from fossil fuels kills and makes people unhealthy.  We have numerous ways to make nuclear power safe.  To add to this it gives us plenty of time to boost our renewable energy sources wind, solar while dropping our reliance on fossil fuels.

Im not a fan of hydro electric as it causes fights over water rights among states and countries and can cause problems for wildlife in the rivers they are built on.  Your of course free to say its kind of like nuclear power in that it has its problems and is still better the fossil fuels, and i would not disagree with that.  Im not super opposed to hydro electric i just don't think its the best source of energy.


the second part about how will prevent monopolies from existing?  Assuming your talking about corporate monopolies like standard oil or us steel.  We already have anti trust laws in the united states and other countries if an energy company gets too big or totally integrates to the point of monopoly then it will get broken up.  if your talking about an over reliance on a single source i would say that only matters if said source has dangerous elements to it, fossil nuclear etc. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-09 22:26:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What you have posted is total bullshit all of it.  Your post also suggests you clearly did not even read my post.  I  suggest reading my post again.  None of it is junk science its rather well cited in fact.  Just because you refuse to accept it does not make it not true.  Also your continued refusal to accept facts has been noted once again.

Either you glossed over or did not read the post.


"We also need not worry about environmental calamities even if the current natural warming trend continues. The Earth has been much warmer during the past 3,000 years without catastrophic effects."

Yes do continue to ignore that Earth atmospheric CO2 levels has never been above 300ppm. Also continue to ignore the completely unprecedented rise in temperatures.


"Mankind is moving the carbon in coal, oil, and natural gas from be low ground to the atmosphere, where it is available for con - version into living things."  

My god you don't even understand the carbon cycle properly.



"The whole point of global warming is to sway unacademic idiots like yourself and to put an end to capitalism, gain control of the economy through subversive means, fund the green party/environmentalists, profiteering through a frivolous tax and etc."


Blatant and pathetic strawman.


"As coal, oil, and natural gas are used to feed and lift from poverty vast numbers of people across the globe, more CO2 will be released into the atmosphere. This will help to maintain and improve the health, longevity, prosperity, and profuctivity of all people."

Complete bullshit fossil fuels will make people more healthy?  Why surely a few black lung providing coal jobs is just what people need.  You also must have missed the current massive poverty worldwide in countries that have plenty of fossil fuels.

You are an infantile troglodyte who is still wrong and still unable to provide any valid sources.

Please continue to cry about how i am "disrespectful".  A quick run through of your comment history is more then enough for anyone with half a brain to see that you are extremely disrespectful troll yourself. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Tillerson, Lavrov to meet in Washington on Syria and Ukraine </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-09 22:12:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Tiffany   Co. makes pro-Paris agreement plea to Trump </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-09 22:00:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-09 21:55:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Of course he has globalist in triple parentheses [which also happens to be an antisemitic symbol that has been used to highlight the names of individuals of a Jewish background.](https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Triple_parentheses)

I am sure that its just coincidence though. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-09 20:59:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Wrong refute my points or fuck off retard.   Its real whether you think so or not.  Ps i am done wasting my time with you.  You can troll others with your retardation. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Donald Trump May Escalate the Afghanistan War He Spent Years Calling a Terrible Mistake </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-09 20:50:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Italy seizes huge drugs haul intended for Isil fighters in Libya </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-09 20:29:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Robert De Niro Criticizes Trump Administration's 'Hostility Towards Art' in Lifetime Award Speech </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-09 20:04:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Mexico's poppy war: Mexican army fights opium surge feeding U.S. heroin demand </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-09 19:52:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Lindsey Graham Wants to Investigate President Trump's Business Dealings for Ties to Russia </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-09 19:49:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Officials: Trump Approves Plan to Arm Syrian Kurds </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-09 19:25:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Gazprom starts construction of gas pipeline to Turkey </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-09 03:00:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-09 00:54:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Las vegas. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> San Francisco gets record-setting $100m donation to end homelessness </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-08 23:07:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> San Francisco gets record-setting $100m donation to end homelessness </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-08 23:04:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-08 22:10:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Cruz is like the definition of partisanship. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-08 22:06:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> NO Cruz now shut up. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-08 22:02:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Ugh Ted Cruz. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-08 20:44:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Releasing his tax returns, ha yea right he will never do that. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-08 20:01:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [Here you go!](https://youtu.be/QTIwQYfBmpM?t=33s)

He appears at 33 seconds. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-08 19:57:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Bingo the Streisand effect will mean people want to see it who would not care otherwise. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-08 19:31:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The real question is will Mccain grow a spin and vote against the trump administration and other republicans. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Sen. John McCain Warns Rex Tillerson: 'We Are a Country With a Conscience' </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-08 19:30:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Facebook is blocking Thai users from seeing video of their king in a crop top </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-08 19:25:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> City banks could move at least 9,000 jobs from UK due to Brexit </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-08 19:10:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Months After Plane Crash Killed Most Of Team, Chapecoense Wins Championship </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-08 18:59:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-08 18:57:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Not advocating to elect them straight to the presidency. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-08 17:55:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> We will see i personally think there is too much smoke for their to not be someone getting caught in this whole thing. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-08 17:50:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Anything worth hearing probably wont be told during a public hearing. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Swalwell: Classified intel suggests collusion </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-08 17:41:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> EPA Just Scrubbed Even More Mentions of Climate from Its Website </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-08 16:56:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-08 07:35:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If only election day was a holiday. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Canada floods: Montreal declares state of emergency </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-08 07:00:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Pentagon Backs $7.5 Billion Military Spending Boost in Asia </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-08 06:23:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-08 05:47:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Toxic sludge now thats something that we won't be in short supply of. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-08 04:41:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yup go look up how much he got from the fossil fuel industry.  Thats absolutely whats dictating his stance. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-08 04:24:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Btw this basically only happened because massive protests were happening in the streets.   Nixon would never have done that if people didnt protest like hell about the state of the environment. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-08 04:12:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Want to know the worst part of this?  Its who will probably replace them.

"Administrator, Scott Pruitt, said he would consider replacing the academic scientists with representatives from industries whose pollution the agency is supposed to regulate" </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-08 03:46:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The snowball thing was one of the single dumbest things i have ever seen.  Not sure how anyone can actually think like that. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-08 03:42:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Honestly we need actual scientists in congress.  You have people who have absolutely no science knowledge refusing to accept scientific fact.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> E.P.A. Dismisses Members of Major Scientific Review Board </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-08 03:39:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-08 02:59:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Your fucking wrong deal with it!


In the last 650k years, Earth has gone through 7 periods of glacial advance and retreat. The last was 7k years ago, marking the end of the Ice Age.

CO2 was demonstrated to trap heat in the mid 19th century. In the course of the last 650k years, Earth atmospheric CO2 levels has never been above 300ppm, and we know that through mineral deposits, fossils, and arctic ice leaving telltale predictable signs of how much CO2 must have been in the air at the time. Today, CO2 is over 400ppm. Not only have we kept fantastic records pre-industrial revolution, especially the Swedes for centuries, but arctic ice has acted as a more recent history of the last several dozen centuries. CO2 levels has been growing at unprecedented rates and achieving levels higher than we've ever known to occur that wasn't in the wake of planetary disaster and mass extinction. It follows that if CO2 traps heat, and there's more CO2 in the atmosphere than ever before, it's going to trap more heat than ever before.

Sea levels are rising. 17cm over the last century. The last decade alone has seen twice the rise of the previous century. So not only are the oceans rising, but the rate of rise is increasing exponentially.

The Earth's average temperature has increased since 1880, most of that has been in the last 35 years. 15 of the 16 hottest years have been since 2001. We're in a period of solar decline, where the output of the sun cycles every 11 or so years. Despite the sun putting out less energy, the average continues to rise and in 2015 the Earth's average was 1C hotter on average than in 1890. That doesn't sound like much, but if we go some 0.7C hotter, we'll match the age of the dinosaurs when the whole planet was a tropical jungle. That's not a good thing.

The ice caps are losing mass. While we've seen cycles of recession and growth, you have to consider ice is more than area, it's also thickness and density. Yes, we've seen big sheets of ice form, but A) they didn't stay, and B) how thick were they? Greenland has lost 60 cubic miles of ice and Antarctica has lost at least 30 cubic miles, both in the last decade. Greenland is not denying global warming, they're feverishly building ports to poise themselves as one of the most valuable ocean trading hubs in the world as the northern pass is opening, and it's projected you'll be able to sail across the north pole, a place you can currently stand, year-round.

Glacier ice is retreating all over the world, in the Alps, Himalayas, Andes, Rockies, Alaska and Africa.

The number of unprecedented intense weather events has been increasing since 1950 in the US. The number of record highs has been increasing, and record lows decreasing.

The ocean absorbs CO2 from the atmosphere. CO2 and water makes carbonic acid, - seltzer water! The oceans are 30% more acidic since the industrial revolution. 93% of The Great Barrier Reef has been bleeched and 22% and rising is dead as a consequence. The ocean currently absorbs 9.3 billion tons of CO2 a year and is currently absorbing an additional 2 billion tons annually. Not because the ocean is suddenly getting better at it, but because there's more saturation in the atmosphere.

IPCC Fourth Assessment Report, Summary for Policymakers, p. 5

B.D. Santer et.al., A search for human influences on the thermal structure of the atmosphere, Nature vol 382, 4 July 1996, 39-46

Gabriele C. Hegerl, Detecting Greenhouse-Gas-Induced Climate Change with an Optimal Fingerprint Method, Journal of Climate, v. 9, October 1996, 2281-2306

V. Ramaswamy et.al., Anthropogenic and Natural Influences in the Evolution of Lower Stratospheric Cooling, Science 311 (24 February 2006), 1138-1141

B.D. Santer et.al., Contributions of Anthropogenic and Natural Forcing to Recent Tropopause Height Changes, Science vol. 301 (25 July 2003), 479-483.

In the 1860s, physicist John Tyndall recognized the Earth's natural greenhouse effect and suggested that slight changes in the atmospheric composition could bring about climatic variations. In 1896, a seminal paper by Swedish scientist Svante Arrhenius first predicted that changes in the levels of carbon dioxide in the atmosphere could substantially alter the surface temperature through the greenhouse effect.

National Research Council (NRC), 2006. Surface Temperature Reconstructions For the Last 2,000 Years. National Academy Press, Washington, DC.

Church, J. A. and N.J. White (2006), A 20th century acceleration in global sea level rise, Geophysical Research Letters, 33, L01602, doi:10.1029/2005GL024826.

The global sea level estimate described in this work can be downloaded from the CSIRO website.

https://www.ncdc.noaa.gov/indicators/ 

http://www.cru.uea.ac.uk/cru/data/temperature 

http://data.giss.nasa.gov/gistemp 

http://www.giss.nasa.gov/research/news/20160120/ 

T.C. Peterson et.al., "State of the Climate in 2008," Special Supplement to the Bulletin of the American Meteorological Society, v. 90, no. 8, August 2009, pp. S17-S18.

I. Allison et.al., The Copenhagen Diagnosis: Updating the World on the Latest Climate Science, UNSW Climate Change Research Center, Sydney, Australia, 2009, p. 11

http://www.giss.nasa.gov/research/news/20100121/ 

http://science.nasa.gov/headlines/y2009/ 
01apr_deepsolarminimum.htm

Levitus, et al, "Global ocean heat content 19552008 in light of recently revealed instrumentation problems," Geophys. Res. Lett. 36, L07608 (2009).

L. Polyak, et.al., History of Sea Ice in the Arctic, in Past Climate Variability and Change in the Arctic and at High Latitudes, U.S. Geological Survey, Climate Change Science Program Synthesis and Assessment Product 1.2, January 2009, chapter 7

R. Kwok and D. A. Rothrock, Decline in Arctic sea ice thickness from submarine and ICESAT records: 1958-2008, Geophysical Research Letters, v. 36, paper no. L15501, 2009

http://nsidc.org/sotc/sea_ice.html 

National Snow and Ice Data Center

World Glacier Monitoring Service

http://lwf.ncdc.noaa.gov/extremes/cei.html 

http://www.pmel.noaa.gov/co2/story/What+is+Ocean+Acidification%3F 

http://www.pmel.noaa.gov/co2/story/Ocean+Acidification 

C. L. Sabine et.al., The Oceanic Sink for Anthropogenic CO2, Science vol. 305 (16 July 2004), 367-371

Copenhagen Diagnosis, p. 36.

National Snow and Ice Data Center

C. Derksen and R. Brown, "Spring snow cover extent reductions in the 2008-2012 period exceeding climate model projections," GRL, 39:L19504

http://nsidc.org/cryosphere/sotc/snow_extent.html 

Rutgers University Global Snow Lab, Data History Accessed August 29, 2011.

Not wasting any more time with a moron/ troll who just posted in r/ps4 about how mass effect is anti white.
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-08 02:58:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> 3rd quarter is the new first quarter. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-08 00:26:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> He needs to go back to his safe space in the donald. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-07 22:22:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If you doubt how much just check the subreddit rules. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-07 21:34:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> They think that if you u cut the funding they wont be confronted with facts. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-07 21:31:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Evidence? citations? anything? Because almost all the information says the opposite as what you are saying. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-07 20:58:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> 3 billion muslim obamas interfered in the french election. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Chris Sale Has Emerged As A Leader For Red Sox, Both On And Off Field | Red Sox First Pitch </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-07 20:27:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-07 20:23:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Take and pay attention in a college level, or hell even high school intro earth science class and then see if your opinion changes. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-07 20:17:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This just in 3 billion illegals voted in the french elections - the donald probably. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-07 20:14:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yep people tend to think things like alligator and shark attacks are far more common then they actually are. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-07 20:12:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Wait they will say 3 million illegals voted in french election. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Alligator bites girl in shallow lake waters at Florida park </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-07 19:09:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Young protester dies, taking Venezuela unrest death toll to 37 </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-07 19:04:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-07 19:02:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What do you expect them to look at the ~~plebs~~ People who are going to lose their coverage.

These people are huge cowards. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Wildlife refuge fire forces evacuations in southeast Georgia </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-07 17:45:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Republicans are messing with a major source of American jobs </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-07 17:08:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Gov. John Kasich slams GOP health bill </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-07 16:57:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-07 15:18:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Lets be honest you have to be pretty dumb to go to north korea. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> US citizen detained in North Korea </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-07 15:10:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> West Virginia airport reopened after cargo plane crash </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-07 14:18:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Penn State frat brother says pleas to call 911 for unconscious pledge were dismissed </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-07 14:17:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Trump to Tell Turkey: Were Going to Take Raqqa With the Kurds </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-07 05:03:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Pedro Martinez Helps Children In Need Through Feast With 45 At Fenway | Boston Red Sox </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-07 04:47:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-07 04:42:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That is one of the worst designed shirts i have seen in a while. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Trump's pick for Army post drops out amid growing criticism </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-07 04:26:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-07 00:27:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That was quite a goal to win it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-07 00:23:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Copyright strike got him.  Just in time to miss the game winning goal too.
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-07 00:12:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yea 37 is way too young and they don't list the cause of death. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Team USA bobsled driver Steven Holcomb dies </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-07 00:00:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Team USA bobsled driver Steven Holcomb dies </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-07 00:00:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Commerce secretary warns Canada against 'retaliatory action' on lumber tariff </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-06 22:09:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Theresa May urged to persuade Trump not to quit Paris climate accord </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-06 21:57:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-06 20:37:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Its felt like nixon since he got elected. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Donald Trump former aide Carter Page refuses to provide Russia contacts to Senate </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-06 20:34:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Jared Kushners Sister Highlights Family Ties in Pitch to Chinese Investors </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-06 19:17:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Judge blasts 'ridiculous' 18-year sentence for marijuana </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-06 10:50:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-06 09:37:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Is this going to be on the test? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-06 07:50:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yea it seems every time a move happens that makes no sense its neely pushing for it.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-06 07:47:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Better be able too. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-06 07:47:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yea we should just keep him for now at least. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-06 07:46:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yay! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Trump-Murdoch friendship will test Sessions, former U.S. attorneys say </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-06 07:15:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-06 06:47:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Your absolutely correct that she is not free by any means.  I wish I could be more clear and put that in the title, but i think your only supposed to post the direct headline here. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Microsoft Testing Anti-Malware Feature For Edge Browser </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-06 06:41:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> E.P.A. Chief Recuses Himself From Suits Opposing Obama-Era Rules </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-06 06:37:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Scotland's One-Woman Rubbish Party Wins Seat In Local Elections </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-06 05:34:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-06 05:25:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Corruption kills almost anything it touches. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Egyptair crash: no trace of explosives on victims, says French newspaper </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-06 05:24:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-06 04:48:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yea i felt the same, half expecting the zombies to show up. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Official: Cindy McCain eyed for senior State Dept. role </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-06 04:45:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-06 04:28:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> But the republicans said we have "access" to health care, and by access they mean rich people have access. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Hugo Chvez statue torn down as death toll rises in Venezuela protests </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-06 04:16:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-06 04:14:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Suprising/s. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> GOP Uses Health Care As Means to Tax Cuts </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-06 04:09:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> France bans extremely thin models - BBC News </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-06 04:08:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Measure on Pre-Existing Conditions Energizes Opposition to Health Bill </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-06 03:58:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-06 03:49:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Imagine being so fucked up that you see being gay as evil enough to warrent pushing a 17 year old off a balcony. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-06 01:55:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I would say if you don't get a notice within a total 6 - 12 months your safe.  Keep in mind the less popular the music the less likely it is  lead to anything.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-06 01:50:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I would assume the most that would hapen from google drive is they might delete the file off of drive and suspend your google drive or something. 

When you torrent a file some of the trackers are actually people like the recording industry association of america or companies they work with who track who downloads what.

Google drive is probably much safer.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-06 01:43:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yea im not certain whether they would send one but i would just google your provider and see if anyone has gotten notices, if you don't find much then your probably fine and i would not worry.  Some providers don't care at all. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-06 01:41:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Burn everything to the ground scorched earth!!! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
