<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject4719</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-03 14:32:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> you're totally right! thank you:) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-02 20:51:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I teach math! When i type i used Times, the numbers seem to look better that way :) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-02 20:48:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That's ok! You're human :) I teach high school math and my brain sometimes derps out on me mid proof in precalc and that's ok! I apologize for my brain 'malfunctioning' and we figure it out together :] I used to be super embarrassed about it, but now i just joke about it. I think it is important to demonstrate how adults respond to and recover from mistakes.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-02 20:37:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> k12jobspot is a site i visit daily. I also made a spreadsheet with all the districts i'm willing to drive out to, and found direct links to their employment page. I check those everyday and apply if anything is up!  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-02 20:35:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Very true! Thank you so much!  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-02 18:30:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> thank you so much!! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> 2 interviews today, nerves on 1000%, Help? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-02 16:08:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The past two years i've been teaching at a private school, desperately applying to public. I didn't hear anything back for months from my applications, so I accepted the responsibility of having a student teacher next year. HOWEVER, I now have 2 interviews lined up. I know I'm thinking waaaaaay ahead of myself, but I already feel awful ditching a student teacher if I find a new job. I feel like I'm in the wrong for being selfish about my own advancement. I can't be the first teacher to do this when assigned a student teacher, right?!
I've become more nervous about the possibility of getting the job and having to leave this job than the actual interviews today. 
I know I haven't posed an actual question but...... Any advice on all of this?? 

Thank you! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-28 20:24:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> thanks! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-26 17:00:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thank you very much!!  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-26 16:59:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> how do you get yourself to not think about work? I feel like my mind goes there way too much.  
I do the same thing! coming too early!! I should probably cut back on that a bit too! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-26 16:58:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> lolol thanks :D </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-25 21:34:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> :)) That's a given! Anything else?? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-25 20:37:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> thanks for sharing :D </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-25 20:00:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> thank you!!! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> End of the year stress </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-25 17:43:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I teach high school math to seniors and juniors. The year is coming to a close for the seniors and unnecessary stress is piling. I've already prepared everything from today till the end of the school year for all of my senior classes and am about a third done with my junior end of the year prep (review + final).  
however, for some reason, i'm still on the high end of stress. I broke out in acne recently, and i've never broken out this bad at the end of the school year before (i barely brake out at all actually!!)

SO my question is: how do you destress?    How do you deal with the constant need to do something and feeling like you're behind even when you're not?   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-24 15:53:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I pass back work daily at the start of each class or during lecture myself if it is graded, and I let students pass it back to their classmates if they are not (beginning or end). I try not to let myself hoard papers, but missing a day is ok sometimes too :) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-12 18:23:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm what's labeled as a "nice" teacher, but I am consistent  with my rules. I can imagine not smiling first semester, how are you supposed to build relationships with your students if you're a stone cold rock??
My kids know that I love to joke around and have fun in class, but they also know that if they misbehave they'll get detentions, zeros or whatever other consequence there is. My students know that I take their education and success seriously   their behavior matches that! 

ultimately: consistency in how you reprimand and respond to behavior issues is key!
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-12 15:11:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thank you!! So helpful!! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-12 15:11:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thanks! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-12 15:11:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thanks </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-12 15:11:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thanks! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-12 15:11:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thanks! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-12 15:10:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Oh i'll be year 4 next year! the requirements are a minimum of 3 years experience. 

Thanks! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Getting a Student Teacher, Suggestions? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-11 16:48:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm very excited that I will have a student teacher next fall, and very nervous because its only the end of my 3rd year teaching and 2nd at this school/high school level :)

I have a very basic idea on what i'm supposed to do with my student teacher, based on my memory of what my mentors had me do: self - reflections, lesson plans, week plans, unit plans and of course the mentoring part :) 

If you have had a student teacher before, is there any advice you can give me? 

Thank you! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-28 21:46:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I agree!!!! I have a feeling it will reduce next year exponentially :) I dont know if it will ever go away though!  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-28 15:23:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hi! Second year teacher here - I dont get it as much as last year but yea, i still get plenty those moments! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Participation Points </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-06 14:56:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm a second year (full time) high school math teacher.  I've been thinking of giving participation a place in my grading. However,  I am unsure of what that looks like on paper and in class.  If you do participation points,  how do you record it?  What % of the  grade do you set it as?  What do you expect your students to do to get full or partial credit for participation?  

Thank you in advance:)) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-14 21:04:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I dont think i ever chose to be a teacher, I think it was always who i was. I fully discovered that teaching was my path when my dad suggested i help out at the hebrew school at my synagogue. I knew from that day on that this is my only career path! I cannot imagine doing anything else with my life. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-10 19:55:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> logic puzzles or riddles!! Or some one day fun activity  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-10 19:53:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> My experience was that most of my college education was philosophical discussion on how to teach and endless sample lesson plans. I learned the most when I started student teaching. The more I taught the more I learned. Teaching is an art form, and although the philosophical background is nice to have, the only way to really learn is by doing.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-02 20:51:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I second this answer! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-30 20:28:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thats a good idea! I'm was planing on doing no ipad next year, and i really like your idea! There was a big push by the school to go "all tech" (since students are not required to buy an ipad for school?!) but honestly it's creating problems  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-30 17:46:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> my school does ipads too, which sometimes is worse (since they take notes on it too) I think it would be great if it could limit ipad use as well!  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
