<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject5188</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Poland working with Egyptian authorities over Hurghada death </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-09 23:44:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-14 17:30:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Shit dude, I always thought it was Duke Roufus  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-28 00:53:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I wasn't a huge fan of the Bats v Supes fight, mostly because it really didn't look to me like either of them was actually trying to..I guess, win. The entire fight felt forced to me. From the speed of the actual blows to the space between them, I wasn't sold on the idea of either guy actually trying to win. One of the moments that stands out to me is when Bats grabs the sink to smash Supey with. He slowly walks to the sink, picks it up, slowly walks back, makes a few manly grunts, then drops it on him. It might just be me, but I felt a distinct lack of urgency in that confrontation, which went completely against the drama of Superman trying to save his mother from Lex. 

I think one of the reasons the warehouse fight really works is that it genuinely seems like Batman is trying to kill the mercenaries (which goes against the traditional image of the character but whatever). That urgency is there.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-09 20:47:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> He's takin that shit that makes your head grow!  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-08 00:09:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> 100% </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-03 17:38:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What are you talking about? Cody viciously moved in for the attack and Conor used EXTREME PUSH DEFLECTION SKILLS BECAUSE HE IS A MASTER OF HEWMAN MEWVMENT  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-19 19:43:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Shut up guys Steak Fed Cononor is a natural welterweight and Nate is a 17 foot super heavyweight when he cutting wheat smh u kno nothing about this sport  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-19 16:51:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> At the same time, couldn't you say Conor is under just as much pressure and as much scrutiny regardless of belts? He's the money fight, and has fighters from bantamweight all the way up to welterweight (maybe even middleweight) asking to fight him. We joke about it plenty, but he is the champ of the moneyweight division and is in the crosshairs of multiple divisions worth of contenders.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-19 14:08:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Triangle triangle triangle triangle  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-18 18:47:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> AAAAAARRRRRGGGHHHH </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-16 19:11:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> A Thief's End. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-12 15:51:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I thought he injured his knee during the world tour earlier in the year?Training with Rory, in Toronto.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-20 17:11:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I do sometimes. Having music in the background can set a good rhythm for my movements in game. It also means I can't hear minor audio cues and such, which usually forces me to adopt a different play style.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-07 00:49:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Instinct kicking in I guess. It is a fight. It's not really a heinous offense, if you'll pardon the pun. [Here's Aldo grabbing the cage to avoid a takedown (although he did end up getting taken down immediately after)](http://rashadface.com/upload/2013/03/22/20130322082044-1fcf1f94.gif).  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-14 01:25:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> *fook </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-26 14:22:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> *buddeh  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-17 13:28:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I don't really agree. I think this was the best Uncharted soundtrack across the board. I thought the action scores like New Devon and Cut to the Chase were very intense and adrenaline fueled, but that the more ambient tracks like A Normal Life, The Lure of Adventure, and For Better or Worse were very strong and stood out. I thought it had a level of energy that the previous OSTs never had. It made me feel like I really was experiencing something special. There were these especially great bits in buildup from ambient to more grand where you can kind of hear the intrigue and wonder and sort of excitement of discovery that I never really heard before in the previous three OSTs. But that's just my two cents.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-11 13:30:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thank you :) no such thing as talent though.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-10 23:12:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thank you. I'm probably going to make a few more. :) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Hand Drawn LiS Polaroids </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-10 15:43:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-06 12:59:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Any Fast and Furious movie. I know Vin Diesel is jacked, but he can't get in a head on collision and walk away like nothing even happened.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-29 23:30:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> *You'll do nuttin*

Without your glasses that is.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-29 00:54:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Probably justifiably so, yeah.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-28 19:30:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The Robbie Lawler Soul Taking Curse lives on.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-28 16:35:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yewl do fookin nuttin </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-23 13:51:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Tarzan, George of the Jungle, etc.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-21 19:12:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> He landed a ridiculous number of strikes in round 3. That's probably it.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-20 18:52:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I know that you can get the ppvs on PlayStation network for an absurd price. Does it apply to Ireland though?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-13 23:56:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The smoke and the orangey-bleedy-rewindy effect in the top left are very nice touches to the shot. The cosplay is really nice, but the gesture doesn't strike me as very Chloe. But I'm just nitpicking, maybe Max is behind the camera :P </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-12 19:01:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Personally I prefer 189's Hobo Viking McGregor.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-03 23:58:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That pink haired ref tho.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-01 13:04:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The Diaz bros are a vigilante crime fighting duo, giving them a rocky relationship with the UFCPD.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-18 22:53:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thank *you* for being a part of this community with us. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-17 23:01:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That really doesn't sound good.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-14 15:23:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> There are plenty of things to dislike about Chloe, but at the end of the day that's what I love about Chloe. She's a human being. Sounds like a cop out answer but I like that she's far from perfect, from both a personal and writing perspective. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-14 13:08:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I am upset that we didn't see or hear her, but it wouldn't have made sense to include her in this story. We barely got enough of Sully as is.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-14 13:06:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You have a point. Even when your jump is clearly too short, Nate will make it. Even when you have absolutely zero momentum, Nate gets a massive leap off of a rope swing. It's really goofy looking, but that never bothered me. I felt like a goddamn superhero and loved every second of it. Rope swinging is bae.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-14 12:39:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Well so far MacLife productions just seems to be an attempt at producing entertaining content that revolves around McGregor. Of course it's going to make him look good; that's what the audience they're aiming for wants. (and what Conor wants) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-03 01:27:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> How many people here remember the first 10k last year? Shit's AWESOME. This sub is awesome. And now...

[PARTY!!!!!!!!](http://i.imgur.com/RZxZEo4.gif) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-02 02:30:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It is not! I resent that. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-01 23:14:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thank you! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-01 21:50:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I posted this to a LiS Facebook group when I finished it last week, so if there's any crossover, hi.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> I don't have to see you right now </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-01 21:49:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-01 01:56:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The word that comes to mind is "ambient". Very very nice.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-01 01:53:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I've been detached from games, movies, and pretty much all the shit I really enjoy for a little while. LiS is in a weird place for me where I remember the game meaning a lot to me, I remember it making me feel things, and I remember having learned things from it, but right now I can't remember what they actually were. I've considered replaying the game, maybe refreshing my memory, but (like with other games I used to play often) I can't really bring myself to do it. I think my gaming days might be kind of over. Or I'm just being dramatic. Such is life I suppose. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-01 01:47:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Come out of the closet, and SMOOCH SMOOCH SMOOCH.

It actually forms a nice narrative too.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-01 01:46:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Another one. 

But seriously, it's cool to see that people are still picking up this game for the first time, and still getting hooked by the first episode. We might not be able to relive the first time we each played LiS, but there is a really cool nostalgic feeling from seeing other people getting to experience it fresh just like we did. 

Good luck with the game, and keep some tissues handy! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-01 01:42:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I never actually thought about the choice mechanic that way...

A year out and I'm still gaining new perspectives on this game. Pretty fucking amazing.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-01 01:36:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> At the end of the day, Nathan's a human being. He has issues. Serious issues, more serious than most's. It means his shortcomings are understandable. But it doesn't mean they should be forgiven. He made mistakes, and should be held accountable. 

He definitely didn't deserve to die at the hands of Creeperson.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-01 01:33:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  It made me question my morals more times than I'd care to admit.

I found this to be the case as well. In my case, I discovered that I am a much more selfish person than I originally knew.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-01 01:31:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Max must have gotten *mad*. 

*MAD*. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> This seemed familiar... </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-26 16:28:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-26 16:22:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> They're a bunch of close-minded individuals. It doesn't matter what they say. People will doubt you and make fun of you, so it's up to you to prove them all wrong.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-22 15:17:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm imagining Max breaking character in the middle of the phone call and being like "go to the lighthouse nigga its safe there." If someone were to fully dub LiS with lines like this and call it "Thug Life Ain't Strange", I would be able to die happy.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-09 00:10:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Introducing, *Coffee is Strange*.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-06 13:43:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The composition of this shot is really nice. The diagonal tilt to represent instability, the way she's looking right at the camera, the way that shadow forms behind her, it's just an excellent picture. Really conveys a sense of panic and paranoia to me. The cosplay is great too.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-06 13:41:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Forgot to wear a bra.


Can't pretend I didn't look there...for an extended period of time WHY AM I STILL TYPING STOP MAN STOP </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-04 00:20:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Well Chloe's got (at least) 99 problems, and a bitch is probably one. 

Not that I'm calling either Max or Rachel (or William) a bitch. But all of her pain stems from abandonment. I'm not saying it's the direct cause of everything, but in a butterfly effect sense it is the root. Specifically the joint death and departure of William and Max (respectively). That sent her tumbling down her path. It distanced her from her mother, it made her angry and depressed, it resulted in David entering her life. It led to her smoking as a coping mechanism, which probably led to her trying other more exciting drugs, which either began from or led to Frank, which led to her debt, which led to her getting shot by Nathan. Somewhere in there she met Rachel, which led to her falling in love, which led to her getting manipulated, which led to her plan to leave Arcadia with her, which led to her taking a loan from Frankie, which led to her debt, which led to her getting shot by Nathan. So it's a complex branching path. 

But then again, that's life isn't it? I could say the root of Chloe's problems is the death/departure of William/Max, but that's dumb. Shit happens. Obviously Chloe got played a shitty hand, but you can't pin the blame on anyone or anything. Chloe's problems, at the end of the day, begin and end with her.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-04 00:12:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> In ambiance and art style, and because it's recent, Firewatch comes to mind. Definitely check it out.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-04 00:10:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You know what they say. There's always a lighthouse.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-04 00:09:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> "I double dare you, kiss me now." </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-04 00:08:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This is actually so beautiful. Whether it's in memory of Chloe or not, it's super fucking touching. Personally, I feel the cool colors and the fading/blending around the edges of Max's hair and sweater make it seem like a sort of eulogy to her. I love it.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-04 00:05:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hella cute. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-29 02:09:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Get him the hat and change his name to Walter McWhite.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-26 12:33:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> ...

I hate you.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-26 00:12:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Tell them about the general theme and tone, and that I think it's the most atmospheric game/movie/anything ever. And that this is probably the only thing you can take my word for.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-26 00:10:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  I'm just glad "Nathan" didn't text me when I left.

How much would that have blown your mind though :P </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-26 00:09:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Max's Time Travel Helmet don't need to obey no laws of logic. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-26 00:07:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The face she's making at Maxster is making my heart melt.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-26 00:06:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I agree that Sacrificing Chloe is the "right" choice, but that doesn't really make a difference to me. I didn't sacrifice the town because I thought it was the right thing to do, I did it because *I* was given the choice. I didn't have to choose the right thing. But yeah, Chloe was 100% willing to die, which really speaks for her character growth, but I was not willing to let her go. It's selfishness at it's purest. Even if there are moral justifications for sacrificing the town, they weren't my thoughts at the time.

Also, completely agree about David. From a writing standpoint he's my favorite character. Very complex, and *thoroughly* misunderstood. While Chloe is a very well written and complex character as well, she's really always framed as one of the good guys. For a substantial chunk of the game, David is the villain. I think that makes a difference as far as interesting-ness goes. Super great character right there (and great performance too!).  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-26 00:01:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> How, oh how, will Max decide? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-25 23:59:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  He deserves whatever happened to him.

That's a fair point. Even though you can't help but think he didn't deserve to die, he did bring it on himself. He was manipulated by Jeffershit, and he needed help, but it's not like it was one incident that fucked him over. He consistently made the wrong choice, and it ended with him paying the price. Call it karma I guess.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-25 23:57:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The kid needed help. And to pay for the awful shit he did do. Just not with his life. 

Though at the time, I couldn't have really cared less. I had bigger problems on my hands, such as saving Chloe and the town (little did I know).  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-25 23:55:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  Thug Life Ain't Strange

I'm dying rn, that is amazing.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-22 18:01:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> They look positively adorable. Also, that natural sunlight is the real MVP. It makes them kinda look like they're glowing.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-22 17:54:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Civil War you say?

*When the mob and the press and the whole world tell you to move, your job is to plant yourself like a tree beside the river of truth, and tell the whole world, "No, you move."*

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-21 19:51:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> For a second there I thought that was a cardboard cutout of GSP.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-21 17:04:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> They're a step up, but we're talking greatest of all time here, and I don't know if they belong on that list.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-21 17:00:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm not shitting on her. Best female mma fighter of all time. Far from the best UFC fighter of all time.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-21 14:00:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Werdum, Conor, and Ronda. I don't know if any of them belong on the "greatest of all time" list. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-18 18:10:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'd love one! I'm from Ireland. I haven't played UC4 yet (exams, ugh), so I figure why not postpone playing it a little longer and replay the first three?

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-16 21:22:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Great way to chillax after I get home. Now only if I could find some dank OG bud... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-13 02:18:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The sane and realistic, and slightly depressing and perhaps boring theory that I lean towards? Max's powers aren't real, and the entire week in Arcadia Bay is in her head; she's just coping with Chloe's death in the bathroom.

The more fun and creative theory? There are old spirits and nature gods that reside in Arcadia Bay, ones from native american legends, that gave her the powers. Max was Arcadia's favorite daughter, and her and Chloe were a perfect duo. When Max left and Chloe's life went down the drain, Arcadia began to crack and decay. The town grew dark and shadows spread. The Prescotts take over. Drug trouble. Wildlife in danger. Etc. Arcadia doesn't have much longer. But then Max, the favorite daughter of Arcadia Bay, returns. These spirits give Max the power and the responsibility of saving the town from disaster, as well as the power to save Chloe and reunite the dynamic duo. Ultimately, they've given Max (and Chloe) a shot at saving Arcadia or, if shit really hits the fan, escape the collapse. 

It's a weird one, but I like it. Makes the story something both more epic and still personal.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-13 02:08:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> She has big, um, eyes. 

But really, it's a fucking excellent cosplay and she is *hella* pretty. And she does actually have very pretty eyes.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-09 18:26:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Oh my god, she's so fucking adorable.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-09 00:12:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I acknowledged this.

 even within the fucked up world they already exist in.
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-08 22:25:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> As much as Joel thinks he saved Ellie, she can never live a "normal" life, even within the fucked up world they already exist in.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-04 22:03:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I replayed the game for the first time a little while ago, and that scene had me pouring out tears because of nostalgia. Such fond memories. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-04 02:00:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Well, passion and hostility do often go hand in hand.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-04 01:58:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Just went back and checked the video again. I stand corrected. Sorry.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-04 00:57:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm not an advocate for sacrificing Chloe in any capacity, and I get what the choice represents. I'm just saying that I've seen people in the LiS family who love Chloe to death but chose to sacrifice her. And that it's very rare to find, and difficult to obtain, a truly random sample survey. Your Trump analogy is spot on.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-04 00:53:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I believe on Mari's first playthrough, which she streamed, she sacrificed Chloe. Then spent the next 20 minutes in tears, then replayed to see the other ending. But I might be wrong. I am not an elephant, so my memory is not immaculate or super accurate.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-04 00:43:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I wouldn't rule it out. But at its core, more than superpowers and blue hair and even friendship, I feel what makes Life is Strange Life is Strange is the theme of growing up. I think having the protagonist be a high school senior and having just turned 18 is a perfect fit for this. While Dontnod could do it with a younger character, it's not really the same is it? How do you tell a story about becoming an adult with a character who's barely even gone through puberty yet? 

Also it might limit them in terms of the material they can cover. Depression, suicide, murder, "DRUGS?", even romance, how do you approach subjects like these (which made LiS stand out from other games' stories) from the perspective of a tween while still giving the player control?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-04 00:28:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> YES! Me too! That moment is my favorite moment from the whole game. I mean holy shit, the emotions are running so high after the whole alt-Chloe situation, and seeing her again in the morning light with In My Mind playing in the background, and that slow fade in and pan-up shot before you know where you are and if she's there...in my opinion that's the most perfectly crafted scene in the whole game. Even without the serious emotional impact of it. 

But yeah, I was grinning ear to ear for a solid 10 or 15 minutes afterwards. I just stayed sitting on the edge of Chloe's bed for a long time, it was one of those moments that I wanted to stay in forever. The most pure moment of bliss in the game for me. 

I could rant and rave about this one scene all day, seriously, but I've done enough of that over the past 9 months or so. :P  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-04 00:22:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If it's worth anything, Mari from Geek Remix even sacrificed Chloe first time around. You don't have to dislike Chloe to have sacrificed her. 

But yeah, it's very likely that a sizable chunk of the GT fanbase is biased. But that's just the thing about sampling and collecting data; there's always factors that result in inaccuracy. 

Edit: Mari did not sacrifice Chloe first time around. Whoops.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-04 00:19:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm an N type, ENFP, but I didn't choose to sacrifice Chloe. I know that the theory doesn't apply to everyone, it *is* a theory, but I did find it odd when MatPat began going on about how the intuitive N types were such logical thinkers and were more likely to sacrifice their best friend to save the lives of many while I personally never even considered sacrificing bae. Even looking back now, I don't even entertain the notion of that ending. 

But then again, every time I've taken the Briggs Meyers test (always ENFP) it's always said that my preference of Intuiting over Sensing is very very slight. So I suppose I'm not the best example of an N type. Regardless, "save teh bae." :P 

Loved seeing MatPat finally do a LiS theory though. Been a long time coming! Even if it wasn't about the actual lore of the game, I thought this video was hella intriguing.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-02 13:53:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It should say that on the box. 

 Life is Strange: "it's like digital cocaine...shaka brah" </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-02 13:52:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It is an excellent cosplay though.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-02 13:50:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I think this is my favorite Max cosplay. I've seen a hell of a lot of great Chloes, but I think this is the best Max. And you can't even see her face! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-28 18:25:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hot damn, Holloway vs Lamas. Looking forward to that one.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-25 23:17:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  match 

I see what you did there. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-25 18:53:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hopping on that plane like "Time to go mobile."  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-25 17:24:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm glad that they intend to deliver the same kind of cruel and difficult choices. Usually when games give you the option to kill someone for personal gain (vampiric reasons here I assume) or spare them, the right choice is pretty obvious. I'm curious how they'll make the choices more complex.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-25 17:16:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> LiS never goes fully dark because it's visuals and style continually keep it anchored in a more bright and colorful world. Visual style plays a key part in the tone of a story.

Vampyr on the other hand, is black and grey and blood red. That's a game that will be dominated by a dark and horrific tone.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-25 16:55:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Especially since he shaved his head earlier this year, it seems like Conor's going for [that Bane style](https://www.fjackets.com/product_images/c/770/bane_coat__91325_zoom.jpg).  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-22 17:58:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You sir, are the real mvp.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-22 17:17:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I looked, can't find it. Maybe I'm just dumb, but a link would certainly help.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-22 17:08:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Anyone have a link to this video? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-17 16:02:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This made my Sunday morning. So adorbs. I feel all fuzzy inside now. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-08 08:49:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Well deserved. *Well* deserved. I'm so happy to see Dontnod and LiS get this recognition on such a high level. 

Time to party! (Someone get the gif of Max dancing!) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
