<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject5839</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> "Nipple Jesus" - What is it really about? confused. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-07 18:34:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hello there.

I recently read "Nipple Jesus" by Nick Hornby and I'm slightly confused regarding the message it is trying to send. I did feel that the message was "don't judge a book by its cover" but when I searched on google, I didn't find much. All I could find is that Hornby is trying to tell how different art can be definied by different people.

Do anyone know the intentions of Nick Hornby's novel? All I could find was some "forum discussions".

Thank you in advance :D  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-15 15:37:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> hey dude. I did indeed look at the prices HERE in Sweden. But I'm not a reader therefore I don't know any alternative "good sites" that regular e-book readers go to so they can buy their books from.

Do you know what I mean ? :D </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-15 13:47:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Oh. Thanks for the clarification. I didn't know the real story behind the letter and the whole strategy amazon is using, which is actually pretty interesting. Thanks so muuuuch! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-15 13:40:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Oh. So it's about "control" rather than Amazon actually being the "good guy". Thanks for the answer guys, you've been so helpful 3 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-15 13:37:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Oh, that must have been it.
It is not my stance though. I don't know what my agenda would even be in that case since i got the impression that e-books ARE more expensive due to that specific article. But I knew that something was wrong when there was mixed comments about that topic, hence My question in this thread :"/. 
But Thanks for clarifying that, and I'm sorry for anyone WHO actually thought anything bad. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-15 02:18:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> oh thank you for this elaborated answer I love it.

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
