<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject3154</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-09 23:15:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The CDU, for example, is still against gay marriage. (I'll count that to family issues) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-09 22:34:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Infinite Jest is awesome. The pace of /r/infinitediscussion is really lax, too. So you can read something on the side, if you don't want to skip ahead of the reading group. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-09 13:00:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's a cool moment when you realize who wrote the article that comes up in that footnote. There's no way you could know it when you are first asked to read it but later, when it comes up again, it's really obvious. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-09 12:58:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You notice so many new things on the second run. The whole first third is completely different if you already know about the politics, experialism, Quebec seperatism and the life of the Incandenzas. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-08 22:55:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Have you read any late DeLillo? I've only gotten to read Zero K so far and it was pretty good. I've heard his earlier stuff is much different, though. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-08 21:47:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I've answered it already but, yeah mostly from context. Sometimes the font is slightly different for kanjis than for kana. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-08 19:19:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I've only read Inherent Vice and The Crying of Lot 49 so far and I found them similarly difficult, so if you managed Inherent Vice, you're probably as prepared as one can be. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-08 15:35:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The kanji is a bit larger but kanji's usually have a different font. If they don't, you need context. A katakana-ka won't stand anywhere on it's own. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-08 15:13:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You are correct, I mistook 'chi' for 'sa'. I'll correct it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-08 12:58:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Not really. I think you've misunderstood. The katakana would usually be used to form a loanword involving "ka". The kanji for strength or power (Kanji is not the pronunciation of that symbol, it literally means "chinese character", such chinese characters are mostly used for nouns, adjectives and verbs, while Hiragana mostly serves conjugation and Katakana is for loanwords from other languages) would be pronounced "chikara", if it means strength or power, or "riki/ryoku" if it is used in a combined word with multiple chinese characters in a row. To confuse people the first word would need to end with  and the next would have to start with . However, there is something called particles in the japanese languages, which are short markers, defining the role of a word in a sentence, which would lead to  and  being seperated by some particle in most cases. In addition, it is not hard to recognize when one full katakana word ends and another word begins because you would never write  on it's own. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-08 08:43:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The first one is the kanji for power/strength, the second one is just katakana "ka". </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-08 00:19:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> DFW said in an interview that since about a third of the novel got cut before publishing, it's more like a very fractured Sierpinski triangle. Now one can only guess how that is supposed to apply. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-07 23:53:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I think it's pretty agreed upon that Lovecraft was very racist, even for his times. If you can look past that while reading his novels, good for you, they are very imaginative and scary. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-07 23:36:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I just upvoted for my favourite book being there. Eraserhead is awesome though. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-07 18:12:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I've heard it said before that what stands Infinite Jest apart from many pomo door-stoppers is the fact that the characters are fleshed out and given a level of respect instead of just being cardboard cut-outs.
[Spoilers](#s "
Very interesting!
If I remember correctly, it is also mentioned that James Inc used to make his films in such a way that there are no side characters and that every character is fully fleshed out which is what, the book, Infinite Jest does too. In the first third, we see a lot of introduction for 'secondary' characters, such as K. Erdedy, C. Henderson, K. Gompert, T. Ewell. There are almost no characters whose backstory we don't get to know, even Bruce Green's past is told. There is also a kind of symmetry to the last third of the novel, where each of the 'side characters' exits, by visiting Gately in the hospital one by one, after which most are never mentioned again.
I think it is pretty agreed upon, that the structure of the book resembles that of the priapistic cartridge, with its circularity and addicting narrative. I like what you said about how the ending is written as if the novel didn't end at all. If you didn't know that it was the end, nobody would actually notice because there's no great climax and the storylines never seem to converge 'on-screen'. It's funny how the less there is left of the book, the more one starts to think 'oh no this can't all be solved in 50 pages'. The message at the end seems to be, stop reading, go into the real world and connect with people. The novel teaches you what happens when everyone starts to isolate themselves and retreat into vapid entertainment. Some people don't like that sentiment, because they feel trapped by the author to read the book again in the hope of finding the missing pieces of the plot, only to realize that some questions simply cannot be answered. Though, personally, I like the writing and the characters so much, that I can live without a resolved plot. I would also argue that no single writer could write a decent conclusion to the plot of that monster.")
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-07 13:07:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Further, I will say--without getting to theory heavy--that this book does something structurally in the last 50 pages that I have never seen a book do before and it continues to blow my mind every time I think about it.

Care to explain? I'm curious as to what you mean by that. You can use the spoiler tags, as described in the sidebar. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-06 15:18:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I haven't read it yet, but I heard that that's what happens in The Corrections. I could be wrong though. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-06 09:58:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The last sentence in Infinite Jest is one of my favorite final sentences of any book. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-06 09:54:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I actually liked the ending. It wasn't amazing, but something about these annoying, horrible people redeeming themselves was really satisfying. I was somehow rooting for Walter and Patty, even though both are pretty obnoxious in the second half of the book. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-05 22:51:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> She's really big among pre-teen girls in Germany. Her content pretty much consist of clickbaity vlogs. Just look at the thumbnails. This is her first (and hopefully last) entry to her singing career. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-05 22:49:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Upbeat ukulele with claps and metallophone actually makes me angry. It sounds like the beat was just bought from some web store. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-05 16:37:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's not a contradiction, it's doublethink. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-05 10:33:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Don't worry about it, I wish you best of luck! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-05 10:25:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Maybe I worded it poorly but I don't condone trivializing mental illness in any way. Of course it's wrong to claim having a mental illness if you don't. It's just that, I've never seen anybody "soo bipolar lol" in real life ever. Only ever on the internet, when these people are mocked. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-05 10:21:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> A friend of mine is _actually_ bipolar, like diagnosed bipolar. All of her friends including me know about it because she's told us. Of course not in a "lol my mood changes, I have OCD, I can't even."-straw-man way. I'm sorry if I worded it poorly but that is my personal experience. No need to call me a fucking idiot. It's true that I have no idea what's it like to be bipolar and I've never claimed that, but I've been struggling with depersonalization and light depression for a while so don't assume that I'm just talking out of my ass. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-05 10:01:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That would be hard and take years though, Kana should be enough, you can read English loan words you already know /s </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-05 09:51:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I think it's pretty mean to assume that just because a girl is annoying, she can't _really_ be bipolar, because... Yes, why? Imagine you're bipolar and pretty open about it and people go around calling you an attention whore, who doesn't know what being bipolar is really like. That's what rubbed me wrong about this whole comment chain. Of course there are going to be people who unjustly call themselves bipolar but I think that we should cut back on the cynicism and maybe consider the possibility that that person actually needs help and is not looking for attention. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-04 07:45:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Wherever the third season is :( </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-03 23:32:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thank you very much. Honestly, what really encouraged me yesterday was that I was still able to take my A-level math and English exams pretty well, although I'm in a constant state of brain fog, it seems like if I really need to concentrate on something, I can do it and I can remember everything I've learned. The problem is the motivation. I guess I'll just force myself to do all these things that I'm expected to do and I don't mean that in a cynical, disillusioned way, fake it till you make it, I guess.

I definitely have the advantage of very accepting friends and I've told my mom about the weed and she was honestly relieved to find out that my weird behaviour had a cause and that I didn't feel extremely shitty out of nowhere.

I like comments like yours, because whenever I feel worse, I'll come back to them and instantly feel a bit better and more hopeful! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-03 23:11:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thanks, this thread is really giving me hope, I've been experiencing dpdr for a bit less than a month, also weed induced, and it's terrifying. The symptoms only get more pronounced and it's really hard to ignore such things as extreme light sensitivity or numbness of the skin. Did you also experience pseudo-physical symptoms and how did you deal with them, did they pass? It's very frustrating to have a day where you definitely feel a bit better than yesterday, just to be back to "normal" the next day. At the start of every day questioning whether I feel better, whether I am less numb and every day being disappointed by it. I know that in the scope of others, I haven't been experiencing it for long but my biggest fear is that it won't go away. I don't care if it takes 9 months or 2 years but I just want to be sure that it does get better someday. My ambition really took a hit and right now it's difficult for me to focus on activities that I had fun doing before and now they just seem, don't know how to say, pointless. Of course that's stupid, because nothing is more pointless than to worry about oneself 24/7 when the mind's going at 100 mph.

Just needed to vent a bit. Feel free to share your insights on these topics. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-03 22:51:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm pretty sure I got weed-induced dpdr and I'm experiencing exactly the same visual symptoms as you are minus the visual snow. It really is like you can't see the big picture, only the parts that make it up. The insane light sensitivity really gets me, because it is difficult to ignore. I also seem to have worse eye vision at a distance, like I can't read very small text but it's not like my vision is blurry. It's hard to describe. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-03 22:26:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Utopia reference? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-03 14:39:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Get Out had a similar approach and it ended up being a pretty great film, that a lot of people were bitching about after they saw the trailer. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-02 22:17:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Beats the shit out of passive aggressive political posts. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-02 19:41:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I have just found out, that there will be a reprint coming out on July 11, so one can buy it for about 20 bucks! The edition is not very pretty but at least it's sub 100.

https://www.amazon.de/gp/aw/d/0979312396/ref=mp_s_a_1_1?__mk_de_DE=MZ qid=1493746726 sr=8-1 pi=AC_SX236_SY340_FMwebp_QL65 keywords=women+and+men+mcelroy dpPl=1 dpID=31tN%2BOwDsXL ref=plSrch </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-02 19:36:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thanks for the answer, I'll consider reading it when I've got Pynchon, Bolao and maybe even Gaddis under my belt. :) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-02 19:17:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> How did you manage to get your hands on "Women and Men"? I can't seem to find it anywhere. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-02 11:51:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> True. And the question mark in Infinite Jest (V?) In the filmography does not really do much to clear it up either. Maybe there's an unlisted version. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-02 11:25:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> However, it is possible that this made the copy deadly in the first place. The conversationalist chapter takes place in YTMP, where he has supposedly implanted a cartridge in his head. But Infinite Jest V(?) only came out in the Year of Trial Size Dove Bar so did he implant Infinite Jest IV? V was supposed to be a completed version of IV and was the last film he made. Maybe the microwaving and his death made the cartridge so hypnotic and perfect, improving Infinite Jest IV into the perfect entertainment. It would have a symbolic message, with the artist literally having to sacrifice himself to create the perfect piece and would also tie in with JOI's conceptual, apres-garde, cleverness for cleverness' sake films he made. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-02 10:57:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yes JOI was very much done with the world; him being a failure on most levels, his films hated by most, his crippling alcohol addiction, Avril having more affairs than you could count up to, Mario probably not even being his son, Hal supposedly not talking to him. James Inc is a very broken character, so his suicide was probably not caused by a single event, such as creating Infinite Jest or anything like that. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-02 10:33:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Either it's just a reference or he must mean Avril or Joelle. He has a lot of contempt for his mother but we don't really know what caused Joelle and him to break up. Yes, it could be the acid but DFW has made it intentionally ambiguous, whether Joelle is really disformed or too beautiful and ashamed of that, seeing what it has done to her dad. Joelle is also talked to by Steeply around the ending of the novel, so it could well be her too. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-02 10:29:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> JOI's wraith seems very inconsistent to me. Why would he appear to Gately but not to Hal, Orin or Mario? Why would Lyle appear to Gately? The wraith can put words in people's head and he does so throughout the novel. You really notice it, if you read it twice. Characters often use esoteric words and then wonder where they came from, or it is remarked n a footnote that the character didn't actually use this weird word. Why does he do it? Is he the third person narrator for most of the novel? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-02 10:25:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Congratulations! There has been a similar thread a few days a go and I can only tell you what I told the other poster:
 
I would be wary of seeing Aaron Swartz's theory as the correct one, the whole aspect with the DMZ and IJ being made for Hal by James  just can't be proven in any way. We just don't know what happens to Hal and that's probably intentional. The ending does not make sense in some places and that's fine. Don't beat yourself up over it, you've clearly understood most things that are to be understood. DFW did not write "Infinite Jest" to be solvable and everyone who tried it (including myself), even read it twice for that matter, will tell you that it just doesn't add up.

Here is what I think is _actually_ implied in the book and what we can assume to be true. We can make up theories about the other stuff but they can't really be proven:

[IJ Spoilers](#s "It is made very clear that Orin has had the master copy of IJ for the longest time, up until the end, where the AFR took it from him by seducing him with Luria P__. The tape that the medical attach recieves in the beginning of the novel has 'Happy Anniversary' written on it. It was send on April 1. The anniversary of JOI's suicide. Also the package came from Phoenix, Arizona, where Orin lived. So why did he send the package? To take revenge on Avril, who he thinks has driven JOI to kill himself by having lots _and lots_  of affairs with different attachs. He wouldn't harm Avril directly, though, because he has deeply rooted Mommy issues, as becomes clear through his sexual attractions to married moms and, of course, because she is still his mother. Also Hal asks Orin why he went to the post office, when he doesn't usually write letters. He went to send deadly copies of IJ to previous love affairs of Avril. Steepy once remarks how many attachs have been dying by watching the deadly film, which is why he suspects that it is a terror attack by the AFR. Next up, we know that the Year of Glad is the last year of Subsidized time, it is mentioned in footnote 114. What happened? At the end of the novel, the AFR comes to the ETA but can't get hold of Hal, because he is send off to a hospital. Somehow (this is the part that can't be solved) Hal and Gately and Wayne get together and dig up JOI's grave to find the master copy and to save ONAN but Orin or the Antitois brothers already got it long ago. ('Too late!', as Gately dreams when he is hospitalized) And such the AFR threatens to release IJ to the public and the US administration has to follow their demands; take back the Convexity, stop subsidized time, and stop dumping their trash in Qubec. Wayne helped Hal and co. and has either been killed or disappeared otherwise. Marathe mentions at one point that there is an agent placed in the ETA already, that must be Wayne, so it would make sense for the AFR to execute him for treason. Wayne's father was a mine worker and in the footnote about the Jeu de prochain train, it is said that miners often played the game. Also Wayne is also canadian and has had sex with Avril, possibly to spy on her. ")


Now to what we can't know:

[IJ Spoilers #2](#s "What caused Hal to have feeings in the first chapter again but nobody can understand him? Is Joelle really disfigured or just too beautiful and ashamed? What is up with JOI's wraith? And Lyle's wraith for that matter, which also appears to Gately. The wraith can put thoughts in peoples minds and through rereading the novel there are a _shitton_ of spots where f.ex. Gately says something and is then commented by "that was not the word he used" or Mario says something else and it is commented that Mario doesn't really know the meaning of the word and where it came from. This happens often. Is JOI's wraith the third person narrator for most of the novel? Did Hal take the DMZ and how? If not, where did it go, Pemulis couldn't find it at the end. Is what we know of the film, IJ, true? Is it really what Molly Notkins described? What the hell is up with the end of the conversationalist chapter from page 27 onwards? How did Fackelmann die? Was Gately's dream towards the end, where he takes the bus through the Concavity and digs up some grave with Joelle and a sad boy, Hal, a premonition induced by JOI or just unexplainable coincidence? Has JOI made the DMZ and the film IJ for Hal? This is what Aaron Swartz suggests but I'm not sold on it.")

There are many questions that can't be solved and probably never will be but I personally still like, that there is an ending, if you look close enough. It is just, that many questions remain unanswered and you have to accept that. I made a similar thread in /r/InfiniteDiscussion, asking about the ending of the conversationalist chapter (p.27), which seems to throw up even more questions. You can look it up, if you want to. There are some interesting tidbits on that, as you've already wondered yourself what's up with the cartridge implanted in his brain. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-01 12:47:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Geez dude, don't scare me like that. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-01 12:12:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> An amalgamation of Pynchon and Franzen could _almost_ pull it off. Pynchon for the amazing, complex prose and the weirdness and Franzen for the human connections and feelings. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-01 12:09:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yes, but Infinite Jest is actually more zany than many people think: JOI's wraith, Lyle, 'Helen' Steeply and Orin, James Inc's films. It is a depressing novel but the world in IJ is not as bleak as in, say, Brave New World or The Road. Atleast it isn't for me. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-01 12:00:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> They are very difficult but also very rewarding. I'd suggest to start with either "Inherent Vice", "Vineland" or "The Crying of Lot 49". </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-01 11:38:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yes, but the story still makes sense to some extent:

[IJ Spoilers](#s "It is made very clear that Orin has had the master copy of IJ for the longest time, up until the end, where the AFR took it from him by seducing him with Luria P__. The tape that the medical attach recieves in the beginning of the novel has 'Happy Anniversary' written on it. It was send on April 1. The anniversary of JOI's suicide. Also the package came from Phoenix, Arizona, where Orin lived. So why did he send the package? To take revenge on Avril, who he thinks has driven JOI to kill himself by having lots _and lots_  of affairs with different attachs. He wouldn't harm Avril directly, though, because he has deeply rooted Mommy issues, as becomes clear through his sexual attractions to married moms and, of course, because she is still his mother. Also Hal asks Orin why he went to the post office, when he doesn't usually write letters. He went to send deadly copies of IJ to previous love affairs of Avril. Steepy once remarks how many attachs have been dying by watching the deadly film, which is why he suspects that it is a terror attack by the AFR. Next up, we know that the Year of Glad is the last year of Subsidized time, it is mentioned in footnote 114. What happened? At the end of the novel, the AFR comes to the ETA but can't get hold of Hal, because he is send off to a hospital. Somehow (this is the part that can't be solved) Hal and Gately and Wayne get together and dig up JOI's grave to find the master copy and to save ONAN but Orin or the Antitois brothers already got it long ago. ('Too late!', as Gately dreams when he is hospitalized) And such the AFR threatens to release IJ to the public and the US administration has to follow their demands; take back the Convexity, stop subsidized time, and stop dumping their trash in Qubec. Wayne helped Hal and co. and has either been killed or disappeared otherwise. Marathe mentions at one point that there is an agent placed in the ETA already, that must be Wayne, so it would make sense for the AFR to execute him for treason. Wayne's father was a mine worker and in the footnote about the Jeu de prochain train, it is said that miners often played the game. Also Wayne is also canadian and has had sex with Avril, possibly to spy on her. ")


Now to what we can't know:

[IJ Spoilers #2](#s "What caused Hal to have feeings in the first chapter again but nobody can understand him? Is Joelle really disfigured or just too beautiful and ashamed? What is up with JOI's wraith? And Lyle's wraith for that matter, which also appears to Gately. The wraith can put thoughts in peoples minds and through rereading the novel there are a _shitton_ of spots where f.ex. Gately says something and is then commented by "that was not the word he used" or Mario says something else and it is commented that Mario doesn't really know the meaning of the word and where it came from. This happens often. Is JOI's wraith the third person narrator for most of the novel? Did Hal take the DMZ and how? If not, where did it go, Pemulis couldn't find it at the end. Is what we know of the film, IJ, true? Is it really what Molly Notkins described? What the hell is up with the end of the conversationalist chapter from page 27 onwards? How did Fackelmann die? Was Gately's dream towards the end, where he takes the bus through the Concavity and digs up some grave with Joelle and a sad boy, Hal, a premonition induced by JOI or just unexplainable coincidence? Has JOI made the DMZ and the film IJ for Hal? This is what Aaron Swartz suggests but I'm not sold on it.")

There are many questions that can't be solved and probably never will be but I personally still like, that there is an ending, if you look close enough. It is just, that many questions remain unanswered and you have to accept that.
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-01 09:44:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You're not alone with that, many people felt frustrated with the ending. Especially, when it seems so close to being solvable. One could say that DFW pulls a trick on the reader, gets them addicted and then pulls the rug from under them, just like the characters in the book and their addictions. I mean, the book is very circular in its structure, just like IJ, the film, you could read it over and over again. Some people believe that DFW wanted to show the hollowness of entertainment that way. I think that's pretty cynical and ironic, which is exactly what IJ criticizes and it would be kind of hypocritical, when DFW advocates connecting with the reader again and telling stories with emotional impact, without the hip, cynical, ironic distance.

I'm also not sure what to think about it, but I like to believe that DFW would not write a book with many philosophical insights and great writing for almost a decade just to prank the reader but who really knows? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-30 23:41:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I have only read "CivilWarLand in Bad Decline". The atmosphere is incredibly bleak and I loved most of the stories on there. Really looking forward to reading more of his short stories. Do you have suggestions? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-30 23:34:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I like that theory but I would be careful with viewing it as the "solution" because there are some flaws in it and it is impossible to prove it. I agree with some of his points, though. I've come to the conclusion that you shouldn't try to solve Infinite Jest. It's not possible and that is probably also the point it's trying to make. It's best to enjoy it for what it is and for the little insights that DFW scatters on almost every page. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-30 15:58:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Why? Do you have an example? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-29 23:25:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yes, you're probably right. I have my doubts with Swartz's theory too, there simply isn't enough proof for his claims. I mean, I love Infinite Jest. It is probably my favorite book but is it ever frustrating to know that Wallace probably didn't try to explain all those things for himself, which may be the point but it is frustrating nonetheless because the solution seems to be just out of reach. (Kind of like Pynchon's "The Crying of Lot 49", which clearly influenced Wallace while writing IJ. W.A.S.T.E, weird names that could mean anything or nothing, an unresolved plot.) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-29 17:53:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yes, if you phrase it like that, it's a really interesting thought. The question mark in "IJ (V?)" might suggest that the cartridge actually only became deadly after his suicide. We know the content is similar to "IJ (IV)" because it is supposed to be a finalized version of it, which would imply that "IJ (V?)" literally only exists posthumously. This would also shed a bit of light on why JOI stuck his head in a microwave. Not the most common way of killing yourself. It's a wacky theory but Infinite Jest is zany enough that it just might be possible. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-29 15:21:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> In my opinion, one shouldn't attach DFW's suicide to the plot of Infinite Jest too much, since it was written more than a decade earlier. Sure, he did experience depression and anxiety but I wouldn't go as far as to say that his suicide was planned way before, so it would accord to the plot of IJ. I haven't read The Pale King but for that one, it seems more likely to be influenced by DFW's suicidal thoughts. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [Spoilers] What do you make of the April 1st Y.T.M.P conversationalist chapter? (p.27-31) </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-29 11:38:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I have been rereading the book for a while now and I thought that I had a rather solid grasp on what happened with the master copy of "Infinite Jest" but reading that chapter again, where Hal talks to JOI disguised as a conversationalist seemed very disorienting to me.

The scene is also found in JOI's filmography, titled "It Was a Great Marvel That He Was in the Father Without Knowing Him", dated Year of the Trial-size Dove Bar. JOI had previously made films about his personal life, too. (Avril's infidelity, him discovering cold annular fusion, the beginnings of the Gentle administration etc.) Why is that important? It tells us that the conversationalist scene (p.27-31) is most likely real, and has happened, which leads to many question:

1. When has Hal stopped talking like a smart-ass, like he does in that chapter? For the most part (Y.D.A.U), Hal outwardly behaves like a normal person, although we know that he doesn't really feel much of anything. In the last chronological chapter (Y.O.G), Hal seems to be back to talking like a smart-ass but this time, nobody can actually understand him, yet he feels real emotions again. What triggered his first change? Was it JOI's death? Did it actually affect Hal a lot more than he himself thinks it does? Does his own process of grief/denial end at the end of the novel, when Hal is watching JOI's films in the Cartridge Viewer room?

2. At the end of the chapter, James escalates into talking about Avril's infidelity, mnemonic steroids that she is supposedly feeding Hal with, that a "priapistic-entertainment cartridge" was implanted in his brain after a series of surgeries. These are interesting clues, but what in the hell is up with that cartridge? "Infinite Jest" is said to be "priapistic" and there are often references of the cartridge being buried with him, hidden in his skull. Does JOI already have a copy of "Infinite Jest" implanted in his head, exactly one year before he kills himself? Why does he tell Hal about it? (Aaron Swartz's theory suggests that JOI made the DMZ and "Infinite Jest" for Hal but that can't really be proven. http://www.aaronsw.com/weblog/ijend Here it is, if you're interested.)

3. If he has "IJ" implanted in his head, which version of "Infinite Jest" is it actually? There are multiple listed in his filmography and the most likely answer seems to be "IJ (IV)", since it was made in Y.T.M.P. "IJ (V?)" (Why the question mark?) was created the year JOI killed himself and it was reviewed by "Cartridge Quarterly East", which would mean that "IJ (V?)" doesn't have the same hypnotic effect, as one would expect. Additionally experimental camera setups are mentioned in the filmography, which makes sense, because Joelle described how the film was created using a weird wobbly lense. It just doesn't add up to me. Which "IJ" version is the deadly one, is it IV or V? We find out on multiple occasions what the supposed content of the film is. I know that there isn't an explanation, as to why the film is so deadly but I'd like to know what is up with that conversationalist chapter, because it seems to invalidate some established facts. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-27 15:04:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> "It can't be science if it contradicts my personal experience" </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-25 21:42:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I liked both IV and TCOL49 but I enjoyed TCOL49 a bit more. I really liked the feel of IV but I'm also not sure whether I did not understand all of the character connections and motives or whether you're not really supposed to. TCOL49 actually reminded me a lot of IV as far as the conspiracies and the paranoia goes. W.A.S.T.E, the Post Horn and the Golden Fang in IV. I guess I liked Oedipa Maas more than Doc but I'm planning on rereading Inherent Vice at a later point in life again. I'm very looking forward to reading his other stuff, although the hardest part for me are the flood of references to 20th century American culture, music and historical events, since I can't relate to much of it. I wonder how well I'll do with Mason and Dixon but GR, for now, is next on the Pynchon list for me. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-25 20:54:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I've only started getting into adult fiction at the end of last year with "House of Leaves" and "Unendlicher Spa (Infinite Jest)", which I finished mid-February this year. Since then I've read:

* "Ruhm (Fame)" by Daniel Kehlmann
* "Zero K" by Don DeLillo
* "Inherent Vice" by Thomas Pynchon
* "The Fifty-Year Sword" by Mark Z Danielewski
* "If on a winter's night a traveler" by Italo Calvino
* "Freedom" by Jonathan Franzen
* "The Crying of Lot 49" by Pynchon, again
* "Die Taube (The Pidgeon)" by Patrick Sskind
* "CivilWarLand in Bad Decline" by George Saunders

Currently I'm reading Faulkner's "The Sound and the Fury", which is pretty hard but it seems quite rewarding. The writing is beautiful. Meanwhile I'm also rereading "Infinite Jest" but in English this time. I got to say, it's better in English than in German, although the translation is generally well done. Also, the second read is way more rewarding and coherent, for me at least.

I would like to read more but sadly I've been pretty busy studying for my A-levels, though reading many of the mentioned books in English (not a native speaker) has massively improved my word pool and comprehension of complex narratives.

I gotta thank /r/books (and to /u/nothingcleverleft) for introducing me to many great works, some of which I'm very eager to read already. (2666, Gravity's Rainbow, Wind-Up-Bird Chronicles, Pale Fire and many others) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-25 10:20:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> **The Sound and the Fury, by William Faulkner**

Insanely difficult but it manages to keep my attention. I'm almost done with the second part, which started off way easier than Benjy's but gradually became similarly confusing to me. I'll probably need to read it again, after I'm done.

**CivilWarLand in Bad Decline, by George Saunders**
Extremely bleak and depressing but also pretty funny and surprisingly hopeful. Saunders is really good with dark humor. There are pages in here, after which you just need to take a moment to breathe and to digest what had just happened. Great book, especially for fans of dystopian literature.
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-24 22:32:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It wouldn't be, because the fluorescent compound was dissolved in water, which was dried off. That also means that the title of the post in not really correct since it's not the Nylon that is fluorescent. By pulling out the Nylon out of the beaker, a lot of water and solvent got trapped between the Nylon, which made it look like the Nylon is glowing. You wouldn't be able to make glowing clothes or anything with it, though. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-24 19:56:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Same, I got it with 16 for no discernable reason but I learned to live with it and it barely affects my life 2 years later. Granted it's not an extremely loud or intrusive form of tinnitus but the first weeks were hell for me and even now this starter pack reminds me of myself back when it just started. In my case, I found these "rain sound websites" helpful short term but I stopped using them because they made the ringing a bit worse afterwards. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-23 11:38:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Well, I'm pretty sure that your opinion does not get to decide what is a mental illness and what isn't. There are actual classifications for that. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-23 08:41:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Pynchon, DeLillo and David Foster Wallace? Great taste, dude! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-23 08:16:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Oh it was "Infinite Jest" by David Foster Wallace. I'm currently rereading it in Englisch, since I've only read it in German before. There's a lot of fictional Boston street slang in that book, which is why I thought that "pillowbiter" was also made up. It's not an easy book but it has grown to be my favorite. Not for everyone though. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-22 20:43:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I was about to write that. I know "pillowbiter" from a (great) book I've recently read but I didn't know that it was an actual term. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-22 16:17:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Sure, but you were pretty unpolite about it, too. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-22 15:57:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's just above your own comment. The solution in the video is not an acid. It is Mountain Dew and the spoon is made of Gallium. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-21 14:20:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I thought it was finished but about 1000 pages needed to be revised and his editors and friends took up that task but I could be wrong. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-18 22:57:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The scary part is the urge to look up dpdr or to browse this sup and seeing how many people are still struggling with it after years, while not noticing any improvements or even deterioration in my own condition. Do you have any more advice? Two days ago, after I've noticed dpdr symptoms already, I couldn't look into most light sources, even if they're usually not that bright, aka LEDs or fluorescent lights. Is that also a possible symptom of dpdr and will it go away? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-18 19:00:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I actually think that The Familiar series by him is pretty good. It grows on you. Though I was also disappointed by T50YS. It obviously wants to seem more clever and cool than it is. The whole "different narrators" gimmick did not have any consequence at all and I found the purposefully misspelled words annoying. HOS on the other hand, I still like, because that try-hard unique style fits the found footage labyrinthine story (and house) much better. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-18 16:28:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Did you also get visual distortions? Light sources are kinda blinding or glowing to me but other than that, I can only seem to comprehend the parts of an object or building that I'm looking at right now. Like you can see the different parts but you can't _understand_ the whole object at once? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-17 19:53:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yes, exactly that. Mostly worries about whether or not it is permanent or if it does get worse. It feels bad to know I'm not supposed to think about that stuff but I can't help it right now. It's hard to distract myself from something that _seems_ so important and fatal. Thank you and the guys on this sub for giving me hope.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-17 19:38:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I don't know if part of your experience was this numbness, sudden lack of interest and frantic, OCDish, labyrinthine thoughts. What would be your first hand advice, ignore completely and wait out? I'm a bit worried that I only noticed the symptoms about 3 days after I smoked the weed. And that the symptoms got worse once I really put my finger on what it was, that is off. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-17 19:01:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Did you also experience OCDish thoughts? Have they diminished over time? Right now my mind is constantly racing and getting stuck in bad thought patterns, only making the anxiety worse. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-15 20:08:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thank you very much, it is a huge relief to know that this is not that uncommon. It is just unfortunate that I still have to write 3/5 A-level exams very soon and I don't want them to fuck up my score. I'll need to calm myself down a bit until then. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-15 20:06:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> A bit cloudy but I would rather call it frantic. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-15 18:59:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thank you, you cannot imagine how encouraging that is right now. I actually teared up a bit. I already know how this type of unknown creeping illness feels. 2 years ago I slowly startes hearing a ringing in my ears (tinnitus basically) without listening to loud music or anything else. Doctors couldn't diagnose the cause and nothing helped so far. Nothing but to ignore it completely, while also knowing that it is there. Right now it barely affects my life anymore except I don't like to stay in silence for a longer period of time. The first month was scary as shit. Waking up every day, wondering if it has gone away, only to be disappointed. Sometimes even tricking myself that I don't hear it, only to notice it a few moments later. Worrying every day that this might never go away and that this will be awful. But actually, as my favorite writer David Foster Wallace said, (something like) "no single moment is in and of itself unendurable" that it is just thinking about all the future moments that is frightening.

Again thanks for your message! I hope I'll get better and in the meantime, I'll try to distract myself with books, sports, Netflix or league.

Edit: I highly recommend reading Infinite Jest by Dave Wallace. It really helped my to get a perspective on (kicking) addiction, depression and also, competitive tennis. It's not an easy read but it's worth it. In one chapter, a character describes getting off morphine derivatives in terms of thinking about them every day and loathing every day at first but gradually, noticing that he spent a whole hour not thinking about doing morphine and suddenly a week went by, then a month and so on, which seems similar to what you've described. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Smoked weed once and half a week later I'm experiencing DP/DR symptoms. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-15 18:26:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I am 18 years old and while celebrating my birthday with friends, one of them gave me a joint as a present and I decided to smoke it (with 2 other people). I have been drinking before, I know you're not supposed to do that but I thought that it wasn't that much and after all, there are a lot of people who can handle it. It was my first time smoking pot.

I smoked it sitting down and in darkness, we were outside. And after standing up again, I felt quite bad, like I was going to pass out and I couldn't see anything because it was so dark. I was really scared for half a minute and my head got very light. Anyway, I set one foot in front of the other and by the time I reached the streetlights and my home again, I proceeded to feel fine again and had a good celebration. Seemingly everything was fine. The next few days, I didn't feel anything differently until my family and I went to Italy on vacation(4 days later), when I started to feel really weird, it was very subtle at first and it still is not very pronounced.

After a bit of googling I found out that I check most DP/DR symptoms. Robotic automatization, head full of wool, numbness, feeling _wrong_ in my body, like I'm in a video game I can't control. Like I have some sort of tunnel vision, where I can recognize the different parts of a building/room but I can't grasp the bigger picture. Thinking waaay too much, making it worse. Losing touch with the reality around me. I don't experience loss of emotions and all of the previously described feelings are also rather subtle and hard to describe. I still function normally but I would rather just _wake up_ because it feels like I'm in a kind of dream.

This has been going on for 3-4 days and it's freaking me out. I don't know whether the weed triggered it but I was never prone to anxiety or panic attacks before. I am definitely not going to smoke weed or drink alcohol or coffee for a long time or ever. I did not experience this immediately after the party has ended but I could just have not noticed it until now. I know that this kind of thing could stay for weeks, months, years and some people never really get rid of it.

What are your suggestions to deal with my condition better? I was thinking of getting it officially diagnosed first, so I can be sure that it is DP/DR. Did anyone of you experience drug (weed) induced DP/DR? Did it go away for you and how long did it take?

Thanks in advance. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-11 00:40:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> They just need to find the right sub, where anyone with dissenting opinion is either crushed by the echo chamber or banned. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-11 00:14:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Oh "The Tin Drum" is insane, I'm planning on reading it sometimes soon. When it first came out, it was hated by most critics. Now, it is seen as one of the greatest literary accomplishments of 20th century Germany. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-07 21:55:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I really love "Castration", "Saunter", "Urchin" and "Reverie"! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-06 22:11:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Wahrscheinlich denkt sie, sie lebe in einem Pynchon Roman. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-06 18:56:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The_Bookchemist (https://www.youtube.com/channel/UCWE-DhzTZqCGu_uZmVBOgig) usually reviews interesting books and although I don't always agree with his opinion, he's a great source to discover post-modernist or contemporary literature. Most YT book related channels focus too much on YA and fantasy, which is fine if you're into that. 

Another recommendation from me is Better Than Food: Book Reviews (https://www.youtube.com/user/booksbetterthanfood). He only reviews books he liked and he's good a great taste in music and books. He's very enthusiastic about the books he talks about and usually explains his opinion very well. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-06 16:55:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I have just started Volume 1 and it seems interesting enough, although some of the styles, especially jingjing's, makes me want to throw the book against a wall. I wonder if he'll manage to pull off the 27 volumes without too much filler. The novels are actually much shorter than the page number (and the weight) suggests. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-06 10:28:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yes, it is not really relaxing, but it would also be weird if the subject matters (solitude, depression, addiction, purpose, pursuit of happiness and consumerism) were presented in a light hearted, easy, digestable way. It is done right this way, even if it feels that jumbling up the order of the chapters is a little too much, that's the aspect that makes the book difficult, I think. Even if IJ has been attributed to "post-post-modernism", I think it still has that post-modernist thinking in it, that reality can not be understood on the grand scale. The different parts of it can be understood, but you cannot put them together in a meaningful way. The difference in IJ's take on this is, that IJ doesn't delve into cynicism or irony. It critizises such detachment from real feelings, from taking anything seriously. Whether or not one agrees with it is up to each reader but I think that it is at least interesting to think about.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-06 09:50:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It certainly takes some work, but I found it to be more like solving a puzzle than a chore. Some people don't like that though. IJ doesn't hand you all of the connections on a silver plate. It gives you most of the puzzle pieces (except for one large chunk in the middle of the jig saw puzzle lol) but you have to put them together yourself. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-06 09:00:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yes, it is not about the ending. If you read it for the complete resolution of the plot, you'll be disappointed. Doesn't mean that there is no ending, it is just pretty well hidden, since the most important events happen outside of what's told. If you read the first few chapters again after you're done, you will have a _much_ greater understanding what happened in the seemingly non-existent ending. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-06 08:39:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Good luck, dude. Don't expect a smooth ride, especially the beginning will make little sense but you should be gradually getting it as you go. After you're done, read the first few chapters again, that's very important if you want to understand the ending. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-05 22:42:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Well, the comic only shows the _probability_ of it being good. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-04 15:03:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I have started it in late December 2016 and finished mid February. I wouldn't say that I'm a particularly fast reader but not that slow either. It is long but some passages keep you flipping the pages over and over again. Some may be a little boring to you, depends on whether or not you have interest in tennis and/or AA ceremonies. It is still totally worth it in my opinion. People like to say that IJ is incredibly difficult but really, it is just pretty long and it starts to pick up around page 300. As for the language and the footnotes, it's not that bad. If you don't have the urge to look up _every_ unknown word, it is going to be much less frustrating. You can use the Infinite Jest page by page annotations on the wiki but I'd rather suggest to just read it and enjoy. Be fine with things you don't understand, they'll most likely be explained sometimes later.

I'm reading "Infinite Jest" for the second time (in English this time) right now and I gotta say, that I'm surprised how much I missed and how much I can now understand from the early parts of the book. It is very complex, sad, funny and rewarding. Give it a shot, if you feel up to the challenge!


Edit: There is a periodic reading and discussion club over at /r/InfiniteDiscussion. It is easier to read it in a group and discuss your impressions afterwards. You just need to look when the next round starts, it should be rather soon. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-04 10:27:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Great video. Infinite Jest by him continues to be my favorite book of all time. As for irony, I think he's right. Over time I've been unsubbing things like me_irl and the overuse of irony and especially sarcasm that's been cooking up in political discussions in the last few years is getting more annoying by the day. Especially in the dreaded YT comment sections. 'No, it's not like I don't understand irony or sarcasm, it just doesn't make everything you say funny.' It's cheap and best used in moderation. I can't fathom how people hold up the usage of irony itself as the pinnacle of humor. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-04 10:18:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Have you ever seen both of them in the same room? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-04 09:06:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The opinion of gay people in Germany is not very homogenous either. There is a lot of acceptance in the north, while there is generally less in the south. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-03 23:58:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This is going to sound stupid but after only 50 pages it is impossible to have any idea of the story, since the style jumps around a whole lot and major characters are being introduced up to about p 300. After you more or less know all the characters it gets much easier. There is also the fact that the beginning of IJ is full of first person narration of (yet) unknown origin. This gets much less in the mid-section of the book, when the narration mostly stays 3rd person. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-03 23:54:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I found that not looking up every unknown word is way more enjoyable than pausing all the time. I suggest only looking up words you deem relevant to your understanding of the section. There is a lot of medical and scientific vocab in IJ that you'll never need again. However if you find that interesting; Google ahead! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-03 23:49:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I thought that I was going to struggle with TCoL49 but after reading the much longer Infinite Jest and the thoroughly confusing and disorienting Inherent Vice (Pynchon lite, my ass) it was surprisingly coherent. The only difficult parts were the fake historical events and _The Courier's Tragedy_. These sections were extremely dense with information but other than that, it was easier than Inherent Vice. (To me atleast) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-02 22:03:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Sure, that I believe you. It would be extremely unlikely for that not to be the case but does it really support that it is "so hypocritical" as the user above claims? For such a large platform, as reddit, there needs to be more than just some people (there are always some people) to really call hypocrisy. That's just my opinion. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-02 21:42:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I just don't understand how you find that there is _significant_ overlap? If there's no data, it's just conjecture.

Edit: Emitted badly phrased sentence. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-02 20:42:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Still, are they upvoted by the same people? How is it hypocritical if one group of people upvotes one type of post and another group upvotes another? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-02 10:16:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Infinite Jest is not about finishing it. If you read it like that, you'll be disappointed with the ending. It really picks up around page 300. Although, if you did't get anything from the prose, it might not be worth it for you. Still, most people who've read it will agree: The general understanding of the world, the politics and the character relationships start to come together in the second half of the book. There are a lot of references to events that you could not possibly know about in the first 300 pages. That can be frustrating to many. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-01 23:04:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The Bell Jar by Sylvia Plath also seems to be quite popular here. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-01 01:15:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You mean a "libtard cuck" </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
