<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject251</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-10 01:49:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Fold flop.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-10 00:27:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Popcorn.jpg </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [homemade] Sesame ginger crusted halibut with pineapple salsa and risotto </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-09 23:57:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-08 16:50:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I can do 7lb in a 4g kettle if that helps. I think you'd be ok but just google a good mash volume calculator  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-06 23:31:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Can you tell me the exact diameter of the 2.5g ball locks? I have a small keezer build and have some size constraints  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-05 13:32:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> PM coming  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-05 01:03:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Bink an MTT or two.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-04 23:55:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Lmao this is 100% not legal.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-04 23:54:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Any FT? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-04 13:07:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Oh my god. No. And no. 

12 is extremely standard and probably more on the smaller side for live 1/2. Leading river is fine, it's a disaster if river gets checked through which he does w a large range of his value hands after being called on flop and turn.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-30 14:58:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Welcome. Tony's is a good suggestion, you'll also be close to fat orange cat which is producing some decent stuff out of east Hampton  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-30 04:35:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thought the exact same thing. So dumb.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-29 18:03:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This hand is such a dumpster fire  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-28 10:24:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Rake usually makes these games unbeatable but there are certainly instances where they can be profitable if there's enough action. If pots are never raised preflop and no one is 2 and 3betting post flop, it'll be tough.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-27 14:25:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Spin your chair 360 degrees and chuck Norris side kick your chip stack into the middle while announcing Arrrrr innnnn </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-24 19:43:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That open sizing is so next level zomg  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-24 03:24:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> As wondering how busy that would be. Thanks for sharing  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-24 02:20:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Omg. Soooo sorry about that. Nice fish though! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-24 00:23:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> How are you sitting like that...  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-23 19:32:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Agree, flat is the right play - I was just saying folding AK there after betting half his stack is pretty unlikely.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-23 19:25:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I think AK is bet calling the river pretty frequently honestly. He would be getting an insane price  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-22 00:19:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Flat his flop raise imo.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-22 00:15:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This hand is absolutely a fold pre. I think you're wayyyy overvaluing AJJT. Play around w some equity calculators against random hands.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-22 00:13:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hand 1 4b is fine. Hand 2 I normally flat this hand as getting 4b sucks vs described villain. True that you don't want to play multiway w AJ but I think you allow him to make more mistakes postflop if you play it slower.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-21 15:36:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Edit: 1/3 of EACH for total of 2/3 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-21 14:54:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> c'mon you've never used 0.58333333333 oz of hops before? lol

Probably just a scaling thing.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-21 14:47:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> 2/3 oz of bittering hops per 2 gallon batch?  I'm still learning, but that seems insanely high to me - depending on the AA content I guess.  How many IBUs?

Edit: 2/3 not 1 oz  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [homemade] hickory smoked leg of lamb </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-17 13:43:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-17 00:18:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Cmon... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-15 03:31:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Don't be results oriented. That's a fist pump shove pre.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-12 21:40:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Maybe after you're done there you can visit the Pentagon and then the Oval Office? Let us know which is your favorite. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-11 21:49:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Debt </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-11 14:12:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I was taking into account the context of OP and how he was running his mouth, but yea, i get it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-11 04:46:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Congrats on the win. Also feels great to stick it to greedy pricks who won't make a deal.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-10 18:43:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> White motors are generally pretty great (and this is coming from an ex-Parker employee).  I cant speak to that pump, but its low price is rather surprising... I was expecting something in the 500-1000 range.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-10 13:44:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Maybe link us to the pumps youre looking at so we can find viable single output solutions...

Sizing the motors down in displacement would actually increase the speed at the same given input flow rate.  You can get independent steering/motoring with valving that adjusts the input to each motor. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-10 02:53:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> How does he raise to $50 if you bet $30?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-10 02:01:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Definitely would not suggest going with multiple piston pumps. One large hydtrostat or piston pump would definitely supply enough flow. If not, you can size your motors down to a smaller displacement too.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-10 00:50:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Uncleronaa </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-09 19:33:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Uncle Ron is the nuts. His snap chat stories always brighten my day  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-08 15:49:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> lol @ limping pre. 

As played jam turn - villain is calling w such a huge range of hands  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-08 03:56:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Can't argue w that. Also big fan of Azacca and Amarillo lately  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-07 04:35:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> "Move up to where they respect your raises"  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-06 15:21:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I assume this was an AG batch?  I will say I tried to make a DNEIPA with extract once and experienced this same phenomenon.  The AG batch I made was incredible and did not even compare. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-05 21:17:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> In college I was sitting on the stoop of my new apartment waiting for the cable guy.  A 20-30 something year old African American man wearing nothing but a hospital gown asked me if he could borrow my pair of pants.  I said "like, the ones I'm wearing??" and he said "YES!"

I said "Sorry man I can't help you out" and he said "my roommates are gunna think I'm f***** crazy, 4th time this week this shit has happened to me." As he turned to leave he started singing the Philadelphia Eagles "Fly Eagles Fly" song.

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-05 01:18:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> lol what are you talking about... People profitably 3b and call 3b w those holdings all the time.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-04 15:32:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Well worth it.  The tasting system is pretty sweet.  They give you a small tasting glass along with 4 orange poker chips.  You then can trade in your chip for a pour of whatever they happen to have that day - they had 6 brews when I was there.  Each pour was very generous and you're basically on an honor system to go pay at the register.  Its $5 and you keep the glass, so that was cheap.  Crowler/growler fills were a little pricey but that's okay.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-04 02:12:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Went for their opening last weekend and was pleasantly surprised. The barn/tasting room has a nice charm and the Concensus DIPA was pretty solid. Keep in mind this is coming from a tree house fanboy.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-03 02:10:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Make people aware that you don't chop and always abide by that rule. My rule of thumb is "I don't chop 5 handed or less."

Some will think you're being a tiiiiiny bit rude, but if you pick and choose which hands you chop you're a dick.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-02 21:37:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Lmao at #2. Little Giants reference 

https://youtu.be/Nn4cioLwa30 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-31 20:29:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I really think youre underestimating this.  I would say 30% but still.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-31 13:44:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I've also done this a TON for trades and whatnot.  Only shipper I have ever had a problem with is FedEx and they took 12 cans from me and would not return them.  Been shipping USPS ever since and have never had a problem with medium/large flat rate boxes.  I put each can in a plastic bag, individually wrap w bubble wrap, add padding to the walls of the box, and usually throw in some loose rice as a noise maker.  If anyone asks whats in the box, "care package for a friend who just came back from a year long volunteer abroad trip"

They tell you how sweet you are and you go on your way :) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-31 04:05:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> HU hyperturbo sngo </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-31 03:07:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Adding later is a little better but it's still going to be dark.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-31 00:15:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I would also suggest a bigger whirlpool and bigger dryhop </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-31 00:00:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I've found it almost impossible to get colors right w LME or DME. Be prepared for a super dark beer. Flavors could be pretty good though </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-29 22:45:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You're often going to flop marginal holdings OOP. That is all.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-29 19:43:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> One of those guys... effectively it does the same damn thing. Sorry he didn't make it 1600 to go... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-29 15:35:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You can't minraise 3b with freaking 10bb... just rip it in  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-29 13:33:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> My understanding is you can store it in a tank.  Some people buy 5g jugs and fill them up.  I'm in the same boat as you and considering purchasing one myself so I'd be interested to hear what others say.  I only brew 2.5g batches at the moment so I could totally just RO water a couple hours before brewing.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-27 15:00:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Plastic bucket, thanks! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-27 14:46:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Go to the grocery and buy a small vegetable steamer collapsible rack. It works wonders for me  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-27 14:44:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Have a NEIPA w a layer of floating goopy hop matter from a heavy dry hop.  Can I cold crash this outside on my covered porch?  Don't have a fermentation chamber yet. It's going to be between 40-45 degrees F tonight.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-27 13:52:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Over hyped.  Alchemist was first to market with this style of beer with Heady, and now others are making vastly superior juice bombs imo. I think people are starting to drink heady just so they said they drank heady.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-26 03:35:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hmm now you have me worried lol </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-26 03:01:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Maybe in a keg. I dry hopped for 10 days or so in my fermentor and I can barely drink the shit.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-26 03:00:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Not trying to sound like a smart ass but - Are you sure you're not comparing your OG to your preboil gravity? You're going to boil off water and increase the gravity during the boil.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-26 00:13:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I had this same problem. My AG batches that I did later on were soooo much lighter. As others said, you can add a small amount of extract and boil w your hop additions then add the rest of the extract just before flameout  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-25 23:25:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Wait 11.1 SRM seems super high to me... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-25 16:01:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Depends on your fermentation. For my NEIPAs, normally takes me 7 days to reach my final gravity so I can dry hop literally during high krausen and then a few days before racking. 

It won't do much harm if you leave your beer in primary for longer so that you're not dry hopping before final gravity is reached. In short, should be fine! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-25 15:17:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> 7 is on the upper limit imo. If you leave the DH in longer than that you will develop some unwanted grassy flavors. I tend to use 5 and 3 day.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-24 20:33:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Why am I envisioning him crying while doing this...? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-24 15:21:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Im a huge citra fanboy but do whatever you feel like! Its your beer, flip a coin! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-24 03:13:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Ah the good ol days. Used to drive from Hartford CT area to TS to play when I was 18-19. Just printed money in that place. Good luck finding a ride </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-24 03:12:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So why are you leaving stars? Biggest player pool seems like the best place the play imo. Why not just move up? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-24 02:59:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This makes me want to make a trip to Denmark. Lol 

GL OP </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-22 18:18:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Because AmeriKKKa </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-22 17:51:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I mean, that doesn't sound very practical. Sure it will work if you can accurately make 13 portions... but cmon.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-22 15:45:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yea I use brewers friend but like I said I was measuring sugar in volume and not in mass  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-22 15:01:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Completely agree and I will be doing so in the future.  Reason I asked is before I owned the scale I had to guess by volume.  My first couple batches came out slightly under-carbed.  I'll do one next time by mass and hopefully will have better results.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-22 14:42:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I don't know how many lbs of fermentables you're using, so I tried to "reverse engineer" your recipe.

I have 12 lb total, 8.5 MO, 1.4 white wheat, 0.7 C80, 0.47 choc, 0.47 dark choc, 0.47 carapils. 

 That should theoretically yield:

1.061 OG

1.015 FG

5.97% ABV

SRM 30.82

Personally I brew 2.5g batches and have used 0.5lb choc and 0.5lb of roasted barley.

I would say maybe replace some of the carapils with some roasted barley?  Just FYI, im no expert. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-22 13:52:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If you have the ability to mill your grains at home then yea buying bulk makes sense.  Personally I don't own a mill so I just go to the LHBS when I need grains. Meh </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-22 13:51:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That sounds way off.  I typically use 1.5 quarts of water for every pound of grain. Are you sure you didn't mean 1 gallon per 4 pounds of grain? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-22 13:15:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> roasted barley comes to mind? I tend to use roasted barley and chocolate malt in my stouts/porters.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-22 13:14:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I have seen varying responses to this question, but how many tablespoons would you say 5oz of corn sugar is?  

For the record, I now have a small digital scale to weigh out my priming sugar - although I do look like one of Pablo Escobar's cronies while using it :) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-22 12:39:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I have no idea really, but I would say that its a lot finer and thus dissolves faster in wort?  Complete guess... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-22 02:29:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Shouldn't it be "inquiries" instead on "enquiries?"
Or am I missing a language difference? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-22 02:16:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Wait are you actually dipping a glass to pull a sample? Why not just siphon some into your cylinder before/as you are transferring to primary? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-21 21:19:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> this needs more love </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-21 12:45:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> yea $150 or so at least imo. K7ss has a lot of equity but probably not the best hand if the board bricks out.  We have no problem taking it down here but if we get it in that's not bad either.  Bad would be if QQ guy flats and turn is a 10h or some shit. 

The J9 dude who spazzed actually saved the QQ guy some money. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-21 12:41:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> fair enough, that's true.  I accept my downvotes. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-21 12:40:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Ok, it was like $3 per oz I want to say, when other strains were anywhere from 2 to 2.50, so it wasn't really a price burden to me... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-21 03:24:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You can't play every hand "being scared of a set."

That's a sign that poker is not for you. His sizing on the flop is small imo but it's perfectly fine to raise w a pair and second nfd. You fold out some hands better than yours and if you get called you still have good equity.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-21 03:07:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Um there's no 4-bet to 82... there's a bet, a call, and a raise (2-bet) to 82. 

QQ open should be to at least $18 imo. 

The squeeze to $192 is flat out terrible. K7 guy is never folding there given size of the pot and J9 is almost NEVER good in that spot. In fact, he got it in against the very bottom of the guys range and still is an underdog to scoop the pot. He literally beats nothing but pure air.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-21 01:43:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Are you asking if you should be folding aces full? If that's the case you're probably playing too big for your comfort level.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-21 01:39:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Lmao this clip is amazing. The whole hand is played so poorly. Guy opens to 12  from EP after a $5 straddle w QQ (lol), leads $27 and gets called and raised to $82 (lol sizing), he flats the $82 w another player behind (lol), then last chip in decides to raise to $192 (LOL), then snap ship for $1k+ (mini lol), then a call w top pair no kick and a gutter (lol), THENNNN THE EXPLOSION AT THE END. EPIC LOLZ </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-20 20:17:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I know I have seen this done on this subreddit... Let me look around for a minute, but yea I think it was a raspberry pints type model </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-20 18:10:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Pretty gross spot.  Totally avoidable by checking river I suppose?  I don't know how much value you get from worse hands here </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-20 16:34:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> cool, thanks for the advice.  I'm still learning every day and trying to make a tasty juicebomb eventually! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-20 16:21:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Would something like this work?  5g of water in a about 75 minutes it looks like.  That's all I need for a batch anyway so I suppose I can just get it running an hour or so before brewing and add my additives to get desired chem?
https://www.amazon.com/Portable-Reverse-Osmosis-Filtration-POQ-4B-50/dp/B00GJCE2X4/ref=sr_1_5?ie=UTF8 qid=1490022975 sr=8-5 keywords=reverse+osmosis+portable </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-20 16:15:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Its 2.5g and about 26-27% of the grain bill... I don't think that's outside the realm of reasonability?  My buddy who is commercially brewing NEIPA says hes going 25% or so on his oats.  Ill give the other yeast a shot next time, thanks for the tip!

And whats wrong w mosaic for bittering?  I have found that to be widely acceptable as well... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-20 13:40:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What's a ballpark $ on something like that?? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Critique my first AG NEIPA recipe please! </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-20 13:04:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This is probably about my 5th batch, BIAB - Details below.

Target OG: 1.074

Target FG: 1.018

ABV: 7.32%

IBU: 102.06

SRM: 4.61

Fermentables:

2# Flaked oats

3.54 # of pale 2-row (.04 was just from a heavy hand)

1.5# of carapils

0.5# of corn sugar (used to boost ABV as I was limited on kettle size for my mash.  I really didn't want to do this, but oh well?)

Mashed at 153F for 45 mins

Boil Size was about 3.25g

0.75oz of mosaic at 60

Whirlpool of 0.25oz mosaic and 1oz citra for 20 mins

5 day dry hop of: 1oz Amarillo, 1oz citra

3 day dry hop of: 1oz mosaic, 1 oz Amarillo

OG reading came to about 1.072, so I'm fairly happy with that.  The color during the mash was awesome, after the boil it looked more grey than anything which was a little disheartening but RDWHAHB right...?

Its fermenting healthily with 1056 right now at about 65F in my basement. 

Batch size somewhere in the 2.5g region




EDIT: Also, I have not messed with creating water profiles yet.  I am literally using bottled water from the grocery.
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-20 12:40:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Cool article.  I just brewed a 2.5g batch w 1056, guess ill have to give 1318 a try next time. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-19 22:22:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This. Although if I'm reading it right V1 is checking the nuts but NOT last to act on the river. 

Perfectly fine, although sketchy w the AA.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-17 01:16:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Gunna say spew. Depends really if he looks people up light.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-17 00:16:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If you make $12000 a year there's probably bigger problems with your life than online poker.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-17 00:14:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Seems reasonable to me. Flatting w intention of letting him bluff the rest seems fine too. I guess 99 is in their range too, but prob AQ and some bluffs.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-16 23:20:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> To be fair, lex is restealing suuuuper wide here. It's standard to shove w like a suited 1 gapper imo  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
