<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject7901</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-10 00:04:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Q: Why?   
A: To throttle an independent investigation.

Trump's message to independent investigators: One false move and you're dead. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> White House fires FBI Director James Comey </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-09 23:59:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-09 23:56:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Anything is an excuse to throttle an independent investigation.

Trump's message to independent investigators: One false move and you're dead.

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> President Trump dismisses FBI Director Comey </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-09 23:48:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-09 23:35:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Because, if you hate apples anyway, one bad one ruins the barrel. Or, as DT would say: get 'em outta here. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-09 16:01:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Impeachment won't happen until Congress flips in 2018.  The movement to impeach, however, must start now.  It should be the centerpiece of movement to restore a decent respect for human rights everywhere.
#ImpeachPenceFirst should be the slogan.  What did Pence know and when did he know it?  Mister Clean has no credibility.  Flynn is not the only liar funded by the Oligarch International.  Investigative reporting will be the key to making the case against Pence.
Then impeach Trump.  Using the office of President for personal enrichment is reason enough.
Then select a Majority Leader in the House who Americans would trust as President.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The great British Brexit robbery: how our democracy was hijacked </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-08 15:45:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> In the health care debate over pre-existing conditions, who's lying? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-07 16:52:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> In a Beijing ballroom, Kushner family pushes $500,000 investor visa to wealthy Chinese </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-07 03:37:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-30 17:56:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Obama's comfort level with Wall Street is hard to shake.  You can't manufacture revulsion at the rot that's running our world into the ground.  Obama, like Hillary, just thinks that Wall Street people are intelligent, civil, and, given that they have the power and always will, the best strategy is to convince them that it is in their interest to leave some gleanings in the field to sustain the unfortunate -- rather than scooping up everything.  What they feel is: Wall Street is family, even if they're a bit too greedy. Let's talk.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Is $60 million really not enough for the Obamas? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-30 17:50:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-30 16:30:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's not enough to be against Trump.  You must be for something.  And you must be able to explain why it would really work. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Raising the minimum wage to $15 by 2024 would lift wages for 41 million American workers </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-30 16:27:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-25 15:52:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  Increased competition from cheap natural gas is responsible for 49 percent of the decline in domestic US coal
consumption. Lower-than-expected demand is responsible for 26 percent, and the growth in renewable energy
is responsible for 18 percent. Environmental regulations have played a role in the switch from coal to natural gas and renewables in US electricity supply by accelerating coal plant retirements, but were a significantly smaller factor than recent natural gas and renewable energy cost reductions....

President Trumps efforts to roll back environmental regulations will not materially
improve economic conditions in Americas coal communities. As such, the paper concludes with recommendations
for steps that the federal government can take to safeguard the pension and health security of current and retired
miners and dependents and support economic diversification. Attracting new sources of economic activity and job creation will not be easy, and even at its most successful will not return coal country to peak levels of past prosperity. But responsible policymakers should be honest about whats going on in the US coal sectorincluding the causes of coals decline and unlikeliness of its resurgencerather than offer false hope that the glory days can be revived. And then support those in Americas coal communities working hard to build a new economic future. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Can Coal Make a Comeback? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-25 15:51:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-25 15:49:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  Increased competition from cheap natural gas is responsible for 49 percent of the decline in domestic US coal
consumption. Lower-than-expected demand is responsible for 26 percent, and the growth in renewable energy
is responsible for 18 percent. Environmental regulations have played a role in the switch from coal to natural gas and renewables in US electricity supply by accelerating coal plant retirements, but were a significantly smaller factor than recent natural gas and renewable energy cost reductions....

President Trumps efforts to roll back environmental regulations will not materially
improve economic conditions in Americas coal communities. As such, the paper concludes with recommendations
for steps that the federal government can take to safeguard the pension and health security of current and retired
miners and dependents and support economic diversification. Attracting new sources of economic activity and job creation will not be easy, and even at its most successful will not return coal country to peak levels of past prosperity. But responsible policymakers should be honest about whats going on in the US coal sectorincluding the causes of coals decline and unlikeliness of its resurgencerather than offer false hope that the glory days can be revived. And then support those in Americas coal communities working hard to build a new economic future.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Can Coal Make a Comeback? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-25 15:43:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The Greatest Obstacle to Anti-Muslim Fearmongering and Bigotry: Reality </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-24 16:20:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Climate Change Reroutes a Yukon River in a Geological Instant </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-24 05:23:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Chart reveals how much the Earth has warmed since 1880 </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-23 15:51:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Could Be the Thyroid; Could Be Ennui. Either Way, the Drug Isnt Helping. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-23 04:52:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> March for Science demonstrators make colorful protest </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-23 03:13:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-22 16:09:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The goal of these terror attacks is to make integration of Muslims into predominantly non-Muslim societies impossible.  Shutting down open societies to protect against this kind of attack would kill freedom and the rule of law, without guaranteeing security.  The danger is that demonizing whole sections of the population appears to be a "strong" response, and that feels better than living with constant uncertainty, and the need to reach people who we don't know, don't understand, and whose presence seems to make our life more complicated.  But that's what free society demands. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> France: Voting in times of terror </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-22 15:53:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-22 02:32:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> When vengeance is all that's left of justice, we know that we have a system that is stuck in the original crime.  Nothing is learned.  Forgiveness can never be earned.  Bitterness keeps the wound unhealed.  See [Judith Clarks Radical Transformation
](http://www.nytimes.com/2012/01/15/magazine/judith-clarks-radical-transformation.html)

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Judith Clark, Getaway Driver in Deadly Brinks Heist, Is Denied Parole </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-22 02:25:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Could Leftist Jean-Luc Mlenchon Win the French Presidency? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-22 02:11:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The Free Tuition Trap: Cuomo's Scholarship Plan Is Full of Risky Loopholes </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-21 22:35:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-21 19:54:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Medical debts are the greatest cause of bankruptcies in the United States. Injuries are often unpredictable, expensive to treat, and disproportionally affect uninsured patients...

Our primary outcome measure was catastrophic health expenditure risk, defined as any charges =40% of annual postsubsistence income...

Over 7 in 10 uninsured patients admitted for trauma are at risk of catastrophic health expenditures.

Only a system providing universal coverage -- Medicare for All -- would cure Catastrophic Health Expenditure.  Or we can entirely avoid acknowledging the risk, and say: "It Can't Happen to Me" 

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Cured into Destitution: Catastrophic Health Expenditure Risk Among Uninsured Trauma Patients in the United States </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-21 19:36:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Jared Kushner: Top White House Adviser and NYC Rat Lord </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-21 16:20:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> New York predicts foreign tourism losses of $120M under Trump </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-21 16:11:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Do African Famines Presage Global Climate-Change Catastrophe? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-21 03:58:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Jeff Sessions Marvels At How A Judge On An Island In The Pacific Could Stall Travel Ban | Hawaiis Sen. Mazie Hirono calls the attorney generals remarks dog whistle politics. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-21 01:25:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-20 04:13:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Climate change is a major disruptor that has revved up global chaos, especially in the Middle East and East Africa. Unless we stop hiding from this reality, it will inexorably overwhelm us.  Americans and the other developed nations who benefited from fossil-fuel driven development must respond to this challenge.

Syrian refugees are the lead wave of the coming tide of climate refugees.  Climate change and the loss of habitability in the Middle East is a primary cause for states to fail, descending into conflict, and an independent force pushing refugees to flee the region.

Climate change will, in this century, create hundreds of millions of refugees who will be dispossessed both directly and covertly. 

A global response will require retooling the developed world.  It is this century's alternative to war economy, except it doesn't waste resources -- it saves them.

How can this necessary direction become politically feasible?  That will require a recognition of the bankruptcy of old metrics of success and systems of incentives. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> How a Warming Planet Drives Human Migration </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-20 04:03:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Our Climate Future Is Actually Our Climate Present </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-20 03:33:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Trumps About-Face on the Paris Climate Accord </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-20 03:05:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> A Members Only Public Space in Manhattan? Join the Club </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-20 02:58:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The Massacre at Rashidin: Over 100 Civilians Die in Proxy War Infighting </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-19 17:00:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Leftist Mlenchons team target Frances deprived and forgotten North </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-19 16:44:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Theres No Strategy Behind Trumps Wars -- Only Brute Force </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-19 16:00:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Trump protests planned in New York City </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-18 03:53:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Working More For Less: Dangers of the Gig Economy </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-18 02:52:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Its not just the far-right gaining traction in France: Against all odds, a communist soars in election polls </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-17 05:44:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Thousands turn out at rallies demanding Trump release tax returns </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-17 05:24:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Still More Tightening In French Polls </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-17 01:15:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-16 16:17:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Mr. Asplund, the research director for the MAC Solar Index, argues that even if the Trump administrations energy policies pose a problem, solar power investments can still prosper. The solar industry is a global industry, he said. U.S. installations are less than one-quarter of global. Trump is a negative for solar, but Trump by himself isnt going to kill the solar business.

Fossilized thinking may slow renewable growth, but it can't stop it.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Investing in Solar and Wind in a Coal and Oil Moment </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-16 15:59:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> My Bookshelf, Myself: Leaders in different fields share the 10 books theyd take with them if they were marooned on a desert island. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-16 03:47:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Is 100% renewable energy realistic? Heres what we know. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-16 01:00:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-15 22:56:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Pruitt-Bannon are gung-ho for full-fledged pariah status for the USA, as opposed to Tillerson who represents continuity and hypocrisy -- keep sitting at the table in order to slow-walk limits on fossil fuels.
None of these people feel the heat, and won't, until we hold their feet to the fire. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Scott Pruitt calls for an exit from the Paris accord, sharpening the Trump White Houses climate rift </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-15 22:45:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Dial Congress Chrome Extension Makes Protesting Trump Even Easier </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-15 03:05:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Manhattan Congressman Calls Donald Trump a Fascist </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-15 00:51:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Self-Storage Offers Space for Stuff. But It Gobbles Up Space. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-14 05:47:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Self-Storage Offers Space for Stuff. But It Gobbles Up Space. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-14 05:42:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-14 05:10:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Trumps proposing what Putin is already doing:  farm out infrastructure revenues to Oligarchs.  What could possibly go wrong? 
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> In St Petersburg, long-distance truck drivers are holding out for victory </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-14 04:51:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-14 04:33:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Nothing will be learned from disasters like this one. Bomb = Strong.  It doesn't matter who gets killed.  Trump says he lets the military decide what to do.  But, that creates a bias in favor of slaughter. if you're a commander in the field, holding back until you know what you're doing will not be rewarded, because the only measure that counts is to show Strength.  Caution will not be rewarded by the higher-ups.  And our local allies also lose control of their own cause.  They face the same pressure to identify targets.  The same thing happened in Vietnam, both before and after "Vietnamization" of the war.  We won all the body count metrics in Vietnam, and lost the war.  The real lesson to be learned from this in that counting on American power to win your battle is a big mistake.  You lose credibility as defenders of your own people, and you'll never be able to achieve legitimacy, because you're seen as a puppet working for foreign killers. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Errant US Strike Kills at Least 18 Syrian Coalition Fighters </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-14 04:00:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-13 21:55:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Trump is boasting about a $1 trillion, job-creating infrastructure plan, which he says Democrats will have to support. Capitol Hill Republicans say it could be financed through a tax on overseas profits that U.S. companies have stashed abroad to avoid the 35-percent federal corporate tax rate.

The total is about $2.5 trillion, so a 10 percent tax, which is higher than Republicans advocate, would raise $250 billion, still just a fraction of what Trump wants to spend on roads, bridges and airports. Republican plans to finance the rest privately, through tax credits and other incentives, is a losing proposition for most infrastructure experts, who say it wont produce much, and for Democrats who dont like the politics. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Hunt: Tax reform will be tough for Republicans </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-13 21:54:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> How to Stand Up to Trump and Win </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-13 20:57:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Infrastructure plan: Tax cuts, streamlined rules </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-13 17:36:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What Is It Worth? The State of the Art in Valuing Distributed Energy Resources </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-13 03:35:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The Climate Solutions Caucus: The birth of a bipartisan dialogue </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-13 02:56:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-13 00:48:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Mr. Pruitt has a long history of championing legal efforts to undermine major environmental rules. As Oklahomas attorney general, he sued the E.P.A. 14 times in efforts to undo regulations. He believes in stripping power away from the federal government and returning it to states.

But during his Senate confirmation hearing, he told senators that despite that, he was likely to draw the line at trying to overturn the endangerment finding.

It is there, and it needs to be enforced and respected, Mr. Pruitt said. There is nothing that I know that would cause it to be reviewed.

At the end of the tunnel-vision of climate change denial, is the light of The Endangerment Finding -- a court-confirmed scientifically-based finding asserting the reality of climate change, and the necessity to address its impact, under the Clean Air Act.
All we need is acknowledgement that there is a knowable, real world.  Then acts have consequences, and the actors bear responsibility.  Humpty Dumpty is not safe behind his wall of denial.  There is no body of material evidence to support climate-denial fantasy. Like any bad dream, we see there's no there there. Out-of-control, the dream crashes, and we wake up.  Alternative Reality can't be put back together again.  But, once we see that we're stuck with climate change, and many other realities, we can begin to pick up the pieces.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Scott Pruitt Faces Anger From Right Over E.P.A. Finding He Won't Fight </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-13 00:26:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Assessing the Impact of Climate Risks on the Financial System - FloodList </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-12 16:26:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Putin wants UN chemical weapons watchdog to investigate Syrian attack </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-12 05:26:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Trump Cuts Leave Bridge and Rail Projects Hanging </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-12 01:56:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-12 01:50:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Commuters have recently received a preview of how traveling between the two states could become a nightmare if the current tunnel is closed for emergency repairs. Last month, an Amtrak train derailed near the tunnel, closing half of Pennsylvania Stations tracks and leading to widespread train cancellations and delays. Then on Monday, a New Jersey Transit train derailed in the same area, setting off another round of delays.

Without this project and this tunnel, that becomes the day-to-day existence for commuters, and I dont think anybody wants that to happen, said Carlo A. Scissura, the president of the New York Building Congress, a group that represents the citys construction industry.

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Trump Budget Leaves New York-Area Transit Projects Up in the Air </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-12 01:50:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> EPA staffer leaves with a bang, blasting agency policies under Trump </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-11 21:23:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> EPA staffer leaves with a bang, blasting agency policies under Trump </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-11 21:21:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Trump revolution now looks like fake news, to the relief of some </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-11 15:36:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Massive protest in Hungary against bill that could oust Soros university </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-10 04:35:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Serbia sees sixth day of anti-corruption protests </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-09 15:36:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Tillerson: Defeating ISIS is 'first priority' in Syria </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-09 06:24:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-09 05:19:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> National Fuel's plan to construct the Northern Access Pipeline has been rejected by the New York State Department of Environmental Conservation.

The DEC announced Saturday afternoon that, following a review, the agency has denied water quality certificates needed for the project which would have resulted in the construction of a 97-mile pipeline capable of carrying natural gas from Pennsylvania through Western New York. 

The decision follows three public hearings in which the DEC fielded 5,700 comments. The agency said it based its decision on the project's "failure to avoid adverse impacts to wetlands, streams, and fish and other wildlife habitat."
...

Late last month, area protesters took their fight to Albany, assembling in front of DEC headquarters to call for an end to the controversial $455 million project. Protesters also took their message to the state Capital building, where they attempted to inform onlookers about the potential dangers the pipeline could pose to those living near it. They also delivered copies of a letter that was signed by more than 140 organizations, businesses and faith communities that want to see the DEC and Gov. Andrew Cuomo deny the permits the project needs to break ground. 

Denial of permits by the DEC effectively kills the project, however similar decisions made by the agency have been challenged in court in the past.

One recent example is the Constitution Pipeline, which was designed to carry Marcellus Shale gas produced in Northeast Pennsylvania to Schoharie, N.Y. The project partners filed a lawsuit after the DEC denied a joint application for water quality certification permits. A federal court recently dismissed the partners' case challenging the state's permitting requirements.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> DEC denies Northern Access Pipeline permits </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-09 05:15:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-08 03:51:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> In the War Powers Resolution, Congress put a crucial tool in the hands of future members of Congress... : the ability of a single member of Congress to introduce a "privileged resolution" -- one that can't be buried in committee, but can be forced by its sponsor to the floor for a vote -- to withdraw US forces from a conflict that hadn't been authorized by Congress.

You can urge your representatives to invoke the War Powers Resolution to withdraw US forces from unauthorized conflict in Syria by [signing the petition at MoveOn](http://petitions.moveon.org/sign/congress-oppose-illegal?r_by=1135580). </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> In Attacking Syria, Trump Breached the War Powers Resolution </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-08 03:51:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-08 02:43:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> In the War Powers Resolution, Congress put a crucial tool in the hands of future members of Congress... : the ability of a single member of Congress to introduce a "privileged resolution" -- one that can't be buried in committee, but can be forced by its sponsor to the floor for a vote -- to withdraw US forces from a conflict that hadn't been authorized by Congress.

You can urge your representatives to invoke the War Powers Resolution to withdraw US forces from unauthorized conflict in Syria by [signing the petition at MoveOn](http://petitions.moveon.org/sign/congress-oppose-illegal?r_by=1135580). </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> In Attacking Syria, Trump Breached the War Powers Resolution </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-08 02:39:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Comptroller Stringer Releases Analysis of Trump Tax Plan : Office of the New York City Comptroller Scott M. Stringer </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-08 00:55:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-07 22:18:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This administration has acted recklessly without care or consideration of the dire consequences of the US attack on Syria without waiting for the collection of evidence from the scene of the chemical poisoning," Gabbard said. 

"If President Assad is indeed guilty of this horrible chemical attack on innocent civilians, I will be the first to call for his prosecution and execution by the International Criminal Court." she said. 

"However, because of our attack on Syria, this investigation may now not even be possible. And without such evidence, a successful prosecution will be much harder," </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Tulsi Gabbard opposes US air strikes on Syria </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-07 22:15:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Rising Waters Threaten Chinas Rising Cities </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-07 21:31:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-07 21:27:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Well that high sure wore off fast. Time to re-insert American power until we're tired of winning. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Syrian jets take off from air base US missiles struck </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-07 21:27:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-07 21:25:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Well that high sure wore off fast. Time to re-insert American power until we're tired of winning. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Syrian jets take off from air base US missiles struck </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-07 21:23:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Trump intervenes in the Great Mideast Civil War in Syria </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-07 16:24:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Trump launches Syria flip flops </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-07 16:07:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-07 04:43:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> No investigation.  No legal basis.  Assad remains in power.  And the war goes on.  And on.
But it feels so good to DO SOMETHING (while feelings are still hot). Donald's a decider, just like W.
His poll's been sinking, but a quickie tomahawk strike restores potency, at least for one night.
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-06 23:35:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Just in case you thought you didn't understand anything about what's happening in Syria and why, here is a report filled with so much confounding intrigue that you may just want to throw up your hands. Burning down the house may be a tactic to get rid of unwanted occupants, but what you win is a burnt ruin.     </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Idlib  more than Raqqa  may be decisive Syria fault line </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-06 23:11:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-06 18:10:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Safe zones are a good idea if there is agreement by the major players to let it happen.  Nothing is safe from asymmetric warfare by terrorists like ISIS.  So is such a deal possible?  Assad's crossing-the-line chemical warfare attack was an attempt to break up any entente between Russia and the United States that could eventually leave him as a redundant player.  Russia would be happy enough with its Mediterranean presence in western Syria, and a regional regime run by a Russian-oriented Syrian military establishment.  For that to work,    a centralized Syria must be replaced by Bosnian style regions loosely connected to a national state.  The attack by Assad is an attempt to prevent that kind of resolution from evolving.  Closing down peaceful options has been Assad's game since Day One.    </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> House Republicans are finally making a big admission: They like Obamacare! </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-06 15:31:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> CAIR Calls on Trump to Fulfill Syria Safe Zones Promise After Deadly Gas Attack on Civilians </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-06 04:28:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Mortality and morbidity in the 21st century </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-05 03:59:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-04 23:14:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> On Monday Trump signed a CRA resolution repealing broadband privacy protections. He has also signed resolutions killing rules meant to expand background checks for mentally ill gun purchasers, change public school assessments, and reduce coal waste runoff into streams.

Last Friday was the deadline for introducing any new CRA resolutions on regulations enacted by Obama's administration. Now Republicans must complete voting on resolutions already in the legislative pipeline by mid-May.

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Window closing for Republican stealth assault on U.S. regulations </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-04 23:12:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Britain allocates one billion pounds for Syrian refugees, host countries </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-04 22:56:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-04 15:56:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Gorsuch should be opposed based on his legal philosophy.  A real, old-fashioned filibuster would give Democrats (and Bernie Sanders) the opportunity to speak as long as they had something to say about what  it will mean for Americans to have enforcement of our laws protecting workers and the environment overturned by a Supreme Court ruled by corporate-loving justices like Gorsuch.  When they've made their case to the American people, it will be time to take a vote and put Senators on record so that Americans know which side each one of them is on. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Neil Gorsuch on the issues </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-04 14:31:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-04 04:46:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Judy Clarks story makes us ask what is the purpose of our system of justice.  Clearly Judy has gone through a personal transformation.  If we seek a more caring world, we would clearly benefit from her presence in it as a free woman  not a prisoner.  We will soon know if revenge trumps justice, when the Parole Board rules on her case. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Studying Torah With Judy Clark </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-04 04:46:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-04 02:28:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The Trump administration and the UAE appear to share a similar preoccupation with Iran. Current and former officials said that Trump advisers were focused throughout the transition period on exploring ways to get Moscow to break ranks with Tehran.

...

Michael McFaul, former U.S. ambassador to Russia, said he also had discussions with people close to the Trump administration about the prospects of drawing Russia away from Iran. When I would hear this, I would think, Yeah thats great for you guys, but why would Putin ever do that?  McFaul said. There is no interest in Russia ever doing that. They have a long relationship with Iran. Theyre allied with Iran in fighting in Syria. They sell weapons to Iran. Iran is an important strategic partner for Russia in the Middle East.

It's easy to make a deal when you don't understand what's involved.  Russia has as much chance getting Iranian influence out of Syria as the United States has of getting Iranian influence out of Iraq.  The Saudis and Emirates can't win hearts and minds.  Their answer to Mideast turmoil has been to fund Al Qaeda and Isis against the Shia. Trump is well on his way to becoming a useful idiot fighting for the dead end goals of the Saudis and the UAE. Courting Russia is just part of this misguided mission. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-04 01:36:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The Trump administration and the UAE appear to share a similar preoccupation with Iran. Current and former officials said that Trump advisers were focused throughout the transition period on exploring ways to get Moscow to break ranks with Tehran.

...

Michael McFaul, former U.S. ambassador to Russia, said he also had discussions with people close to the Trump administration about the prospects of drawing Russia away from Iran. When I would hear this, I would think, Yeah thats great for you guys, but why would Putin ever do that?  McFaul said. There is no interest in Russia ever doing that. They have a long relationship with Iran. Theyre allied with Iran in fighting in Syria. They sell weapons to Iran. Iran is an important strategic partner for Russia in the Middle East.

It's easy to make a deal when you don't understand what's involved.  Russia has as much chance getting Iranian influence out of Syria as the United States has of getting Iranian influence out of Iraq.  The Saudis and Emirates can't win hearts and minds.  Their answer to Mideast turmoil has been to fund Al Qaeda and Isis against the Shia. Trump is well on his way to becoming a useful idiot fighting for the dead end goals of the Saudis and the UAE. Courting Russia is just part of this misguided mission. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Blackwater founder held secret Seychelles meeting to establish Trump-Putin back channel </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-04 01:03:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Ecuador election: Lenin Moreno headed for victory amid opposition fraud claims | World news </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-03 14:42:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-03 04:52:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It was known that Dunnigan, who succeeded Amos J. Hochstein at the US Department of State, expressed her wish to represent the US administration at the signing of the contracts between Cyprus and ExxonMobil on April 5 for the third licensing round in Cyprus` exclusive economic zone.

... ask what you can do for ExxonMobil </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Visit by US energy official a sign of Washington's support, spokesman says - Cyprus Mail </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-03 04:51:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-03 00:11:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It was known that Dunnigan, who succeeded Amos J. Hochstein at the US Department of State, expressed her wish to represent the US administration at the signing of the contracts between Cyprus and ExxonMobil on April 5 for the third licensing round in Cyprus` exclusive economic zone.

... ask what you can do for ExxonMobil </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Visit by US energy official a sign of Washington's support, spokesman says </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-03 00:10:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> 86 percent of Trump counties make less in a year than 27 Trump staffers are worth </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-02 18:33:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Analysis | A judge rules Trump may have incited violence  and Trump again has his own mouth to blame </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-02 16:58:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-02 13:59:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This is another example of a promising new development in solar and energy storage.  The questions are: which will become mature commercial technologies, and when?  Assuming that some become competitive, what does that do to the long-term return on investment in fossil fuel exploration, production, transportation, and use?  For example, can pipelines return their cost of investment over their economic lifespan?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Bio-inspired energy storage: A new light for solar power </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-02 13:53:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-01 23:19:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Comparing the Candidates on Twitter in Michigan. Table 1 reveals that 138,686 tweets were posted in Michigan about politics and the election. This table shows that the overall volume of tweets using pro-Trump hashtags (56.7 percent), was much greater than the volume of tweets containing only hashtags associated with the Clinton campaign (20.3 percent). The overall volume of tweets using neutral election-related hashtags (13.4 percent) was also significantly lower compared with those using pro- Trump hashtags.
...

In previous memos we attempted to catalogue the users with high levels of automation behind their accounts, but for this state-specific sub- sample no accounts generated more than our usual threshold for identifying automation. A close look revealed that only 2% of the platforms used to send Twitter traffic were known sources of botsthe rest were platforms that either supported human users or offered very human-like levels of automation.

It looks like Trump supporters were just more engaged, by a wide margin, in Michigan.  The posting of dubious content news about Hillary appears to be more demand-driven (i.e., hunger for ammunition to attack her) than due to force-feeding by Fake News pushers.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Junk News and Bots during the U.S. Election: What Were Michigan Voters Sharing Over Twitter? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-01 23:02:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-01 21:53:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thank you.  This is very interesting.  I'll check it out further.  The danger with failing states is that there is a nostalgia for lost glory.  It is a reactionary utopian vision. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-01 16:15:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> During the Cold War there were some socialists who called themselves [Third Camp](https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Third_camp) who made clear that both sides were enemies of democracy.  The journal [New Politics](https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/New_Politics_(magazine) continues to represent this point of view.  Putin's Russia is not our friend (even if RT gives good people with serious critiques of neoliberalism air time). Neither are establishment Democrats, even if they decry Putin's authoritarianism.  And we certainly can't rely on the neoliberal and neoconservative establishments to defend civil liberties, due process, and economic justice against Trump. Yes, each of the repulsive hierarchies who rule the world would like to ally themselves with our critique of their opponents.  But we should not do them the courtesy of pulling our punches, and acting as if any of them is a good-faith defender of our rights and aspirations. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> High Tech Layoffs In The Bay Area </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-01 03:00:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> In our Google era, indexers are the unsung heroes of the publishing world </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-30 20:50:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Did President Trump Bestow $100 Million Upon Flint, Michigan? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-30 17:41:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Censorship, Not the Painting, Must Go: On Dana Schutz's Image of Emmett Till </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-30 16:26:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> U.S. War Footprint Grows in Middle East, With No Endgame in Sight </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-30 16:02:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Poll shows Americans trust 3 media outlets more than Trump </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-30 15:31:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> U.S. War Footprint Grows in Middle East, With No Endgame in Sight </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-30 03:44:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-30 02:46:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> opioids are the opiate of the people </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Jewish Defense League activists beat Palestinian-American at AIPAC </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-30 02:24:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-30 01:05:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> In 2001-2002, there were similar rates of heroin use between whites and non-whites, but by 2013 there was a significant race gap, according to the study.

Now that heroin addiction is predominantly a white problem, it may gain respectability as an illness, and at last has a chance of getting some support for treatment rather than imprisonment. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Heroin use, addiction up sharply among U.S. whites: study </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-30 00:57:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The battle for Raqqa explained </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-30 00:50:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> New York Has a Great Subway, if Youre Not in a Wheelchair </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-30 00:22:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Immigration a Demographic Lifeline in Midwestern Metros </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-30 00:20:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-29 21:51:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  The theme of this years Peoples Summit is moving beyond the resistance and the protests.

Going beyond "resistance" must mean making contact with those people who supported Trump who are now discovering that their trust was misplaced.  What is true is that no one was listening while life has gotten harder and harder for working people.  If Clinton had been elected there would have been no compelling need to face this difficult reality.  Now we've plunged into a crisis, and old-style governance can't get us back out. America can't live off the credit card provided by the Almighty Dollar.  It doesn't have the power to force its will. Trump's bluff and bluster won't change that.  We need to live within our means, and can't afford to waste resources.  Fighting against each other -- white, black, immigrant -- is a bad gamble.  It's a game in which only the casino owners win. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Sanders to headline progressive 'People's Summit' </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-29 21:32:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The Hidden Risks of Trump's EPA Cuts: Birth Defects, Bad Air </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-29 04:21:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Analysis of Trump Administration Proposals for FY2018 Budget for the Environmental Protection Agency </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-29 04:18:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Manafort's NYC real estate moves raise money-laundering suspicion </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-28 23:47:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-28 03:32:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> More Trumped up bluff and bluster.  Sessions claims that "sanctuary cities" will lose funding from the Dept. of Justice if they refuse to hand over alien felons for deportation.  This is a non-issue.  Dangerous felons should, of course, not walk the streets to commit more crimes -- whether they are aliens or citizens.  From the perspective of protecting Americans from criminals, the simple answer is to put convicted criminals into prison.  If they are not citizens, they are subject to deportation after they have served their sentence.  But we are actually safer if they are in the U.S. prison system rather than if they are deported right away and set free in their home countries.  In fact, it's an incentive for criminals to claim that they are not citizens -- get deported and walk free -- a Get Out of Jail Free card.  And then, perhaps, come back.    </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Was financial threat to sanctuary cities real or just bluster? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-28 03:11:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What America Could Be Losing Out On Because Of The Proposed Trump Budget Cuts </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-27 23:02:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-27 03:57:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Edward Snowden, whos currently living under asylum in Russia, condemned the arrests: Sanctioned or unsanctioned, meeting peaceful protesters with force is clear injustice. He also illuminates the arrest of journalist Alec Luhn (of The Guardian), who was taken into custody after he took a photo of protesters being arrested (while identifying himself as a journalist) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Russian Police Arrest Hundreds Of Anti-Corruption Protesters During Rallies Against Putins Government </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-27 03:56:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The implosion of Venezuela's rentier state </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-27 03:40:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Working class white Americans are now dying in middle age at faster rates than minority groups </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-27 03:28:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The Dows tumultuous 120-year history, in one chart </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-27 02:30:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Protesters clash at violent pro-Trump rally in California </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-26 06:56:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-26 04:46:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Once Trump-Price put their hands on it, they own it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Trump's Choice on Obamacare: Sabotage or Co-opt? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-26 04:45:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-25 19:24:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> As a Jew, I believe that Israel's creation was the result of a tragic failure of the international community to openly receive the victims of Naziism.  There were crimes committed by Jews for the sake of survival.  I understand why they happened.  I do not believe that peace is possible until there is acknowledgement, the desire to live with each other because we must, and restitution of as much as can be repaired as possible.  The alternative is eternal unwinnable war. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-25 17:18:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> My grandmother heard what she wanted from a leader who promised simple answers to complicated questions. She chose not to hear and see the monstrous sum those answers added up to. And she lived the rest of her life with the knowledge of her indefensible complicity.

The attractive vision offered by demagogues like Hitler is never about the hard work of solving real problems with other people.  It is about treating other people as excludable enemies.  Demagogues offer fear, and nostalgia for a glorious past, threatened by malevolent others. The cherished identity is mythic  pure and simple, powerful, without a doubt.Its unity requires enemies. Its paranoia engenders its belligerence. It needs conflict and finds war, at home and abroad.  Standing up against this is dangerous.  It means getting cast as aiding the enemy.  But people do have the power to resist.  Normal people in the countries occupied by Germany joined the Resistance  risking (and often losing) their lives.  What gives people the courage to resist is as important to understand as understanding why people become accomplices to barbarism.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> I Loved My Grandmother. But She Was a Nazi. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-25 17:17:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> California Upholds Auto Emissions Standards, Setting Up Face-Off With Trump </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-25 15:49:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> California Upholds Auto Emissions Standards, Setting Up Face-Off With Trump </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-25 15:49:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-24 21:16:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It turns out the Republican Party is a big tent, without poles or guy lines.  When it comes to doing something, there's no there there. The collapsed tent is now flapping in the wind, with its resident members tangled together in the ruins.  Paul Ryan remains optimistic, which means he has learned nothing.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-24 14:58:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Finally the Fed has the signal it's been waiting for to raise interest rates: a strong enough job market to give workers some bargaining power.  This must be stopped.  That's because in a system based solely on private profit, and in which there has been little real expansion of demand, the only way to keep profits up is to continuously depress wages. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The State of American Wages 2016: Lower unemployment finally helps working people make up some lost ground on wages </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-24 14:51:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Blame game: Trump casts immigrants as dangerous criminals, but the evidence shows otherwise </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-24 14:46:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The Forces Driving Middle-Aged White People's 'Deaths Of Despair' </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-23 18:17:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Why Does Trump Want to Stop Investigating Chemical Accidents? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-23 16:12:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Republican health bill would widen Americas big wealth gap </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-23 09:31:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-23 04:34:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> *Putin for Trump* is not listed among the Super PACs registered with the [FEC](http://www.fec.gov/pages/brochures/indexp.shtml).
But, if the Russian State, or its agents, registered as a Super PAC, then its communications coordinated with the Trump campaign would be counted as a violation of federal election law:
 When financing communications in connection with federal elections, it is important to understand that the rules differ significantly depending on whether the communication is coordinated with a candidate or party committee or is produced and distributed independently. In general, amounts spent for coordinated communications are limited, but independent expenditures are unlimited. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-23 01:57:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Strangely, *Putin for Trump* is not listed among the Super PACs registered with the [FEC](http://www.fec.gov/pages/brochures/indexp.shtml).
But, perhaps this was on purpose, so that communications coordinated with the Trump campaign would not be counted as a violation of federal election law:
 When financing communications in connection with federal elections, it is important to understand that the rules differ significantly depending on whether the communication is coordinated with a candidate or party committee or is produced and distributed independently. In general, amounts spent for coordinated communications are limited, but independent expenditures are unlimited. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> US Officials: Info suggests Trump associates may have coordinated with Russians </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-23 01:38:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Pulitzer Prize winner on her Broadway play about Trumps America: Being poor is one of the hardest jobs in the world </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-22 20:07:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Paul Manafort Ukrainian Gas Pipelines </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-22 19:34:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-22 19:21:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Mr. Trump, according to one longtime adviser, is perpetually playing a soundtrack in his head consisting of advice from his father, Fred, a hard-driving real estate developer who laid the weight of the familys success on his sons shoulders. Mr. Trumps other mentor was the caustic and conniving McCarthy-era lawyer Roy Cohn, who counseled Mr. Trump never to give in or concede error. 


[The devil in Donald: How the ghost of evil Roy Cohn lives on inside Trump](http://www.nydailynews.com/opinion/arthur-browne-devil-donald-trump-article-1.2813483)

[What Roy Cohn Taught Donald Trump](http://dailycaller.com/2016/10/03/what-roy-cohn-taught-donald-trump/) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Why Letting Go, for Trump, Is No Small or Simple Task </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-22 18:58:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Prison Dispatches From the War on Terror: American Explains What Drove Him to Extremism </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-22 18:54:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Health Care Deal Might Create A $2.3 Billion Budget Problem For New York </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-22 17:08:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Republicans lied about healthcare for years, and they're about to get the punishment they deserve </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-22 16:55:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The controversial New York 'giveaway' in the GOP healthcare bill would shaft some Republican parts of New York </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-22 16:41:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> How Americans Think About Climate Change, in Six Maps </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-22 16:37:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The 7 Big Revisions Republicans Made to Their Health Care Bill, and Why They Made Them </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-22 04:34:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-22 03:47:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The party's over. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> ObamaCare Repeal Vote Failure Threatens Tax Cuts  And Stock Rally </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-22 03:44:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> We Must Filibuster Gorsuch's Federalist Society Agenda </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-22 01:57:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-22 00:45:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What happens when all you have going for you is momentum, and you hit a wall?  The Reality Principle is ugly for fantasists. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> ObamaCare Repeal Vote Failure Threatens Tax Cuts  And Stock Rally </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-22 00:42:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-22 00:34:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> EPA's rule-making process will take time to undo.  But Trump and Pruitt's malevolent destructive will is apparent.  What will come quickly is stopping rational planning for the future.  According to this article. Trump

is also expected to order White House economists to revisit an Obama-era budgeting metric known as the social cost of carbon. Economists and policy makers used the metric to place a dollar cost on the economic impact of planet-warming carbon dioxide pollution: about $36 per ton. That measure formed the Obama administrations economic justification for issuing climate change regulations that would harm some industries, such as coal mining, noting that those costs would be outweighed by the economic benefits of preventing billions of tons of planet-warming pollution.

Eliminating or lowering the social cost of carbon could provide the Trump administration the economic justification for putting forth less-stringent regulations.

The draft order would also rescind an executive order by Mr. Obama that all federal agencies take climate change into account when considering any form of environmental permitting.

$36 per ton of carbon emissions was already a low estimate of the present value of the future damage that will be caused by carbon emissions.  Deliberately blinding itself to the consequences of climate change puts an end to rational planning by the U.S. government.

The appropriate response to Trump is planning ahead. What would a sane society invest in for its survival and general well-being? Everyone agrees we need to modernize and upgrade our infrastructure. But, if don't recognize that climate change matters (both to forestall the most severe impacts, and to adapt to the climate change we cannot stop) our investments will be wasted and our needs unmet. Heed the U.S. Army Corps of Engineers: [The entire portfolio of USACE Civil Works water resources infrastructure and programs, existing and proposed, could be affected by climate change and adaptation to climate change. This affects design and operational assumptions about resource supplies, system demands or performance requirements, and operational constraints. Both droughts and floods can affect the operations of these projects. Numerous regulatory decisions made by USACE will need to be informed by climate change impacts and adaptation considerations throughout the U.S., especially in western states.](http://www.corpsclimate.us/index.cfm)  (I believe that page has not yet been flushed down the memory hole) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-22 00:32:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> EPA's rule-making process will take time to undo.  But Trump and Pruitt's malevolent destructive will is apparent.  What will come quickly is stopping rational planning for the future.  According to this article. Trump

is also expected to order White House economists to revisit an Obama-era budgeting metric known as the social cost of carbon. Economists and policy makers used the metric to place a dollar cost on the economic impact of planet-warming carbon dioxide pollution: about $36 per ton. That measure formed the Obama administrations economic justification for issuing climate change regulations that would harm some industries, such as coal mining, noting that those costs would be outweighed by the economic benefits of preventing billions of tons of planet-warming pollution.

Eliminating or lowering the social cost of carbon could provide the Trump administration the economic justification for putting forth less-stringent regulations.

The draft order would also rescind an executive order by Mr. Obama that all federal agencies take climate change into account when considering any form of environmental permitting.

$36 per ton of carbon emissions was already a low estimate of the present value of the future damage that will be caused by carbon emissions.  Deliberately blinding itself to the consequences of climate change puts an end to rational planning by the U.S. government.

The appropriate response to Trump is planning ahead. What would a sane society invest in for its survival and general well-being? Everyone agrees we need to modernize and upgrade our infrastructure. But, if don't recognize that climate change matters (both to forestall the most severe impacts, and to adapt to the climate change we cannot stop) our investments will be wasted and our needs unmet. Heed the U.S. Army Corps of Engineers: [The entire portfolio of USACE Civil Works water resources infrastructure and programs, existing and proposed, could be affected by climate change and adaptation to climate change. This affects design and operational assumptions about resource supplies, system demands or performance requirements, and operational constraints. Both droughts and floods can affect the operations of these projects. Numerous regulatory decisions made by USACE will need to be informed by climate change impacts and adaptation considerations throughout the U.S., especially in western states.](http://www.corpsclimate.us/index.cfm)  (I believe that page has not yet been flushed down the memory hole)

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Trump Lays Plans to Reverse Obama's Climate Change Legacy </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-22 00:09:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
