<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject4399</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [Homemade] Dhal   Rice with curry shrimp and casreep chicken </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-10 00:27:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [I made] Dhal   Rice with curry shrimp   casreep chicken </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-10 00:12:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-09 18:43:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Mp14 player here. Honestly , KD doesn't mean anything to me. I play for fun with silly setups , just cause I enjoiy the game. Sometimes,  people come in my lobby and laugh at my KD being a MP rank. I laugh at them, post lobby after I wreck them. Take a look at my stats. Its shitty. Below 1 KD for a MP14 player. Being master prestige only means you've invested time into the game to rank up so high. I learned to play cod when mw3 released. What I'm trying to say is, being MP doesn't necessarily mean itl reflect a positive KD. it's the player and his skills. I can pick up any gun with ANY setup at lvl1 top the leaderboard of the match. 

MP14 STATS: https://imgur.com/gallery/ktM8U </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-08 16:29:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Repost </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-08 02:43:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Bro, when I do it solo, I loose connection to host. Myself. I have EXCELLENT connection.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-08 01:56:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Well that sucks. Because it's always losing connection to host and kicking me out. Public matches are garbage for IW. I'd rather hit up round 19-25, leave and collect my keys instead of losing everything at a higher round if host dashboards.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Question about public matches ( I'm a zombie noob ) </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-08 01:49:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If I enter a public match regardless if I'm the host or not and we make it to a certain round, let's say 25....if I leave/quit match....do I still get my keys or do we ALL need to die? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-08 01:46:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thanks for POINTING that out.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-08 01:33:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Old. Repost. Indian millionaire.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-07 18:43:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Pics? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-06 22:33:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Agree. I went off topic and detail into people asking for buffs and nerfs and that's all they're doing instead of fixing the current procrastinated problems like lobby connections. Instead, they're just giving us weapons and buffing and nerfing and messing up the gun balance as well as making epic , 4000k salvage pretty much useless. My bad if I came off like a dick.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-06 22:25:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You misunderstood. I WAS talking about the epics. They nerfed the ripper, bomber, sentinel and many others because people were crying.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-06 21:52:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I got the trencher gamma mark2...ugh..hate it. Maybe I suck.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-06 21:49:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You people make me sick. NERF this epic. It's too OP. Omg, buff this gun, it under performs! Under perform? It's a new gun, you don't know how it's suppose to perform. New guns don't need to be OP or evenly matched with mid tier weapons. Post like this make IW only buff and nerf f**king up the entire gun balance of the game.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-06 21:43:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I got this gun from AN epic hack. Used it once. Kicks way too much. Never used it again. Waste of epic. They nerf all the epics because people cry. What's the point in nerfing epics? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-06 20:54:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What's you're regimen? I'm Indian as well and all we cook is dhal and rice and chicken. I'm at 250. My goal is 150.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-06 16:57:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What makes these geniuses think we want these nobody's vo pack? I've never even heard of ozzyman. And I don't like this Chinese dude. Why can't they hold a poll on VO pack recommendations? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-06 04:49:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I got this and hate it  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-06 02:32:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Oh I see. I don't like it. U can have it. I wanted the axe.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Is this suppose to happen? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-06 01:27:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Not sure if it's a glitch or meant to happen, but I opened that triple play bundle and when I opened the quartermaster hack, I got the mark2 version of the trencher - gamma. Anyone else experienced This? Getting mark2 weapons from QM hacks? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-05 22:21:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This was posted 2 months ago </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-05 17:51:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Don't want to work them hard? Do you know how much they get paid? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-04 21:23:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I posted about this when mark2 got released. 

People said how hard is it to do the math?

I said, I came here to shoot people, not do math.


Apparently. People didn't like the idea of mark2 xp number in after action report and downvoted the post. 

I wonder if I can still find it :/ </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-04 01:28:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I've nerved encountered problems with ANY past cod zombies title before. Neither spaceland , nor redwoods.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-04 01:20:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Same with me  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-04 01:16:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Add psn , PUNANNYMAGNET </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-04 01:15:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Wanna play a custom match? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-04 01:14:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Wanna play a custom match? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-04 00:35:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Iw is a big joke. These people can't code. They fix 1 thing and break 5   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> COD ZOMBIES in it's current state is INFURIATING </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-04 00:34:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Not my first post, but for almost 2 weeks a few rounds and BAM! lost connection to host/server/connection timed out. 

People say, " don't play co-op, play solo " . I've tried playing solo SEVERAL times , only to loose connection to myself. What? How? My internet is excellent. It must be YOUR shitty servers infinity ward. 

What's  the point of paying $100 For a game, only to have it BOOT you all the time with it's abysmal servers? I feel robbed. Play zombies, they said. Grind 400 keys easy, they said. 

You keep patching " glitches and exploits " so that players won't farm keys EASILY, just to protect your money, but you can't get decent , stable servers? Come on, people. 

People are going to say, " its not their servers, it's YOUR connection " . I live in NYC with Verizon FIOS and I pay extra for more speed. I did a speed test. 
https://imgur.com/V1tkNqc


When are you going to FIX the servers IW????? 

When are you going to start awarding keys for certain rounds just IN CASE the servers go down? 

When INFINITY WARD? WHEN ACTIVISION?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-02 22:32:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I need my keys!! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-02 21:51:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> They patched the glitch spot by the fence. :/ </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-02 17:18:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It takes me 29 mins to get to 25.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-02 06:31:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Ice-t? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-02 06:13:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I've gotten some other epic weapons that I forgot to SS.

Some Common drops https://imgur.com/a/8Udx6 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-02 05:42:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Actually my friend, I'm the one robbing ...them. I NEVER save commons.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-02 05:19:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Bro. I play solo and lost connection to myself...4 times in the past 3 hours. https://imgur.com/gallery/U5LQx </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-02 05:18:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I play zombies now and Have over 5,000 + keys.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-02 04:29:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I just played another solo game and lost connection to myself again at round 27


GRR: https://imgur.com/gallery/U5LQx </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> I posted about losing connection to server/host playing co-op....they said play solo....how did I loose connection to myself? I have EXCELLENT internet. Round 46 and this happened. GIVE ME MY KEYS IW </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-02 03:12:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-01 03:15:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What's ur psn? I'm playing right now  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-30 17:31:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Don't nobody care about his, friend.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-30 17:24:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Lmao. Oh please. Ain't nobody getting banned. And why don't glitch videos get taking down by Activision? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-30 09:40:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If funny, I just started play SS today. I messed around with ZISL for a few weeks when the game launched. I NEVER played RITRW. I've seen gameplay of all and thought SS is the best one.....so far. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-30 09:34:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thanks man. I will. Plenty days left to grind 400 keys.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-30 09:30:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Solo. Not public. 

Zombies https://imgur.com/a/3M1sE </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> I've been trying to play zombies all day, but.. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-30 09:18:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This nonsense keeps happening in HIGH rounds. All GOD DAMN DAY. It's f**king infuriating investing so much time in game and not getting the keys because of..https://imgur.com/a/3M1sE


Everyone complains about this and nothing gets done about it. But cry OP on mp guns and shit gets nerfed right away. Only reason I'm bringing it up once again is to get the 400 keys to open the QM drop. So I turn to zombies. But no, the game wants to f**k me. 

Keys should be awarded by checkpoints/rounds/milestones just in case of this connection crap. God dammit, Bobby. 

Note: first match I went to round 32...

Second match...29....


No keys for all that time. Thanks IW.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-30 09:01:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I was actually going to put that , however some people might correct me with birthDAY. I can't win.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-30 09:00:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> True.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-30 07:49:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Bro just YouTube glitches 
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Technically, you only have one birthday and every year after that is just the anniversary of your birthday. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-30 07:06:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-30 07:01:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Does anyone have the levels and key rates for zombies ? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-30 06:50:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Lmao. Do the glitches.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-29 20:54:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Bro. It's  the controller. Call PS and if it's still under warranty. They will replace it. I should mention that you have to provide proof of purchase. I didn't keep my receipt from 3 yrs ago. So I went to target and bought a controller for 44.99 and spent $5 on a 2yr protection plan. Ds4 has a tendency to stop working after a few months with the sprint thumbstick. Trust me. This is your best option. 

I bought it last week. 

http://imgur.com/qUhcVl5


Anything happens within 2 years. They fix it or replace it. 

Also, I should mention, you get the newest ds4. The one with the light on the swipe pad that comes with ps4 pro.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-28 17:48:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I tilted my head up 20 degrees for the first time in months. Felt great.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-28 17:12:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Mark2 weapons should be upgradable with salvage and for weapons we already own.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Nature and animals, when they reproduce, they look 100% the same, but why when humans reproduce, we look different? (Excluding Identical twins) </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-27 05:08:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [Serious] Nature and animals, when they reproduce, they all look 100% the same. So why when humans reproduce, we look different (excluding identical twins)? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-27 04:58:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-27 00:35:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> nother afternoon fucking that ass. 

_ Clinton. FG.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-26 23:30:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I got the yokai in a common drop and umd mod3 legendary in another common right after.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-26 23:29:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What's ur psn. Let's play hc </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-26 23:28:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What's ur psn  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-26 22:49:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Want gone. Nigerian boots. 

Want. Nigerian jetpacks.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-25 03:01:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Kya baat hai? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-25 01:38:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> There's a fine line between being a dick and proving a point. I proved you wrong. Deal with it.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-24 23:37:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> U mean like the cyclopean or sentinel or any other weapons they moved from QM TO PROTOTYPE LAB? THEY CAN'T BE CRAFTED WITH SALVAGE? OHH MYYY GOD  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-24 23:21:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> kd means nothing. I have a .86 and I posted about shutting down Korean savage.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-24 23:18:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> New weapons are dropping tomorrow? I just spent 15k salvage on calling card hack.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> I once told a bully " don't mess with me, I know karate " ... </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-24 18:13:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>   4 other Japanese words.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-23 19:33:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Felt bad she died though. :/ but I guess it was to further progress the relationship between dom and letty raising a kid in the final 2 movies.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [Spoiler][FATE OF FURIOUS] one thing that confused me about that movie. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-23 19:18:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-23 18:15:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> A smile.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-23 01:52:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I did. 9k salvage. I got all weapons already.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-23 01:49:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You're crazy if u think a death kills a series. A brand new story with new characters or a pre sequel can be written to continue the story to mw3.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-23 01:45:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> A few weeks ago I posted about how he invited me to his lobby cause I kept shutting down his nukes. He was bitchy and said he rather had me on his team. Lmao.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-22 19:36:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That's kim dotcom. Owner of megaupload.com </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-22 12:53:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Excellent  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-22 03:40:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hate that fat guy.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-22 03:27:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Why do people POST his videos here? Every time I scroll thru, I see at least 1 of his videos posted. This video in particular are about his thoughts on the for buff. Don't get me wrong, he's an OK YouTuber amongst many, so why does HE deserve more exposure here more than others ?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> I hope ww2 doesn't have the same art style/graphics as AW </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-21 15:22:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> AW was on ok game for me , but I didn't particularly like their art style/graphics. I prefer the modern warfare series graphics, bo2 or dare I say ..ghosty.

Bo1   bo2 graphics are totally different. I hope this is the case with the new ww2 game. Thoughts? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-20 21:45:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Same here  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Why is frontier the only map.... </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-20 06:13:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-19 17:55:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Had this gun week 1 in Nov. Used it once. Never used it again.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-19 17:35:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's legal in NY. come visit me. Butt ass naked.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-19 06:11:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> No.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-19 03:08:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I got a hacked Pandora and Spotify. No ads and unlimited skips.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-18 15:08:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I played against and with you a few matches last week or 2 weeks ago I think. I remember seeing your psn. I'm PunannyMagnet </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-17 23:59:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm at MP15. About to hit 16. 19 Prestige tokens left. 

WHY? I don't know.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-15 07:21:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Epic guns should NOT receive nerfs.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-14 23:36:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I HAVE EVERYTHING YOU HAVE, EXCEPT I'M MP13,  WHICH GIVES ME 30% XP FOR MARK2 WEAPONS.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-14 23:32:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I just bought the Drake collection, last of us and tomb raider for 23 bucks.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-14 21:46:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I meant if he wants to do this, it's highly he can using synaptic/propulsion  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-14 18:19:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Propulsion  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-14 18:16:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Am I the ONLY one that doesn't use scuff/bumper jumper or stick and move....to make jumpshots and do extremely well?  I press X to jump and move my hand to the aim and fire button and quickly move back to pressing X. There's no flaw in that and I've gotten nukes with it.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-14 04:13:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Man, my gosh.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-13 23:24:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> No, I know who he is. But I mean, who is HE to tell me NOT to session join his matches ? I can if I want and no one is going to stop me. Weather he wants it or not.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-13 23:14:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Who cares what he wants? Who is HE? IM GOING TO MAKE IT MY MISSION TO JOIN HIS LOBBIES AND SHUT HIM DOWN.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-13 16:56:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I posted this a few months back.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-13 16:50:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Add me on psn. I run that every match.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-13 16:44:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> My kd is below 1 because I play with every weapon for fun. Every time I play, I go after a challenge or I'm doing something silly. HOWEVER, I know how to play and can go positive if I want. I have nukes myself. KD means nothing to me because I'm in it for fun. But don't shit talk me in prelobby cause I will laugh at you post lobby.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-13 16:40:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I can join his sessions and invite u. What's ur psn? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-13 06:16:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah I admit I went negative when I was against them , but I held my own with them, just enough to keep making them rage with their nuke streaks. LMAO. They slaughtered my teammates though. R.i.p those noobs. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> These guys got pissed off i was shutting down their nuke streaks and said im better off in THEIR party. They said they were a big deal. I wish i could send them deodorant, cause they're sweaty AF. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-13 06:10:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-12 22:46:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I've had this gun since Nov 7th. Used it 1. Don't like it.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> lobby emojis/gifts </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-12 21:04:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I don't know if you guys are familiar with Zynga poker, but whenever someone loses a big chunk of money, someone else or the person who won the pot might send him a " sad looking tissue box " as a joke because he lost. Can we get some sort of lobby emojis we can send other players that we can buy using salvage? And have it stay next to the players name for like a few mins unless he buys himself something else to replace the " tissue box ". This would be hilarious with all the shit talkers who loses. Maybe I can send a rose to a girl in the lobby or something. Again, using salvage. 10/20/30/40 and so fourth depending on the item/gift itself.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-12 18:55:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Make a video n share </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-12 16:39:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I've posted about this a few weeks back. 

why does this always happen
https://www.reddit.com/r/Infinitewarfare/comments/5x6o0y/why_does_this_always_happen/ </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-12 05:17:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That's cool. Lucky guy.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-12 03:37:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I just went 56/7 with the type 2 impulse.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-12 03:36:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I still got mines.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-12 03:35:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> On ps4, u can't.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-12 03:03:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Mark3, Everytime u get a kill, a camper dies.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-12 02:59:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Which one did it give u?
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The epic weapon hack contract </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-12 02:51:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> 

I know it doesn't say dupe protected, but can anyone confirm that they've gotten a dupe epic from this hack contract? I've got all the best epics already, should I save this for future epic updates? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-12 01:11:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Been had it.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-10 07:09:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> sure point me to the correct sub. i remember INFINITE WARFARE and MWR was being discussed on bo3 sub before they officially had their own subs. please, point me to the next cod subs and ill post it there.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-10 04:03:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> lets assume for now that it is, humor me with some gun possibilities  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> i dont know much about guns used in ww2, but is there a chance </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-10 02:41:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> that ANY gun used in cod4, mw2, bo1,bo2 and mw3 might see its way in the next ww2 cod?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-09 15:18:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> ps4

NYC

mic/yes

casual gaming 

psn: PUNANNYMAGNET 

hit me up anytime.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-09 07:23:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> then maybe it was me. punannymagnet with guyana flag emblem. i got that taunt last week. :x  hyper tdm? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
