<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject7913</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-08 01:45:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Unbreakable was his best film for me, bonus that it's the only superhero themed movie I've seen that felt realistic. Was pumped to see Willis at the end, looking forward to the next one. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-07 00:46:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Tip for softcore - you gain a total of +45 all resist from the rescuing Anya quest in Act 5 (+15 for each difficulty you complete it on). When you die, there is a bug that causes you to lose this resist bonus and this is NOT displayed on your Character stats page.

This won't matter probably until Hell difficulty, but best to just leave and re-enter a game to restore the bonus/grab body. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-05 05:32:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Most things that happen in movies. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-04 17:14:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Watch out - face-dancer! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-04 13:06:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I consider 200 the minimum, 400 is the most I've used - and anecdotally I never noticed much of a difference. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-03 19:51:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Are you using it on your original Bliz or did you respec to Lightning? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-03 17:42:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The term means "intended for young adult audiences" not "including young adult actors."  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-03 16:47:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Oh cool. Maybe I'll make a Council killer - for some reason my Bliz Sorc and Merc get trashed by them. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-03 16:10:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Congrats! I'm doing LK runs trying to get my first right now  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-03 15:37:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Really? Never knew that, so I guess that makes NM/Hell Andy best target same as rings! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-03 12:55:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Are you asking witch RW would be best to make right now between Infinity and Enigma?

If so I would make Enigma personally. I have limited time to play so I play Sorc exclusively pretty much just because of speed. Enigma would allow me to branch out more and still be fast, especially summonmancer is one of my favs. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-03 12:27:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Iirc Roland kills an entire town full of people in the first 50 pages of original series, that gives you an idea of the mood of the series. They took a very dark and unique series and turned it into some generic YA sludge. Actually a great way to get a feel for the series if interested is google "Gunslinger novel illustrations" - all the originals were illustrated by great artists, Michael Whelan, David McKean etc. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-03 12:08:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Looks like they turned it into another generic YA fantasy. Yaaaay...

A great way to get a feel for the series if interested is google "Gunslinger novel illustrations" - all the originals were illustrated by great artists, Michael Whelan, David McKean etc. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-30 13:48:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'd been wondering what has the highest chance to drop uni amulets, is it Andy really? Farmed her some and didn't notice a lot of amulets, just rings. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-29 23:58:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Oh right, Ber then! I got one Sur so far and an Ohm. Have you had any good luck off Council? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-29 23:08:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'd settle for a Jah on my LK runs ;) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-29 23:08:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I thought player# changes only applied before that map area is loaded? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-29 19:23:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That's actually a really nice find, I have a regular, would love an Eth one for my Bliz Sorc. The Merc's kill speed is basically my limit of how many /players I can stack on Chaos/Baals single player. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-29 17:20:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Oh sorry :p </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-29 16:51:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's ideal for any caster build b/c it's the only ring that includes both +skill and +mana (except for a godly rare maybe? I've never seen a rare ring with any +skill tho). </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-29 16:49:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I got my first one from farming NM Andy. You get ring drops almost every run, unis every 10-20 runs I think. I did somewhere between 100-200 runs.

2nd was off a one of those flayer minions lol. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> 2nd SOJ ever drops off Baal minions 10 days after my first! </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-29 04:38:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Can property owners object to photos/paintings of their property? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-28 00:47:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Collecting reference photos for some landscape paintings ideas: is there a potential legal issue with photographing/painting private property? What if you are on a public road/highway when you take the photo? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-24 19:09:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Picture your corpse on a table in a morgue. If there's a light on, it casts a shadow. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-24 17:37:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> TIL about the weapon switch! Thx! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-24 14:18:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Respec bumped it up to 1300, he's still pretty squishy in CS and WSK. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-23 19:06:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> He's at 81. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-23 18:34:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thanks, I was wondering if my Um'ed Viper was worth upgrading.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-23 18:32:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> My first Hdin, my hp is a little over 1k, is that low? I think it would be higher if I respec my stats, I had a ton of dex to max block before the HoZ dropped. Now my block is maxed without Holy Shield activated lol. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> SP Unmodded HDin advice pls </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-23 07:44:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm playing Single Player with zero mods. The biggest way this impacts my first HDin attempt seems to be the lack of Spirit's FHR. I just had some luck on a HoZ so I'm wondering what the best socket would be for it / what armor I could use (no Ladder RW) or boots possibly to add FHR and other good mods. I don't have Enigma so no competition from it for armor slot. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-20 18:26:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Is this your first summon Necro? Check out "Fishymancer" guide if so. You should be able to easily clear game without farming for runewords if you spend your skills correctly.

But I'd go with NM Countess for medium/low rarity runes (Lore, Smoke, Spirit). Your problem with Spirit is the 4os shield, which you won't get until A5 NM/Hell. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-20 17:44:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> PlugY also adds some battlenet content that normally you wouldn't have in Single Player like Ladder runewords (Spirit, Infinity etc.) and Ubers. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-18 19:55:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Ya I ran her specifically to try for SOJ, tempted to go for 2 but I have a Wedding Band already so moved to Hell for awhile - I can only hope I'll get some luck on Jah/Ber too ;) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-18 19:46:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Ya I just started playing again recently and I converted to SP purty quick! Don't even have online runewords or PlugY yet and still prefer it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-18 13:51:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yep! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-18 13:48:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Doing NM Andy runs on p8 :) I probably only did about 100-150. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Got my 1st SOJ drop ever. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-18 07:32:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> "There are many like it but this one is mine." </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-14 05:39:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Lol, I might try one actually. People seem to hate archon gameplay but I've never played an archon Wiz so maybe I'd like it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-13 05:07:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I've played a little Monk, which build do you think would be best? High mobility, strong on trash? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-13 04:04:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What WD build are you thinking? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-13 00:55:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thought UE for the combination of trash clearing / elite killing. Looking for any class though, not just DH. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-13 00:33:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Should toilet paper hang from behind the roll (facing away from the operator) or from the front (facing the operator)? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Best 2 player team for an Impale DH? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-13 00:31:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> My buddy is about to start playing, wondering what would compliment Impale build! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-12 09:35:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's boring but basically every build benefits most from A2 Mercs.

Personally, I spec mine for max physical melee damage: Might Aura (NM merc) with Guiliarms Face, Treachery armor, and Reaper's Toll scythe. If you look up those items you'll see you get a kickass physical element merc at fairly low cost/rarity of items. The rarest drop is the elite scythe, I got mine while moating Hell Mephisto.

FYI I don't have an option to mod bnet Ladder runewords into my single player, so I play without Infinity, Spirit etc. But for Bliz, I don't think I'd change my merc even if I was on Ladder.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-11 10:24:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I've found it really hard to get away from Sorc. I play self found single player, so no Enigma runes yet. It just saves you massive time. I'd recommend Bliz Sorc. If you really want to be able to kill Cold immunes you can swap to Meteorb Sorc but you need a lot of +skill to be efficient in Hell with dual element. Straight Bliz is probably more efficient, you just need to build up a badass merc. 

I won't seriously try any other class until I have an Enigma for tele.

My goal for SP is to get a char for /players8 MF, but as far as I know only Hdins can pull that off. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> ELI5 How do emotions create physical sensations? Like "butterflies in the stomach" etc. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-09 18:28:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-07 09:51:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Specifically on drawing from life, a large degree of it is a science, a skill that can be learned by anyone if they are dedicated and have good guidance. Most of drawing nature is learning to think the right way, it doesn't require anything special physically.

Personally, I believe any kind of drawing on toned paper is the best way to practice because you can directly draw both the darks and lights. It's faster and more straightforward. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-06 20:09:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Ya idk why it looks like daylight, with the naked eye starlight makes everything look B W. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-06 19:49:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If it's clear skies and there's low enough light pollution you can actually see well enough to walk around at night from starlight. It's pretty amazing. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-06 19:40:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Broadly speaking, WW2 does seem like the closest major war that fits the good versus evil paradigm. Sure, the allies were no angels. But it's hard to argue that their opponents weren't close to a total personification of evil conquering the earth. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-06 19:37:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I think he's complex, and obviously he wasn't an abolitionist. I think it's an interesting question because ya, most of human history is dark. Probably nothing perfectly qualifies as capital G good. But what events come closest to that ideal?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-06 19:33:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thanks for replying. I didn't mean "conquer" literally necessarily. I agree it's hard or maybe impossible to find any example of a purely altruistic war. But that's why I thought it might be interesting to discuss. What events come closest to realizing that kind of ideal? Even something like the invention of penicillin for example might be a good example. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-06 19:29:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I meant to imply that ambiguity by putting good and evil in apostrophes. Maybe a better phrase would be, what events come closest to that ideal? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-06 19:20:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I have a little experience with a longtime hoarder, who will probably lose his house over it eventually. He once lied to me 2-3 times over a couple hours to get me to pick up and transport something for him. I had a car full of people and I could tell he felt humiliated once it became obvious to everyone what was going on. But he'd do it again no question. It's a compulsive behavior, like other addictions. I think a lot of hoarders can't stop without serious intervention. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-06 19:13:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Lincoln's Emancipation Proclamation is what got me thinking about the question. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [Serious] What are the greatest examples of 'good conquering evil' in history? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-06 19:10:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-05 00:18:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It just sounds like epic trolling.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> ELI5 People believe the earth is flat? This isn't a joke? How is this possible? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-05 00:14:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> There are seriously people who believe the earth is flat? It's not a joke? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-05 00:02:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-02 10:19:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> To add a tip to the other comments, try doing quick sketches of smiles, when you start getting the hang of capturing a less detailed version move to a more detailed attempt. Practicing anything as specific as smiles can be frustrating when you're trying to do a complete drawing each attempt! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-02 10:13:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Couple unsolicited self-portrait tips: try playing with lighting, and you can also do more angles, like a profile, if you use 2 mirrors. It's a great way to practice if you add controlled lighting and an extra mirror! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-02 10:08:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I did the same thing if it makes you feel any better ;) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-02 06:39:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Did you use a stylus? Been thinking of about trying one out. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-31 07:13:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's just...cool for that cow in particular. I'm happy for him, but still stoked on eating his family. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-31 07:11:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I find my happiness for this cow in particular doesn't impede my happy anticipation about eating the pieces of many other cows that have been smushed together to make the burger I'm waiting for right now. Win win! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-31 01:00:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> iirc it's estimated in the mid-90's, similar to all the other builds that are behind LoN. 70's will be a breeze, people were clearing into the 80's with S6 Karlei's when it was still comparatively weak. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-30 04:35:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What's the advantage of this? How is a Xbow better than quiver? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-29 05:08:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Folks seem to think S6 will only be slightly behind UE for general farming? I haven't played in a season or 2, is it really not going to be worth it to run an UE for farming? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-29 05:01:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Crap I just did about 50 Andy runs on P8 lol. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-28 23:44:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> We ought to balance this, the reduction in barbarity, with the massive destructive quality of modern major wars. Modern wars have been many magnitudes more destructive but far less frequent. Here's to hoping we dodge WW3. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-27 23:58:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Noticed the doc on Netflix quotes her a lot! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-27 13:52:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> My speech professor used this as a textbook example of an inspirational speech. I also remember her using Hitler's speaking as an example of a wide range of pitch and volume... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-27 08:45:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Great thank you! Watching Burns' doc tonight :) Will definitely try some of that fiction. I'm doing a coast to coast road trip soon so def need some audio books!  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-27 07:10:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> In the hopes that someone will help me find some, years ago I heard some old school Haitian music, which was in French I think, was phenomenal. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-27 04:41:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> "Unoriginal"? Dam, shower thoughts, you've seen it all. How many times has this been posted? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Your teeth are part of your skeleton poking out of your flesh. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-27 03:56:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Introductory Reading List </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-27 02:46:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hi, I'm looking for some good recommendations for books. Primarily historical but excellent historical fiction too. I'm moving to N. Virginia, near Manassas and figure it's a good time to explore the history since I'll be living in it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-27 01:49:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Your ancient is near perfect with all the right stats, does seem better. I think a perfect IAS primal is just a little over 3k. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
