<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject7391</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Using a multi tier distribution multi level marketing system... </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-10 13:55:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-10 12:43:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> hey throw a packed bong in there and thaaasssa me! (boyfriend of 2 years will never take the pizza eating beer drinking stoner sloth out of me) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-09 03:11:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You can also read it as Carl from Family Guy or Bob from Bob's Burgers and you'll get the idea </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-07 07:06:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> there is absolutely no way you made this up. great job at life, my friend. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-06 18:55:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> such a sweet little baby! I can already tell by your gaze and how you hold the nugget that you will be a fantastic fur momma </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-05 01:52:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> would you like to expand on that  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-03 23:14:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I can always tell who has been petting my dogs. Perfume, cigarette smoke... all of that transfers so easily. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-02 13:24:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If anything she is catching her breath, enjoying the feel of the sun and the smell of outside [: it must be a lot to take in for such a sweet girl  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-02 13:20:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Just because it's a 'well-known' spot doesn't mean it was well known to this guy!! I went to Charlie's Bunion for my birthday 2 months back! Planned a whole trip out of seeing this bulbous chunk of rock... most amazing hike. I can't even imagine walking the AT and discovering this for myself the first time. Good for you! Keep hiking, exploring, and discovering!! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-30 20:07:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> how long did this trip take for you guys? this is amazing!!! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-12 17:26:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> why does he have a bulge </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> MONCH </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-09 01:24:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-07 18:04:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You really should try on every pair you can find - but i also have wide feet (bunions!) and high arches. I love my Merrill's. breathable and very easy to walk in. Light on the feet but still tough  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-04 12:00:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm taking OP for a mani/pedi date </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
