<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject4153</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-10 11:06:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> thanks, hope people get some enjoyment out of it. 

https://wh.reddit.com/r/nosleep/comments/6abnih/shadow_people_made_me_move_out/ </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-10 11:05:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I am in no way trying to advertise myself, neither of these acounts have any other media other than video and images relating to my story. What has happened to me needs to be shared with more than just my friends. You all need to know, I needed to learn to respect those that haven't passed all of the way on yet. They don't like to be mocked.

This is the video of a shadow man moving my plate as I prepared dinner. https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=ONvK1KlGM5Q

And this is the the shadow man stencil after it was repainted. I never took any pictures of what we had drawn on it. http://imgur.com/m8JHBaG
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Shadow People Made Me Move Out </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-10 11:04:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Ive Made a Mistake

The university that I call home was once a prison to many. The halls of housing and the lecture rooms are refurbished mental institution quarters and facilities. Even though most of the buildings have been dressed so well that youd never guess it. There are still entire buildings on campus that are locked and off limits. On a tour with a few police officers Id made friends with I saw the rooms that still wore padding and the beds where the mentally ill once laid. Many of the faculty would rather have you focus on its fresh start and academic resources and tend to put away the thoughts of mental patients being neglected and kept against their will for awful and unjust reasons. I however had been told the stories from my father that worked as a maintenance man on the premises when I was a child long before the university was anything more than abandoned garbage. Patients bashing their heads against the walls, homosexuals committed by their loved ones, easily treatable high functioning mentally disabled patients treated like maniacs, the graves for those who died without name, the list goes on and on.

So I did my digging and decided that I wanted to learn more, I am.. was was a horror fanatic and loved the creepy pastas that fill the internet. Thats when I learned about them, the shadows that still inhabit the same halls we do. The officers where quick to chuckle about the calls where a woman was heard screaming and seen in at the far end of a hallway in panic. Only to find that the cameras showed no one. Whispers and voices heard in rooms with limited access. Doors of abandoned buildings slamming from the inside only to find that there was no sign of trespassing. Just talk of silhouettes and figures without any real concrete descriptions. Plates moving on their own and chairs being placed facing corners, the list goes on and on.

This is where I come in, I fell in love with this school and its charm. The fresh new feeling of the facilities and the faculty. The boom in local education, but I cannot lie, I was madly in love with its history. I used to spray paint stencil graffiti when I was in high school and for a while after. A few friends had caught nasty fines and jail time and seeing as how I had managed to remain unscathed by the hobby I decided to call it quits and burn all stencils that were anywhere illegal and delete all of my memory cards. That is.. until I found the room. Adjacent to a small university gym there is a room where the walls are free to paint on. I hadnt seen anything like this since my days stumbling around old abandoned buildings inhabited by tweakers. I couldnt help myself, that very same day I eagerly cut a new stencil in the shape of a slack jawed cynical face. I wanted to paint a shadow man.. our unofficial mascot.

The thing we thought about as we walked to our dorm rooms alone from an event. The thing we thought about when we struggled to find a comfortable spot to sleep at night. Every noise that could not be explained right away was attributed to these night stalkers. So I wanted to make my own. I painted the shape of a huge stalky shadow with its head cocked to the left in black. And I in white I stenciled in my slackjawed Shadow Man face. I was proud of it because the window you had to pass in the hallway that looked into the art room showcased a shadowy horror figure standing in the corner staring at you. I had hoped that it would cost some of my classmates sleep. What did I care ? I had nothing to fear, I used to traverse abandoned buildings and sketchy hobo camps armed with nothing more than a few spray cans.

How was I to know that it would backfire this way ? How was I to know that some one would take offense ? How was I to know how much truth there was to the stories ? I was a skeptic, ok ? I see them everywhere now, the bushes whisper when I walk past as if someone was watching. I hear people in my hallway at all hours of the night. I look through my peep hole and could swear I see someone scurry away just as I look. But the buildings... the ones that are left abandoned... refurbished... some great lie meant to comfort those that know and mislead those that dont.

I cannot go near them anymore let alone go back inside. The wails of those lost call me, slamming, scraping, clawing at the walls I can hear them. Theyre upset at me for outing them. I cant even take it back, my first thought was that finals were getting to me and my imagination was running wild. So I got some sleep at a friends house and took a few of them to the art room without telling them to paint a few flowers stencils and goof off. I encouraged that we cover the ugly weird thing while I painted. I had to ignore their desire to paint anywhere else because of how much they liked the damned thing. I returned to my dorm and took a fresh razor to the stencil of the slack jawed shadow man. I slept like a baby and felt no fear as I shut my smart phone off for the night laying there in the darkness. The next day I walked by the art room after a nice workout only to find that my Shadow Man was back as if nothing had ever been painted on it at all. I own the only stencil of the shadow man! Me and only me! I thought I could stay out of the night and maybe if I got enough sleep they would leave me alone. I wish I could say going to sleep early helps. Accept now they dont wait for nightfall anymore, now they play with my food while Im cooking.

I have proof... I caught it on my cell phone. I never believed in anything paranormal, It was always entertainment for me. But the game is over... listed in the links below I will post a youtube video that has never been uploaded by anyone else other than me... with photos of a room you wont find anywhere else on the internet. This semester is almost over and I havent slept in my room for a few days. Ive found a new apartment off campus. Ill update with new information as it happens.
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-10 10:52:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I am in no way trying to advertise myself, neither of these acounts have any other media other than video and images relating to my story. What has happened to me needs to be shared with more than just my friends. You all need to know, I needed to learn to respect those that haven't passed all of the way on yet. They don't like to be mocked.

This is the video of a shadow man moving my plate as I prepared dinner. 
https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=ONvK1KlGM5Q

And this is the the shadow man stencil after it was repainted. I never took any pictures of what we had drawn on it. 
http://imgur.com/m8JHBaG </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Shadow People Made Me Move Out </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-10 10:49:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-10 09:51:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> they don't want links to videos and paranormal stories but I have both and neither are easy to just write off. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-10 09:50:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> they don't want what could be considered paranormal. but i have a video that's hard to explain and a story to go with it that will genuinely cost sleep. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-10 08:57:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I've got a good one that will be sure to scare the shit out of you all. Coping with a unexplained situation by writing it out. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> what is the most popular subreddit to share a real scary story ? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-10 08:56:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-09 23:19:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Because I don't work my schedule around the comfort of others. Especially when you're not doing me any favors by being open in the allotted amount of time you said you were.

Went to a cold stone about 40 minutes before they were due to close the other day and the entire staff of 17 year olds were treating the gf and I like a burden. They even lied about their business hours and said they would serve us but they are technically closed even though the sign on the door and website said otherwise. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-09 23:05:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> sacajawea !! sacajawea !! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-09 23:03:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Kill Donald Trump and make a leather jacket out of the skin. You don't get any monetary value from the act, and i get sweet new conversation piece. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-09 22:58:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Which dictator ? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-09 22:57:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> did not know that was a thing </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-09 22:56:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You already stole it, might as well burn it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-09 22:55:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Ha, I respect that. A lot of beautiful places are off limits because some rich cunt owns it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-09 22:54:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> monster </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-09 22:54:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Than burn it ? I'd burn it after. Yea.. i'd burn it. Maybe beat it with a nice sledge hammer first. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-09 22:52:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Woman often times get so much leniency even though they are bat shit crazy. My buddy's mom stored her friends piss in her mouth so she could piss clean for a drug test for visitation rights and still do heroine.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-09 22:51:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Why a panther ? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-09 22:50:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> "You were the chosen one, mother fucka" But all of the Gungan and Jarjar bit's would get uncomfortably racist... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> If you had the ability to do one illegal thing without monetary gain, but free of consequence, what would it be ? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-09 22:48:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-09 21:11:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Right ? I have to work with kids on the weekends and the older ones kept saying it till I finally said something about it. They looked at me like I was some unreasonable pansy.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-09 21:07:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I've got a brother that has dealt with autism his entire life, hearing this new trend is like nails on chalk board everytime I hear it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Why is calling stupid things "autistic" common place ? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-09 21:05:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-09 20:46:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If i could still retain my mind inside of the body of dog owned by a nice well-off family i'd be in heaven. Hiking on four legs, swimming in lakes, everyone thinks i'm the most adorable thing in the planet, sneaking me all of the foods i'd miss on the side. I'd miss my nuts though :( </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What animal would you trade places with, and why ? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-09 20:44:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-09 19:59:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Choking, ex got my into it and I don't know how to ask my gf if I can strangle her lightly while I make love to her. Also if she finds out it was something an ex and I did her self consciousness will get the better of her. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-09 19:23:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I don't know if it's the best but man it is high on my list. Tornado of Souls by Megadeth, it starts off so strong that the rest of the song has to keep up.

https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=Lcm9qqo_qB0 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-09 19:11:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Zack Snyder's Dawn of the Dead, gave me my first film nightmare outside of childhood. and it gave off this hopeless feeling at the end that sticks with you. Makes you think a lot more than your average action film. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-09 19:04:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It was hot so I let it go. But man do i have a mental image everytime that song comes on. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-09 19:03:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Ex girlfriend once was having a deep conversation with me about her inability to get over her ex. During which she said "You can get addicted to a certain kind of sadness," I lean pretty prominently towards metal music so I bet she thought she could slip it past me. It didn't and I totally didn't let it go. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What quote has some one shamelessly tried to work into conversation as if it was original ? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-09 19:01:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-09 19:00:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> She moaned out that bit from Offspring's Pretty Fly for a White Guy "Give it to me baby, ahhow, ahhow," </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-09 18:58:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thall shalt not be a prick. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-09 18:54:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Personally I think you should tell them about the rabbits and cure them with a .22 but... maybe they can be saved </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [Serious] Girls of reddit, how would you cure an incel ? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-09 18:52:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What prank have you witnessed that's gone too far ? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-09 00:02:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-08 20:22:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I am too, sort of. The reason i responded with that on here is because I feel darker now. I feel like the passive person i was before is terrified at what i've done. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-08 20:04:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Why the ponies by the way ? was it just liking something because it was weird to like or what ? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-08 20:03:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> A man took my sister's virginity through rape, she only had one virginity. The man was born with ten fingers, he's learning to live with nine. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-08 20:01:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Neil Patrick Harris </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [Serious]What was the most embarrassing thing you've gone through ? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-08 20:00:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-08 09:56:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> they removed it every time 
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-08 06:38:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So the university i live on has an interesting history as a re-purposed mental institution. There is this art room that is free game to paint up the walls and people walk by it at all hours. I wanted to put up something to make people feel a twinge of uneasy or at least provoke a small jump scare of something they didn't expect to be watching. Kind of like a porcelain doll does. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> CSUCI shadow man, Paint, 960 x 717 </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-08 06:38:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-08 02:44:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So the university i live on has an interesting history as a re-purposed mental institution. There is this art room that is free game to paint up the walls and people walk by it at all hours. I wanted to put up something to make people feel a twinge of uneasy or at least provoke a small jump scare of something they didn't expect to be watching. Kind of like a porcelain doll does. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Something to make foot traffic double take. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-08 02:44:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-07 22:28:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So the university i live on has an interesting history as a re-purposed mental institution. There is this art room that is free game to paint up the walls and people walk by it at all hours. I wanted to put up something to make people feel a twinge of uneasy or at least provoke a small jump scare of something they didn't expect to be watching. Kind of like a porcelain doll does. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Something to make passerbys double take. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-07 22:25:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-06 19:54:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Dawn of the Dead the Zach Snyder remake. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-06 16:38:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Waters the experience down to some base level shell of what it once was. I wanted to celebrate day of the dead with some friends so I got the whole thing ready and one of my buds shows up dressed like he was in the 80s because he thought it was just Mexican Halloween XD. LUCKILY ! You are %100 wrong and the country of origin is where the true culture will thrive and be passed on for future generations to get the authentic experience. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-06 16:34:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's kind of like the idiots you see on the news durring a march or protest. They often love to pick the biggest idiot of the crowd to put in front of the camera. When asked simple questions like, why are you out here today ? What is this all about ? Can you tell me about why you support this ? They give answers ewuivelent to that of a second grade last minute essay. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-06 10:08:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Violent sexual offenders, if there is sufficient evidence to convict. Spay and neuter the fuckers. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [Serious] What do you wish you would have never said ? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-06 10:06:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-06 10:04:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Never got caught, a few close calls but your be surprised what you can get away with when you're dressed like a worker. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-06 10:03:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I spent just under two years doing stencil graffiti in broad daylight with the help of a hard hat, reflective vest, police scanner, and tool bag. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-06 09:59:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I hurt some one that hurt a loved one. They did something irepairable. So I did something irepairable. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-06 09:53:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I think it's more of a desire for them to actually get to know the culture instead of just making some weird characiture of it. Why are you getting a phu dog and Chinese calligraphy tattoos when you were born in Texas and know nothing about the culture ? Why do you have a dream catcher on your rear view mirror ? Ect. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-06 09:41:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> But as I said, if you cup your and over where the filter used to be it suctions the entire face. No air comes in through the nose or mouth. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Wanted to paint something that would make people at night double take. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-06 02:30:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-06 02:28:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Channel Islands Mental Institution  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-06 02:10:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thanks ! The face is a stencil i hand drew so the moment some one paints over it. It will come back exactly the same. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-06 02:09:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Sort of empowering actually, less afraid of whats waiting for you in the dark if you know you can fuck it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Wanted to paint something in the artroom that would make people passing by at night double take. keep in mind that our campus is basically a refurbished mental institution. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-06 02:07:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-06 02:04:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I was thinking about getting a couple of friends to come over and paint pentagrams and weird symbols on all of walls.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-06 01:58:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Did this earlier this week, my campus has a history of being a refurbished mental institution so i wanted to paint something that made people double take as they walk by at night. 

http://imgur.com/a/Old1J </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [Serious] What would you paint on a wall to scare some one as they walked by ? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-06 01:58:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> My campus has a history of being a refurbished mental institution, I painted this in the art room to give people passing by a heart attack. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-06 01:56:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-06 01:52:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Cheese Cake </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-06 01:49:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Had a canadian friend visit recently and they tried mexican food for the first time. Up until then their idea of mexican food was taco bell. Taco Bell is like the dollar store of mexican food. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-06 01:47:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> surprise day off, and i'm about to go share a meal with the gf and some friends. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-06 01:44:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> RIGHT ?! I was watching that richard spencard dude talk to a gaggle of his kkk budies at a holiday inn. And the conversation went from an already appalling conversation about concentration camps for black people, straight into jewish hate. And i'm sitting there thinking, wait a second, this man is clearly a maniac and his ideas are bullshit. But i expected it, you have a movement for black people rising in the US so naturally there is going to be some shit head that starts up an anti black people movement. But than BAM !! segways straight to jews, I don't get it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-06 01:40:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Can't say, lady was like an aunt to me so it was scaring. But she's an attractive lady. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-06 01:06:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> My buddies dad asked me to get his phone from the other room, his wife sent him spread eagle nudes. I saw the bush of my buddie's mom. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-06 01:04:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I get what you're saying. There's still a good portion of us that are so self destructive that they would still find some reason to discriminate and fight. We're not as smart as whole as we need to be. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-06 01:00:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Nah, fuck that guy. The biggest embarrassment since Arnold Schwarzenegger  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-06 00:58:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> have you played it ? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-06 00:58:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> message in a bottle was great </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-06 00:57:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Sad Statue </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-06 00:57:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> hot for teacher </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-06 00:51:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Haha, no, we had a system. She keeps a hand on the wrist and if she taps she gets a breather. Kind of like fucking a monster with the gas mask on though. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-06 00:33:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Totally, what's the point of having unlimited access to all of the free media you want if you can't slap it on 60 inches of screen and watch the latest and greatest with the homies ? Also 60 inch monitors are expensive... got mine on sale at target with my buddies employee discount on top of it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-06 00:04:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> hooked up my computer to my tv. Gf and I pirate stuff and put it on the big screen. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-06 00:03:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> selfie stick </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-05 23:58:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> spreading the word so you can all try the gas mask thing, she creamed her self like five times. Makes her nether regions tense up around the cock like a lubed up velvet hand. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-05 23:57:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So this chick was really into getting choked while we have sex, I was really shy to it at first. but then slowly but surely every now and again we'd do it and I began to like it. Towards the end of our relationship she would have me put a gas mask on her with the filter taken off. Id put a hand where the filter hole used to be and the whole mask would suction cup her face.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-05 23:57:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So this chick was really into getting choked while we have sex, I was really shy to it at first. but then slowly but surely every now and again we'd do it and I began to like it. Towards the end of our relationship she would have me put a gas mask on her with the filter taken off. Id put a hand where the filter hole used to be and the whole mask would suction cup her face.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-05 23:56:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  So this chick was really into getting choked while we have sex, I was really shy to it at first. but then slowly but surely every now and again we'd do it and I began to like it. Towards the end of our relationship she would have me put a gas mask on her with the filter taken off. Id put a hand where the filter hole used to be and the whole mask would suction cup her face. 

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-05 23:56:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So this chick was really into getting choked while we have sex, I was really shy to it at first. but then slowly but surely every now and again we'd do it and I began to like it. Towards the end of our relationship she would have me put a gas mask on her with the filter taken off. Id put a hand where the filter hole used to be and the whole mask would suction cup her face.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-05 21:24:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> ha ! burn </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-05 20:31:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Also the first cup of coffee on your day off. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-05 20:30:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Racking the first round of the day at the gun range, sighting in your target, and landing it at +200 yards.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-05 20:24:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I also used to spend my days off wearing a reflective vest, hard hat, and a police scanner with ear buds. A couple of cans of rustoleum and some stencils blasting the walls of where ever i saw fit. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-05 20:05:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I work for a well known department store with an added super market. Every day at lunch i grab a trail mix and a naked juice drink and just walk into the break room and have it for lunch. I've done this for over a year and no one has caught me. And if they do i'll say something like "Ohh, just muscle memory, wasn't thinking" than go pay for my lunch. I've done the math and we're in the hundreds now. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
