<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject6807</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-10 08:11:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>   I'm hesitant to watch "Don't Breathe" for the same reason.

Don't Breathe isn't exactly that because the protagonist isn't the disadvantaged one.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-10 07:55:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I just meant maybe they don't have a whole day or afternoon, or maybe they were asked to prioritize others shows. That's why I mean it might be the site, or newspaper or whatever it may be, that is to blame.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-10 07:44:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Isn't a deadline a decent excuse?

At least for the critic, maybe not so much for the outlet. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-10 07:11:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Pretty much. I also liked You're Next.

With both films I had very limited knowledge about what I were about to see, hadn't watched any trailers or anything, that probably has something to do with my reaction. Not sure how I would have felt if I had been primed for something specific. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-10 07:09:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm not a mega found footage fan, but I did watch The Visit recently and enjoyed it a lot, so I won't rule out the genre. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-10 07:04:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I personally don't give most shows that much of a chance. 

Too many other things too see.

But I'm not sure what approach I would take if I had to write about it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-10 07:02:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Certainly an interesting choice to block people's view of an action set piece.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-10 06:56:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I get why it's less creepy when he takes off the mask, but whatever reason it didn't bother me. Maybe it's because I wasn't really expecting anything specific, so when it became more of a suspense thriller than a straight up horror film about the unknown, it didn't disappoint me.

Entertaining little film. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-10 06:53:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I had read it too. It was a pretty faithful adaptation, but I felt something got lost in the translation. 

But now that you have reminded me of the film, I do remember thinking there were some scenes with Doctor Manhattan and Rorschach that I enjoyed as well. 

In the end I just didn't feel that much about it though. It came and went, whereas the comic has stayed with me.
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-10 06:48:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I don't really think much about that film. Just one of those that didn't leave much of an impression, but I do remember the credits. They were indeed very cool. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The Best Opening Credit Sequences In Movie History </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-10 06:44:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-10 06:35:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Ben Travers seems to (kinda) agree with you, but he also says there are practical limitations. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-10 06:31:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I really appreciate that you're doing this. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-10 06:28:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The critics seems to have different takes on this, but it seems to me that at its core reviewing shows simply is a difficult thing. Do we really expect every single one of them to watch an entire season of Bojack Horseman before they form an opinion? It of course makes sense, but on the other hand, that's a lot to ask. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> How Much of a TV Show Do You Need to Watch to Review It Properly? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-10 06:21:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-10 06:06:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Talking about the Lost ending is one of the most relaxing things you can do. No one ever gets upset or anything. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-10 03:59:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Psycho II? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-10 03:57:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thanks.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-09 13:01:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Oh, I have seen the show. Four times actually.

I'm a huge fan. I just think the rather old school look might be a problem for some, so the new remastered version is good in that regard. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-09 13:00:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Then I think there's no money to be had. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-09 05:52:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> His movie The Glass House wasn't all that good though.

But that seems to be a recurring thing. People who doesn't have much luck making films move to TV and find their groove there. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-09 05:48:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It was Bound to be brought up.

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-09 05:46:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> There are. It's hard to miss if you're not on your phone.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-09 05:45:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  What do you think the odds are that the guy above me is a Trump voter?

This is not a good luck.

But I'm not surprised to see it, sadly. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-09 05:42:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If you haven't seen the show, I wouldn't recommend seeing that clip.

It works much better in context after four hours of build up </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-09 05:41:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That's what *really* sold me on the show too and yep, that's the hospital escape. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-09 05:40:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Everything is paid promotion at this point.

Nothing is real.

Something about The Matrix... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-09 04:45:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Now that you mention it, I do recall that too. 

But I'm still blank on everything else. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-09 03:36:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Being a del Toro fan is never easy. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Jean Giraud </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-09 03:28:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-09 03:21:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You never know when or where you might run into something biblical. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Moon Pool, Bernie Wrightson, Mixed Media, 1978 </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-09 03:17:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Sabine </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-09 03:13:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-09 02:58:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I do think about giving it a shot, but the caveats are a bit of a stumbling block. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Blue   Gold </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-09 02:50:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-09 02:42:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  although Simon thinks that diminished the quality of some of the scenes that were so great in 4:3.

He might be right, but it has certainly made the show more accessible. I know someone who saw it recently. not sure that person would've been able to get into it if it hadn't been remastered- </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Diner </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-09 02:31:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-09 02:29:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I have no actual clue, but I would imagine they have to be in pristine condition. And Ducktales I don't think is worth anything because it's so recent. But maybe...

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-09 02:08:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> In general subs dedicated to specific TV shows are not filled with laid back people.

It's mostly uptight central. Not sure why, but it is what it is. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-08 18:50:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yes! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-08 17:34:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I wasn't being 100% serious. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-08 15:51:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I have only ever seen one episode of Babylon 5, so whatever references there were went completely over my head. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-08 15:28:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This is going to rock. 

I'm really not sure what to expect, but I hope you're right. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-08 15:25:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah, but I'm not actually a huge fan (do like the original though).

That said, he was indeed good in the film. Hell, he was the best thing in the film. Eating apples all evil style and everything. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-08 11:54:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Kill List perhaps? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-08 11:48:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Brothers? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> David Lynch on the return of Twin Peaks and why he will never make another film </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-08 11:37:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Swamp Thing cover by Bernie Wrightson </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-08 11:22:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Walt Disney's Comics cover by Walt Kelly </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-08 11:19:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-08 10:15:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  She just kicks everyone's ass and is ridiculously likable while doing it.

And her brother is probably the most loathsome bad guy in the show. 

He almost makes Whispers seem like a friendly old fella. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-08 09:46:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  I always assume any threads praising The Leftovers or The Expanse are paid marketing

What a silly idea. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-08 09:46:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  Please give me a one good reason why should I keep watching.

You probably shouldn't.

Not every single show is for everyone. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-08 09:22:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  I took to skipping the boring scenes come Season 2 to get to the pirates. 

When season four ended I saw several people who were very surprised and confused because they had for some reason managed to miss a major plot point a couple of seasons back. They had been watching for years, having no idea what they were watching.

Why even watch if you haven't gotten a clue what's going on because you're just randomly skipping parts here and there? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-08 09:17:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Sure, it's a big part of the show, but saying it's *purely* that is silly and doesn't actually reflect what the show is about. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-08 09:16:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Clue: an actor from The Man in the Iron Mask (1998) is in this film. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-08 09:07:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I also would like to see more experiments in TV, but I don't think analysis and experimentation are mutually exclusive. Why would they be? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-08 01:32:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> He's been good in almost everything I've seen him in. Didn't like the season much though. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-08 00:49:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I try to spread them out a bit because I don't want it to end :)

I tried the same. Didn't work out.
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-08 00:43:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  Reminds me of Buffy a little actually now that I think about it..

Never crossed my mind.

I will now mull it over.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-08 00:35:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Indeed. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-07 23:42:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hope you can get into it. Good luck. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-07 23:05:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's not for everyone. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-07 23:03:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Is season 2 better than season 1?

It moves much faster and is more conventional plot wise. Not sure if it's better in my opinion.

 Can you understand season 2 when you quit season 1 halfway?

No. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-07 23:01:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> In that case I would say give it a few more episodes. 

I personally liked it from the first one and *loved* it by episode three, but many didn't even like before they had seen episode four.

I feel like asking someone to watch more than an hour or two, is asking a lot, but it's the best answer I can come up with, since so many genuinely felt like you but still ended up at least enjoying to some degree. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-07 22:54:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Not sure, depends on why you didn't like it? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-07 22:34:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I did my first fist in the air "Hell Yeah!" in episode two of this season.

No idea where you are, but enjoy what you've got left. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-07 22:32:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Maybe they will. 

I'm hoping for something like they got an unofficial semi go ahead for a third season, so they already have everything in place and doesn't need to renegotiate contracts and get all the behind the camera talent back together again. Just straight ahead into a new season.

But who knows. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-07 22:30:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah, I too am wondering if he/she just watched three or four episodes.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-07 22:26:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I love it too, binge through this stuff like my life depends on it.

I know it's incredibly difficult to make, but I still hope it won't take two years before we get a third season.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Netflix's Sense8 is complete nonsense, but deeply lovable </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-07 22:12:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-07 21:59:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  There's a reason it was cancelled after such a short run.

Commercial success means nothing when it comes to quality. Never has, never will. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-07 21:58:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>   When watching Black Sails, I feel like there is not much of an attempt to make the characters well rounded and instead really press the gratuity factor of more boobs, more sex, and more violence.

They tone down the T A very much as the show goes along. As for the violence... these are incredibly violent people living in a turbulent violent time. Makes sense. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-07 21:57:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Depends on if you mean don't care, or actively dislike. 

If you're just sort of they're-okay-I-guess, there's plenty to enjoy, but if you're Jesus-I-hate-those-bloody-pirates this show won't change your opinion- </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-07 21:27:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I takes a few episodes to get going, but if you're willing to sit through those, it gets pretty damn amazing.

Season two, three and four are all fantastic. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-07 11:26:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> For whatever reason I never noticed. I'll delete this post. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-07 11:25:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Wincott was a fantastic badguy.

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-07 11:20:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This one is newer. But they do share the genre thriller on IMDb. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-07 11:12:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Finished the season.

It was exhausting, but in a great way.  

Please don't take two years to bring us another season. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-07 11:00:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Not sure what to say, so here's Metacritic:

http://www.metacritic.com/movie/the-salvation/critic-reviews </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-07 10:36:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Not science fiction or comedy. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-06 23:22:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  Plus the action scenes are always entertaining, and if that's your cup of tea - rather than the friendships and romances that I enjoy - there's a shit-ton of it in the new season.

I enjoy both and think they reinforce each other. The reason why it's so exhilarating when they come together to beat the shit out of someone, isn't just because those scenes are so amazingly well done, it's because you care about and know the characters. Sure, seeing them switch back and forth would be cool anyway because it's so well shot and edited, but knowing the people makes it immensely more satisfying. 

And vice versa. Understanding just how far they go for each other and the extremes they experience, makes the light farcical stuff with Lito for instance, hit that much harder.

It's a wonderful blend of all sorts of genres and at no point do they ever seem to look down upon any of it, which makes them all believable in some way.

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-06 23:08:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I just watched episode 8.

Some next level shit. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-06 23:00:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Ha ha... I smoke, so not a problem for me, but I imagine if I tried to quit this show would've killed me. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-06 22:03:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I would never throw that many hours away just for one episode of TV and to be honest, if you aren't enjoying most aspects of the show by now, if perhaps not all, I don't think you'll find International Assassin to be that amazing.

But good luck with your endeavour.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-06 21:47:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I know most people do this, but I just don't get it. I would never watch hours upon hours of something I didn't enjoy at all. But to each their own.

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-06 21:29:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This one made much less at the box office. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-06 21:26:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This film has a lover RT score. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-06 21:25:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This film is newer. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-06 21:23:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This film has a shorter running time. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-06 15:43:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  the shop

Oh yeah. Cool name.

I have read those other books, but I don't think I've ever noticed, or I forgot, that connection. 

Thanks. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-06 12:58:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  David Lynch

What specifically are you thinking of? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-06 12:57:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Vertigo got mixed reviews and lukewarm box office.

The Thing also flopped.

And Blade Runner.

The list goes on and on. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-06 12:52:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I started talking to the screen during episode two. Always a good sign that it's some involving stuff.

Either that, or a sign that I'm insane, but I prefer option one. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-06 12:38:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>   I found myself skipping though the plot

No wonder you found it badly paced. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-06 12:37:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> And I hope it won't take two years to arrive. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-06 12:35:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  He also did "Cape Fear"

And it was a great film. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Jordi Lafebre </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-06 12:32:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The Fairy That Disappeared, Theodor Kittelsen, Mixed Media, 1910s </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-06 12:29:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-06 12:08:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I think it's the kind of film that can rub some people the wrong way because it's so languid and takes everything very seriously, but it was interesting and I enjoyed seeing it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Sense8 Is Auteur Television Thats Actually Fun </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-06 12:02:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-06 11:57:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It may be insecurity at times, but at other times it's just wish fulfilment. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [GTM]Spring Cleaning </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-06 11:53:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-06 11:49:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It was, but they leaned into it and did it sincerely, so I had no problem with it.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-06 11:46:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It makes sense within the story, so I went along with it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Sabrina Nichole </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-06 11:40:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-06 11:37:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I know it was always a loose spin on Psycho, but to me they finally went a bit too far away from the film. Kind of tainted my view of the series a bit.

I don't know how I would have felt if I had watched not knowing the movie. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Lobster Johnston by Toni Zonji </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-06 11:34:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-06 10:55:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I see this unsubstantiated rumour is still floating around. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-06 10:51:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's The Wachowskis.

Well, it's one of them, but even just one Wachowski is better than a bunch of other directors. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Ukraine bans Steven Seagal as threat to national security </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-06 03:02:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-05 22:48:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> One serious moment that *did* land for me was those tiny quick cuts when Peter finally looked into his heart. It's a simple old trick, but I felt they pulled it off here and it made the death at the end a lot more impactful, despite there only being one short shot of him and Peter as a child.
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-05 22:42:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>   maybe they wanted to create the ultimate girly scifi fantasy?

I definitely think that was the aim.

But if so, they should have found someone who can carry a film, not Kunis. She's pretty and seems awfully nice, but damn is she ever bland in this film. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-05 22:38:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah, like I said, if my audience is anything to go by.

In general I laughed quite a bit more than my audience. Maybe they were just a depressed bunch, though they did love Mary Poppins and Pac-Man.

I don't take these films all that seriously, so I'm always pleased when they're funny. Think that's one of the main things I look for in them. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-05 22:34:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I figured he gave her cancer because he was aware otherwise he might actually end up going back to her and he had bigger fish to destroy.

It was one of those, he's a psycho, but he still has emotions moments. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-05 22:30:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  Most notably for me was Nebula's spending of her reward money into a throwaway "uh...huh..." joke delivery in response.

I don't think anyone at my screening laughed at that. Besides me.

So if my audience is anything to go by, you are probably right that there were too many jokes from a commercial POV, but it worked for me personally. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-05 22:24:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hope you find what you're looking for. and who knows, maybe some other cool comics too. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-05 22:11:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I would imagine you'll have to buy them. Or go to your library, if they have them. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-05 22:10:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  RIP Bernie.

The guy traumatized me since I was a little kid.

He is missed. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-05 22:09:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah, guess I took that too literally. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-05 17:39:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The comment you're replying to is so dumb, I suspect it's just someone trolling. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-05 17:20:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I have no idea what that sandwich is all about, but I want one. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-05 17:19:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I want to him to make many more films as Roland Deschain, so I hope the Bond thing doesn't lure him away. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-05 17:18:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>   Sure it had some moments, but they were too disconnected for me to enjoy the movie as a whole.

The production didn't went smoothly, they changed director for reshoots and such. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-05 17:16:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Made sense to me the way it was done. Didn't really feel like they needed any more to make it clear that time is passing. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-05 17:14:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Eh, isn't that just you repeating what you already said?

Like I said, it doesn't ruin anything because it's not the point.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-05 16:39:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I haven't read it in twenty years or so, I just like Wrightson.

I should probably pick up a Poe book again though, the guy was a great author. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-05 14:12:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's from a book with Poe illustrations, don't think it has anything to do with Lovecraft. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-05 13:57:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> They are. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-05 13:55:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I rarely hate a movie immediately. It has to earn it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Radio FM </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-05 13:50:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> the Masque of the red death, bernie wrightson, mixed media, 1976 </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-05 13:48:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Scrooge in the Wild West by Don Rosa </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-05 13:34:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Andreas Martens </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-05 13:32:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-05 13:25:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The entire excitement for the shows comeback depended on the surprise of where the characters and actors are in life is gone.

I don't think that's the case at all. It's about seeing the world again *and* seeing the characters again, but just knowing what the actors look like now won't ruin any of that. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Trick or Treat by Carl Barks </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-05 13:07:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-05 12:42:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> No, but knowing this sub someone will probably come along with the answer. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Deep in thought </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-05 12:17:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-05 11:08:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  frankly i don't know why "mythos sandwich" isn't a more popular genre

With that name, I am now also wondering why it's not more popular. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-05 11:07:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's such a clever economical touch.

Fun film, never really got why it was so disliked. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-05 11:01:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Indeed.

Though I like spins on it, using the aesthetics to go different fresh ways, I also want Costner to do one more like Open Range. That film is just so damn *solid*. But I suspect he wouldn't be able to get the funding.

Incidentally, have you seen The Salvation? I got some Roland vibes now and again while seeing it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-05 10:53:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That's quite a bit different from his "it's a Cadillac with no engine", it's misogynistic and whatever else he's managed to call it through the years.

But hey, people change. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-05 10:48:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  The problem is, if they did such an adaptation, the film might get lost in the shuffle as just a Western with a Sci-Fi twist. 

I agree. I also think the entire climax would make for a quite arty movie, not the kind of thing that's a solid foundation for a franchise that's going to need money later on. That's not to say it wouldn't be cool, just that it wouldn't be commercially viable.

King is a great storyteller, but he doesn't always seem to care all that much about making his stories fit neatly into the classic mainstream Hollywood three act structure with inciting incidents, resolutions and all that jazz.

All that aside, I've been watching some modern westerns lately (Bone Tomahawk, Open Range, Meek's Cutoff) and it's a great malleable genre, so it's a shame people don't really watch it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-05 02:12:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Glad to hear that and hope it's representative of people at large. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-04 23:52:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I believe most of the technicalities are left deliberately vague. 

I know that doesn't at all answer your questions, just saying that's seemingly the intention of the film and in my opinion part of what makes it work.

But good luck with people answering your questions. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-04 23:46:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> https://drive.google.com/file/d/0B5lHQAVEce61bmtjSHJ0MklVVVE/view </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-04 22:24:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> No, you're probably right about that.

Still didn't love it though, but will give it another watch as a lead in to the new season. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-04 21:59:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> With the right part he could do extremely well, but really, I just want him to gather enough money to direct another languid cool western like Open Range. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-04 21:55:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> As someone who's been doing this internet thing for too long, I just want to say welcome and hope you enjoy your stay.

To be honest, at times you really won't enjoy it, but stick around anyway. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-04 21:42:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  My point is, don't get hung up in the vocal minority who are claiming that it's the worst movie ever made, when none of them have seen it.

Maybe it's because I read so many of the r/movies reaction I never got the feeling it was a minority and then saw those things repeated on other sites. But I do hope you're right and that more casual people might make it a hit. Fingers crossed. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-04 20:50:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I haven't read Game of Thrones, but going by the show it strikes me as a much more conventional political intrigue and drama within a fantasy setting type thing than any of the bananas stuff King threw in his books. 

Sure, it's violent and there's sex, but Wizard of Oz elements doesn't pop up and there aren't any cowboys and junkies encountering a cyborg bear.

Some things are simply easier to adapt into another medium. That's not to say they are easy, just easier. And King has a feverish crazy imagination that often makes his stuff hard to deal with when visualized (and then a turtle showed up).

I think epics can be filmed (Hollywood has been making those things since the silent era) if someone is willing to throw the money at it and who knows, if HBO weren't already doing a fantasy show and lining a huge science fiction show up to take over their money making throne, they maybe would have or could have done The Dark Tower, but it's not in the cards now. And I believe they were asked at some point while it was being dragged around and rejected everywhere, so they must have declined for a reason.

And like I said, if this film is as badly received by the general public as it has been by the internet, no channel is going to touch it with a ten feet pole. Major flops have a tainted vibe too them. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-04 20:37:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  My only problem with the first episode was it felt like Hannibal instead of its own unique thing.

Auteur TV. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-04 20:37:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah, basically the same here. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-04 20:35:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> No one is going to pick a major failure up right away. It'll be at least a decade, likely a lot more.

People tried for years to get a more faithful adaptation off the ground, but no one would have any of it, so they finally decided to this one in the hopes that it could work as a sort of backdoor pilot to an expanded universe of films and TV shows. If people completely rejects this and it bombs, as it looks like after the trailer came out, it won't suddenly become a hot property. The opposite in fact.

I understand people want a 100% true to the material adaptation, but most also seems to want something with at least some money behind it. Those two things are not possible at the same time, since the material is so strange and out there. If this one had been well received, I think the money folks would have been much more willing to go *"A talking train you say? Guess it could be worse..."*

Blockbusters can make the people sitting on the cash oddly adventurous, but they aren't just going to throw the dollars out for the fun of it.

Btw, there was some rumours the W G show would have ended up a Netflix production since the company has worked with them before. Alas... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-04 20:23:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I have no clue, but if not, I suspect she'll be replaced with someone else that's vulgar. Seems to be that kind of show. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-04 20:22:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I was all, hey I don't remember writing that...

I maybe need to get rid off my flair. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-04 20:21:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The choice to go with extreme close ups during the "chat" was inspired. Made that shit intense! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-04 20:19:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I mostly give shows one episode, maybe two or three, so good for you that you tried for that long.

Life's too short and there's too much stuff for me to spend many hours on something I don't see any value in. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-04 20:18:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If you didn't like episode three, I genuinely don't think the show is for you. 

Or alternatively, you could do as some say and just skip season one completely and go and watch season two. I personally find that absurd, it's a not a procedural show, but many argue that it does go from complete shit to best show ever between those two seasons. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-04 20:15:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That is probably true actually. Doesn't make it any less depressing to see the end result of it though. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-04 20:13:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's a bummer that people are so strongly against this film, since that means no Ka-tet, no Blaine, no Wizard and Glass TV show, none of the things we would have gotten in future instalments.

At least not in any near future.

I know the budget isn't *insanely* huge, but I still think they are already trying to get rid off the rights after seeing this amount of hatred.

I'm still going to check the film out, but I was hoping it would be the beginning of something, not the end. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-04 20:05:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Have you seen how people who have read the books have reacted to this? If not, let's just say they have mostly been... less than enthusiastic. 

So I would recommend that you wait and read the series after having seen the film. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-04 20:01:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I wasn't particularly hooked either. It felt aloof. 

But I'm willing to go along for the ride and see where they'll take me. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-04 20:00:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I suspect so. But it makes sense, there's a great flow to each season and the way they build up, so the last few episodes when everything is at 11 can get mixed up. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-04 19:58:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I wouldn't mind if there was a separate television sub for late night talkshows. 

Nothing particularly to do with this clip, just something that came to mind. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-04 19:56:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I have no clue what to expect and if this will be any good, but I'll give it a shot and it is nice that they have managed to get so many of the people back again. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-04 19:42:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I live in an area with a lot of immigrants/foreigners/whatever you want to call them and this culture war with tons of attacks and rapes from those people is not something I observe in my daily life. 

Obviously this is anecdotal, but I do find it weird that as soon as I turn on my computer or read a paper or turn on the TV, I'm supposed to be at war and the government needs to do *something*!

As I look out of my window right now, I see people of all kinds of backgrounds just going about their day, doing their thing. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-04 19:14:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Cool. Wolves are cool.

As long as you don't run into them, I imagine. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-04 19:13:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I liked that it was ambitious and in that sense you can certainly compare the two shows. They are also both often quite odd.

I would love to see even more fresh ambitious shows, so even if I found plenty of things wrong with The OA, I also appreciated for what it was trying to do. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-04 19:11:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The spy stuff is mainly a way for us to get to see the characters navigate a bunch of difficult circumstances. It's essentially a drama disguised as a spy show. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-04 19:08:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I do not remember a single thing about this film.

That's about all I can contribute with. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-04 19:06:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I know I'll be watching, so no need to see any more trailers. But hey, good that they're promoting it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-04 19:02:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> No offence dude, but no thanks.

I hung out with those kind of types when I was very young and they mainly seemed to be people who had never read a book and couldn't tell you the name of a single newspaper. They sure did hate McDonalds though. And private property. Except for their own property of course, that shit was dope and no one should touch it.

I'm left wing politically (a pinko commie I believe is the term), but that doesn't mean I have to sign up for everything the left stands for. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-04 18:58:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I don't think there's any point in denying we do have some problems with regards to immigration in Europe, but why would anyone think the way to solve those problems is to join hate groups and go out on the street and beat people to death? Maybe certain populist politicians does fan the flames, but there already has to be something wrong with someone if they figure this is a "solution".

Or maybe I'm naive and people really are that easily influenced. I don't know. 
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-04 18:53:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Ha ha... Okay, makes sense. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-04 18:53:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I didn't mind it was trippy, not at all, just don't see any vast difference in quality between it and other episodes. For instance, the acting in the well scene is indeed fantastic... but this show consistently have fantastic acting. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-04 18:51:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  The Eleventh Hour isn't a bad jumping on point, but it is made better by watching the previous seasons of New Who. 

I guess it did make it better when I went back and watched from Rose (even read a bit up the history of the show and saw a couple of the old series as well), simply because the universe and the show's longevity is fascinating, but as a jumping on point with no knowledge I felt it worked perfectly.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-04 16:48:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I think I only watched an episode or two of that show, so I can't recall at all. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-04 16:36:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If you haven't already seen it, check out Hannibal. You'll probably like the way it looks. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-04 16:32:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Another fantastic episode.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-04 16:29:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I can't even tell if this is a parody or genuine. 

That's a bad sign. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-04 16:26:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Reading shit like this is just depressing. He had kids for fucks sake... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-04 16:13:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That's in episode ten, I believe.

Another great episode. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-04 16:12:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The intention was to do a show after this film (based on Wizard and Glass), but seeing the extremely negative reception to this trailer, that's probably out the window.

I don't think we'll be getting any more films or shows, sadly. I would have loved to have seen some of the later stuff like Blaine and the rest of Roland's crew, but I especially would have loved that prequel show, which has apparently already been written.

I imagine right now the studio are scrambling to just promote this one film hard enough it'll make a tiny profit and then sell all rights as fast as possible. Probably not what they expected when they released the trailer, but at least the money people who said no to Howard's original extremely ambitious plan are likely happy.

It's weird to me that so many fans say they want a 100% faithful adaptation, despite knowing that would never happen within the studio system (these books are insane), but then at least we get this that should lead to much of that stuff they want, like the Ka-tet which the director said he was looking forward to introducing... and then the fans shit all over it.


Ah well, maybe in a decade or two, someone will try again.
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-04 16:00:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> We really need to see him killing an entire throng of townsfolk all by his lonesome...but I suspect they're going to leave this part of him out.

The scene is in the 2014 draft they are still using as their blueprint. And yes, he kills women and children too. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-04 15:49:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Theroux is excellent at looking confused and perplexed.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-04 15:49:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The kind of people who will click on a spoiler filled post about a season two episode of a show, don't care at all and would likely never watch or enjoy the show anyway. They could just as well go to Wikipedia and spoil themselves there. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-04 15:47:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Makes me think perhaps the OP "acquired" those other episodes, in some way. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-04 12:27:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  Haven't read Firestarter so not sure about that. What's the tie in?

Firestarter is about a little girl with incredible powers and *evil* government (I think?) institutions who're trying to harness her powers and abuse them. There's even a pretend father figure type dude, who's totally not a nice guy.

And yeah, the tracks was an homage to Stand By Me </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-04 11:57:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Just seems like the OP made a mistake.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-04 11:57:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Don't forget the Firestarter inspiration in Stranger Things. And the title credits font. And they're walking along railroad tracks...

I think king himself called it a greatest hits and it's fitting. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-04 11:48:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Love the score, the camera work and just how crazy overwrought and melodramatic it is. Pretty sure there's a shot that's an homage to Dario Argento, which is also amazing and fitting. Derek Jacobi doesn't hold back, which is a lot of fun to watch.

And Robin Williams' little part is great. 

I just love this film in general. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-04 11:36:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I just checked Wikipedia and it says only one episode has aired? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-04 11:35:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Damn!

I thought it was a weekly show. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-04 11:34:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> How come you found this three months old post? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-04 11:19:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I thought only one episode had aired. No idea how I missed the second one. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-04 11:05:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I feel a little alone in that I'm one of the few fans who doesn't think it's better than the rest of the show.

Don't get me wrong, I think it's a terrific hour of TV, just not in any way vastly more interesting, well made or well acted than other episodes.

It only works because of everything that surrounds it, like most good shows.

I wonder if it's because it dives deep into the supernatural that most find it to be in a class of its own? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-04 10:18:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Exactly what I did.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-04 10:18:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That didn't work for me. I of course expected it to be campy... but not *that* campy. I dropped the show for years after that.

After I got into the show I went back and was able to enjoy it, but it really is rough for a newcomer with regards to production values, style, tone and all that. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-04 10:16:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I agree.

But it's different for everyone, so you'll always get different answers. For me season five's first episode The Eleventh Hour was what finally got me into the show. Like the 10th season, it seems kind of designed as a jumping on point. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
