<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject6524</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-09 19:48:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah I had thought there were more than just a few DC games playable with overclocking, that was the only reason I asked. Too bad.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Building my first Pie. I plan on playing a ton of ps1 and dreamcast games. Should I get a heatsink or fan for my pie 3? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-09 14:59:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I have a larger case with better airflow, but plan on binging on this thing hours at a time. I was planning on overclocking it a little bit and am unsure if it will need any sort of cooling. Thanks guys.

edit: thanks for all the helpful advice. Going to skip DC and just grab a cheap heatsink to play it safe. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-09 13:42:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I like it, but I am not in love with the characters like I was in lost. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-09 05:06:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> No, Lizard butts. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-09 02:53:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I havent tried it myself, as I am in research mode rightnow, but from everything I have seen and read, most people seem to agree that the Wii U Pro controller is very good. You may will need [**this**](https://www.amazon.com/Mayflash-Wireless-Wii-Controller-Adapter/dp/B00E6553PW/ref=sr_1_1?ie=UTF8 qid=1494291290 sr=8-1 keywords=wii+u+pro+controller+pc) I believe.

edit: nevermind maybe you dont need what I linked, Im not sure. I just know that Wii U pro is a good controller for retropie.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-09 01:20:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yet 20% of the US is still pissed about Hillary's emails. We are living in pure insanity.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-07 15:36:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> TB is such a better guy than me. If some hypocrite talked shit about me to the entire country, It wouldnt be so easy for me to put my arm around them and smile. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-07 15:35:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> TIL I'd have sex with Katie Couric....possibly even take her out for a nice seafood dinner. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-07 05:50:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> They will never learn about me. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-07 04:11:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> How is it that low wtf </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-07 04:10:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> He has to go back!! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-07 04:01:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Was one of them a HDMI 2.0? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Any sites that let you browse TV torrents by full seasons or complete episodes? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-07 03:48:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Just trying to get a good library going, and its going slowly. Quality isnt a massive deal, 720 and up is fine. Figured it was worth a shot here to ask. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-07 03:38:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Is it possible you need a better HDMI cable for that monitor?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-07 03:33:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> From the looks of that it's impossible to be ergonomic. Careful. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-07 03:32:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Who the hell has been watching me eat? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-07 03:23:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Username checks out </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-07 03:22:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Enhance </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-07 02:53:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I have hated the fonts used in FF ever since 13. Its always looked off to me. Like....too mechanical. I dont know how else to put it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-07 02:49:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I feel like this is the one thing that big business fails to understand. And I know a lot about business because I bought things as recently as 5 minutes ago. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-06 23:32:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah just figured Id let you know as I am currently going through my 3rd month in a row unable to game because I made these mistakes for too long. Sucks. Its a nice little setup you got though and your welcome! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-06 15:08:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You should really switch those monitors positions unless you want to develop chronic neck pain. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-06 13:08:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I feel like turn based combat would have been better for thus game </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-06 12:54:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Get those monitors sides touching each other's or prepare for serious neck and back problems in a year or two. Trust me. Also you should re center them so that you can make sure your keyboard can go directly in the middle.  Move pc if needed.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-06 04:03:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You have gone to space? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-06 03:59:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The Earth needs to survive until February. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-05 15:59:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Viagra should invest in this team. The Patriots find new and innovative ways to make me erect by the week.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-05 03:07:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It was a legal screen. Not his fault your team is soft. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-05 03:07:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Go to the supermarket, find a stranger, do what he did, then see if you get arrested.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-05 02:52:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Stay classy Washington. Cheer and high five the guy who just assaulted someone on the court. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> I wish NBC had basketball so we could hear this again. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-05 02:06:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-04 22:58:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What about Bob? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-04 22:16:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Well now *I'm* the one sketched out! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-04 18:38:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> After I die, I will come back as a ghost to keep reminding them.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-04 17:36:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I forgive them....they probably have never had the joy of bonding with a pet and that makes me feel bad for them. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-04 17:34:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So hard! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-04 15:37:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Awe, thanks guys. [Here](https://streamable.com/ukqqr) is a little clip of Baxter I saved of him enjoying his favorite spot in the backyard (He was mostly blind, so this is about as active as he got, lol). This is how I like to imagine he is spending his time now up in doggy heaven. Thanks for the help with #5, Bax, I miss you so much dude. Thanks to you all as well.

edit: Didnt realize there was audio, if you are sketched out by the random "good boy" I dont blame you, lol </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-04 13:24:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Nah, it implies James white didn't do anything in the reg season, which is crazy untrue. I get the idea though and laughed. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-03 14:54:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Did you though? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-03 05:12:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Well the players looked bitter when they walked off the court that night. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-03 05:11:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> i get this, this is what the comment was referencing! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-03 05:10:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> and he has a huge daddy dick </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-03 05:08:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> UP IN CHHEERRE </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-03 05:08:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> say what </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-03 05:07:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Still bitter from when we ended the streak huh? Damn that was a fun night. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-03 04:59:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> CELTICS IN 2 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-03 04:56:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> IT,because Wall has fallen off since mid 4th </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-03 04:53:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thats me! Holy shit! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-03 04:42:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> And what are you doing there? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-03 04:40:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Neither can I </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-03 04:35:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> disagree with second part, I think WAS fans do too </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-03 04:29:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Zero to hero to zero again...a jae crowder story. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-03 04:24:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Lol omg fans at their arena want foul calls!!! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-03 04:20:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What's unlikeable about al horford? Or jaylen brown? Or the bigger one...Jonas jerebko!? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-03 04:02:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'd literally pay 100 bucks for a series of this </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-03 03:47:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Not happy about the score at the moment but what a fucking game so far </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-03 03:05:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You are probably the best dog I have ever seen at selfies  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-02 22:49:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hence me saying it wasnt quite as touted as Lebron. I wont disagree with the Duncan comparison though. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-02 20:04:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I lost my pup in January and I still have a hard time pooping without getting upset. Now writing this is making me laugh and cry. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-02 17:33:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The only hype you can compare him to was when Lebron was entering the draft. It wasnt QUITE at Lebrons level but I cant think of another player with as high expectations as Bias had at the time. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-01 01:31:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Call more good things like this plz </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-01 01:24:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> For only 25 Nets picks in the next 10 years, this too can be yours </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-01 01:17:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That's why the Colts are one of the few enigmas of the NFL. Lots of people hate them and on top of that they are pretty shitty. I enjoy it.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-01 00:19:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hey coach </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-30 21:59:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> 2 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-30 21:58:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I guess next game if you guys just plan to guard people its an easy win </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-30 21:57:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Bradley has had that fire ever since coming back from injury, imho. Crowder went from zero to hero, though. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-30 20:21:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Fuck the Colts (and I know u don't care but the jets too for safe measure) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Buying a new monitor. Need help deciding if I should make the switch to 4k. Details included. $500-700 budget. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-30 18:08:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> A bit of crosspostception here, but I wanted to word this differently here and hope to get a few more responses =)

[/xpost from r/buildmeapc](https://www.reddit.com/r/buildmeapc/comments/68g1mi/buying_a_new_monitor_need_help_deciding_if_i/)

I plan on using my [asus VE278H 27.0" 1920x1080 Monitor](https://www.amazon.com/ASUS-VE278H-1920x1080-Back-lit-Monitor/dp/B0099XBO5E/ref=sr_1_1?ie=UTF8 qid=1493568575 sr=8-1 keywords=Asus+VE278H+27.0%22+1920x1080+Monitor) which is my current monitor, as my second (assuming its VESA capable of which I have my doubts).

I dont play a lot of fast paced games. Mostly RPGS and strategy games. The Witcher and Mass Effect are about as intensive stuff I play. I play multiplayer games, but not FPS ones (a little overwatch but im not serious about it), so I am not too worried about the things a serious multiplayer gamer would need.

As of now I am thinking my money would be best spent on a top of the line ultrawide or curved 1080 with IPS and 144 hz.

This makes sense rather than getting a 4k monitor that is in my price range, right? The only ones I see that I can afford are 60 hz and standard 27 inches or so (I have been under the impression that 27" for 4k and 60 hz doesn't get as much out of it, let me know If Im wrong.)

I do want to make sure its something I will be ok with using as my main monitor for 4-5 years at least.

As of this moment I would love someone to tell me that a nice, curved ultrawide underneath my old asus would be a solid looking setup. 

 I have a GTX 1070 SC 8GB and a I7 6700 by the way if it matters. 

Thank you for the help. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-30 18:04:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I dunno, I've never even heard of /r/nbastreams before, man </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-30 17:57:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If put into a short zone coverage, and given time to study and prepare, I bet TB would find a way to succeed in it. Im only 20% joking. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Buying a new monitor. Need help deciding if I should make the switch to 4k. Details included. $500-700 budget. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-30 17:37:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I did try r/monitors first, but didnt have much luck [there](https://np.reddit.com/r/Monitors/comments/68a207/can_someone_help_me_choose_the_right_4k_60_hz_to/)

I plan on using my [asus VE278H 27.0" 1920x1080 Monitor](https://pcpartpicker.com/product/nsTmP6/asus-monitor-ve278h) which is my current monitor, as my second (assuming its VESA capable of which I have my doubts).

I dont play a lot of fast paced games. Mostly RPGS and strategy games. The Witcher and Mass Effect are about as intensive stuff I play. I play multiplayer games, but not FPS ones (a little overwatch but im not serious about it), so I am not too worried about the things a serious multiplayer gamer would need. 

As of now I am thinking my money would be best spent on a top of the line ultrawide or curved 1080 with IPS and 144 hz.

This makes sense rather than getting a 4k monitor that is in my price range, right? The only ones I see that I can afford are 60 hz and standard 27 inches or so (I have been under the impression that 27' for 4k doesn't get as much out of it, let me know If Im wrong.

I do want to make sure its something I will be ok with using as my main monitor for 4-5 years at least. 

As of this moment I would love someone to tell me that a nice, curved ultrawide underneath my old asus would be a solid looking setup. Thanks for help. 

edit: Oh and also FYI I have a GTX 1070 SC 8GB and a I7 6700  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Tennessee Titan's new pick Corey Davis has interesting answer about who the best cornerback in the league is. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-30 16:42:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-30 16:28:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> no its /r/nbastreams i think </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-30 14:00:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> R/nbastreams </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-30 13:19:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Know what makes someone cultish to me? Someone who writes an article that says someone is being investigated for something, when it turns out that it was actually 6 years ago, and it wasn't the person themselves being investigated, but a sale in which they were involved.  The article even says itself that she "may still be being investigated"

This person went online, found something from 2011, then decided to play it off like it was new news to get cucks like you to fall for it. Grats, moron. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-30 13:00:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I don't get why you are asking me why I want 4k? Does it matter why? Also my specs are fine.... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Can someone help me choose the right 4k 60 hz to compliment my second monitor. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-29 17:59:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I am putting together a battlestation. Right now, I am using a single [asus VE278H 27.0" 1920x1080 Monitor](https://pcpartpicker.com/product/nsTmP6/asus-monitor-ve278h).

I am going to be buying a nice desk, and I plan on getting mounts for my monitors. 

I play mostly RPGs, so I dont mind 60 hz, which also helps my price range. 

I am open to curved, ultra wide, whatever. Just looking for advice. Even after reading and looking through loads of monitors, I just cant figure out what I should get and the setup I will have with it and my other monitor. 

I have about 500 dollars for a monitor. Could squeeze a little more if persuaded. Thanks for the help.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-29 16:00:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  reading is more nourishing to the brain.

Id love to see your evidence of this, considering that reading is just one of the aspects of playing a video game in its own right. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-29 15:21:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That cant be said of people who are crazy into movies or books as well? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> ELI5: Why are video games, or gamers themselves, viewed in such a negative light by a large portion of society in relation to other mediums? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-29 15:15:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-29 12:39:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Wtf? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-28 20:09:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I like to call the Browns ownership and management of the last decade "bad management". </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-28 20:05:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> As if I needed another fucking reason to hate this guy </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-28 13:06:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Good luck to you all I really hope it works out!!! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-28 13:05:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> We have to go deeper </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> I want to blow up to $1000 on a sick sit/stand desk complete with the works. Has anyone here had success with one they would recommend? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-27 23:29:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-27 16:57:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Can I ask how that is possible when there are like 3 games out for switch right now?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-27 13:24:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Lol? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-27 04:23:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The bulls have a plethora of ugly white dudes </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-27 04:20:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Win or lose this series, I hope people remember that AL Horford showed up in the playoffs for us big time.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-27 04:10:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Seriously why does jae crowder suck now </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-27 04:08:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Sometimes I wish IT wouldn't waste possessions with threes likethat...but I'm a fat 34 year old who sucks at basketball </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-27 03:47:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> He's just not good any more. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-27 03:39:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I feel like crowder sucks donkey tits in the playoffs. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-27 03:37:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Further negative comments!!!!! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-27 03:30:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm starting to get pissed. You know what that means. I will write further negative comments about the referees. Take that, nba. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Do I leave the film on, or what?? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-27 01:29:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-26 23:45:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Shit, I missed the memo from society to stop laughing after childhood! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-26 20:05:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Even funnier the 250 th time in the front page... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-26 17:40:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> so like.....80% of their staff? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-26 17:38:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> When Donald, after death, is told by god that he is an unrepentant sinner and is being sent to hell, I'm fairly certain he will respond to him with "see you in court" as he is dragged downwards into the depths, never to be heard from again.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-26 13:57:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It'd be a shame if that ended up available for us all to stream. A real shame. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-25 19:38:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> At yeast you tried </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-25 16:23:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> We, or atleast I,  desperately need a new "a man can only get so erect" type catchphrase for this sort of thing. It keeps happening so often. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-25 14:42:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> He's been out of his mind for a few years now </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-25 14:41:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> He's a liar tho </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-25 13:17:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If the ff7 remake was turn based it would be #1 for me, but I agree with japan! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-25 13:10:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Lol yes....the only thing the ps1 brought to Chrono Trigger was load times. Just play the snes version. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-25 13:09:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I feel like the last year or two I see more Posts like this. I think a lot of u you kids have just hit a point where you can't appreciate older games, no matter how epic they are. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-24 23:21:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Zombie dogs from the windows in that hallway in resident evil 1. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [WP] in the future, the super rich have achieved immortality for hundreds of years, granting more power than ever. They forgot one thing though, that one hero of the middle class 500 years ago who stole the serum for themselves...you. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-24 14:24:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-24 13:25:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hahahaha hahaha hahahahahaha </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-24 13:24:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Found the guy with the boring family! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-24 12:55:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I want to embrace Abby very badly!! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-24 03:04:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> jizz in my pants basically </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-24 01:20:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> No one's taking thay away roflcopter </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-24 01:16:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> *vigorously creates wood in my pants* </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
