<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject6914</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-08 20:24:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Paper in Nature Human Behavior: https://www.nature.com/articles/s41562-017-0102 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Chipping stone tools uses same neural processing circuits as playing the piano, not areas of language processing </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-08 20:23:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-06 00:48:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I think if you read the article, it becomes clear that black jockeys were denied opportunity during the age of Jim Crow. 

I would guess that these days it is more a factor of the demographics of people who grow up around horses and want to devote their life to horses.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-25 15:23:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The fungus was from Asia.  So we'll need a sea blockade. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> At Final Marijuana Hearing, Lawmakers Contemplate Taxes, Role Of Drug Offenders </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-25 13:42:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-25 13:42:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> They only take 'like new' items.  It's not ideal for getting rid of your old stuff, but they take seriously the idea of making needy kids feel respected and not like they're getting any old crap. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-25 13:39:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What makes it clear that this is security theater is that it does not offer any reasonable security.  Say I'm a bomber determined to disrupt the T.  All I have to do is get on the Green Line, where it is impossible to create a security checkpoint without it being visible blocks away.  Then I ride downtown and take my choice of stops to explode. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-25 13:15:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Of the estimated four billion American chestnut trees that once grew from Maine to Georgia, only a remnant survive today. The species was nearly wiped out by chestnut blight, a devastating disease caused by the exotic fungal pathogen Cryphonectria parasitica. This fungus was accidentally introduced into the United States over a century ago as people began to import Asian species of chestnut. It reduced the American chestnut from the dominant canopy species in the eastern forests to little more than a rare shrub. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> TIL that almost all 4 billion American Chestnut trees were killed, and most of the remaining ones turned into shrubs, by an imported fungus </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-25 13:15:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-13 13:59:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I always thought a Tale of Two Cities was really only about Paris. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-07 15:58:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Not ALL Trump-supporting trolls are working for Russia, AFAIK. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-07 13:38:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> tl;dr: the folks from /r/The_Donald are trolling France now in /r/Le_Pen  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Making Europe Great Again, Trumps online supporters shift attention to the French election </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-07 13:35:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
