<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject8135</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Baby on Board </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-10 13:37:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-07 00:58:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Old </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-28 12:59:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I dunno man, it worked just fine on my Xbox here in the US!!  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Felt kinda strange giving this 5 stars. Wow </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-28 05:37:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The amount of dead caterpillars on this tree </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-25 22:40:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-25 02:23:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The itsy bitsy spider had a good day I'm guessing.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-06 23:57:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Ya oops </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-06 19:50:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Oh wow, I've been here for most of my life. I don't think I could leave! But that's cool, I hear Seattle has actual seasons!

Out of curiosity, how's the housing market compare up there?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-06 19:43:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That's awesome, it's a good place to live!!

Yes, saved as much as I could. My hobby/passion is in my vehicles. So honestly that was my first priority 2 years ago when I bought my nice one. The other is a daily purchased for less than a paycheck. I personally don't see anything wrong with financing a vehicle.

It's not that I've "arrived" either... I'm obviously not a millionaire. But I damn sure am proud of myself given that I didn't go to a formal college. Also, not so easy in the sub $100k budget. I've been putting offers on houses since last June, 95% of them get snatched up by investors before they would even look at my contract. I'm just excited man. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-06 16:29:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> D E V I S T A T E D 

E

V

I

S

T

A

T

E

D </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-30 13:47:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Back when I was about 6 or 7, my mom and I had gone to Target to get some things while in town to visit my grandmother. Being that age, my natural tendency was to wander off and do my own thing. 

I happened to find a grasshopper that had wandered into the swinging automatic door area, so I crouched down (crawling on my hands and knees) to chase it. 

I was completely unaware of my surroundings, and someone was coming through the doors right next to me. The sensors automatically flung the doors open and the left side door wedged itself up on top of the three largest fingers on my left hand. 

Here's where the stranger comes into play. As I lay there on the floor of Target, screaming and bleeding out of my hand, a woman came through the now open door. She was very pretty, red hair with pale skin and wearing a nice scarf. She was the one who set off the automatic door sensors. She stared down at me like I was some disgusting, wretched animal that needed to be put down. 

I'll never forget the look on her face as she scoffed and kept walking past me without saying a word. 

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> He Killed it Y'all </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-26 16:17:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Florida man is upset at someone who speeds past his house regularly. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-22 00:52:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-18 06:16:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Not modded, just shot out the rear suspension and scooted a crate into the bed for added sag lol.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-18 06:15:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's actually just a normal Sandking with wheels on Xbox with the rear suspension shot out. 

You have to not have bulletproof tires, shoot the center or the wheel on each side 16-18 times with a marksman rifle to get it to drop.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-16 21:15:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> While this is true and while it is true....

Aria Alexander attracts actual autism. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-15 18:42:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah, but mathematics is plural. So it's definitely 3. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-12 07:31:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Just driving around the map bro. I never thought they were that rare tbh  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
