<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject5968</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-17 05:10:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> can confirm now that Grabacr shoots Bartlett and Pops.

I started hauling ass away from Schwarze and inadvertently found myself on the southeastern edge of the map where Bernitz was firing at both the MiG and Tomcat. 

I locked the Sukhoi up with an MPBM and fired. 

I got the "Hold Fire" message as I watched all three of them disappear. 

Guess I fouled up the canonical sequence, because I (Cipher) definitely smoked all three of those guys at once. 
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> WHERE THE F*** IS SCHAUER </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-14 03:51:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm trying to 100% AC0 again and I cannot, for the life of me, get Schauer to appear during "Inferno" 

What am I doing wrong here?? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-13 21:06:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm aware this is several years old, but here's some food for thought about the Raptor.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-13 20:07:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You've clearly not been in the military, at least the US military. 

We love, in order:

The A-10 because brrt

The AK because it doesn't have to be cleaned

Dip

Rip-It's
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-13 20:04:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> please, God, let it be this. 


http://vignette2.wikia.nocookie.net/acecombat/images/9/92/Scarface_KF-C7.jpg/revision/latest?cb=20110416143715 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-13 19:57:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Personally I think we'll find out that Nagase was the result of a cloning project, thus all the inexplicable appearances of her around the strangereal world.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-13 19:51:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> this.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-13 19:43:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> man where does one even FIND these?! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Zero: Hrtbrk One, Huckebein, Battle Axe </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-13 19:35:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Curious as to whether or not anyone has ever managed to capture in-game footage of Bartlett getting hit over B7R during the hairball. 

I've definitely seen him in amongst the allied units, but have always been to busy to focus on him for more than a few seconds. It'd be neat if B/N actually took the time to depict him getting hit during the battle. 

Obviously Buchner is Cipher's kill (along with Schwarze) so I've definitely watched that one go down. 

Post a link or description if you've ever watched Bartlett get shot! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Salvia 60x report </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-10 18:36:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This is an almost instant report of what salvia 60x did to me.
Everything I type is as I remember it. 

I'm currently coming back from wherever this stuff took me.


I made a trip nest in the bathroom (blankets and pillows piled up in the bathtub),  turned on some calm electronic music, closed the curtain on the bathtub, scorched the bowl, took a single hit and held it for 30 seconds. 

I then became the parking lot of a small convenience store. 


I was aware that I was also a set of curtains on a window looking UP at the parking lot. 


I wanted to get up but the person (not actually there) in the room with me would not give me permission to get up.
I tried two more times to get up at which point I became aware that the person had put pokey sticks in the curtains with me and they were poking me.
Like wood chips or splinters.



I became aware that the curtains were wrapped around me but I was not actually the curtains.

I started to focus more on the parking lot and in doing so realized that someone had put me in a shopping basket and was spinning in circles. 

I realized that I needed to close my eyes, and as I did I put my knees on the side of the tub, the coolness of the tub against my skin became fire-y heat. It dawned on me that I was touching the sides of the shopping basket and that I was trying to hold on and should stop. 

I kept thinking to myself "I'm not allowed to be here. Someone is here with me." over and over and over again.

I had this overwhelming feeling that I was not allowed to be seeing what I was seeing. I did not have permission. 

At that point I started falling UP through the parking lot the curtains and eventually clawed my way back up into my bathtub where I had accidentally kicked the faucet that was now dripping onto my shoes and blanket. 



I said, out loud, "The person here with me will not like this. This is not good." 

At this point I realized that my tongue had a brass weight on top of it.

I was still being poked so I took my sweatshirt off and put it in a drawer. 

I then laid down in my bed with a pillow over my face. 

I pulled the blankets up on top of me at which point I realized that there wasn't actually anything touching me. If I closed my eyes, it became very easy to comprehend that if I couldn't see what was on me, it probably wasn't there at all. 

I had the feeling of someone getting up off of me, a weight being lifted, and I came back. 

The weight on my tongue is gone, and I am sure I am the only one in the house again. 

Thanks for tuning in.

whew.

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-04 22:53:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> we're all dying anyway </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-04 22:52:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> there it is. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-04 09:28:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Oh and I guess I should mention that I felt like everything was about two and a half feet further away from me than it should have been. 
Reaching for things was sort of a task because I'd realize I hadn't reached far enough.
Also, my near vision went absolutely for shit, so I'd be laying on the floor looking at my hands and only seeing blurs. I have 20/20 vision so that was a big "huh..." thing for me. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> slamming IV benadryl </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-04 08:31:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Maybe I'm just stupid and inexperienced but I recently got hold of some 50mg vials of IV DPH (high potency) and slammed 300mg in about 4 seconds by injecting it.
I never had the "shadow men" or bugs experience some people have had, never conversed with anyone who wasn't there, and never felt any impending doom.
More than anything, I felt immediately intoxicated; the same feeling I get when I've been drinking a lot, but this time it hit me instantaneously. 
I also felt like someone had nailed me to the floor. So getting up and walking around was really fun because I felt like I was fighting gravity to even move. 
I wouldn't even call it a "trip" just more like being wicked drunk in a record amount of time...that, or maybe like having sustained a head injury or something. I don't know.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-04 08:27:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> See, I've done IV benadryl in 50mg/ml doses up to like 350mg (so 6 vials) and all that ever happened is this:
 it made my skin get real blotchy, my pupils get huuuuge, I had to pee every 10 minutes, if I sat down I felt like I was nailed to the floor, and anytime I went to reach for something I realized that my reach wasn't long enough. I felt like everything was about two feet farther away from me than it should have been.
I've never had any physiological issues (stomach cramps, nausea) etc from it and honestly it's more like getting wasted in freaking record time than anything else.
Also never seen any shadow men. But I always did it with the lights on.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-27 00:31:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm a vampire so I drink blood.
Working in EMS is like winning the lottery every day.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-27 00:29:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> was working in a smallish, yet unreasonably busy city as far as 911 system traffic goes. 
Hear the PD radio channel start to buzz about a traffic pursuit that morphed pretty quickly into a foot pursuit when the perp ditched his car on an overpass.
After we heard them exiting their vehicles to go on foot after the guy, my partner and I sort of stopped paying attention.
What we didn't know, though, was that homeboy ditched his car over top of the railroad switching yard and had jumped from the overpass onto a moving set of freight cars. 
Apparently it wasn't like the movies though and he didn't stick the landing; ended up rolling off the side of the car, whereupon his legs got caught under the wheels and so subsequently his left leg was amputated mid thigh. 
Call goes to us since we're sitting point like three miles away from the train yard. 
So we get there and homeboy is still alive so we load and are getting ready to go when my partner is like "shit we need the leg."
I hop out and head back to the car this dude got caught under and sort of squish the leg out from between the wheels. Just kinda grabbed it by the ankle and slung it over my shoulder and headed back to the truck. 
The whole time I'm walking back to the rig, I can feel something smacking me in the center of my back, but I've got to get back fast so we can boogie to the nearest level 1. 
We transfer care, and are cleaning up the truck when my partner spins me around and says, "oh man, we've got to go back to central and let you change. Your shirt is disgusting."
Turns out that slapping feeling in the center of my back was the guy's femoral artery hanging out of the end of the stump; a bloody, gooey, severed garden hose of vasculature just bobbing along back there as I moseyed back to our poor, failed attempted-stuntman criminal patient.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-12 18:07:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> optimistic Canadians trying to play pond hockey on a lake that isn't even frozen yet.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The Ringing in My Ears </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-12 04:25:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I remember clearly the first time I went to the doctor for a general health checkup. If memory serves me correctly, I was approximately five years old. There was a vision screening, shots, blood-work, the usual stuff. What I remember most clearly, though, was the hearing exam. You know, the one where you put on the uncomfortable headphones that put pressure on your ears in all the wrong places and then listen to the almost un-hearable little chimes and tones that test your ears sensitivity and hearing quality? 

The box was stuffy; in fact Ive never been in one of those little sound-proof cubicles that wasnt stuffy and oppressive. Ive always felt like I was in trouble when having to sit in one of those cramped boxes. I remember feeling small and alone, probably for the first time really in my life. So much of childhood is spent under someones watchful eye or with a hand grasped firmly by someone much older and more responsible, and now here I was, for all I knew, locked, alone, in a box that felt as though it didnt like me being there. I was uncomfortable, to say the least. 

A mans voice first told me in a rather flat tone that Id be taking a hearing exam and to push the button whenever I heard something. I pushed the button. Being that I was a rather literal kid, I did as I was told: I heard him talking and I pushed the button. Im sure that pissed off some tech analyzing my readings somewhere else in the lab complex, but I had no idea what the rules were. The recording abruptly cut off and a new, flatter toned voice informed me that I was pushing the button when no tones were available and to please be sure I heard something before I pushed it again. Medical-ese for Hey, quit fucking doing that, youre messing it up. 

Then the tones started. Shrill, subdued, tinkling, silvery, deep, whispery, they played through both ears. I remember feeling intensely concentrated on hearing even the slightest little pitch. And then it happened. My ears began to ring. I could still hear the sounds of the test, but, in the background, an incessant, singular tone had begun to pervade the previous silence of my young ears. Through the tone, I could hear my pulse. My jaw began to ache and my eyes welled up with tears. The air in the booth felt hotter, stuffier, and more malevolent than ever. I wanted to get out. I pushed the button five more times before the flat-voiced man told me the test was complete and that I could exit the booth and receive my scores from the attending technician. 

Since that day, the ringing in my head has never stopped. In the dead of night, when my wife is snoring peacefully and I am, again, sleepless, that singular tone pervades the silence. Sometimes it is just a whisper; I wave it away and it disappears into the machinery that chugs along in my brain. Other times it is a freight train barreling through my skull, and I wonder where it is going. My pulse thunders in my ears and I am convinced the train is steaming by at full speed. I often dont hear it again for extended amounts of time. 

But some nights, I wonder what they buzzed into my ears that day in the little hateful box. I fear that Ill hear the train stop, the wheels grinding on rails that wend through my skull, and a little man with a flat voice will tell me, The test is now complete. Goodbye. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-12 03:11:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> nailed it.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-15 22:55:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> He's sort of the embodiment of what evil does in cold, dark places. 
Look up the "FiftyFootAnt" stories, you'll see more about him there.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-31 03:29:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Tandy.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-31 03:28:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Tandy doesn't differentiate. He just goes where there's evil afoot. And everyone suffers for it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-31 03:26:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Congrats, your friend met Tandy.

If you don't know who Tandy is, you need to get educated.

Tandy's what happens in the cold and dark, when you let the winter in. 

Run. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-21 04:11:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Erusea. Who doesn't secretly want to be a Yellow? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-21 04:08:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> See, I've always thought that 13's two lines of solo dialogue were what summed him up and characterized him best:

"Eject, Yellow 4."
"Did anyone see 4 get out?"

There's never any machissmo "let's kill em all", or, "this will be a fight to the death" crap from 13. He's just a flight lead who does his job and looks out for his squad mates. 

Those two lines of dialogue he has prove that, even in the midst of a chaotic aerial gang-bang, led by Mobius 1 and the rest of the victorious ISAF fighters, 13 only had eyes for 4 and her plight. 

What a leader, am I right? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-21 03:57:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm personally a fan of the MiG-28. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
