<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject8925</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2011-03-14 03:10:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Well, there was a girl named Agatha who was more fucked up than I was. Drug addict, prostitute, abusive mother, etc. Then there was a couple named Fishe   Ari. They were...actually sort of boring. I honestly think they were created just because I was lonely and scared, nothing more than that. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2011-03-13 21:00:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I've always thought that was clever of my psychosis, a real excellent way to protect itself from logical outsiders.

I mentioned this just now in another comment thread: I found out my senior year of high school, years after I had seen any of them last. Talking about it with my therapist quickly unraveled them. It shook me up real badly for the better part of a year. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2011-03-13 20:46:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This is the point of an AMA, isn't it? No, thankfully, since the original three people I haven't had any other imaginary friends (so to speak). </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2011-03-13 20:43:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> My mother has really kept our family together. She's a strong lady who doesn't take much bullshit. She issued an ultimatum to my dad when I was six - he could either get help, or he was out of the family. He's been sober and medicated ever since. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2011-03-13 20:42:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I don't feel like my polisci classes focus on the dark things, even if it did I probably wouldn't mind. I'm inherently dark. 

I'm reading every post, don't even worry. I'm sorry that current events make you depressed, but right on figuring out the source. That's totally half the battle. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2011-03-13 20:37:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I mentioned something like this earlier: I was on sertraline and seroquil every day for four months, stopped taking them because they didn't seem to work very well. They just sort of made me sleepy and lethargic. I don't trust myself to self-medicate, I don't know what'll trigger a psychotic break and the risk is too high for me.

I think of my crazy as a genetic thing - my dad's pretty crazy, which is great cause he understands me. I wasn't raised in a wholly chaotic household, both my parents loved me very much, I wasn't subjected to any sort of religious indoctrination... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2011-03-13 20:35:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What do you mean - like, their suicidal urges could be triggered by certain... academic courses?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2011-03-13 20:34:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Tell someone you trust implicitly and ask them to take you to the mental health clinic. I actually did that with my friend (the one whose place I'm at), sat with him in the waiting room while he filled out intake forms. It's really hard admitting you need help, having someone you trust to not judge you is incredibly helpful. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2011-03-13 20:31:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I only found out that they were hallucinations when I was in my senior year of high school. I hadn't seen them in a while and started discussing them with my therapist, they slowly fell apart to me. It was an extremely difficult realization.

I'm very distrustful of new people and new situations, I try and have someone I know is real - my brother, or an old friend - meet new people I like, just in case. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2011-03-13 12:45:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> My dad has more depressive episodes than manic episodes. It's upsetting sometimes, but he knows what he's doing to keep himself sane. He's in a far better place than where he was twelve years ago. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2011-03-13 12:30:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's my father, really. My dad's bipolar, he was on 800mg of lithium for several years when I was a child. Whenever my mother knows that I'm having an episode, she hardly handles it well. When my dad knows I'm not doing so well, he handles it excellently: he has concern, but is able to treat me like a human being capable of making my own decisions. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
