<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject792</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-10 15:09:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> There's something about how slick this whole scene is, even minus the 'matrixness' of it.


 The editing is spot on, just the right amount of cuts, the framing, and the camera is always in the perfect spot. You can see everything thats happening (something that bugs the hell out of me in other films) and its paced really nicely. 

Yes its not the longest or most intricate of duels, but its so silky smooth. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Imo one of the best 'fight scenes' in a movie ever. The Dojo scene from 'The Matrix' </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-10 15:05:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-10 14:47:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> you wouldn't change superman into a woman, so...... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-08 19:52:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> yeah it def couldve been better, but its still a pretty good popcorn movie. I mean, its dragons, its gonna be silly. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-08 19:45:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Did you put this as a spoiler to tie in with the post apocalyptic theories surrounding GoT's? Cuz, cool.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-08 19:42:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm glad this was posted as so many people seem to be unaware of it. I loved this film and will always watch it when its on. Didn't realise it was 'panned' on release tho! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-08 18:35:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> well, thats made my mind up. I'm sticking to my good ol fashioned asbestos mattress.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-07 14:39:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> we've had a fair few go our way yeah, but the majority against. Even simple off side calls seem to be astruggle in the championship. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-07 14:38:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> true that, you wouldn't think there would be such a drop in standard of refereeing going down one league, but its been terrible all season. And not just for us. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-06 18:19:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> i seem to remember them trying this a lot, and not always being so successful... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-06 16:01:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> can i get one without it looking like hes soiled himself </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-05 21:20:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Nice trailer, but i really only needed the cast list to make me want to see this.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-05 21:18:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It could be this generations Saving Private Ryan. 

That film changed a lot and became a staple film for schools in educating the youth on the horrors of war. Popular culture has changed a helluva lot since SPR first came out, so it will need some kick to it. Killing harry stles might just do it tho. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-04 23:21:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> part of me thinking, oh god its gonna be as bad as all the horrific marvel spin off stuff. Part of me thinking, fuck yeah. 

Even a bad job on half of the 'back stories' we already know about will be worth watching. 
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-01 20:59:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> whoa. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-30 12:06:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Essentially all he did was copy myspace tho right? It wasn't until it copied all the things myspace already had that it really took off.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-30 00:40:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> genuinely awesome fight for once! Fair play to klitschko and he'll be gutted he didnt end it after making Joshua 2 inchs shorter in the 6th(?) 


But F**K! AJ is a beast after taking that hit, somehow staying in it with enough left in the tank to go for the knockout, which he needed. Great fight! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-29 18:52:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> everyones hoping these rich kids come back with a different take on the struggles faced by millions of impoverished, but really they will just come back wanting to invest in subway.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-28 23:43:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> this brings back the feels of Echo the dolphin on the megadrive. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-26 18:43:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> shouldve been banned a long time ago. Absolute filth. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-25 20:18:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> absolutely perfect line to finish with 

9/10 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-22 18:00:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Apart from making me feel old, i've often thought about how crazy and 'far away' the 80's seemed when i was younger. But rn 10-15 years ago doesn't seem that different to what we have now.


 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-22 17:48:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> can't wait to see the sand picture of this </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-22 17:35:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [Yh Tom's already filmed some stunts for 6] (http://i.imgur.com/jE68kCh.gifv) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-22 12:54:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So do only humans see magenta? Can we ever know? Cuz people say like dogs only see this and cows see that, but how the hell do we know what they are actually consciously seeing? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-22 12:47:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> that we know of! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-22 12:45:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> i've often wondered about this. Using gravity and water, say you had a big drop from the top reservoir to the bottom and had multiple turbines all the way down, would that create enough electricity to power the pump to get it back to the top reservoir?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-22 12:16:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> leave tom cruise alone! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-18 22:35:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> not got the legs to last another 30 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-18 22:29:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> hummels is  a beast.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-18 22:24:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> ref really really wants to make it home tonight </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-18 22:23:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> ref is far too concerned with getting out of the stadium alive </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-18 22:18:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> ha. get rekt
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-18 22:17:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> doesn't change much, bayern still need to score </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-18 22:02:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> robben will win this game unless they change things asap </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-18 21:55:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> madrid bayern game has just caught alight if anyones interested </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-18 21:12:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> sorry to keep on but does anyone have  a good stream? everything is freezing or cutting out entirely! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-17 17:17:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> u ever been to a match at a stadium?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-17 14:56:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> holy fuck a flare? What did everyone do? i hope they all survived </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-17 14:55:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yh the guy doesn't look like he cares, but chances are hes worked that gate for ages and knows them all by face anyway.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-17 12:13:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> First i thought some kind of bin lifting device but they look sturdy enough to be some kind of clamp, parking control. Maybe for towing motorbikes? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-17 12:05:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> the only reason i havent bought the switch and BOTW is cuz its getting on to summer and i know it will eat my spare time up! Will make a good christmas present tho.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Easter Egg hunt turns to chaos when man mistakes dog poo bag for chocolate. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-17 09:51:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-16 19:11:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> to be fair, they're more like the LMFAO of EDM. They can make their own 'interesting' stuff, but have deciced to just make stuff that sales instead. Which is basically a microcosm of what Aoki and Dimmak have done anyway. 


People like Calvin Harris have done the same, he just has solid back catalog to go with. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-16 15:49:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Troy McClure got arrested for less </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-16 09:53:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Toadie's having a rough time of late </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-15 18:47:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> ha, who wouldve thought r/soccer is out of touch with the fans on the terraces. Why is anyone getting touchy over this? its the sun, who gives a fuck.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-14 21:07:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> seemed unnecessary, i don't see why they would treat this drug differently to all the others they've done. Which they did in a relaxed fun way, but were still analytical throughout. This was a step away from that.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-14 21:02:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> adding mysticism to it doesn't help the situation tho surely?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-14 20:31:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> really? i hated it. The whole reason i watch these is because they are pretty scientific about things. Wtf was all the bs about? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-14 20:09:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> yh re-watching it looks like this. Looks great </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-14 20:04:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> smoke screen to hide things n stuff?
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-14 20:01:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> was hoping rey would have a staff of some sort </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-14 19:57:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> admittedly haven't played every star wars game, any idea what those speeder type things are doing with the red smoke? simple as a smoke screen? that battle will be visually spectacular! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-14 19:53:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> eeek. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-14 18:00:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> would you say this could work on small mammals? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-14 17:54:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> this is entertaining n all, but i would bet your house on it being fake </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-14 17:53:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> the mad man! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-10 20:59:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> i think hes ok, he made it under the table pretty quick </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-10 18:41:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> thor meets guardians equals cool. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-10 18:36:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> he wasnt even the band kinda asian
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Recently, whats that one song you wish made it to a 'mainstream' audience? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-07 21:10:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> For me, it grates on me that Zibra were never given enough airplay (uk). They recently disbanded before really 'making it' leaving behind a bunch of awesome songs including some awesome re versions of 90's tunes like alice deejay and Tomcraft. And original stuff like this [Great White Shark] (https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=9tNGgXfpraA)  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> With news that London is bringing in a 'toxicity charge' with aims to be a diesel free city by 2025. I give u the disgusting irony of a hugely successful Honda tv ad </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-05 18:25:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-05 08:15:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> so you're saying buying an electric car won't make much difference afterall? fuck.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-04 23:37:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> pretty sure 90% of this thread is spotify corp trying to push their premium service. 

And no thanks. I wish to own my music and at a decent quality to boot </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-04 23:33:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This sorta thing will push people back towards music blogs n such, pretty shit move on their part.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-04 21:27:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> well theres a certain body guard that never leaves her side that may stop this, i like the premise tho.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-04 19:54:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Brazilian Rick n Morty sounds fun </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-04 19:05:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> ha, he seems legit. Glad he's not gonna try and bullshit a reason to cover plot holes. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-03 23:27:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> literally the only good thing about that episode was carl going John Wick. But it counted for nothing and was stupidly implauisble anyway.... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-03 23:26:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> yep, and its getting worse </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-03 23:19:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> mystery still remains why she went for a guy stood doing nothing rather than batman </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-03 21:23:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> seriously tho, pretty much everyone that used this wants it 
permanent. Why stop? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-03 19:07:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> youd be mad not to keep this a sub </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-03 18:43:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> exactly, the warzones are the art. The thing as a whole not the individual pixels. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-02 23:30:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> we should get soemthing on r/place before the kneelers </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-02 23:10:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> yeah, thats what i mean, r/place is a warzone. When something global happens only then people will unite in one way or another. 


Its funny cuz as i understand it, this sub didn't tell people to join with their factions or subs, quite a social experiment they got here. This really is a microsm of humanity!

 Soon enough people will 'figure out' that their number of active users equals space on the board. That means land grabs, alliances, broken alliances... and then global events irl that will unite people for a day or two before the war continues.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-02 21:31:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Love it. This sub will be awesome.

 A microcosm of reddit itself, an absolute warzone until something global happens that unites everyone. For a day or two at least.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Can we get something onto r/place ? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-02 12:49:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Suggestions?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-01 22:23:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> think we've just found snoke </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-01 22:05:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> faker than your mums tits </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-30 20:54:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> dude... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-30 20:53:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Wish they got colin furze onboard with top gear earlier and had him part of the reg presenters. The guys a madman.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-30 20:48:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Literally the only thing of interest was Dany being at Dragonstane, which when i think about it is kinda obvious and maybe even said about last season? 


Though the whole thing was like a bad panto lineup or an ad for the next episode of eastenders... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> As seen on facebook, not sure where on reddit it belongs, but, well.... </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-30 20:46:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-30 20:34:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> ABSOLUTE PANTO


Thought this was awful. Altho, previous seasons expectations were high, so probs better to start off by lowering them this time round </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-28 20:07:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The only reason i will see this film is to answer the question, do we really need another spiderman movie? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-27 21:21:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> wait, why is this?

He's done way better shots, with way better crowds and way better gifs to show it all. 

What is this potato? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-27 18:41:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> all those other shows are terrible! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-26 21:25:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I thought all the films and tv stuff were a joint effort as such, between Fox and Marvel? I know disney basically own marvel now, so i guess theres some conflict there? Seems needlessly complicated.... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-26 21:18:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> eh?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-26 17:19:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This is one of those 'surely can't we just replicate what it is' kinda things.

So, surely, can't we just replicate what it is that makes it work? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-26 17:16:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Find a robot woman with a vagina and a brain that are kept in seperate boxes </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-26 14:46:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> There could be so many awesome twists, but usually its the dullest most obvious one thats true. So i'm just gonna go with the confirmation that professor x is his dad.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-26 14:36:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Professor X could easily show up in the final episode. The timescale thing is interesting and something that has been talked about. I'm guessing its to fit in with the new x men movies timeframe.

 But i'm not sure you can base any timeframe on what people are wearing etc,most of those things are about personality traits more than anything. Altho my personal theory is because most of the characters are different parts of Davids split personality. 

I agree there are and always will be plot holes, as always with the x-men universe. The alternate reality idea is def possible, as its done alot in the comics, but things would get very messy if they went down that route.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-26 14:11:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Bad case of boneitis. Probs better with the [sound] (https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=B3uk5bJcyM8) tbh.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> All i could think of when Lenny has her way with The Eye </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-26 14:10:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-25 21:05:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> where were you sat to get that view? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-25 21:03:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> ha this should be at the top. Exactly sort of little thing thats pointless, doesn't even come under politeness. You don't say 'bless you' when i fart or hiccup or take a shit on your mums front lawn. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-25 21:01:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This isn't exactly a social custom? unless you mean you wish you didn't have to concentrate on driving? Which i agree with. Driving is very easy, i can do a variety of things whilst driving and still be completely safe and get to where i'm going as fast as i can. Its not doing other things that cause accidents. Only IF those things make you worse at driving, if ya get me. 
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-25 18:00:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> From what i read online, one of the biggest complaints about Batman vs superman was how dark everything on screen looked. 

And, well, hmm... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-25 14:27:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Wow, just watched this last night, truly great film on its own merits, and a great addition to the x men world. So many great little bits about getting old in there, crazy how a 'blockbuster' mutant action film can be really touching at the same time, they pulled it off tho.


Loved the line at the end "don't be what they made you to be" line, but is that from a previous film? Reminded me of the "don't let it control "you line from the professor.


 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-23 23:23:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Only prediction would be that 'the eye' comes back in some way. As i would be amazed if thats how its left with him, whats his deal etc. 

Not sure if he will become one of Davids personalities tho, only cuz from a TV show pov, his character didn't really have much of one?... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-23 23:17:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Well she is the shadow KING. So maybe the HMS is just a little playing around? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Razorlight - Who Needs Love [Indie/Pop] </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-23 20:47:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-23 18:55:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Please, Americans, why is James Corden on TV? I mean, i'm glad he's not on our screens much anymore, but do you guys like him? Why do you tolerate his utter shittiness. 


I really hope you don't assume all of our tv hosts/personalities/people are like him in any way. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-22 18:29:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> at least one person must be live streaming from the london eye. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-22 07:59:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Guessing this dudes lost? maybe got on the road and kept on going? Either way, you should probs eat him. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-21 18:59:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Star stories at its best.

 I put this up the other day, but people somehow thought this 'documentary' was real .... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Being Tom Cruise. How Scientology isn't mental in any way.... (satire) (do i really need to put satire?) (yes.) </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-21 18:58:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-20 21:09:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> just the other day i had a long (semi drunk) argument with someone who thought people shoot upwards when they open their parachute. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-18 19:11:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Would love more of the matrix universe, exploring all the themes the original trilogy did. But prequels, i'm not so sure of. A young morpheus would be one hell of a badass, but knowing where its heading would take so much away from the/his story.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-18 09:01:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Well, bristol has a 'healthy' drugs culture to go with its nightlife. And a big ol river running through the city, so, dunno. 


I immediately suspect the op tho, this post is a classic serial killer brag......  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-18 08:53:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> From a distance (Uk) it seems the press are constantly playing games with him and vice versa. They must know he won't like being harassed into doing something, even something like a handshake with another leader (which he had already done). Merkels actions are interesting enough here tho as she kinda plays along with the press.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-17 21:10:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Real mystery is why the he would just start spraying bullets anyway.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
