<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject7051</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-08 20:06:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> My 14 year old says the fourth is his favorite. On a completely unrelated note, I have a child for sale.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-04 15:08:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Me too! Me too! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-02 03:17:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I hope yours does as well! If you need to talk to someone, you can always drop me a line!  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-02 03:13:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> No worries! We all have our days. It was a very Monday Monday for me, if you catch my drift. No hard feelings at all.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-02 03:10:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Ugh. I feel ya there. I'm working full time and taking University courses to complete my BSc. Just wrote a huge final last week. I hope your semester perks up!  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-02 03:08:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I am well! Thank-you for asking! And you? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-02 03:01:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thank-you for your service  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-02 02:58:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Got the "joke".  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-02 02:57:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> whoosh yourself.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-02 02:11:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> And the appropriate word for a line separating two political or geographical areas, especially countries. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-02 01:28:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Borders.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-25 11:59:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> My son read it for Grade 8 this year. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-25 06:47:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Walk-in clinics see you same day. Regular doctor maybe a few days. Specialists take longer, maybe a few months unless it's urgent then it's much faster. Source: Canadian.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-22 18:40:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Those pants have GOT to go.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-16 17:35:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I primarily write in cursive as well (I'm a leftie). It's legible to me, at least. I just wrote a lot of notes so printing is too slow.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-16 17:34:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Sounds like you write with what is called "the hook". Common among lefties. I grew up in a strange household where everyone was a leftie but my Dad. My mom taught me at a young age to just tilt my paper so I wouldn't have to write with "the hook" technique.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-16 01:03:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It was! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-15 22:57:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> My doctor actually recommended it to me recently as an informal treatment for my clinical depression. It's really a great movie (Inside Out, that is). </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-15 16:37:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Coven is by far my favorite.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-10 22:16:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This was my thinking.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-07 02:29:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm 40. Cystic acne is fun  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-07 01:44:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> EVEN BETTER! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-05 22:55:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Well he IS an angel, after all.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-03 16:16:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I feel the same way. I feel like my work keeps me sane but my home and personal life are a disaster. If you need to talk, PM me! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-23 13:11:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> A reserve is a resource that is economically feasible. The two words are not synonymous. The point I am making is that oil and gas are running out and without economically viable renewables, i.e. Cheaper than coal, the tendency will be to go back to relying on coal for energy. I'm not saying it's right, I personally think it's an environmentally irresponsible thing to do, but if it's cheaper than renewables, that's where we'll see the industry swing.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-22 19:03:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Current reserves are put at 1000 billion barrels. Currently consumption is 31 billion barrels per year. While new technologies are continually transforming resource petroleum into reserve petroleum, it doesn't take a genius to figure out that our petroleum reserves will be depleted in the next 50 years. Coal reserves, however, are estimated to last over 200 years. 

edit: These are 2009 numbers, 2016 projections are 1700 billion barrels of oil and consumption has risen to 35 billion barrels a year. That puts world reserves as lasting 48.57 years.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-22 14:21:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Biggest problem is that coal has more reserves than petroleum and natural gas. As petroleum and natural gas run out, if there are no economically viable ways to completely shift to renewables, there will be shift back to coal.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-14 16:36:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> As a Canadian (Alberta), I completely sympathize. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-13 03:27:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> We had ducks beheaded, apparently it's the MO of Owls. Sure enough, trapped an owl in our barn a few weeks later. Not sure if you have owls where you are, though. 

Edit: Apparently you do have owls.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-12 19:51:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That brindle reminds me so much of my girl, Brody, whom we had to put down in October. Beautiful pup.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-10 23:20:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yes. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-10 06:05:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> 50/50 WAS AMAZING! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-09 15:50:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> God, what? Those clamping forceps things? My rather elderly, male, gynecologist uses a speculum so he can see and off he goes. That's it.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-09 15:03:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Little pinch and it's in. I found it not much more painful than a Pap smear. I'm on my third IUD, not altogether pleasant, but seriously not that bad.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-07 15:02:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I think this?

https://youtu.be/G4Sn91t1V4g </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-04 21:37:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> NicER you mean (I love the tattoo, by the way). </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-04 21:19:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That's a nice arm.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-28 02:02:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> They appear to be Ameraucana Chickens.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-21 04:43:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I have two boys and regularly remind my husband that it was his stupid chromosome not mine that got us here. This is easily one of my favorite ones.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-16 04:25:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> My husband is "Stud Muffin" in my phone. Has been for years! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-27 16:22:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Everybody's rock bottom is different. So the only thing you said right in your statement is that it's subjective. No, it's not a contest. You don't know a single one of these people's story. How do you know that they haven't suffered from all of what you listed and more? You don't get to judge ANYONE'S rock bottom.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-21 23:53:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Well, nobody's perfect.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-19 16:41:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> As the wife of someone who ran over a beloved family pet, I have to say, please don't blame yourself. This was an accident, no more, no less. These kind of things happen, Sorry about your loss. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-18 19:49:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Glorious! Happy Birthday!!
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-17 20:23:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Sounds like you need to join us over at r/raisedbynarcissists. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-16 22:52:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> OMG. There are so many here! I don't know what to pick!! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-16 17:06:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Geese are complete assholes. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-12 21:37:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Ah. I see what you're saying. Interesting.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-12 20:48:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> IIRC Chernobyl did indeed have a concrete and steel structure built around Reactor 4, colloquially called the Sarcophagus. The issue with the Sarcophagus is that the seams were never seal properly. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-10 16:31:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Fun fact: The pH scale does not go strictly from 0-14. There are negative pH's (mainly in mining waste streams) and pH's that are higher than 14.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-07 17:23:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> r/Letterkenny is leaking again (and it's WONDROUS). </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-06 23:10:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Fucking 10 ply.
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-06 21:31:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Just finished a LOTR marathon. Looks like I'll be doing another one.
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-04 19:08:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> "And as I always say, If it's not baroque, don't fix it".

Sorry first thing that popped in my head. They look beautiful.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-04 01:29:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This is completely fair. I guess you can say that GOOD owners that have worked hard to train their dogs can trust them to be gentle. I often forget that some people don't take the time to train or form a bond with their animals.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-03 23:03:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I had a dog just like this. A gentle soul. She would wait for eggs to hatch in the incubator (she knew as soon as we took it out). As soon as chirping started she would anxiously wait for us to show her her new friends. We just lost her in October. I miss her so much. My point is, owners know when they can and cannot trust their dog to be gentle.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-01 07:03:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Played Dr. Mario on N64 with my 14 year old for a few hours (kicked his ass, too). Now in bed browsing Reddit waiting for sleep.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-01 00:31:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thank-you for doing this!

Top goals this year:

- lose the 50 lbs I put on this year.
- get at least 18 more credits towards my BSc.
- start running again.
- continue to succeed at my amazing job.
- get my depression and anxiety under control (get meds for bipolar disorder sorted out).
- be a better wife and mother.
- quit drinking. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-09-22 14:51:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Why don't you sit back and bitch about the problem instead of being part of the solution?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-09-22 14:50:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> While I thoroughly enjoyed your PM that dressed me down, I should make you aware that I am not interested in troglodytic micro-phalluses and that I'm Canadian. So really I'm not part of the problem, I'm just laughing at you. Like the rest of the world.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-09-22 03:49:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [](/ggg)
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-09-22 03:43:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Let me guess, you're tired of your tax dollars going towards welfare recipients aren't you? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-09-22 03:06:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> They are stored sealed off the line just like you would receive it in the store. We'd just walk from the lab out to the line and pick out what we wanted. Then we'd store the refrigerated samples in the refrigerated warehouse and "abuse" samples in a separate location in the warehouse (logistically impossible to keep two weeks of milk from each line in the lab). If milk goes bad sooner it's likely a cleanliness issue or pasteurization temp issue. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-09-21 15:06:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> My 19 year old son loves it. I really think you DO need to commit your brother. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-09-21 03:53:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It really has a lot to do with the cleanliness of the milk processing plant and the conditions of the store refrigerator. A few degrees warmer might not seem like much but it makes a huge difference in terms of rate of spoilage. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-09-21 03:50:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I worked at a milk processing plant in QA/QC. Samples of all lots of milk are kept until after the Expiration Date for testing. These lots have half kept refrigerated, half kept and room temperature. Surprisingly, it was rare to find spoiled milk. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-09-19 04:24:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> GAH! Only one in Edmonton, over an hour away :/ </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-09-18 14:11:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm saying they'd be better off never having lived. As one of those abused/resented/neglected children it would have honestly been better. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-09-18 05:09:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah, but way more unwanted children. What's worse? An abortion or a resented/neglected/abused child? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-09-17 15:28:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Brain zaps, fucking awful.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-09-17 06:22:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Don't you bring your shit show here.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-09-17 03:55:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Sounds like America to me. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-09-16 22:46:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> \\\_()\_/ 

Edit: Cool! Thanks!! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-09-16 22:41:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That means he understands the constitution very well then. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-09-16 22:08:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I think your girlfriend is traumatized by what happened you. It was serious enough for you to be hospitalized. I think she feels she could have lost you, hence her emotions. I'd highly recommend that she talk to a professional. My husband was assaulted by a neighbor and had to have surgery, it was very traumatic for him, but also me and our two children. 
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-09-16 19:57:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> There have already been a few offers to pay for his tickets. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-09-16 19:56:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Oh, he's not ours anymore, the US lost that bet.
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-09-16 17:09:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> "A source close to the RCMP" has indicated it was the subject under arrest who led police to Hailey's body.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-09-16 06:41:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> They found her... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-09-16 06:34:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> They just confirmed that her remains were found and closed the conference without answering question. There's supposed to be another one at 10AM tomorrow. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-09-16 06:31:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Sadly, she is not. Her remains have been found. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-09-16 06:30:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Been there a few times for Sinister 7, great little town. This sucks. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-09-16 06:28:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I just can't even comprehend how. How does a person's mind not register that killing a two year old is wrong? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-09-16 05:29:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Just awful. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-09-16 05:28:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Her remains have been found. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-09-15 18:54:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I always have to be Toad. There have been arguments with my children over this fact.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-09-15 18:51:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Nope. They don't. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-09-15 18:49:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The rest of the world managed not to choke... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-09-15 03:05:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Such a relief, he's a neat little guy who's overcome many many obstacles. Social skills with his peers are just not his forte. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-09-15 03:03:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Oh, it wasn't a physical teller, it was deposited by a business, so I assume a Dropbox deal. The business was a bunch of assholes. No hate for tellers here! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-09-14 20:59:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Oh my goodness. This is my 12 year old. Could never get along with his peers but has no problem with the older kids and adults. We've worried so much about it. This made me feel 100x better.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-09-14 06:33:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Two words: biological warfare. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-09-14 06:22:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> He got downvoted for assuming "cheque" was the incorrect spelling. Dude, Google that shit before you look like an ass incorrectly calling people out. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-09-14 06:20:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I've also learned from experience that banks don't give a shit about post-dated cheques either. They'll cash them whenever.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-09-13 16:53:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> And there you are! Proving my point. I hope your girlfriend seriously reviews this relationship because she doesn't deserve you.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-09-13 16:46:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> My friend left her husband with whom she had two children. After a few months she started dating a man who regularly told her that if she didn't have kids they could do things "like regular couples do". She refused to take this a sign that the relationship was doomed. Fast forward six months and she finds out he's an abusive closet alcoholic that deliberately antagonizes her children and steals from her. He even stole her little girl's teddy bear she had since birth because he though she was too old for it at age 6. If you are going to date again you need to make sure that your man is a good fit for your kids as well. They have to be the number ones in your life. He needs to go.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-09-13 16:34:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> No, you came here for justification of your actions and back-up in your thinking that your girlfriend is in the wrong. You refuse to accept the actual productive advice that you are, indeed, the person who was wrong in this situation. You have a fantasy that people in relationships always respect each other's feelings and never say anything harsh and cruel to each other. I'm sorry to have to break it to you, but that just isn't the case. People in relationships can get nasty when their feelings are hurt, and bad stuff is sad when you are mad. As stated above, if you aren't a child you accept this and are able to move past it. I highly suggest that you apologize to your girlfriend and then grow up.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-09-13 16:26:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Kids these days! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-09-13 16:23:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yes, it would be and it should happen more often. I have a sister-in-law who needs a reality check. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-09-13 16:22:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Jesus, shaddup. He's a man-child who does nothing but play video games. I doubt he's contributed much to the household and THAT'S why he was kicked out.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-09-13 16:14:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I said attracted, I didn't say anything about wanting to fuck them. As in "oh, that girl is pretty". That's attraction. Grow up. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-09-13 01:51:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Honey, I've been married 21 years. There is no way in hell you are going to get a man to be solely attracted to just you. If he's straight he likes looking at women, fantasizing about them and probably masturbating to those fantasies. If he's a good man then he'll have those fantasies but the woman he'll always be the MOST attracted to is you.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-09-13 00:30:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> As a Canadian I really and truly hope that you are right. Watching the GOP is just unbelievable. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-09-13 00:08:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Let's start at the whole "Weapons of Mass Destruction" thing. As a Canadian going to war with Iraq was simply pointless and a waste of lives.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-09-12 23:18:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The key here is reasonable amounts. Anything in excess, a big turkey dinner, too much fried chicken, even salads with heavy dressing can raise blood sugars. It's interesting to learn exactly what you don't know about diabetes from a diabetic.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-09-12 21:39:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Calories in general raise blood sugar. If my husband eats too much of anything his sugars go up. Also, honey is sugar my darling, semi-retarded sister in law.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-09-12 21:09:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Oh, but you do? You just KNOW that they have behavioral problems due to their past even though you have no clue what it is? Little teensy bit hypocritical aren't we? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-09-12 17:51:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The point is that you are wrong and "many" is still a stretch. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-09-12 17:08:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I think "many" is a stretch. Some senior dogs have aggression problems. Many do not.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-09-12 08:45:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Don't forget elitist! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-09-11 22:01:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Looks like a post-attack nap.
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-09-11 21:59:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> She had to agree not to interfere with the deputies who are issuing marriage certificates. She interferes, she goes to jail. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-09-11 18:17:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That was downright pretty.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-09-09 17:21:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> He was a fucking coward.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-09-09 15:16:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> He'd be a politician. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-09-09 07:52:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Must be the first responders in the area. I rolled my car two years ago and the Firefighters that extracted me were wonderful! Joked with me about the accident "rolled it huh?", I was hurt (not severely) and terrified and they were great.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-09-08 21:55:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> We chased Target out of Canada, so alas, I shall have to settle with Wal-Mart. But maybe I'll give Canadian Tire a try. If all else fails I'll drop them off at EB Games and say "I'll be right back!" And then run for the border. Sadly they are 19 and 12 and have gotten better at finding their way back home.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
