<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject9951</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-27 16:09:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Ahh yes, my first golden legendary. Got it right at the start of WotOG too  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-19 02:19:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The big Pyrocynical </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-07 21:03:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Play of the game </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-29 03:30:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm pretty sure that being a lesbian means you ARE putting yourself in a box.

ayyyyyyy </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-25 12:47:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> My winstreak was broken twice, never made it to even 15 in a row. One of those was by Majin Vegeta's Ult which dealt damage per every character. Even with king yemma, i got slaughtered. That's kind of messed up. I exited the game, but i don't think i did it quickly enough. 

And that wasn't even at 20x... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-21 15:55:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah, but what's the Great Saiyaman doing there? No one knows his real identity. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-17 19:20:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Y-you like a bit of that Chuck Norris?


Yeah, remember the trollface guys? That's still funny right? Le epic man who tricks people, amirite... guys?




Guys? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-28 18:23:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> He's a useless unfunny tumour who only has any fame because of maxmoefoe and FilthyFrank.
Now he's riding Keemstar's coattails too. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-13 00:44:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Lost my game recently due to smartphone space issues. Shortly before the recent update, i planned on putting it back on my PC with Bluestacks, but before that, i wanted to try to put it back on my phone after uninstalling it. So after it worked, my phone was completely full and i uninstalled it again to free up space. As i was unaware, the transfer code only works once, then it becomes invalid.

Any way to get it back? I just recently got some great characters there too, including Gogeta and SSJ3 Goku in one pull... :( </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Dry spell running 1 year, 3 months and counting. Ever get that feeling of just not being wanted by anyone? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-22 11:43:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-17 09:31:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Man, just listen to that engine purring. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-06 17:09:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Wilfred was garbage. If i wanted weed jokes, i'd watch Harold and Kumar, at least they're funny. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-23 09:16:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It wouldn't be out of place to call him a faggot here. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
