<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject4639</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-10 06:50:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Whitlock can't even remember what the start of a sentence is by the time he reaches the end of it.  Nothing but incoherent rambling that makes little to no sense.  

So yeah, it's totally believable that he would completely forget any shittalking he'd done, but Stu remembers it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-10 06:09:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Note: yes those are almonds. I had lots of almonds so I used those. Traditionally, there are peanuts. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [Homemade] Carapulcra - a peruvian stew with pork, potatoes, peanuts, and dark chocolate served w/ cauliflower rice </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-10 06:01:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-10 02:19:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The part you seem to be missing is -

Win10 is an **Operating System**, not an ad-platform.

Advertise inside Bing all you want!  Inside the Windows Store, sure! On the Windows Phone (if those still exist), go at it! 

Windows is an **OS**.  The more you treat it as an ad-platform, the more interest I have in linux. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> TIL a larger number of bumper stickers on a car indicates a higher likelihood of being involved in a road rage incident. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-09 18:41:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-09 18:19:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Same here. I live in a small-ish town and pretty much everywhere I drive is 5-10 minutes away, so taking the time to plug in my phone/mp3 player, find a song I want to listen to, etc...I was at my destination by then.  So I found sports radio easier as something to listen to while driving.  Then I got a better job that involves a lot more driving and the habit stuck.

I would actually be interested in sports radio if there was a lot more X's/O's breakdown type of stuff, things that make me more knowledgeable about sports.  But 99% of it now is just a bunch of stupid "what if" crap like "If Chris Paul was on the Warriors and Durant was on the Clippers, would the Clippers be in the finals?"  Like, sure, debate that for half an hour, but it's not reality and it's not gonna happen.  So what's the friggin point? 

So yeah, I've come to love DLS because they make fun of all of that idiotic pontificating that will never have a real answer because the nature of the questions means no real answer is possible. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-09 18:13:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [Alligator vs Stallion](https://youtu.be/Ttj4kW9A0hw) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> LPT: You should use 3 to 4 email accounts. 1) for personal correspondence, 2) for account signups, 3) for really shady account signups. This really helps with online security. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-09 17:23:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> YACHT - I Thought The Future Would Be Cooler [EDM] </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-09 16:53:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-09 16:37:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Longtime alcoholic, depression since puberty basically. I'd like to try to offer some tips for this.

First - one of the harder parts is dealing with the idea that improving yourself isn't an accomplishment but an ongoing process.  This can be very overwhelming. (If I start to exercise to improve my body/health/looks/whatever, then, jesus, does that mean when I'm 60 I'm still going to be running 5 miles a day and doing tons of situps? Noooooooooooo......)

I think of all the work between here and 60/70/80+ years old, and it seems so overwhelming. That's a *lot* of work, and that's just exercise, not anything else!  So...

Second - Thinking small.  Think about the old trick-question; would you rather have $1million now, or, 1 penny now, but each day for a month your money doubles? (By the end of the month, you end up with more than $1mil.)  Improving yourself isn't winning a lottery, it's adding pennies. 

Third - Improving small. This month, start with just making your bed after you wake up.  You don't have to do a professional hotel-maid job of it; re-stretch your fitted sheet so it's on the mattress nicely, lay your non-fitted sheet on top of that, lay your comforter/blanket on top of that.  Smooth it out.  It should only take 45-90 seconds. Are you worried that spending those 45-90 seconds means you'll "miss" commenting on a reddit post? Once you start doing this, you'll see it's really a pretty damn quick/easy thing to do, and it isn't something that's going to interfere with any other aspect of your life. You have that much time to spare, it's okay to do it.

So just do that for a month.  Don't worry about other improvements. That's all.  Make your bed in the morning. 

When you're ready, start to keep your room clean in general. When you get home from work and change out of work clothes and into your comfy clothes; fold/hang the clothes you're going to use again before washing them, put the clothes you're going to wash straight into the hamper.  This is also something where, once you start doing it for awhile, you realize how quick and easy it really is, and doing it won't interfere with your reddit-browsing. 

Two months have passed, and every time you walk into your bedroom, your bed is made and your clothes are nicely put away.  This starts to feel really good.  And you realize what a ridiculously small amount of time you've spent doing it. You've still been browsing reddit this whole time, you've still been playing plenty of games of Rocket League or dota or whatever, you've still been doing all the things you normally do, you just also have a clean bedroom at the same time.

After that, figure out the next thing you want to improve that's most important to you.  Don't join a gym, enroll in Intro to Japanese, start learning to program Java, and try to cook homemade dinners all at the same time.

Figure out something you do too much of (play video games, drink booze, masturbate, whatever) - don't get rid of that thing entirely.  Just take a portion of the time on that, and put it towards something else, even if it's just one day a week.  

Maybe you love playing DotA - in the time it takes to queue and play one (good-ish) game, you can walk 2 miles, cook a small meal, or finish a section in Rosetta Stone. You don't have to stop playing DotA. If you play three dozen games per week, just "sacrifice" one of those games per week. 

The small things add up. And if you can get into it, and keep it up, you realize the time "lost" on them is pretty minimal, and it starts to make your "non-improvement" things feel a lot better.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-09 15:54:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> ha! No worries, we have special parts of town for builds like that! 

(Well, I've been taking a break from Minecraft/that server, so I can't speak to what's going on now.  But generally, Rose people are usually willing to help out with designing/building.) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-09 07:55:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Eh. They can just wait a few weeks for all the outrage to find a new target and just start advertising again. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-09 07:42:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> heh I made an almost identical post like this about 5 years ago when I first moved back. 

At pine nursery park in the NE I sometimes see people playing, but, the once or twice I've seen it happening, it included a lot of children, and I think once baseball starts talking over the fields it might come to an end. (This was very early Sunday when I did see it.)

Many many years ago the fields between Cascade middle School and broken top had regular pickup nights, no idea if that's still a thing.

Edit: oh also sometimes when I played disc golf at cocc before that went away I would see what looked like pickup games on the weekends, mid afternoon ish. But those might have been practices or classes.

Was considering joining there PandR summer league but I'm not sure how serious that is and I'm not in the best shape to play "seriously." 

If you find something tho, if love to know. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-09 07:22:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Which makes Chuck freaking out over it a stronger testament that it's all in his head and he's not well mentally. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-09 06:43:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Why are people who drink to much allowed to do really shitty work while hungover and everyone high fives them for getting super wasted? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-09 05:55:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> 13 hours in and one the main quests bugged and I had to start from scratch. Couldn't get a certain dialogue to appear with a main character. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-09 03:54:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> My first thought when I saw the reviewer's video was, "isn't it incredibly stupid to start publicly speaking about an active lawsuit?"

He obviously wanted to sway public opinion to put pressure on the company to (hopefully?) drop the suit. But isn't he just giving more fodder to the plaintiffs while doing so? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-09 03:16:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This made me laugh.

Then I saw the username. You uh... Didn't happen to sometimes play on a certain nerdy multiplayer Minecraft server off and on did you? I may or may not have told you to join my town but you were worried you build too derpy... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-09 03:07:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Oh shit I thought this was for an /r/patientgamers response whoops.

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-09 02:10:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Did the same thing and had a much better experience than fallout 4, which I bought full price pretty early, bought the first DLC, rapidly lost interest in. Probably spent 1/4 of the hours in FO4 compared to Witcher 3. 

I'm a (former) Minecraft junkie and thought I'd spend months/years with all the crafting, but there game was just so damn boring and I regretted buying it (especially at full price). </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-09 00:55:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I think you've now spent longer fake laughing at me than it would take to make your bed. You really know how to use your time wisely.

Take care :) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-09 00:53:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Then you should start vacuum sealing your head every night before you sleep.

Note to children and idiots: don't vacuum seal your head </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-09 00:15:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> heh. Glad I could make you laugh. Your projection issues in no way confirm anything. Have a nice day :) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-08 17:44:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> No, bored </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-08 16:58:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Links to most of the funniest things -

Hulk shirt rip Better link with video - http://www.telegraph.co.uk/football/2017/05/07/former-arsenal-defender-nelson-vivas-rips-shirt-protest-sending/


Matt Harvey sex toy - http://assets.nydailynews.com/polopoly_fs/1.3141350.1494100265!/img/httpImage/image.jpg_gen/derivatives/article_750/metstoy6s-1-web.jpg

Knitting at hockey - https://www.russianmachineneverbreaks.com/2017/05/06/penguins-fan-knits-behind-pittsburgh-bench-during-game-five/

Lost ball home run - http://m.mlb.com/cutfour/2017/05/07/228965338/aaron-hicks-lost-javier-baezs-home-run-in-the-night-sky </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-08 16:22:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  There is literally no downside to leaving your bed unmade 

Not gonna browse your history, but I wouldn't be suprised if yourself and a lot of the people who upvote you deal with some amount of depression.

Wanna know something that kinda helps in some way with depression?  Doing something nice for yourself, like improving your surroundings, and living in less of a shithole.  

It takes like 90 seconds to make a bed. "Oh no, but I had so many comments on reddit I could have posted during that time! I'll never get those shitposts back!"  

Please.  You aren't painting your walls, you aren't doing an oil change.  You're putting your sheets back, and laying a comforter on top of the sheets.  

It feels good to "achieve" something nice, even if it's small. If you aren't taking pride in your surroundings, how much pride can you take in yourself?

Quit being a child.  Make your bed.  You'll feel better. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-08 15:58:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The ad break was about 3 minutes earlier than normal...

But I only tuned in at 6:45 (9:45 for you jerks on the east).  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-08 15:55:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> aaaand that was a dump from the network </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-08 09:55:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The only time I judge handshakes is when someone really squeezes hard. I think that person is an asshole. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-08 08:23:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> lol

Please tell me this is from something... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-08 08:23:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> My only working theory right now is that with the new format, not enough people were accidentally clicking the lame "Open with the App" button on the bottom, so they went back to the old style to keep tricking people into clicking that. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-08 05:44:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Awesome, thanks for the extra info for the setup! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-08 05:32:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Quick unrelated question if that's okay...

What happened with the imgur mobile site in the past month?

For the longest time it was really slow to render, and there was a ~5 second lag between when the page "loaded" and when I could actually play the gif.

Then a few weeks ago the look/layout changed and suddenly I could play gifs instantly and it was great.

And then in the past week it went back to the old style and everything is slow and laggy again? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-08 04:30:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's okay to not like pretentious crap. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-08 04:19:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Damn, I would still love a pair.  

Stupid idiots slowing down the future.  Something nearly identical is going to be around sooner or later.  Get over it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-08 04:16:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> heh, yeah, noticed some jerkass doing that.  

Hope you enjoy the rest! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-08 02:52:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> And Shaft.  And Scientology, tho I guess that's part of South Park.  

Bit of a shame how forgotten he is as being pretty damn innovative.  I mean, who names a funk song Hyperbolicsyllabicsesquedalymistic, really?  Isaac motherfucking Hayes does, that's who. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-08 02:33:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [Isaac Hayes - By the Time I Get to Phoenix](https://youtu.be/r_Kb607VNKM)

Just shy of 19 minutes long. I love it. It's like if Godspeed you black emperor made a 70s jazz/soul song. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-08 02:29:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Eh, this is one where the common meaning took the place of the original meaning. Another thing to blame stupid people for. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-08 02:14:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You think smartphones are amazing? Bahahaha check out your carrier options!

Love your amazing new computer? Bahahaha you're stuck with Wintrusion10, Desperate-forum-search-for-a-solutionux, or a Simpple.

Maybe you love the outdoors instead? All you have to do is contribute to its destruction to get there!

At least you still have your loved ones. Have you checked their Facebook posts lately? You should, really, it'll be fine.

In the end, there's always the comfort to be gained in loving and being yourself. Miniscule changes to the amounts of a few random chemicals in your brain chemistry can't screw that up too much, right? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-08 02:01:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm so fucking tired of shaking hands. I am perpetually "still getting over a cold" so I don't have to.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-08 01:29:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If you paid attention to their ads for their gross gyro wannabes, they changed the meat in them. 

The original ads actually looked like gyro meat. Fooled me and I ate there for the first time in 10+ years to discover it's just their gross roast beef instead. 

Now the ads show their gross roast beef. Someone must have brought a complaint to the BBB or ftc or something.

(I only ate there because nowhere serves gyros in my town, don't judge) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-07 19:56:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> About 80% of the Netflix Originals from the past 1-2 years are a disappointment.. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-07 17:37:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I started searching the property history to see what it might cost to buy it.  

Apparently there is a not horrible log cabin up in the hills, and it is a very large piece of land.  (They are asking a lot of money for it.)

But yes, the idea of that being Little Sweden made me giggle and stop to take a picture. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-07 16:50:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's very /r/generallyannoying </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-07 16:20:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Scandia village is a pretty common name for certain places here. But I know that horse </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-07 16:18:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That's Oregon :) 

[We also have these signs](http://gorgelodging.com/files/47f4b498e2904c930787e113978d672f.jpg) which...the right side is where the plow is moving the snow... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-07 06:28:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I was just at Powell's and saw she had a book called something like "Nobody is weird on the internet."

...really?  Have you used the internet before?  You sure you wanna stick by that statement? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Linux mostly-noob; I've seen lots of comments about issues with dual booting with Win10. Is using 2 SSD's with a single OS on each and switching boot order in BIOS a "better" solution? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-07 05:54:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I've been considering trying to use linux more, currently Win10 on my current rig (see note below).  Pretty much any time a complaint about Win10 reaches the front page of reddit, there's an inevitable chain of comments suggesting switching to Linux, replies about "I still need Windows for gaming," then talk of dual booting, then lots of people with lots of problems dual booting and it's generally (judging by the comments/upvotes) considered a huge PITA. 

I know the solution in my title isn't perfect but...would switching boot order for two SSD's (as opposed to boot order for two partitions on a single SSD) be "easier" overall? 

Hitting F2 on startup and going through BIOS isn't ideal obviously.  But ...eh?

Personal Note: I use Linux (Mint) on my work PC.  It is my really old PC that was replaced when I could afford a better rig, so the hardware is junk, I expect it to die any day, hence installing Linux to play around with it and see what's up. About 90% of my experience has been fine, with that 10% being...very annoying.  

And it seems a lot of the problems with dual boot involve a whoooooole lot of that 10%. So if your answer is, "Just dual boot, once you get it working, it will be a lot easier," the "once you get it working" part seems frightening. I can't even get my scanner working on my single boot Linux box. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-07 04:16:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [Google Street View if you want to explore the full town](https://www.google.com/maps/@44.7573322,-122.3107365,3a,75y,72.5h,95.04t/data=!3m6!1e1!3m4!1silua2_dByMybqpe7Nq3WEw!2e0!7i13312!8i6656) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-07 03:58:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That place is called "Little Sweden". </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Now /r/Sweden can cash in on that sweet Oregon karma. Took this on my way to Portland. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-07 01:49:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-05 12:58:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> you do this to literally any movie in existence

Nope.  Just the stupid ones.  Batman v Superman was boring, but it wasn't stupid. And there are plenty of great movies out there, some might even have a moment or two of "huh?"  

This movie was stupid.  Sorry. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-05 12:27:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Posted a reply to someone else. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-05 12:22:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This is an inherent flaw with the upvote downvote system. I have to explain why something is stupid.  Quote a line from the movie, an upvotes galore! But sure. 

Because if the director/producers/writers/audience ask "But why?" to just about every aspect of that film, none of it makes any sense.

First fight.  Gold people can't fight the alien because...each one is engineered for a specific purpose? So they can't fight this alien using typical weaponry (it dies from a fucking sword), because...why?  They're able to chase the Guardians and attack them using typical weaponry. (Note: using typical as in "weird space guns that are typical for the universe.)  But they can't use those same ships to target an alien, only another spaceship?  

All to protect their batteries, which are super important.  But...why? They can't make new batteries? Rocket stole their batteries, they end up exploding at the end, so that race isn't ever getting those batteries back.  I guess that planet is just doomed to extinction now because their super important batteries are lost forever?  

A daring escape through a quantum asteroid field! I'll ignore how stupid "quantum asteroids" are because it's a wacky universe.  They get through the other side and "oh no, the gold people went around!"  So you went through the asteroid field...why? It wasn't a shortcut, the gold people were on the other side in the same amount of time.  

Somehow the jump they take will get them to safety.  But why? The gold people can't follow them through? Yandu's ship later goes through 150 or whatever.  The jump is safety...why?

They crash, Kurt shows up. Somehow knows right where his son is. (Why?)  Rocket suddenly doesn't understand how perspective/vision works. (Why?) Daxx heads to Ego with the others instead of helping Rocket. (Why?) Groot doesn't understand how buttons work, but is able to free Gamora at the worst time. (Why?) The one and only other life form he tolerates is because she helps him sleep. (Why does he need to sleep? He existed since the birth of the universe but only lately he needs sleep? Or was she around since the start of the universe too? Why?)  

Kurt explains stuff; he decided he wanted to explore the universe "to know what it meant to be human," but he didn't meet humans until 34 years prior to when the movie takes place? His whole plan is to essentially destroy the universe so it's just him.  Wait, didn't he start exploring the universe in the first place because it was lonely being just him? So...why? 

Sylvester goddamn Stallone.  Why? Oh, he's there to show that these ruthless scumbag shitheads have a super serious code about no children.  Yandu didn't eat Peter, didn't molest him, raised him up. So...why is the head of this shithead gang mad? They suddenly have some weird honor system? 

These same people start throwing their crewmates out of the airlock just a bit later. Why? They excommunicate a member for kidnapping a kid, they have a super elaborate space burial ceremony for a fallen member.  But they'll toss their fellow crewmembers out of the airlock, people they've probably spent years working alongside, probably even friends with them, yep right out the airlock they go.  Why?

Yandu gets his ship back and promptly blows up 90% of it.  Why?

There's a button on the bomb that blows up everything instantaneously.  Why?

Second in command at the very end is playing with the arrow, even though Yandu specifically states the other fin was a prototype, and literally the scene before you watch it evaporate with the rest of his corpse. 

Do I need to go on much further? Because I can, but that would require giving this movie more thought than the people making it did. 

It just reeked of "people are bored, it's a sequel, we'll make hundreds of millions, who cares if it doesn't make sense."

So when I left, I thought, "I gave them money.  But why?" </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-05 11:52:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Sorry for not liking what you like. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-05 11:18:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I regret not walking out. Stupidest movie I've paid to see in a very long time. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-05 10:30:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Seems like it's that hypnic jerk thing someone linked. 

Back when I had people to cuddle with it was definitely a weird thing to try and explain </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-05 09:59:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Huh, wow. TIL. Thanks for the info, that sounds like what I get </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-05 06:46:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Zach Snyder and Brian Singer...so many underwhelming movies.  Those two combined have accounted for so much disappointment in my movie-going life.

I don't shit on the movies quite as much as others.  They're...okay.  But holy crap why they keep getting to do the same franchises when they're almost universally panned, or their best reviews are "that was...meh." </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-05 06:10:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Well yeah... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-05 04:59:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Uh, hm.  I wonder if I have some variation of this.

I don't hear a loud noise or see a bright light.  But I'd say about a quarter of the nights as I'm falling asleep, my whole body experiences a spasm.  Almost like I'm being hit with a jolt of electricity?

No pain or discomfort really.  Just kinda...all my muscles fire at once... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-05 04:33:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I thought he would make a great smarmy/stuck up/playboy Bruce, kinda like when Bale buys the hotel, but instead he was super dark and serious the whole time.

And then as Bats, he was just kinda boring and generic.

But again, to each their own. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-05 03:48:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I've had a lot of issues in almost any movie lately.  Is everyone going deaf out there?

During Logan there were a lot of times I was plugging my ears during the action because they really hurt. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-05 03:39:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Because there was 10 minutes of action at the start, then 2 hours of boring bullshit before the fucking monsters and robots start finally fighting, but even then they have to add a lot of stupid bullshit in the middle of all of the fighting.

I don't care about dipshit working on the wall, or fighting a girl with sticks, or girl dealing with her past, or Sexgod Elba having cancer, or scientists fighting, or a useless cameo from Hellboy. 

JUST. GIVE. ROBOTS. FIGHTING. MONSTERS.

Edit: The first robot/monster fight ends at 15 minutes.  The next robot/monster fight happens at 1 hour 10 minutes.  55 minutes of stupid boring shit in between fights.  To the downvoters - there was obviously some hyperbole, but for fuck's sake. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-05 03:31:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This is exactly how I felt about Affleck as Batman before seeing that crap movie.  He could be a great Bruce Wayne, but not a great Batman.

Then I saw the movie and he wasn't good at either. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-04 15:34:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thanks :) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-03 18:30:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm not a prohibitionist, I'm fairly libertarian when it comes to personal choices like smoking or drinking.  

But cigarette advertising was banned decades ago, while alcohol continues to be the primary sponsors of just about everything.  And that's just utterly ridiculous. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-03 17:02:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The difference between the vilification of cigarettes and the glorification of alcohol is astounding and disgraceful. 

Let's set aside direct deaths (lung cancer for smokers; alcohol poisoning for drinkers). 

Deaths from second hand smoke are greater than deaths from drunk drivers, sure.   After that, the problems to the general well being of the public in general are so much greater from alcohol.

First - in the history of the planet, there hasn't been a single unwanted pregnancy due to smoking too many cigarettes. (I would argue that children who were unwanted pregnancies contribute to many of the problems in the world, and comprise the majority of prison populations, but that's another debate for another thread.)

How many women or children (and, sometimes men) are beaten by an abusive significant other, largely because of the influence of alcohol?

How many suicides or manic depressives are alcoholics/children of alcoholics? 

How many just generally terrible ideas resulting in terrible injuries (/r/holdmybeer) are due to alcohol? 

How many people have just plain drank their lives away, getting whatever work they can wherever they can just so they can afford to keep drinking when they get home, and contributing little to nothing else in society?

But go to any game thread for any sporting event, one of the top comments will be a gilded remark about how drunk that user is. Alcohol sponsors all of those events. People tell themselves they don't have a problem with alcohol, but what's the primary reason they leave the house for entertainment? Alcohol.  

I say this all as an alcoholic (3 months sober) who still smokes (bought patches, trying to get an Rx for Welbutrin). The stigma attached to one far outweighs the actual societal effect of the other, which is cheered and glorified. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-03 16:13:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's my cat's name... 

... But it's very fitting for her personality </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-03 05:02:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> hahaha 

And it's really the AMC's that give me the most problems... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-03 04:35:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hi, Mortgage Loan Officer!  Real estate appraiser here!

Can you guys actually read through supplemental addenda before rejecting appraisals and requiring additional commentary?  That'd be great.

;) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-02 17:57:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Not just lawyers. Real estate appraiser here. Buying a house or doing a refi? It's my job to tell the bank roughly what the property is worth for the loan. So many times I want to tell the homeowners to shut the hell up. 

Just yesterday, called to set up an inspection. The guy was confused about why I had to inspect the interior (because that's what the bank asked). He really wanted exterior only. Exterior only happens sometimes sure, and we include a statement about making an assumption that the interior condition is equal to the exterior condition.

The guy then started telling me about how the floors and walls in two rooms were ruined and required thousands to repair. Guessed what, dumbass? Now I can't make the assumption the interior matches the exterior, I'm required to put that in the report now.

Value goes way down, dude probably won't get his loan. Because he couldn't just shut up. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-02 17:17:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm a Nexus 6p owner. Had it with Fi service since December 2015. I've felt so frustrated by this phone pretty much since day 1, and lately almost everything seems to be starting to die at the same time. 

I've been considering upgrading, but seeing all this frustration with the pixel...I don't know if I'll buy another Google phone again. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-02 06:12:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah the sleeves were the part I was hoping to tailor.  The right shoulder has a bit of a wonky seam.  

Tho I think the sleeve length is more of the shirt being a bit big. I haven't measured myself, just grabbed shirts I thought "probably looked about right."

But when I take it in I'll ask about the sleeves, thanks! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-02 06:08:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Oh sure, all of those are great, but their impact is well known and the people behind them fairly well known.  Sure, Berners-Lee might not be a household name, but most tech-savvy folk know it. Same with Google, Intel, Microsoft, etc.  The torrent format, now you're starting to get into less known even in that circle.

What % of those same people know the inventor of the mp3?

(and I've had internet service since 1988.  Prodigy Classic ftw.) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-02 06:05:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> For an instance that just popped up, I've had an electronic station playing for most of the day.  Exactly two songs by The Prodigy have come up - Firestarter, both times.  

I'd love for more songs by The Prodigy to come up.  I'm getting tired of this song. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-02 04:40:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Oh for sure I thought about iPods and all of that.  I'd been meaning to make a proper post in praise of edit:the inventor of mp3s elsewhere.  IMO, top 3 of the most revolutionary-but-overlooked ~~technologies~~ inventors. (I'd say *the* most, but I'm probably overlooking some others.)

Something similar would have been Real Audio cementing its grasp, and compression being almost entirely proprietary.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-02 04:28:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thanks! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-02 04:28:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thanks! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-02 04:24:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I like radio with a variety of artists.  The problem being; in radio stations with some level of overlap, the same songs by the same artists appear in each.  

For instance, I have radio1 which is "experimental" electronic music, along the lines of Prefuse73.  I have radio2 which is more dancey electronic music, along the lines of Daft Punk.  

In both of them, the song Odessa by Caribou appears.  Caribou's earlier albums are closer to radio1.  That song in particular is closer to radio2.  

I don't want to thumbs down Odessa - I like his music, I like this song.  It just isn't the most appropriate for radio1.  And even in radio2, it's the only song of his that ever appears.  

This happens across a ton of genres.  I enjoy 1960s Roy Ayers (jazz), I detest 1980s Roy Ayers (synthy soft jazz). If I thumbs down 80s Ayers, does gMusic know I just don't like that decade of his music?  Or is it just going to stop playing all Ayers on my jazz station? (Seems like the latter.)  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> If gMusic added this feature, it would cement their status as the best music service </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-02 02:09:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-02 01:24:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Did you see my language? I get worked up too ;) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-02 01:11:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I enjoy what my car looks like. That's why I was fine spending money on it.  

But they won't get another dime from me in the future. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-02 00:56:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Aside from the loot farmers, I wouldn't have minded the Rocket League system.  Except for their bullshit fine print bullshit about trading in items from the crates.

"Trade in any 5 items of one quality to get an item of higher quality" it says in game.  Great, if I don't like my items I can trade them, I'm fine with that deal.  

FINE PRINT (only on their website) : the items have to be from the same series (same crates).  I have 9 goddamn snakeskins, all the same quality, CAN'T TRADE THEM.  Because they came from different crates.  

Fuck you, Psyonix. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-02 00:51:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The inventor of the MP3 deserves a fucking medal. They forced so many industries to give us things we take so much advantage of.

If not for MP3, we would probably be stuck using goddamn real audio, streaming 15 gig movies at 480p. It's not like content providers would want a better compression source out there, and ISPs would salivate over the bandwidth they could charge for.
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-02 00:44:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I saw it was The Oregonian website and thought "of course."

I was disappointed it was NJ for totally different reasons :( </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-01 06:53:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm also on Fi.  People constantly tell me my connection is terrible when on the phone, even when the signal on the phone's screen shows full/nearly full bars. And that's around a number of places in town. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-01 00:15:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Former San Diegan living in Central Oregon.  It's 63 and sunny out, but there's a slight breeze.

I'm wearing my thermal underwear. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-01 00:13:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I think length of time dramatically changes things.  I'm sure anyone who spends a month there could love parts of it that aren't the tourist/easy to find stuff.  If you're just there for a week, I could see people thinking, "Huh, it's just a lot of tourist traps like any other big city."

But this might explain why I enjoyed Nice more than Paris in my brief time in France. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-01 00:09:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> God damn this is so true.  It was fucking depressing going to a shop, and it was nothing but IPA with 1 hefe, 1 stout, and 1 cider as the only other options. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-30 20:43:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Since you're Black Widow, does that mean we have to fight now? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-30 20:43:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [A garage sale pickup from about 5 years ago.](http://imgur.com/a/WVzTI)

I put it up there when I first moved in and never bothered moving it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-30 20:42:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah I need to take the pants in a bit (flash back to an episode of the Wonder Years where Kevin is trying on pants with his mom).  And the right shoulder has a few stitches that are a wee bit wonky, so might get those done too.  

I actually tried this on the week before and didn't buy it for those reasons.  But it was still there the next week and I figured a tailor could finish off the perfect fit, and for a reasonable total price. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Why's it so fly cause hiphop kept some drama, when Butterfly rocked his light blue suede Pumas </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-30 20:38:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-30 19:17:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah, I'm pretty skinny too.  And for my height, it seems like my torso is a little short and my legs are a little long.  The last few thriftstore suits I had were definitely a bit off and I felt like a little kid in them. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-30 18:36:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Got that. The score hidden comment I didn't get </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-30 18:33:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I don't get it? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-30 17:43:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thanks! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-30 17:43:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Well, now that you've revealed my secret, I'm going to assassinate you.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-30 17:42:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Er. The original was 880 calories per serving.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-30 09:41:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Here, make this catfood thing, but with 1/2 the tomato sauce.

In a different pot, softly melt 1/2 a stick of butter.  Once it's liquid (don't let it boil), add, let's say, 1 tsp curry powder, 1/2 tsp turmeric, 1/4 teaspoon cumin, 1/4 teaspoon just about any other spice.  Start slowly adding/mixing 1/2 cup of flour, one spoonful at a time, wait until all the flour is dissolved into the butter before adding the next spoonful. You'll end up with a consistency of a thick paste.  

Add 4 cups of veggie/chicken stock.  Now throw your catfood into that.  

Now you have a curry, that will look presentable, and you have about 4x the amount of servings out of it by adding a minimal amount of other ingredients (some butter, flour, spices, stock).   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-30 09:29:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This looks...disgusting...and could so easily be made not disgusting.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-30 08:55:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> /r/pics exists for a reason dude.  This pic goes there.

I'm getting really sick of all these subs getting filled with the same generic bullshit and losing all their identity just so they can reach the front page. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-30 07:27:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> ...thanks? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> $10 Nordstrom/Ralph Lauren Suit Jacket and Slacks. Near perfect Fit! (Bonus: Two antacid tablets left in a pocket) </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-30 01:05:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-29 04:49:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm fairly new to saving up, but I've been following some personal tips, and they've been working well for me.  

1) Check clearance at your grocery store.  It's "embarrassing" if you really care what strangers think. But bottom line is it's a grocery store, they are **not** going to sell you rotten food.  Most of it is there because they need to clear shelf space for new product.  (As a side benefit, you get a lot of healthy food this way because guess what doesn't sell that great?  In the month I picked up a number of of these V8 fruit juice things, not the Fusion sugar bullshit but veggie blends, all 50%+ off.  Among other purchases.)

2) Debit cards make everything easy! Including spending too much.  After I take care of rent and my monthly bills, I withdraw $100 a week.  That's my budget for that week, including gas and food and all that.  

3) Related to #2, everything I think about buying becomes high priority or low priority.  High prio is fairly obvious; gas, essential food (not lousy snacks).  Low prio is just about everything else, and usually I only spend on that at the end of the week before withdrawing my next $100, or at the end of the month for bigger items (as long as it doesn't eat into the amount I want to save that month.  If I want to save $400, and I have $450 available, I really only have $50 available, is how I try to think of it.)

4) Related to #1, I go grocery shopping 2 to 4 times per week.  Yeah, that's time, time is money.  Instead of once every 2 weeks, and throwing out a lot of shit that's gone bad.  Plus, there are usually daily sales you don't normally see.  Awhile back Chex Mix was 10 bags for $10, normally $3 per bag.  So I got 10 bags of Chex Mix, I have about 6 months of snacking out of that, and only got that deal because I happened to be there that day.

Good luck! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-29 00:19:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The only good solution to pain management in the NFL is for people to stop playing. 

How about you give up your addiction to the NFL, if you're actually concerned for their health. 

Now stop side stepping the truth. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-29 00:09:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Actually I think it was taught in reverse. I noticed a pattern to the numbers, and after giving a 90% correct explanation to the class is when the teacher told us about Pascal's </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-28 17:08:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I was a pretty typical teenager, B or C grades in most math classes in High School.  I "use" math allllllll the time in my work (real estate appraising).  There are a few problems as someone in between the love/hate spectrum.

1) Presentation.  My high school years were the late 90s.  We were still doing questions about trains leaving Chicago etc.  I don't think a single person in my entire school had ever been on a train.  I still have no idea why I had to learn how to graph curves.  If a class included practical applications (here are identical water bottle rockets, calculate how to get the most distance i.e. figure out how to plot a curve) maybe it would have kept my interest.  Even then, it would have been a neat practical application experiment, but something I don't actually "use."

2) Semi-purposeful obfuscation.  This happened in Junior College, when I was more mature and a good student. We were learning about...something.  It involved making a big triangle out of numbers in order to work out some sort of function? (Not how to calculate angles/etc in a triangle.  It was one number(integer?) at the top, two numbers under that, three under that, etc, and some xyz function thing. [Maybe this](http://world.mathigon.org/resources/Fractals/pascal1.png) )

Some part of my brain started tingling as the teacher was walking us through how to solve whatever this triangle number thing was. I found out on my own there was a shortcut to solve this.  I approached the teacher after class and asked him if my shortcut worked; he got a huge smile and said I was right.  He even asked me to teach the class my shortcut the next day. I was incredibly proud.  

The next day after class, I asked him why he didn't just teach this shortcut to begin with.  "Well, you're supposed to learn the longer and more difficult way first, because it's the proper way to learn it.  But you're right, your shortcut works faster."

Really? Edit: and along these lines, not being allowed to use a calculator.  I mentioned I use math all the time in my work.  Mostly, that's plugging in numbers while calculators/software actually do the equations for me. 

3) Math is a language.  And, again, a language not many people use that often. Imagine if you were forced to learn Farsi, Latin, Greek, Serbian, or Swahili throughout your K12 years, and lived in an area no one spoke those languages.  You'd grow up, forget most of the language because you never have anyone to speak it with, and eventually you'd "hate" it.  You would ask yourself "Why did I have to learn this language that I never use, and I forgot almost all of it because I never use it?" </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-28 15:11:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Living up to your username? (I kid, I kid) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-28 14:49:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Dude you're being really dense. Technically throwing a ball involves calculus. You aren't actually doing the equations in your head to throw a ball. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-28 14:45:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Tried to play rocket league. BUT THEIR SERVERS WERE DOWN ALSO! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-28 14:38:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I didn't earn $1,000.  I earned $1,000 *more* than I'd earned in a month before.  i.e. if my previous best was 5k, I earned 6k this month. If my previous best was 10k, I earned 11k this month. See how that works? ;)

And rent is typically around $1,000 per month here too </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-28 06:40:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Same exact place for me too and man this feels good. I found out today my gross earnings this month are going to be $1,000 more than I've ever earned in a month before. That grand it's going straight into savings and I'm happy "just" acting like I earned as much as my previous best.

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-28 06:33:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah the part about the second one needing to be electric made me think it had to be an area that didn't do permitting really (i.e. Texas) if they had any hope of selling the house in the future. 

But I didn't rule out most of the South.. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-28 06:27:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> haha nailed it

Oh Texas... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-28 06:06:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Er. Is this in Texas? Because that sounds like something you probably couldn't get permits for in most places... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-28 06:00:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> As a real estate appraiser, this gives me nightmares. The bracketing, oh god the bracketing. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-28 05:41:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> He exited his mom's vagina with a 3x5 card  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-28 04:25:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Seemed okay, I'll probably go back to it before the others. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-27 22:32:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I've received 2 text messages from a (formerly) close friend in the past 3 months.  

The second to last time I saw him (and his girlfriend), was about 3 weeks after they started dating.  Where 100% not joking, she said, "it's time for me to get fat now."

Good luck, dude. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-27 22:24:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Good.  Because, isn't this *incredibly* slow?  No offense to whatever arm of the forces this is but I swear I've seen similar gifs posted from around the world, and they've been a *lot* faster and better coordinated than this.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-27 20:39:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Is pedrovier Belgian for pedophile? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-27 19:41:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Not just the oceans but the jetstream and wind in general. A lot of atmosphere hitting Toronto travels across the vast icy parts of northern Canada and the Arctic. Air moving into Spain is travelling over the cold (but not nearly AS cold) Atlantic ocean. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-27 16:58:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It hasn't been any better over in Bend. You guys are supposed to soak up all the water and keep us sunny over here. Get back to work. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-27 16:39:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That's why I bought it :) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-27 06:31:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm right there with you, OP. I've installed 5 games in the past month (Star Trek Online, Sins of a Solar Empire, Cities Skylines, Europa Universalis IV, Warframe) all because I was burned out on games after "finishing" Witcher 3 and losing interested in Minecraft.  I tried going back to Fallout 4 and was tired of it by the time I reached Codsworth (about 5 minutes in - I'd played ~50 hours when I first bought it.)

I keep going back to Rocket League because I can just hop in, play for however long I feel like, and quit whenever I feel like.  Games that require me to accomplish specific tasks are just...tiring now.  

Might try Mount   Blade as it's the most upvoted at the moment.  If you find one that fits the bill, would be great to know. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-27 05:32:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> https://youtu.be/rxUm-2x-2dM </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-27 04:09:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Google is in the classic pattern of the right hand not knowing what the left is doing. Except they have a dozen hands and none of them have a clue. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-27 00:59:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> On the other end of the spectrum - I picked up a GT Team Zaskar for cheap-ish because I loved the classic frame, and it was going to be my "project" bike (mostly because I couldn't afford a "proper" bike and need to spend a little bit at a time fixing this one up).

Took it to the bike shop that was my local cool shop when I was a teen, and this was 15 years later, highly gentrified and very high end.  I didn't really know it had changed that much as I'd just moved back.

They installed my brand new disc brakes on it.  Very, very, very poorly.  I ended up having to practically reinstall them on my own at home.  

Got the strongest impression that the shop looked at my bike, went "this is a piece of shit," and did the bare minimum work "installing" them.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-26 18:16:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The Warburton live action was underwhelming, maybe because I had to much hope as a huge fan of the animated series.

Watching it again years later, it had some really good moments. But it seems they were mostly relying on "people in silly costumes are acting like Seinfeld!" And that wasn't enough.

Side-fun-fact: The Tick TAS was one of the first projects by the guy who made Venture Bros. When I found that out it made so much sense. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-26 18:01:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Cool. And thanks for not resorting to insults and wild speculation about who may or may not be a school board shill.

FWIW, I don't approve of this measure. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-26 17:23:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What's wrong with being a small, non-front-page subreddit? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-26 17:18:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> People do, the mods don't. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-26 07:12:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> "A friend of mine told me that he heard that 45% of the funds raised by this measure goes straight to PERS and the extravagant pensions of state employees. Has anyone seen the full text of the measure? I can't find it."

I mean, that's how you put it when you were trying to explain it.  

So my question still stands - why not ask your friend where they got the 45% figure from?  

And some people might think that making gross assumptions about another forum member being a part of the school board (with absolutely zero evidence), and then calling them a jagoff, and then saying you're better than them, isn't really "contributing."  

I hope I don't need to repost your own words again for you to understand what you've said.  

Have a good day :) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-26 06:22:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So your friend told you something and you're believing it as fact? 

If you can't find this information, how did your friend?  Did you ask your friend for their source?  I mean, you're having such a difficult time finding specifics, it seems like your friend would be a great place to go for those specifics.

...except your friend doesn't have those specifics, do they?  But you're just going to blindly believe their statement about PERS? 

...and then insult people...

What exactly makes you think you're better than...anyone? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-26 06:17:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I think my favorite part of the voter's ballot is there isn't a single argument against provided?  

As people noted elsewhere, a lot of the budgets are very poorly defined. "Modernize institutional space" - so are we buying iPads for all our 3rd graders?  

This reeks of "you HAVE to vote yes, for the children!" and hoping no one stops to question if that much money is really necessary. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-26 04:46:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Why?  To become a top 10 sub?  Is that the whole point of this sub? 

Sacrificing what the sub is actually about in order to become another generic /r/pics subreddit.  Neat. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-26 01:38:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What's wrong with just posting a nice picture to a sub for nice pictures, and leaving this sub as it's name suggests, and not posting that stuff here? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-25 22:13:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The live ad reads?  Those are still in the podcast... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-25 19:42:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Maybe I worded things poorly so we're confusing one another...

They have always taken the ads out of the podcast that they put on the ESPN app (what I use when I missed shows in the past).  They included the occasional ad for ESPN content, usually 2 per hour at about 20 seconds per ad, but you're correct, all other ads were removed.

They still do this, yes.

What I am saying is that they used to remove ads, and the shows would have roughly 40 minutes of content per hour.  They still remove ads, and now the shows average 33 minutes of content per hour. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-25 18:52:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Well yeah.  But at some point this has to cause more people to stop tuning in live. 

Even before this recent addition, the show already had more advertising per hour than, for instance, The Walking Dead, the #1 show on TV.  (Or any other show, for that matter.)  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-25 18:42:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I mean, wouldn't you imagine this makes even more people download the shows later, where there's almost no advertising?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-25 18:15:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> "You can put a junior on anything and it's funny to me"

I gotta admit, Hitler Jr. sounds pretty funny... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Did they add more advertisements? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-25 16:51:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Looking at recent uploads of each hour on the ESPN app, each hour is 32-35 minutes. Local hours are usually 42 minutes. I remember the non-local hours being closer to 42 minutes until the past month or so. I know they started cutting out segments with music, but that shouldn't cut the show length by 5-8 minutes per hour.

It's getting kinda ridiculous. Kinda sad I'm going to have to give up listening live because having a nearly 50/50 ad-to-content ratio is just insane.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-25 09:07:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Did you read the part about paper cups requiring two layers of plastic lining? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-25 09:05:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I remember reading something similar in a wired magazine article maybe a decade ago about reusability. The part I remember is it takes something like 1000 uses of a single ceramic mug to equal the carbon footprint of a recyclable cup. Can't recall if they meant foam or paper, but after reading this probably foam. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-25 08:36:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  but /r/libertarian has the best sub for political discourse right now. 

How on earth can you say that?  Almost all of their top posts from the top month are crappy memes or comics "making fun of" /r/latestagecapitalism or Joe Rogan quotes that belong in /r/im14andthisisdeep 

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-24 18:17:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Remember all the advertisements around Christmas, specifically for the Samsung VR? My mom was considering buying one for my dad.

I told her to watch those ads, and count the number of times they show what the users are seeing.  (Because the answer is zero.)

It was obvious from their own ads that they didn't really have a clue what VR was good for, they only knew they had a product they could sell for a high price tag.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-24 17:15:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [The Chargers did it too just a few years before this clip.](https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=tMwml58ddFU feature=youtu.be) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-24 10:18:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What the fuck did we just watch?

What the fuck.

I told a friend about halfway through last season my own theory on this show.  "They're just trying to set the record for having the most people say 'what the fuck' about a tv show in history."

Thank you for confirming my theory. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-24 10:11:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The second I heard Francis's voice I knew it was him.  Then immediately hoped for Micallef, although that would be too good to be true.

I lived in Melb from 2000-2003, and meeting Micallef one day on the train is still one of my favorite memories of my time there. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-24 10:08:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> FRANCIS GREENSLADE! 

Oh my god the second I heard his voice I was so damn happy.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-24 08:32:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> "Is it Friday? Let's go to a local brewery's pub!"

"Is it Cinco de Mayo? Let's go to a local brewery's pub!"

"Is it the second coming of Christ? Let's go to a local brewery's pub!" </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-24 08:03:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Lately I've been wondering if Intel/Microsoft are the primary reason for the Singularity not appearing to come any time soon.

I love my computer, I love that I can play Witcher 3 on Ultra settings while also running Kodi and watching a 1080p movie, with Chrome sucking down memory in the background.

Thought we'd be a little further along by now, though... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-24 01:07:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> heh yeah I saw your other post right after I replied. Personally I enjoy all of their guest hosts, but I know I'm in the minority there. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-24 01:00:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You are hilarious.  I mean, sure, blame Californians.  All they're doing is taking advantage of the City Council members that continue to line their own pockets.

Instead of whining on reddit, you could go out and vote during the election, and get some people who care about the non-Northwest parts of Bend.

But I'm going to assume you (and probably everyone who complains about rent prices in Bend) didn't even vote for any local offices.  Or, if you did, you just filled in the bubble that matches your party affiliation without any regard to their policies on affordable housing.  

It was the **local** government that decided the UGB needed to expand in the Northwest, rather than any other part of the city that could provide cheaper housing.  In a few years, it will be the **local** government that decides Newport Avenue is way too small to handle all of the traffic in the NW (it already is), and starts paying exorbitant sums of money to buy up properties and build a proper roadway in the area.  

Put your Pabst and video games away, and start making yard signs for your campaign for a city council position in the next election, with the promise of making more affordable housing.  You'll get my vote.  

People making themselves rich from corrupt politicians is hardly unique to Bend. Go make a difference, or quit whining. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-24 00:32:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> And it's rumored that Glenn Howerton (Dennis) might be quitting the show, and he's voiced how he's kind of tired of his character because there's nowhere left to "grow" the character.

Notice the last few seasons have involved minor plot points about everyone in the bar dying or the bar being completely destroyed. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-24 00:21:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm curious - did you listen to the early part of the show when Mina Kimes was recently on? Thoughts?

Pretty much every one of the men in the studio was making me cringe from how they kept steering the discussions towards sex and mildly flirting with her... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-24 00:16:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> We dont want a sterile environment 

Coming from the most sterile of all of the sports subreddits... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [Opinion Rewards] Always being asked about stores near the stores I've actually been to. Is this calibration or is my location not being received properly? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-23 19:53:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-22 16:36:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Meh </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-22 06:52:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Added an edit to save some responses. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [PC] [H] 4 Series1, 6 S2, 7 S3, 10 S4, 11 Player's Choice, 10 Turbo [W] Trails, Wheels, Keys, maybe Skins </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-22 06:36:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I have a bunch of these crates collected.  I'd prefer some "specific" items, but some keys work too as a last resort.  

I definitely **do not** want almost every single skin.  The Vector skin is pretty much the only one I care about. 

Up for hearing offers.

Edit: Wow this blew up faster than I thought, so just to help save time for everyone - 

Bodies - I also have almost every body I want.  Esper and Endo are the only ones I care about.

Wheels - I mostly only want animated ones.  Already have Spiralis, Zomba, FSL sienna, Pulsus green, and Voltaic.  Maybe want rare+ non-animated ones, but already have a lot of those too.

Trails - Again I already have a lot of these.  Outatime and Polygonal are the only non-imports I'm interested in; also interested in a few of the imports.

Antennas/Toppers - meh. Would take a pretty special one for me to care. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-21 15:19:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Looking at you, rocket league.. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-21 14:47:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> uh...it's a parody website dude...

"Does OP lack reading comprehension skills | Yes." /r/savedyouaclick </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-21 14:34:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Wow you really love to willfully ignore entire sentences to reach faulty conclusions. I'd hope an anthropologist could apply critical thinking.

Key words: 3rd-5th generation descendants; speaking the same language. 

That is very different than "all Europeans/Africans/Asians."

Did you get your degree from COCC? Your lack of reading comprehension is astounding. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-21 07:35:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Because the content providers couldn't play nice with Netflix and had to launch a few dozen different services. To watch everything I want to watch I'd need to buy accounts to Netflix, Hulu, Amazon prime, hbo go, and that still probably would leave out a ton of shows/movies. At that point I'm paying more than the cable TV I ditched. Granted it's (mostly) ad free, but DVRs are mostly ad free too. 

They could have worked with Netflix, increased the monthly fees a bit, and had it all in one easy convenient location, like Spotify/gMusic do for music. Instead every channel needs its own service, most with their own fees. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-21 06:34:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> He was hired by one of those terrible websites (I think BuzzFeed?) and stopped doing independent stuff for the most part. A shame because I would love more of this type of stuff from him. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-21 06:16:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Ah, you graduated from the Internet School of Being Technically Correct While Ignoring the Actual Point.

If you're going to be a pedant just so you can force your anthropology 101 conclusion into the discussion, fine, I'll rephrase OP.

Does Bend have a population of ~95% who are 3rd-5th generation descendants of primarily European heritage, primarily speaking a single language, with very similar phenotypic traits? 

How's that work for ya, darlin? Now can you stop shoehorning first semester "race is a social construct" conclusions into a discussion when you know damn well what the person actually means? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-21 05:05:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I mean, did you read OP's post?  It was only two sentences, shouldn't take long.  They're specifically asking about race/ethnicity.

Put your "I have a worthless anthropology degree" card away and stop acting like an ass.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-21 05:03:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> huh, I didn't realize they were open that late.  I know that other coffeeshop/bookstore is open kinda late-ish, but last time I was in there it seemed like a place for the 50+ year old crowd and didn't really have a great atmosphere. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-21 00:06:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Any political subreddit that allows image submissions should be avoided at all costs. They all end up like this. It's a shame.  I'm not a libertarian but I believe it's healthy as a nation and personally to be exposed to other points of view. 

Unfortunately, it looks like this sub will be added to the other ~50 subs that I have hidden.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-20 22:30:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Someone needs to become the "official" person who records the local hour and throws it on YouTube for times like today... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-20 22:25:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Have a direct link? I tried that link just above but can't find anything for today's local hour there </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-20 16:43:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> er.  I guess I missed a great local hour?  Damn you West Coast... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-20 07:37:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Pretty sure op is the choosingbeggar here... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [Semi-Serious] Sports Boredom </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-20 03:25:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> A point Dan brings up pretty often is he thinks part of the success of the show is people bored with other "normal" sports radio shows.  Definitely true in my case, but I wanted to bring up a similar point.  

I still catch parts of other shows from time to time while driving, and there's been an annoyingly common theme to almost all sports radio for awhile now, one even this show falls into.

The first round of the NBA playoffs - Two nights ago driving to the movies, I caught one show talking about how boring the first round of the playoffs are.

The masters - No Tiger Woods?  Boring.

NCAABB/Final Four - No Kentucky or Duke?  Boring.

Super Bowl - There aren't any good storylines with the Falcons and Patriots.  Boring.

Hockey and Soccer - They're just always boring.

World Series - The Cubs win, that's neat! ...and before the Gatorade had even dried from their uniforms, shows started saying how now that the Cubs have won?  You guessed it.  Now they're boring.  

______

It's reached a point where I'm starting to wonder if these sports radio hosts actually enjoy sports.  It really seems like what they actually enjoy is the bullshit drama surrounding sports.  But when it comes to the actual games themselves?  They can't wait to point out how boring each event is.    </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-20 02:56:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Neat read, but this doesn't address my biggest single issue with the film, which came up repeatedly.

Jennifer and Chris **constantly** voice out loud things that are either; a) very obvious, or b) just plain stated out loud already to begin with.

I'd have to watch the movie again to name all of the examples, but the two that come to mind **spoilers** - 

1) When they're trying to find the damaged component that's making the ship go nuts.  Cut to a montage of them searching the one area of the ship they've narrowed the problem down to.  They open a panel.  I'm pretty sure the dialogue goes exactly like - 

Chris - "This panel won't open."  
Jennifer - "That's a problem."  
Chris - "We were looking for a problem."  
Jennifer - "We should check this out."

All that was needed was a single wordless shot of them having trouble opening a panel and realizing it was the problem they were looking for.  Instead, a bunch of stupid dialogue that just explains something *already explained*.

2) And near the climax of saving the ship, same exact thing.  It's well established that when Chris goes out to recomboozle the fizzamatron with the engine, that it will burn him up and he'll die.

He gets to the engine.  He gets to the recomboozling of the fizzamatron.  

Chris - "Open the hatch!"  
Jennifer - "But you'll die!"  
Chris - "But if you don't, then the ship will die!"  
Jennifer - "But I love you and you'll die!"  

Again, all of that was previously explained, and a dialogue-free (or less dialogue) would have made such a stronger impact.  But instead, the filmmakers decided the viewing audience is too goddamn stupid to remember that he might die.  So it all has to be spelled out for a second time in really shitty dialogue.

If I watch the movie again, I'm pretty sure I could find many more examples of this.  The final cut gave zero respect to the viewers, and ruined a lot of the pacing/drama by having the characters spell out what is happening/will happen at almost every moment.  

I agree with the start of this youtube video - it wasn't a terrible movie, and I'm sure I'll watch it again from time to time over the coming years.  But my god those moments were so insulting and just plain bad.
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
