<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject7254</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Goku v. Superman in taking the biggest dump? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-17 18:17:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-13 20:45:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yup yup. Not like a different cutscene every time. There's three main endings with Ciri. Then there's the combination of other events. Like, who wins the war, plus who you chose as love interest, who lived, who died, etc.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-13 06:08:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I see what you mean. But at the same time, the way he edits the videos and his narration with his voice reminds me of a BBC documentary  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-13 04:57:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I've played through the game twice. Once with both DLC. I'm currently on my third play through. I don't think I'll ever stop. Not with 36 different endings. 

445 hours logged according to steam. Do it. I peer pressure you  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> One of my favorite pictures I ever took of my Brittany Chrissy. This was taken about 3 years ago on a hunt. She's 7 now. And my little girl. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-28 16:18:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-12 14:39:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The reboot (2016) is actually pretty fucking sweet. I just beat it a week ago. I never played the original, but from what I've read, the original was just about shooting everything in sight and making you feel powerful. That's the vibe I got playing the reboot </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-15 00:05:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I agree. Fucking sunflower seeds. More debris than food with those  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-15 00:03:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I have to agree with you. Crab is one of those foods where you probably burn more calories trying to eat it than you gain by actually eating it  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What food is the most labor-intensive to eat? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-15 00:01:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-12 19:38:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Maybe something like the Balrog? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-12 19:36:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I think they should take ideas from all sorts of mythologies and incorporate them into new biomes. Like in Greek mythology, there are the fields of Asphodel, basically a huge Kansas field with black poplar trees growing every now and then. They could add some kind of Nether grass too and have lava lakes. And the black poplar trees could be fire proof. 

Obsidian spike biome would also be cool. As would something akin to the seven rings of hell.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> 20 [M4F] Mid-Missouri. Virgin looking for an actual friend with benefits. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-07 00:58:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm 20. I'm a virgin. Like, the furthest I've ever gotten was making out. And just with one girl. I'm looking for a friend. Like a real friend. Someone I can really get along with and talk to and stuff. But also is completely DTF. 

If there's one thing about me, I like to learn. I'm wanting to learn the ways of sex. 5'9", 185 lbs. Fairly athletic, but I've kinda let myself go lately. Not a bulky guy or anything. Not fat. Just got some extra doughiness. 

I'm a real optimist. Like, I'm one of those, "I'm just happy to be here!" Guys. If we can drink together, then hell yeah let's do it! 

I'd love it if we could actually talk about shared interests. Anything nerdy or movie related. Hell, if you're a martial artist, we'll have that in common. 

I'd like to discover myself sexually. If you're a college age lady in my area (18-23) and I sound interesting, PM and we can chat more. See what happens.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [M4F] Mid-Missouri. I'm a 20 year old virgin. I'm looking for an actual friend with benefits. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-07 00:44:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [M4F] Mid-Missouri. 20 year old virgin. Looking for an actual friend with benefits. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-07 00:20:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm 20. I'm a virgin. Like, the furthest I've ever gotten was making out. And just with one girl. I'm looking for a friend. Like a real friend. Someone I can really get along with and talk to and stuff. But also is completely DTF. 

If there's one thing about me, I like to learn. I'm wanting to learn the ways of sex. 5'9", 185 lbs. Fairly athletic, but I've kinda let myself go lately. Not a bulky guy or anything. Not fat. Just got some extra doughiness. 

I'm a real optimist. Like, I'm one of those, "I'm just happy to be here!" Guys. If we can drink together, then hell yeah let's do it! 

I'd love it if we could actually talk about shared interests. Anything nerdy or movie related. Hell, if you're a martial artist, we'll have that in common. 

I'd like to discover myself sexually. If you're a college age lady in my area (18-23) and I sound interesting, PM and we can chat more. See what happens.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-07 19:17:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Huh. Today I learned. How exactly would a man go about producing milk/breastfeeding? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-07 19:16:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Well, I mean, like I want to actually plan out the first two kids with my SO some day. After that, we just won't worry about having more kids and raise the two we have. All the while, like I'm sure many couples do, we'd have sex. If there's a pregnancy then, then we'll raise that kid, love them all the same, then after the birth, I get the vasectomy or she gets her tubes tied.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-07 17:15:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I too am in that boat. I definitely want kids someday. But I'm a 20 year old broke college guy. 

At the same time, my maximum amount of kids I think is 3. Two planned and one accident. After the third, either I'm getting a vasectomy, or she's getting her tubes tied. 

Also, as a side note, I think it's really unfair how little men get to contribute to the actual physical nurturing and development of a child. Yeah, we can help raise them, but the woman has to carry them for nine months going through all the shit of pregnancy. We men on the other hand say, "I helped! I was there for the fun part! Threw in some chromosomes!"

I wish that guys could like breastfeed at least </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-03 05:03:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You know, the back part of the brain is the occipital lobe. That's the part in charge of interpreting sight. 

So, he plucks out the part of his brain that allows him to see... and looks at it... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-31 18:03:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Ah. You right.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-31 17:45:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It was Liam Neeson who played Ra's Al Ghul.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> I love how, according to Assassin's Creed lore, Jeremy Irons... </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-30 17:11:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> He's technically played two Templar Grandmasters in his lifetime. 

Of course he's playing Alan Rikkin in the upcoming movie. But before that he played Rodrigo Borgia in "The Borgias" series. 

I know the tv show has no connections to AC, but still, if you look at the show from the AC lore, then yeah, Irons has played two Templar Grandmasters. 

He did a fantastic job in "The Borgias," and I can't wait to see the movie. 

Also, don't spoil anything past Season 1. I'm starting Season 2 soon.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [Casual] Who would win: Geralt of Rivia vs. the Xenomorph. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-30 02:41:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Geralt has accepted a new Witcher contract. He is to hunt down and kill a Xenomorph Alien. He can use all and every tool available at his disposal, but help from other characters is prohibited. And, for the sake of argument, we'll say the convergence of spheres simply dropped the Aliens into his world. So no firearms or nukes or whatever. Tools and magic from his world only. 

Round 1: a single Alien Drone. He must find a way to kill the creature. 

Round 2: he discovered a nest nearby a deserted village. Apparently the Xenos wiped out the inhabitants and are at risk of spreading further. He estimates roughly 20 Aliens plus a Queen. 

Round 3: another nest, but this time the Aliens have apparently spawned from other monsters. Werewolves, necrophages, Rock Trolls, Cyclopes, and Lesser Vampires. About 30 Aliens plus a queen. Geralt can enlist the help of the witchers of Kaer Morhen, Triss, Yennefer, Kiera, and Ciri.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-17 16:22:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I really hope we get some information plotwise. 

I have complete faith in Fassbender. I know the director is gonna make it look amazing. But I need to know if the plot will hold up. 

That being said, I'm still going to see it.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-17 06:01:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I love rogue. Currently replaying it. And I love Shay. The thing that really bugs me though is that none of his Templar outfits have hoods. The Crusades outfit does, but you can't even put it up. All that happens in any of his Templar outfits is he pops up his collar. 

I know hoods are more of an Assassin thing than a Templar thing, but I wish we could have the option of adding a hood, like in your beautiful artwork. And in the trailer. The perfect mesh of Assassin and Templar.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-06 19:52:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The Selene

Easy Mode

http://imgur.com/a/TnfTg

She's my new brig. And I love her already </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-05 01:05:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Well, he's explicitly stated in an episode about sex that the one with the knowledge has the power. 

He could simply explain to any character why they don't exist and they'd disappear  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Mermaid-Man and Barnacle Boy (in their prime) v. Radioactive-Man and Fallout Boy? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-05 01:02:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-19 07:14:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's not about winning. It's about sending a message  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-16 20:14:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This is the ammnra version.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> TIFU by passive-aggressively threatening a child. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-15 02:55:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-10 14:30:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I don't understand your concept lol. I'm sorry. If you have any better pics, I'd probably be able to help  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-10 14:10:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That would be great! I've been working on a design like this for a while too. Just started getting it to work on my computer simulation.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-10 14:08:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I don't think you could make it double action with just those parts. You can make it single action. But not double. Sorry man </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-10 04:51:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I've wasted a lot of time I could've been using getting my college homework done.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-10 03:42:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Well, I think I've figured out my plans for the scissor mechanism. Once that's built, dart launcher is next, then gun </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> To all hidden blade builders out there... </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-09 23:53:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Has anyone successfully built a dual extended action blade using the scissor jack mechanism shown in the codex? I know all about ammnra's design, and I love it. But I want to know if anyone ever built the device with mechanics similar to that in Altair's codex? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-08 14:48:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I have to agree. He's simply the most physically gifted Assassin we've played as so far. Dude's what? 6'2"? 6'3"? And back then, most people were a little shorter. Not like during BC short. But still. Then there's his combat skills. He mowed down an army in the cinematic trailer. Fast. Strong. Skilled. Connor definitely  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-07 01:10:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The Desmond MD portions in AC III were fucking amazing. I loved how it really showed how much he'd learned and developed since the first game. He really became a badass Assassin. It really sucks that they killed him off. 

I feel continuing the franchise in that vein would have been spectacular. Still have him in the Animus for about 85% of the game. Get the amazing historical aspect. But the other 15% shows off his skills as he looks for the clues in the MD according to the info he found in the past.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-06 02:27:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I mean... There's being comfortable with strangers. But anything involving the butthole is best left for a later date </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What's the weirdest thing someone did that was a relationship deal breaker? [serious] [NSFW] </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-06 02:20:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What story do you tell people about how you met your SO, and how did you REALLY meet them? [serious] </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-02 21:58:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-09 14:13:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Who needs therapy when you can go out for a good pillaging </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What's your version of "I'm a twenty-year-old male, and I still sit when I pee"? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-08 14:37:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What is your "Krabby Patty Secret Formula?" [serious] </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-07 02:26:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What is your "Krabby Patty Secret Formula?" </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-07 02:10:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-06 22:19:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Honestly doesn't seem like much of a problem. More of a solution really </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-06 19:22:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I don't want to sound all high and mighty, but I was tested and have an IQ of 118. I love So-Bad-They're-Good movies. Unfortunately, after I watched Birdemic, I think I lost about 20 IQ points. Which brings me down to about average, but still </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-06 19:16:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I lost it at "I had a wet dream last night!"

Also, can we discuss how creepy it is that the coach just carries around those diagrams? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What's little itty bitty white lie you told that had huge consequences? [Serious] </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-06 00:26:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> If you died and became a ghost, then a family moved into your home, what would you do with your new spiritual powers? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-17 21:29:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-11 02:30:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This pleases the One True God </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Spider-Man v. a Xenomorph. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-06 21:47:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Round one: Spidey has one year's experience and has beaten one of his supervillains. The Xenomorph is a regular alien spawned out of a regular Joe. 

Round two: several years experience for Spidey, having beaten four villains. The Xenomorph spawned out of Wolverine, has the claws (made of his carapace) and has Wolverine's healing factor. 

Round three: Iron Spider, has worked for the avengers for many years. The Xenomorph is a Queen. 

All fights take place is downtown Manhattan.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What movie makes you cry every time? [serious] </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-01 05:53:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> So, I thought she was real, screwed up big time, then realized she was a bot. Spoiler alert!! </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-31 00:46:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-25 17:25:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Can I just say that I actually like it? I mean, it works very well, very simple, and can be used decoratively. I say keep it </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-24 21:53:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> My cat has a foot fetish. He just loves feet. He'll curl up on strangers feet, rub his face on them, etc.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What funny habits do your pets have? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-24 21:48:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-16 07:48:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Survivabililty isn't the problem. Broken legs can also hinder a mission.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-16 07:15:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The problem is that it's been stated they're going for a more realistic thing in the movie </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> About the Leap of Faith in the trailer... </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-16 07:04:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> They're not gonna use a haystack to break the fall right? I mean, it works well in the games, but I don't think it would work cinematically. Even water would be ridiculous from that height. I personally hope they use Leonardo da Vinci's parachute design instead. I mean, the historical segment of the film takes place roughly at the same time as Brotherhood, when Leonardo invented the parachute. Maybe enough time has passed since the end of brotherhood and the beginning of the movie for the design to have spread to the Spanish Brotherhood? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-11 23:11:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> EpicCraft is what I'm currently using. Looks realistic. My only gripe about it is I'm not overly fond of the paintings </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-02 16:56:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I played Black Flag how a pirate would. Take, pillage, and take some more. I always play the Assassin's Creed games how I imagine the character would.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Ok, this is something that bothers me about Newt in Alien 3 [spoilers] </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-28 03:09:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> During the autopsy scene, what the hell were they using for Newt's body? I highly doubt it was the original actress, considering the several year gap between films. Was it a real girl? Was it a realistic stunt body or something?

I mean, they showed nipples and stuff. That's really creepy/illegal to show a 10-year old girl's nipples. Can someone explain what they did exactly? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-16 06:28:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> And you didn't even invite me  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> I need help starting Tyranny of King Washington. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-15 03:41:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I bought the DLC on Steam through the Season Pass. I entered the code through the UPlay application. I open the game. Select "Tyranny of King Washington," but the only thing that happens is a message appears saying, "The Ubisoft server is not available at this time. Please try again later."

I've been trying again later for the last five days. Same message when I go to extras. I need help, this is pissing me off. Thanks! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-27 06:36:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yes. And I believe you meant *hole* community </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-27 00:55:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> My friend, I believe it is up to the players to provide the other half of the ass. They supply the tools, we supply the imagination  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-25 06:02:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I believe you have to poop, my friend.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-25 05:59:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I was thinking about tacos </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Superman's dead body v. Decomposition. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-21 18:51:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The Man of Steel is now recently deceased. He is buried just like a human. 

Some little earthworms see the kryptonian and see a meal. 

Will Superman's body even decompose? If so, how long will it take? 

Takes place on earth </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Today for Valentine's Day... </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-15 04:52:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-27 16:54:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> /r/firstworldanarchists  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-19 17:34:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Sorry this took a while. Bottom of the base is 123X75, and 4 steps high. The top is 117X69. All the towers are 16 high, 7X7. The walls are 7 high. The "hub" in the center leading to the Holy of Holies is 11 high, 5X13, with the stairs leading to it being 4 high. The Holy of Holies itself is 38 high, 31X26. Feel free to ask any more questions. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-16 20:36:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Well, any ideas would be marvelous lol. I'm trying to think of more builds </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-16 20:31:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm at work now and on my phone. When I get home, I'll get you the dimensions  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-16 20:30:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> In all honesty, I googled "Temple in Jerusalem". Temples very similar to each other popped up in images. I based my design mostly on these </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-16 00:48:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thanks! It's Romecraft </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-15 23:56:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Welp, a bit of both. I took some creative liberties. Looked up several designs.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-15 19:53:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> One side is the nazi's, other's team Indiana </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-15 04:09:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yes.


All joking aside, it's Herod's. Based it off a model I found online of what it supposedly looked like </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> I made the Temple in Jerusalem a while back. Just now actually posting it. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-15 02:49:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-03 23:01:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> We don't know what the creeper thinks about that though. 

"Fine!" *sniffle* "I don't wanna play anymore!" </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> How would Yami Yugi fare in a Beyblade Tournament? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-30 05:07:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-23 07:17:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I did both. Two completed files. A way to see both outcomes </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-11 17:12:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What do you think you need it for exactly? And you're talking about the Boxer right? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-11 16:18:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What is that resource pack? It looks beautiful! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-09 22:26:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Is there an EXACT release date? My body is ready </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-09 22:24:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You shouldn't need it. Grates bro. Then use voice synthesizer to order them to open the gate. Then shout "SURPRISE BITCHES!" </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-06 01:54:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> As much as I love TJ Dillashaw, Bruce Lee all the way.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What would be the scariest thing to pop out of your chest? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-06 01:49:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Your home now has a safe full of 500 lbs of milk chocolate. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-04 05:30:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You're supplied with $10,000 and twenty loyal special ops trained men. How long can you hold off the Chocolate Fish from Spongebob from reaching his goal?

http://i.imgur.com/9dVMhLd.gif

The men and money are yours to do with as you please. Use them to fortify your defenses. 

The fish is chocolate lusted and will go to any lengths to acquire the delectable chocolate within.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-03 06:35:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's called Crymaxing </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-03 06:23:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What will you do next?? Silly goose! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-03 06:22:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Sorry Supes... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-03 06:21:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You sound like Joker </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-03 06:20:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Maybe they kinda took something from Arrow in that regard? I mean, both are very rich, Bruce Wayne probably more so. He could easily have a voice modifier made.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-03 06:14:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> He's no longer one of us </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-03 06:13:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I just have to say my body is ready for this movie. I would suck off every cast member for it to come out sooner.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-03 06:08:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If this movie turns out to be bad (Batman forbid this please) it could possibly be the biggest letdown in movie history, certainly in superhero movie history </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-03 06:06:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Batman is the one true God </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-03 06:06:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I FUCKING CAME IN MY PANTS BUT I DON'T CARE!!! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-11-25 18:13:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Don't forget he looked like he was out for a Sunday stroll too. He hasn't even reached his final form </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Who's the slowest person who could beat Hammy (Over the Hedge) in a foot race? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-11-25 06:14:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Round one: regular Hammy

Round two: just drank five Monsters

Round three: sniffed a shit-ton of cocaine. 

Who is the slowest person who can beat Hammy in a foot race? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The Predator is hunting cougars. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-11-24 17:56:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm talking attractive middle-aged women. The Predator needs to score a wife, and he has a human fetish. He can use his technology to accomplish this, however the technology cannot control minds, emotions, or behavior. 

Can this Ugly MotherFucker find true love? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-11-24 04:48:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> As a Conan O'Brien fan, I must take it a step further and say there's something RIGHT with the Irish  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What is your most infamous Michael Scott moment? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-11-24 04:35:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-11-20 02:24:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> When I was six, my mother lost me in Target. We don't do Black Friday anymore... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-11-20 02:19:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'M BATMAN!!! AND I HAVE THROAT CANCER!!!! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-11-20 02:12:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hell, dying actually turns me on </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-11-19 21:06:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Think I should take it down? Like I won't be banned right? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Opened up my Minecraft just now to see this. (Kuro Texpac) </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-11-19 20:58:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-11-16 23:59:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Actually, he really is a survivor. He's lasted many many nights by himself </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-11-16 21:57:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Kuro TexPac. It's absolutely beautiful. I think it takes some things from Japanese culture </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> This Villager found a new home in my Survival World. I simply cannot get him to return to the surface. He's happy here. :) </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-11-16 20:51:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-11-16 02:58:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Batman ain't got shit on this... Fucking hell! Very impressive! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-11-02 23:40:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hmm. Interesting... Go on about it's life cycle? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Can you come up with a new monster? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-11-02 23:34:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The zombies, vampires, and werewolves are way too overdone. If you're in charge of making a new horror film, what would your monster be like? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-10-25 02:52:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I have received one. Apparently the girl gave him the wrong number on purpose on Tinder. He replied with a dick pic.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-10-25 02:46:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Honestly, and I'm quite serious about this, it was yesterday with this video. A HUUUUGE plot twist. 

http://youtu.be/VFRZX-wHepk

NSFW-ish </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-10-21 17:58:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Stuck a screwdriver in a power outlet. 

To be fair, I was like 7, I have ADHD, and my parents told me not to after I asked. Amazingly I didn't die and didn't go to the hospital.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-10-18 18:11:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Sooo awesome, yet unethical lol </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-10-17 16:22:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Well... Now you have to include a nether portal. Your Dark Lord Satan requires it </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-10-13 06:09:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hide and sneak?

Take your upvote God damnit </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-10-11 17:51:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> No problem! I'd suggest you at least try to find a pheasant hunting preserve near you. Take your dog out there every now and then.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-10-11 15:29:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Well, I never use hearing protection with her. She's fine as far as I can tell. As for keeping them stimulated and happy, Britannies need just a few things: love, places to run, food, water, hunting trips, and Bird-dog Cocaine (AKA, feathers). Seriously, they absolutely love the feathers and it's just like coke to them.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-10-11 00:36:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Britneys are people-pleasing dogs. I absolutely love this dog! She is my little girl! Great hunting dogs. She's got a hell of a nose on her, an unlimited gas-tank, and when a bird gets just a couple of shot pellets in it, she'll see it and go to hell and back to retrieve it. Comes back with the ones that should've gotten away about 95% of the time. She's just adorable and a great friend, and, I'll admit it, this kinda turned into bragging about my dog :) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> My hunting dog gets happy when she sees me. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-10-10 15:55:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-10-10 08:01:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Batman: Minecraft Knight

With overuse of a Batmobile-textured minecart. 

In all honesty, I do want this.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What would you include in an insanely scary Haunted House for Halloween? [serious] </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-10-07 01:02:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You are charged with making a true pants-shitting experience. Something different from all other generic haunted houses. What do you include? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Looking for Zelda: Wind Waker 1.8.8 Resource Pack. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-10-05 21:55:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I need help finding a pack like this. And from a secure download site so I don't get any viruses. I've been able to find them for previous versions, but not 1.8.8. Thanks! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-10-04 19:10:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> As someone with Asperger's syndrome, let me just say that Minecraft is like porn to my brain. All the shapes and learning how they fit together. It's absolutely glorious. I would think others on the spectrum would feel the same way. She has an amazing imagination! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-10-03 05:43:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Did you find him?? I saw your giant poster! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-10-03 02:33:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> No joke. Mine some gold and diamonds bro. You'll need to craft a ring </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-09-27 16:31:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm not so sure about that. I would love for it to be true, but remember Batman Beyond is essentially a direct sequel to the Animated Series. And Tim Drake killed Joker in that timeline </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-09-24 03:49:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The Minecraft gods either like you or hate spiders </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-09-23 05:28:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> My friend, you have patience </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-09-21 14:06:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Pointless. Annoying. Hmm... I like it! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-09-19 17:38:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Fighter are you ready? Fighter are you ready? Let's get it on! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-09-19 17:36:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> God Fucking Damn. I have some work to do </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-09-12 07:46:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Aaaaaaand summoning /u/Fuckswithducks  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-09-08 23:24:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm a black belt, not Master Shifu </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-09-08 23:24:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I used to have rings in my backyard. They have since broke. I wasn't nearly as advanced in my fitness back then </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> A list of advanced bodyweight exercises? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-09-08 21:40:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I've been training for the last 4-5 years. I've gained some pretty neat athleticism. I only do bodyweight stuff and train martial arts. Of course it's important to always test your limits. So, I'd like a list of the most advanced/insane bodyweight exercises /r/Fitness can think of. I love muscleups, clap pull-ups, clap push-ups, handstand push-ups, and hanging sit-ups. Working on the Dragon Flag (getting there). Mostly I prefer the skill increasing exercises that could possibly help me in my martial arts training. I'm starting to run a bit short on ideas. 

Thanks! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-09-05 19:18:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That would be insane. The amount of data... Are you telling me that I can travel the world through Minecraft??? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Let me ask, what is your dream build? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-09-05 18:54:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What would you love to build in MC, but you don't have the time, patience, or the game simply doesn't have the proper blocks/redstone mechanism/decoration?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
