<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject3202</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Can we talk about the N word in books? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-09 23:14:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I like when authors don't shy away from using these words in their work. America has a sordid past and we can't shy away from it. In fact, we have become so sensitive that the mere version of the vanilla version of the word is considered *offensive*. 


* * * * * *


There, I said it. Is the sky falling? Is the world in flames? *Did I just even hurt anybody?*. No no and no. And yet, I bet this post will be removed, and I will be banned. But you know what? That's a price I'm willing to pay to get my point across. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-09 22:13:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Do you think your wife would mind if I massage your bulge in those panties? :) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-09 02:59:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The First Law Trilogy is really good and a must-read for fantasy fans.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-08 21:09:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> However this turns out, it's gonna be hard topping the ending to the movie.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Idea: flashlights and dark maps </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-07 05:52:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Think about it. In real life i imagine a lot of raids happen in dark environment. The ones being raid often kill the lights. And when it happens at night the team must go with flashlights and vision goggles. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-02 08:49:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I want to start reading on Heroin.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-02 07:17:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Lmao </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-02 02:49:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If you like stuff like this, do yourself a favor and read Bird Box. Very different premise, but it is *so good* and one of the only horror books I've read that were genuinely terrifying.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-01 09:12:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Just get a job. Ta da, no more step-father dick sucking </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-01 08:41:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That's fucked up.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What would you do if you had the superpower to make anyone orgasm at any given time? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-01 01:35:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Imagine a Death Note book, but with orgasms instead. I'd do it to Trump while he's on TV giving a speech :) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-30 23:31:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Well that's why I switch to good cop. My aim to come out as an asshole, but a light hearted asshole by the end.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> My favorite msg to confuse Coppers on Xbox. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-30 23:23:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Look, I don't know if you just got this game or you're really that fucking bad, but I swear that if you fuck up one more time me and my buddies won't hesitate to kick you. Me and my buddies won't hesitate to kill you. And trust me , we take turns and we have ideas. 


(This is where I switch to good cop)


More importantly, it is imperative that you practice, because practice makes perfect. Have you tried completing the situations? They're quite helpful, especially since it seems you don't even know how to rappel. Practice makes perfect. Let me know if you need help, buddy. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-29 22:31:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Where can I find your book? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [Spoilers] Will be Saul Goodman the other half end the show with the name? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-29 10:02:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-29 09:56:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Maybe he was just being careful and not saying too much?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-28 19:27:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Tac </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Wait isn't Trump a c*mslut. Put president is a c*mslut wheres the sex tape? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-28 01:57:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> ENCORE is a thriller with black humor- a comedian gets kidnapped by evil twins and forced to perfom jokes for them. I want you to critique the first joke he will tell. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-27 03:50:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-27 01:42:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm lonely  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-26 05:44:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Soo it's bad? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-26 02:34:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You're handsome.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-26 01:24:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> "I'm dripping wet and there's nothing I can do about it!" She did let me know later that problem was solved.  

I think she wanted to have sex </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-25 21:14:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If I killed a lot of people and gain control of trade I would be King. That's how it works. Also Rihanna has more money that Queens in the past 100 years.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Kendrick Lamar -- You Film Me ... Me and My Boys Will Film You Right Back! TMZ and yes I have small dick </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-24 02:18:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-21 20:50:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I don't believe you.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-20 00:05:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> There's still 16 episodes to go. Hold your horses.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-16 06:26:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Last year I attended a conference outside my hometown and on the way back I decided to just sleep around when I got back home because clearly my SO is not looking out to please me.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
