<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject9063</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-06 19:34:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This gif almost loops  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-02 22:52:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Come on man, this is reddit did you really expect me to read the article? The only thing I read was the title and this comment I don't really give a shit haha
Edit: I didn't even read your comment past the first sentence  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-02 16:27:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> But opium has nothing to do with meth... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-01 16:30:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Use it everyday. Make as many beats as you can. One thing that really helped me was watching busyworksbeats fl studio videos and recreating them in maschine. Really helps you learn how to do everything a real daw can while learning on your own </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-01 16:28:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Lol it's only 99$ from NI no one will pay that. 25$-50$ is reasonable  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-01 16:27:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Wow thanks for the heads up! Definitely gonna be part taking in this I've been slacking lately... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-01 16:25:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> No melody always comes first. You can swap out the sounds after I always focus on the melody while using a sound that is somewhat what I want and then swap them out after </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-01 14:43:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Duplicate and chop them individually on each pad to whatever bpm you want. Sometimes you gotta go oldschool </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-29 18:39:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I ended up taking it into Canada computers and they fixed it really quick. Cost around 120+ the price for the new hard drive as well. I don't know what they did to fix it but I'm going to call this weekend and see if they can tell me what was up. Il let you know if I find anything out. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-26 02:19:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Or it's not real.... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-25 22:12:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Okay I will do that

Last night I used an old toshiba laptop that I knew was working and inserted my new hard drive into it as was able to install windows onto it there, but when I put the drive into my hp laptop I get the same bsod. But when I insert the drive from the old toshiba into my hp it boots fine and I can access all the data on the drive. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-24 13:23:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If you re read my comment I couldn't install the os with one of my sticks out </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-24 03:48:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Leafs are sick this year fuck you talking about  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-23 23:30:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> My pic would work with just one? Why would this help? Still going to try it 
Edit: tried removing one stick and it stopped giving me BSOD but just kept looping the hp logo, when I reinstalled that one and took the other out it just gave me the same BSOD  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-23 23:29:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I tried the ISO on another laptop and it worked so it's not the USB or ISO  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Installing Windows on a new hard drive, keep getting BSOD </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-23 21:25:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Trying to install windows using a bootable USB on my new hard drive I installed in my laptop. Keep getting BSOD with the stop code System PTE Misuse. Also ran a 5 hour hard drive test and another 30 minute memory test from HPs system diagnostics screen and they both passed. Anyone have any idea what I'm doing wrong? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> System PTE Misuse error trying to install Windows 10 on a new hard drive </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-22 23:53:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So my old hard drive corrupted and I'm trying to replace it myself. I took the old one into Canada Computers and the guy there recommended a hard drive and said it would work as a replacement for mine. I got home and put it in and tried to boot using a windows 10 configured usb. Once I get past the HP logo  get the error "Your PC encountered a problem and must resstart: System PTE Misuse" and then it's stuck in a boot loop. Maybe I didn't install the drive correctly but I'm pretty sure I did. Any ideas? Maybe this hard drive isn't actually compatable </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-21 20:01:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thanks for this! That's gonna help a lot  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Replacing a hard drive </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-21 18:38:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> A month ago my hard drive broke and my laptop doesn't recognize it. I'm trying to save money by replacing it myself. I've opened up my laptop and unplugged the old hard drive. If I buy the same hard drive will I be able to plug it in and my laptop will work? Obviously there won't be an OS on it so il have to buy windows 10 again but in theory this would work right? 
Would this be a smart thing to do or would I save time and money by taking it to a professional? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-20 02:52:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's probably the cheapest place for an all inclusive vacation from Canada  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-17 22:45:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That makes it a lot less funny lol </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-17 21:13:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This is what got me hahaha what does that even mean  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-15 22:16:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Haha wrong </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-15 21:29:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The assignments in the modules are directly used by TSSA so it's a good idea to go over them, but don't stress too much I found the G3 exam very easy. G2 is another story  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-15 21:27:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yea who the fuck asks how long have you been single for!? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-11 23:42:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Don't know what I expected  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-10 19:03:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Good old Algonquin college  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Anyone in Canada used hvac-exam-guide.com? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-10 02:59:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Bought one of their 10$ Ontario G2 practice exams and never received anything in my email just a receipt from paypal. Bought it on Friday and sent an email yesterday might just have to get a refund from paypal. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-06 21:06:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That's more G2 than G3. Low pressure pipe sizing is on G3s but high pressure and venting charts are G2 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-06 21:05:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's super easy.... just make sure you know your code book well and maybe know some numbers off the top of your head (calorific values, density of NG or propane) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-28 00:44:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Like physically freeze it?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-28 00:43:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That's what I feared, thanks for the help, now I know  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-27 20:39:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yea I'm an idiot, no backups. How much do you think I'd be looking at to get recovered? 700$+? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-27 20:39:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If I were to pay to get the data extracted would I be guaranteed to get all the data? Or would they only be able to recover some of it? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Is it possible to recover my data from my corrupted hard drive? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-27 20:21:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So the other day I went to open my laptop and it was frozen, upon rebooting it I got a message saying there wasn't a hard drive installed. I could also here this clicking noise. I have a crappy feeling the hard drive short circuited and now it's a brick. I had all my school work, photos, and almost a tb of music production software and songs that I desperately want. If I buy a new hard drive, is it possible to recover the data onto the new one? Or is all my data lost forever?
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-23 16:57:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Maybe take a clearer picture? And some more symptoms other than "not working properly" </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-20 16:11:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Not what he said lol </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-17 00:25:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Phillies </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-14 17:51:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I wouldn't buy it new it's just not worth the money. I got mine 2 years ago used for 450 I think probably a lot cheaper now. Just make sure the licence is legit or you'll get fucked. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-08 04:18:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Using hardware or software theirs a ton of ways you could do it with each </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Tattoos? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-21 00:32:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Just got my G3 and OBT 3 tickets in Ontario and am curious about what your bosses think of tattoos? I don't have any but I want to get some in the future and am curious if anyones ever had a problem getting a job because of them in this industry </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-20 20:20:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> How long is this sale for? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-20 20:19:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The first paragraph is about actually subreddit meetups not meeting with dealers. You can't ask for any hook ups on here. Plus I would never meet up with some random off the internet to buy illegal drugs that's just plain stupid. Theirs plenty of other ways to get weed. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-19 07:12:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yea I just get all my acapellas off YouTube lol  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [ORIGINAL] A Miracle Ft. Nipsey Hussle </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-18 21:11:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [ORIGINAL] A Miracle Ft. Nipsey Hussle - Made completely in maschine </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-18 21:09:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-11 03:11:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yup, sticking to manager mode from now in way less disappointing  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-10 20:32:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Sold my whole club doing it 4 times and got fucking Sansone all 4 times </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-10 08:01:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Me too last night!  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-10 02:30:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This is me after selling my whole club to only get Sansone FOUR fucking times in a row </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-11 08:07:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> My dad was a volunteer ski patroller at my local hill and at the end of every year they'd have a big party. Me and my siblings would walk up and down each run looking for stuff and probably made hundreds over the years  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-10 17:21:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Probably nothing really that good </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-10 17:18:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm from Ottawa and we've done this a bunch of times too </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-01 15:42:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Park the bus </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-29 17:10:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This has made the game unplayable for the last week. 90% of my games have been like this but my internet is running fine  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-26 23:17:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> And why can't they tell you... I swear every match I enter it says green bars and then I get in the match and it's fucked </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-26 23:15:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Do you know what difficulty the finals are in offline drafts?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Christmas with the family! [x-post /r/funny] </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-26 20:36:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-26 20:25:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Were still talking about epl keepers...  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-26 18:40:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> But dunnarumma isn't epl..  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-26 02:31:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That's the worst option...  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-26 01:47:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yup... 75 rated Spanish Cb and a 65 rated Japanese player... I didn't notice they can only be done once too...  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-25 16:15:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If you're in the US you can probably do that but here in Canada it is law by code that every crack heat exchanger must be replaced and can't be repaired </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-25 16:13:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Love the fleet foxes, wish I could do more than just up vote to help but I'm just on this sub to learn  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-22 23:56:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> In Canada a cracked heat exchanger is an automatic red tag and lock out as it's a hazardous situation  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-21 19:18:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Lloris is the only keeper that I get worried when I have to face. Guy is like a brick wall you really have to work for your goals </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-20 03:35:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Aim for Fellaini  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Gabonese players are going for max bin </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-20 01:41:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Why does every match I enter have 3 green bars but then INSANE lag in game? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-19 19:42:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Wtf is going on here? I've probably only played 5 online matches since Friday morning some seasons and some fut champions and EVERY one of them has had insane lag. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-18 05:16:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> 100% efficient  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-17 05:52:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I liked begovic more he's better in 1 on 1 situations  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-16 22:41:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> How many gold upgrades did you open?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-16 20:14:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That's what I'm hoping for  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-16 16:44:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hummels boateng  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-16 16:43:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Modric </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-16 16:05:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I guess your right haha there is alot of bullshit already that would probably just piss me off more  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Why aren't handballs called in fut? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-16 15:49:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> They're a part of real football why not fut? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-16 05:41:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Their are programs you can download. I use ds4 but that's for ps4 controllers. Youd have to google for an Xbox version </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> How to get into the controls industry in Canada? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-16 05:24:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I just graduated school today in Ontario Canada. I have my G3 and OBT3 and am taking my tests for the 2's in February. I've heard (someone correct me) that controls is one of the most profitable parts of the industry. Would I need gas and oil experience to get into controls? Or is it more luck and who you know? I love controls, troubleshooting and stuff like that so if I can make more money that way it would be incrdible </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-16 05:14:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Did they say what the sediment was? I've never heard of this. I'd want to make sure it doesn't happen again  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-15 07:32:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I've never seen it in person but from the way it's described in class that sounds like flue gas condensation. I would shut off your furnace and call the company back that installed the inducer  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-15 05:05:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Wow that's really lucky </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-15 05:05:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Futhead app hasn't been updated yet  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-15 04:39:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm still in school so take this with a grain of salt but that sounds like the flue gasses are condensing which can be really dangerous. (someone correct me if I'm wrong)  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-15 01:35:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Loving if dzyuba, just really hard to get good chem links as my main squad is epl </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-15 00:31:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yea I'm pretty sure it's completly random, I just needed a few more guys for the bronze upgrade sbc so I bought a bronze pack and lucked out  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-15 00:21:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I got 9 players in a bronze pack once, never happened again </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Is their no Russian players in the epl? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-14 21:24:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Trying to find a way to incorporate my untradeable if dyzuba to my epl squad cause he's a beast but I cant find any Russian players in the epl is this a thing? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-14 05:47:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I think he's referring to the scream card as the first if </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-14 05:44:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Give us another review after 40 games or so </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-14 04:50:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm only division 6 on ps4 but il play </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-14 02:42:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Switch to an aluminum anode  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Why are my fullbacks playing so far up the pitch? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-13 22:47:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This has been the first fifa I've ever really got into so take it easy on me. Ive been changing my squad up alot but the past couple days [this](https://imgur.com/gallery/oKuk0) has been working well for me the past few days. 

  At the start of the match I switch to attacking, team press, and counter attack on the d pad(not to sure what this is called) which works great except if I give up the ball in the midfield I'm stuck with just my two center backs because monreal and Coleman are in the oppositions zone. Sometimes il try to move it up the side of the pitch and my full backs are in my wingers position.... What can I do to keep my full backs more in position?
  
  Also any recommendations for my squad? My next pick up is gonna be Rooney I think at cm to replace kante or ramsey

Edit: formatting </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-13 22:21:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Anyone have a link to the sway interview?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-13 21:44:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Keep us updated this is interesting  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-13 18:02:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Wow I love reddit </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-13 00:08:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Damn that sucks their should be an option to make custom formations  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> How to adjust formation positioning before match? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-12 23:48:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> When your in a game you can go to the menu and adjust the exact position of a player (and change there position from cm to cdm or cam etc...) is there any way to do this before a match? I want to save a formation a certain way and don't want to change it everytime I enter a match </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-11 17:44:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I use Ramsey then gilfy as my attacking mid </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-09 00:48:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I know that last year I never got fifa 16 and the fifa 15 servers still worked. That was in the past though so I'm not 100% </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-08 05:27:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Busquets is def the worst walkout  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-05 01:15:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Bought xhaxa for like 8k and ended up selling him for Ramsey after a season because he just didn't live up to his rating  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-05 01:14:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Fair enough, that's probably a better way of putting it as he is a great player  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-05 01:13:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I agree with this as well, got him in a black Friday premier league pack and was stoked but I don't even use him cause he just didn't live up to expectations  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Who do you think are the most over-rated players in fifa 17 </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-05 01:03:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> See lots of posts about under rated players in this year's fifa but what about players that don't live up to there rating? Busquets was a big one for me as well as debuchy and bogan. They just didn't live up to my expectations. Maybe its just my play style </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-04 16:04:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Fellaini is great this year and super cheap. Wins every header and can get the ball off anyone  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-04 15:56:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Fellaini is great for the price, wins every header and can get the ball off anyone with ease. He's even got a few goals for me  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-03 05:02:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So what you're suggesting is I make sure I'm hitting the shift key instead of the caps lock? I've already read multiple pages from Bethesda saying that dated back to Nov. 3rd, that is not the answer  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Could not log into the Bethesda.net server </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-02 00:39:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Just got skyrim: se for ps4 a couple days ago and tried to set up mods today but cannot log in on my ps4. Everytime I try I get "could not log into the Bethesda.net server". 

I've read of other people having this problem but couldn't find any solutions. I've tried changing my password but that didn't help. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-01 23:29:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> NI Vintage Organs plugin for Kontakt 5 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [ORIGINAL] Usher - I Still Got It ft. Migos </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-01 22:53:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Usher - I Still Got It ft Migos | a remix I made completely in Maschine </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-01 22:52:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-29 02:04:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Lotsa good people here!  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-29 00:36:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Here in Ottawa at Algonquin college we just had a 30 or so person tournament for 100$ prize. We only had 3 tvs but it was pretty sweet  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-28 01:42:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yup turan was definitely a good investment. This was one of his last matches for him because I sold my squad and for a premier league squad.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-27 21:20:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yea tell me about it.. This guy was the worst guy to play against. Ran down the clock every chance he could, so much lag, used all his pauses at once and had a really racist team name.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Turan goal of the week </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-27 20:55:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-24 17:21:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The more efficient furnaces condense, and use gas or propane  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-21 16:15:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Look into maschine it's great, not a standalone sampler though  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-17 02:53:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Dude...  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
