<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject374</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-10 05:01:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Mister Smith's view would be very interesting, as he is older than the centuries old hotel. He's a very business like and somber character. 

At some point I'd like to do an entry of him observing the behavior of his staff and drawing connections between them and a group of past employees, who met a terrible fate. 

As a result, I'd like to do more posts first from the employees that show the development of Mister Smith into a more paternal figure throughout the series, then have his elaboration and flashback, and have him become both imposing but likeable in the end.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-10 04:56:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'll try to let you know when I discover what the next payment is  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Grandma's Stories Held More Truth Than I Thought </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-10 04:03:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> *There's a path in the Woods,*


*One that twists, one that turns,*


*A road forgotten and dark,*


*'Twas at the end where Witches burned.* 


I sat on the living room floor and listened to my grandmother recite the old rhyme before beginning the story we'd all heard about a million times before. I remember those times fondly, surrounded by my cousins during summer visits. We were all well into our teenaged years at that point, and the stories we were told had taken on a tone for more mature audiences.


Our grandmother loved to sit us all down and tell us the tales that have circulated this town. Often enough they were dark stories, as true history tends to go, but a few I found less believable. The history behind this specific tale was obviously based in fact, but the legend that lived in it's wake seemed too cliche.


As it was told to me, the story is quite simple. Back in the time when burning witches was trending, this town developed a plan for catching witches on the run. Many women who fled their towns in search of safety passed through here, and the townspeople were quite unhappy about this. 


They had a small group of women stand by the road to tell the fleeing women which way to go, the women from the town claimed to be fellow runaways. The accused witches believed they were on the course to safety, and like sheep they fell for the wolves trap. They followed the path into the woods. 


It ended in a sort of clearing, in the middle of which sat a tree larger than any other. That was the tree which they tied the witches to, its bark charred from the numerous executions. The tree was large enough to tie up six girls at once, it stood sturdy and did not burn easily. 


Then came the day when the townspeople led their own daughters to the path, some of them quite young. They were assumed to be witches, and they were told that they would be sent to a town of only witches so that they wouldn't harm anyone. 


They were led down the path, and the daughters burned upon the blackened tree. 


One of these daughters did not belong to the town, and her mother was distraught. No one knew of this woman, or who her daughter was, but apparently she went to the clearing in the woods. She confronted those who had burned her daughter, and they responded by swarming her and tying her to the tree. According to the tale, she burned upon the charred remains of her daughter.


Then there is the part that seems to be mere legend. The part where they leave the clearing as the woman burns, and come back hours later to find no corpse. In the following weeks each person who was part of the witch hunting was dragged into those woods without witness, never to be seen again. 


People go missing all the time in those woods these days, and it supposedly happens every time they stumble upon a strangely blackened tree deep in the forest. They say that woman is still searching for her daughter, taking others as substitute until she is found. 


The first time that I attempted to disprove the legend I was with three of my cousins. I was the youngest at 16, the twins were 17, and their older brother was 19. We decided to go down the path in the woods. 


Caroline and Samantha seemed excited to finally wander the path we had heard about for years, and their brother Andrew seemed to only tag along because he thought we'd get into trouble alone. His presence didn't stop trouble from coming. 


The path was refreshingly cool compared to the sweltering heat we had felt before stepping into the shade. An assortment of greens surrounded us, the thick foliage overhead created a dark tunnel. I expected to hear the hum of nature, but there wasn't a bird call or even the sound of clicking insects. The path was still and silent, save for our feet shuffling along the nearly overgrown trail.


Tall grass and other wildlife had choked the path, leaving the worn down dirt trail just barely visible every few steps. Thorn covered vines snaked along the ground, tripping us at times, and cutting into our ill-prepared sandal clad feet. I almost wanted to turn back, the small wounds stung as we treaded forward. 


The longer we walked, the cooler the air seemed to be. I found myself shivering at one point, and sped up my pace to keep warm. By the time we made it to the clearing my teeth were chattering. 


The clearing was dim, but we finally caught a glance at the sky for the first time in over an hour. The clouds were dark overhead, as though a thunderstorm could begin at any moment. In the center of the clearing sat a tree larger than I thought could exist. It's branches were dry and bare, the tree was long dead but still stood. 


I found myself a bit surprised that the bark of the tree was blackened just as the stories claimed. We split in two groups and wandered about in different directions, planning to meet by the tree in ten minutes. Samantha and I walked deeper into the woods behind the clearing, searching for long forgotten trinkets that may have been discarded by witch hunters. 


Within minutes it seemed as though night had fallen, checking my phone still revealed it to be early afternoon. The darkness was unsettling, and I ran to catch up to Sam who was kneeling on the ground ahead of me. 


We should head back, it's been almost ten minutes, I told her, not wanting to admit that I was actually a little afraid of the dark forest. 


She turned to me as she stood, Yeah, sure thing. 


We had taken only two steps towards the clearing when Sam abruptly turned. She stared deep into the forest, as though someone had called her. 


Sam?


She snapped her head towards me, Did you hear that?


Hear what? I stared at her in confusion, the woods were eerily silent. 


Her eyes widened before she whipped her head back to stare into the woods. Then she started running, faster than I knew she could.


Mom? *Mom!* I'm coming! She screamed as she ran, and I tried to chase her.


Within minutes she was out of sight, and I kept going. I tried listening for the sounds of her voice, but it faded soon after I lost sight of her. I wandered forward, hoping to find some trace of my cousin. I searched for awhile before realizing I should head back, and by then I was lost. 


That's when I saw her, Samantha was right ahead of me. I bolted towards her, and she turned to face me. It wasn't my cousin who stared at me. Her skin was the color of a pale violet sunrise, but most of it was scarred and deformed. She smiled at me, and I stood there like a deer in the headlights.


I'm am Mother. Do you have my baby? She tilted her head to the side as though to examine me.


N-no, I stumbled out as she came closer.


She stepped forward and walked a circle around me, looking me over head to toe. I shivered in fear as she ran a mottled hand down my arm, then through my hair. Then she brought her face close to my neck and inhaled deeply. 


She stepped back and frowned at me, No, but you will. A deal then, though payment made thrice. You will come back in two years, you will bring my baby, and I will return what I have taken.


I didn't know what to do, I wanted to run. I wanted to scream. I was staring at a woman with purple skin and small tree branches growing from her joints. She was a monster, she the *the witch*, and she terrified me. I nodded, too afraid to know the outcome of refusing. 


She bit her thumb, and without having applied any pressure it began to bleed. I shivered at the realization of how sharp those teeth must be. She smeared the blood across her bottom lip, then stepped toward me faster than humanly possible. Before I knew it we were locked in a kiss, and she stepped away before I had a chance to react.


Our deal is binding, she smiled before bringing her blood smeared lips close to my ear and whispering, *Now run, little rabbit.* 


I could swear I heard her laughing as I sprinted in the opposite direction. I started walking when I ran out of breath, and thought over what had just occurred. It wasn't possible. I touched my fingers to my lips and they came back bloody, another impossibility. It took me a minute to discover that I was actually bleeding, I hadn't felt the witch bite me. I licked the blood off my lips and trudged on.


I don't know where I was or how long I had been walking before I collapsed on the ground in tears, but I remember that I heard the sound of birds and other wildlife between my sobs. I couldn't handle the situation I had found myself in.


It was warmer here, and I ended up crying myself to sleep under a mossy tree. I was awoken by the panicked faces of Andrew and Caroline, through the foliage I could see the sun was starting to set. They told me I was over an hour away from the tree, and they were lucky to find me at all. I told them that I'd lost Sam, and we all searched together until it got dark. 


That's when our simple teenaged minds realized that we needed help, and we commenced the long journey back to our grandparents house. We went to every resource to help search for Samantha. I never told a soul about the witch in the woods.


The night passed, a week passed, a month passed, over two years-- three years at the end of August-- have passed and still no one has found my cousin. Our grandparents banned us from the woods after that, but I broke that rule last summer. 


It was the two year anniversary of Samantha's disappearance, and I was due for a visit with the creature who called herself *Mother*. I left my grandparents house in the middle of the night, and set down the path in the woods.


It was cold and dark, and it seemed to take forever. When I got to the clearing there was someone waiting beneath the charred tree. It wasn't *Mother.* 


It was a boy I recognized. He had lived in this town as long as I'd been visiting, and I knew him. We were friends, but we didn't see each other except during summer. If I'm entirely honest, I'd had a crush on him for the duration of our teenaged years. He was the most beautiful boy in town.


Luke? What are you doing here? I gave him a curious look, then glanced around the clearing to check for any other unexpected guests.


I'm um.. not what you think I am, he smiled sheepishly and looked at the ground, it *almost* settled my unease.


What? I accidentally let a nervous laugh slip out, the situation suddenly seemed very awkward. 


I'm here for the Mother.. You owe her something, he seemed to blush when he said it, and it took me a moment to realize why.


The horrifying forest witch wanted me to *have* a baby for her. I don't know what came over me, but I burst into hysterical laughter. Luke stared at me as though I'd gone mad before his very eyes.


Then he walked over to me and gripped me by the shoulders. He looked at me very seriously before telling me that he wasn't human, and he didn't actually look like the person standing in front of me. He told me he was raised with humans who thought he was theirs, and that this sort of thing happened a lot. He told me that he was sorry that I ended up in this situation, and that I should have stayed away from the woods.


He also offered to have a more attractive suitor of his kind attend to me, and I just stood there and stared. At some point during his speech I had realized that this was the only option to save my cousin, and maybe the other missing people. At least it was with a nice guy (is it okay to call an inhuman creature a nice guy?), and it could be worse. Women have babies all the time, and then give them up for adoption. Except for the part where mine would be inhuman and traded to save someone else. *Close Enough.*


He kissed me while I was staring at him, and I just kind of gave in. I won't get into the details, but at some point during that night in the clearing there was a little inhuman creature conceived. 


I've seen Luke a few times since then while visiting my grandparents, but no one knows about what happened. They've made sure of that. Where I live several hours away there is a small section of woods behind my house. Every few days one of *them* comes to the edge of the treeline and watches my house. I didn't tell anyone about them. 


Some of them had horns, or skin of the oddest colors. Some seemed transparent, scaled, or grew plants from their bodies. I didn't understand what they were, but they always requested my secrecy by holding a finger to their lips. 


I kept everything a secret just as I had kept my initial meeting with the witch a secret. When the baby bump became noticeable I lied about a mistaken one night stand with a stranger. I've told my family the baby is going to be adopted.


I'm due in about two weeks, and then I drive out to bring the baby to her new family. I don't know what happens after that.


After all I've been through I hoped to get my cousin back, and maybe everyone else who was taken too, but this morning I woke up to a strange message. 


A note was tucked under my closed bedroom window.


*When the delivery is honored,*


*All the lost shall be let free,*


*Except you, debt ower*


*You still owe payments two and three.*


It seems I didn't pay enough attention to the deal I made.


-----


[HF](https://www.facebook.com/subject374/) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-10 02:32:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I have no idea honestly, I write in random ways that I'm not sure are real or not. 

Thinking of adding a new piece to the Good Shade anthology sometime in the next week or two, just debating on which character to narrate.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-10 01:49:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Linking here later for a longer version of this story ~ </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Grandma's Stories </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-10 01:46:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Back when my cousins and I were teenagers and visited our grandparents each summer, we were told stories. Our grandmother wanted to reveal to us the real darkness of the town's past. I never quite believed one story though.


This was back in the time when witches were burned, and this town developed a plan for catching witches on the run. Many women who fled their towns passed through here, and the townspeople were unimpressed.


They had a group of women stand by the road to tell the fleeing women which way to go, while the women from the town claimed to be fellow runaways. The accused witches believed the false claims, and like sheep they fell for the wolves trap. They followed the path into the woods. 


It ended in a clearing with a large tree in the center. That was what they tied the witches to, the bark charred from numerous executions. It was large enough to tie up six girls at once, it stood sturdy and did not burn easily. 


Then came the day when the townspeople led their own daughters to the path, some of them quite young. They were assumed to be witches, and they were fed lies about where the path led. 


They went down the path, and the daughters burned upon the blackened tree. 


One of these daughters did not belong to the town, and her mother was distraught. No one knew where she came from, but she went to the clearing in the woods. She confronted those who had burned her daughter, and they responded by swarming her and tying her to the tree. According to the tale, she burned upon the charred remains of her daughter.


This is the part that caused my disbelief:

They left the clearing as the woman burned, and came back hours later to find no corpse. In the following weeks each person who was part of the witch hunting was dragged into those woods, never to be seen again. 


It's true that people go missing all the time in those woods these days, but rumour says it happens when they encounter a blackened tree deep in the forest. They say that woman is still searching for her daughter.


I wanted to disprove it, so at the age of 16 I tried. Three of my cousins came along, the twins and their older brother. 


Samantha, Caroline, Andrew l, and I went down the path. We found the blackened tree. Four teenagers went into the woods, and three came out. We told everyone we had lost Samantha.


I knew the truth though. Two years ago Samantha never returned from the woods, and I made a deal to change that. 


I recently found out I'm carrying a baby-- actually the spawn of a strange boy from the woods, but that's a story for another time. Now I'm only six months away from saving my cousin. 


I'll finally give the woman in the woods the baby she's been searching for. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Exhausted </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-08 04:15:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Weary

Tired 

So much pain 

Put me back to sleep again 

I'm sore

I'm sad

It's dark outside 

I can't wait to sleep tonight  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-07 08:07:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> My heart literally stops when I see things like this o.o  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-07 06:34:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If I can pull some poltergeist stunts on this chick, maybe disappearing won't be so bad  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-07 05:51:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm sure the person trying to become me would guess any code with ease, no? This is a decent idea though  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-07 05:49:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Keep an eye on that, you could have a real issue  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-07 02:08:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Maybe *you* are the doppelganger </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-07 02:08:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> O.O </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-07 00:32:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hoping I can do this before I fade too much to do anything </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-06 23:27:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> None of my friends seem to be able to hear me, I don't know how long I have until they're unable to see me, and I'm not sure if they'll trust that I'm the *real* me </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-06 22:52:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This is a great idea, hopefully she isn't enough like me to predict a trap </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-06 22:51:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You've got a point there </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-06 22:31:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> How can I do anything when soon enough no one will be able to see me? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> No One Will Know When I'm Gone </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-06 21:14:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I was at a party when I first saw her. I was a little more than a little drunk, and dancing in the middle of a group of girls who, like me, wanted to avoid the hands of overconfident drunk guys. Normal situation, normal night for us. That's when I noticed the girl, and my mind seemed to block out everything but her at that moment. 


She looked *just like me*. One of my friends bumped into me while I was staring, and I ended up losing sight of her. I was drunk, I could have been staring at my reflection in a window for all I knew, so I shrugged it off. 


I stumbled my way back to the dorm with my roommate, Megan, and we both fell asleep as soon as we hit our beds. The next morning I awoke to an abundance of text messages, almost all of them about similar topics.


*You were acting really strange last night.*


*Who was that guy you were with?*


*Did you make it home okay?*


Concern and confusion flooded my inbox, and I had no idea why. I'd had a few drinks, I'd danced with my friends, and then I went home. There was no guy, there was no acting strange, and there should have been no worry about me walking a few blocks home with my roommate. I remembered the entire night, and none of these messages made sense. 


I responded to everyone in confusion, and most of them dropped it assuming it must have been someone who looked similar. There were a few who pressed on, one even sent a picture. It looked like me, from behind at least. Whoever it was was pressed up against a guy. I disproved that person by sending a picture of myself last night, wearing an obviously different outfit from the girl in the photo. 


I used the same method to calm everyone else down, they had all seen a girl who looked like me but hadn't been dressed like me. The situation stressed me out first thing in the morning, but the day wasn't over yet. 


Megan and I left to head over to our friends apartment, and I received a phone call on the way. I don't remember the entire conversation, but it was a guy who said I'd given him this number last night. I told him he was given the wrong number. 


I didn't start getting concerned until we got to the apartment and our friend Amy answered the door. She gave me a confused look.


Did you forget something? She asked me.


What? Last weekend? I don't think so, I texted you this morning that I was coming over, I responded in confusion.


Danielle, you literally just left. Like ten minutes ago, 


I've been with her, that's not possible, Megan cut in. 


Amy looked back and forth between the two of us, Okay, I don't have time to be fucked with today. I need to study.


She closed the door and we stood there dumbstruck. 


Wow, I attempted to fill the silence in the hallway.


That was weird, but whatever. Let's just leave, Megan responded as she started walking towards the stairs. 


The rest of the day went fine, an average Sunday spent lounging in our room. I had class the next morning, and attempted to get to bed early. I had the strangest nightmare that night.


I was walking around going about my day as normal, but everyone I tried to talk to seemed to be unable to hear me. I would scream, and they would look at me oddly. As the dream progressed people stopped being able to see me, and I wandered around like a lonely ghost. The dream ends when I see my reflection, except that there is a smooth blank plane instead of a face. I woke up wondering how I saw without any eyes.


The dream was unsettling, and I found it hard to wake up from. I managed to get up on time, but somehow I still ended up leaving late. I still had time before class, but I'd be cutting it close.


I felt exhausted, and I needed something to fix that before class. Every morning I stopped in the small coffee shop and ordered the same thing, but when I walked up to the counter I was met with a confused glance. 


Did you spill your drink? 


What? 


I gave you your usual order just five minutes ago.


I wasn't sure what to tell the barista, so I just admitted to spilling the drink and needing another one. I got my drink and left confused, I didn't understand what was happening. 


I was a few minutes late to class, but the professor hadn't started the lecture yet. Things were fine, and the rest of the day seemed normal, and I had the same dream that night.


The next morning I ended up late to another class, and I needed to hand in an assignment immediately. I quickly walked up to his desk, searching my bag for it as I went. I couldn't find it, and I apologized as I reached his desk. 


You already handed that in.


I did?


Yes, when you first got into class, he gave me a look of concern, and I just walked away nodding. 


I could barely pay any attention during that class, wondering what was happening to me. I sat in the back of the room, and I could swear I saw a girl who looked like me sitting several rows away. I couldn't find her when class ended, but the rest of the day went smoothly.


I had the dream again that night, but this time it was faster. I woke up feeling paranoid, and throughout the day I was told that I was in places which I wasn't. 


I went to explain to the library that I needed time to find the book I had to return, but they told me I had returned it the day before. I needed to buy a textbook for a class, and went back to my dorm to grab my wallet. I found my wallet sitting on top of the textbook I needed, the receipt beside it on my bed. 


I skipped a class and went out to eat dinner, but somehow I lost my phone. When I got back to the dorm my phone was sitting on the table, open to a recording of the lecture I'd missed. I thought maybe I was being stalked, and I fell asleep paranoid that night.


Once again the dream taunted me.

Thursday was a mixture of the previous few days, and I found myself stressed out over the entire situation. I felt like I was going insane. Another night of dreaming I was fading away.


Which brings me to yesterday, where things started to become progressively more strange. I went to all my classes, and I spoke to several of my professors who wondered why I'd emailed assignments in more than once. I told them I must have hit something wrong while sending. Several of those professors, as well as a few of my friends asked if I was losing my voice. I'm not sure what they meant because I think I sound fine, but they acted like I was whispering.


Then came the evening, when I went to go back to my dorm room. I couldn't find my key, but I could hear Megan talking to someone in the room. As many times as I knocked no one seemed to hear it, I ended up walking down the hall and running into another friend who was headed into her room. She let me spend the night. I had the dream again, even faster.


I woke up early even though I had no classes in the morning. I searched everywhere for my keys, and was relieved when I found them-- stupidly enough-- in the bottom of my bag. I got back to my room and was prepared to fall into my bed for a much needed nap, but it was occupied. 


So now I'm sitting here in the library typing this up on my phone. I asked the librarian if I could use a computer, but she kept telling me to speak up and I gave up on that idea. 


There's a girl in my bed, and she looks just like me. I don't know what to do, or why she's here, or why I seem to be slowly fading out of my own life, I need help. I have no idea what's happening, but it seems like that nightmare is coming true.


The only thing I'm sure of, is that I don't want to see my reflection. 


-----


[HF](https://www.facebook.com/subject374/)


 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Smoke and Walls </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-05 21:55:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Everything's in a haze

I can't stand to see the world any other way 

Too bright, too dark,

I'd rather not see at all 

But the smoke builds just enough of a wall

Between me and you 

Us and them 

All building walls 

Over and over again 

The day is too cold, the sun too bright

It's all too much 

I'd rather build my walls and such

I'd rather stay warm and veiled in smoke 

I'd rather build barriers and be alone </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-05 21:08:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I felt really sick, but for some reason I didn't throw up. The food didn't taste bad, and my body didn't seem to process the fact that it was *wrong* to eat. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-05 19:42:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It was incredibly over the top, and I would have avoided it like the plague if I knew what we were getting into </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-05 19:41:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I mean, they're probably lost now due to the natural flow of digestion.. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-05 19:40:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thank you 3 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-05 19:40:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That's probably the wisest choice based on everything we've been through.. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> A Dish Best Served Cold </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-05 05:02:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Everyone deals with relationships ending. Sometimes it's because of a mutual agreement that things don't work out, sometimes things end on good terms. Sometimes things end on bad terms, and that's why a collection of businesses have popped up. They mend your heartbreak, give you closure, and ease your overall suffering. 


I never thought I'd be the type of person to use such services, but a few weeks ago my entire world seemed to fall apart. Before that it was nearly perfect. Happy roommate, happy friends, happy boyfriend. 


I was living with my friend at the time, her name was Amanda. She was great, fun to be around, interesting to talk to, a great sense of humor, and a model roommate. There were nights when we bonded while roaming the streets between bars, and she became one of my best friends.


My boyfriend was also amazing at the time, he was charming and sensitive, and he always knew the right thing to say. I started attending the college he went to when the fall semester began, and we ended up dating within a month. He was everything I could have ever wanted, and he treated me like a princess. I did everything I could to make him happy, and he did the same for me.


Unfortunately, he was supposed to transfer to a college that was across the country at the end of my first semester. It was a plan from before we had begun dating, but he had been away from his family a year before that and they had planned to bring him back home. He told me that before we met nothing was keeping him here, and that he'd come back as soon as the next semester ended. 


Things didn't go well once he was gone. He ended up running into an ex about a month after he left. I didn't have a car, and couldn't afford to get across the country to visit him while attending school. He was stuck in the same situation, with his family urging him to stay close to home. He never claimed to be good at long distance, and during a nightly phone call he told me that he cheated, right before he told me we should end things.


I was heartbroken, this being the first serious relationship I'd had since moving into the city. Amanda tried to comfort me, but for weeks I was in despair. I felt like I should have tried harder to see him, that maybe if we hadn't been apart for so long things would have been different. 


One day Amanda broke through my despair with an idea. Someone had told her about a business that helps people get over breakups. She didn't know much about it, so she sent a message to her friend to ask about it. She received a link to a form as a response. 


The form didn't have a header stating the name of the business, and I didn't see it anywhere else. The questions were strangely personal, and I wasn't sure I wanted to give out all that information. Amanda knew it all anyways, and she quickly filled out the form and sent it to the email that was listed at the bottom. 


I tried telling Amanda that I was really uncomfortable sending all that information to strangers, but she assured me that her friend wouldn't have told her about a business that would rip us off. I shrugged in defeat, she had already sent the email anyways. 


Nothing came of it until a few days later, when I received an invitation in the mail. It was for myself and a plus one, so Amanda excitedly volunteered to join me. The invitation itself was odd, but it was obviously from the business that Amanda had emailed. 


*Miss Rebecca Wesley,*


*You and one guest are invited to a formal three course dinner in honor of your recent departure from a romantic relationship.* 


*Please dress accordingly, a vehicle will be at your place of residence at 7pm today.*


Of course, I was concerned by all the information they had-- my home address being part of that-- but Amanda was excited to see what this business could do for me. We got dressed up and met a sleek car in front of our building at exactly 7. 


It was dark, and the windows were tinted to an extent that was likely illegal. I couldn't tell where we were going. Amanda chattered excitedly, but I was faintly worried that something was wrong with all of this. We arrived at a building that blended into the plain surroundings, we could have been anywhere. 


A man escorted us inside, which was far more impressive than the exterior. It appeared to be an incredibly high-class restaurant, and we were escorted to a table for two. Next to our table a small TV screen was set into the wall, but it was blank at that time. 


A waiter came over as soon as we sat down, he handed us each a small menu and asked for our phones. They weren't permitted so that they could guarantee privacy for their clients. It seemed reasonable, and we handed over our electronics. It almost explained the secrecy over the location as well. I could understand people wanting the extent of their misery over a breakup to be kept private.


Upon opening the menu we discovered that we really didn't have any options. There was one selection for each course. When the waiter returned I questioned him about it, and he informed us that the menu was there merely so that we knew what we would be eating.


I wouldn't even know how to begin to spell the foreign names I read, but I believe everything was named something in French. It all sounded strange and exotic, and I found myself a bit excited at the prospect of an elaborate meal. Amanda agreed, there was no point in being worried over dinner since we had no way to tell what it was before it arrived anyways. 


Elaborate it was, I have no idea how to even identify or describe the flavors I tasted. There were sauces, meats, vegetables, and things that I had couldn't even begin to categorize. It was decadent, and by dessert I was nearly stuffed. Everything had been so delicious, I was actually starting to appreciate Amanda's effort to help me get over my ex. 


Two small bowls of ice cream were placed on our table, both covered in what appeared to be an assortment of fruit, nuts, chocolates, and syrups. It looked just as delicious as the rest of the meal had. The waiter told us to enjoy, and suddenly the screen next to us turned on. 


When I registered what was on the screen I was surprised, it was my ex. The screen appeared to be paused during a video of him speaking. Instantly I was nervous, I wasn't sure if I'd be able to keep myself from crying if I heard his voice. I stared down at my dessert, picking off a shaving of some sort of fruit. I nibbled at the fruit piece, worried that the video would start if I glanced back at the screen. I focused on the flavor, it was bitter and tough to chew. It didn't seem very sweet, and I assumed I had only gotten the peel of the fruit. It tasted much better when I tried it mixed with the rest of my dessert. 


Amanda noticed my silence but didn't say anything, instead she quietly ate her dessert as well. A few bites in the video started abruptly, and my exs voice filled the space. 


*Hi, I'm Matthew Hambleton. Recently I made a horrible mistake, and I've been given the chance to make up for it.* 


I stared at the screen as Matthew seemed to look at someone off camera, he nodded before continuing. 


*I fell in love with a girl, and it ended with me breaking her heart. I didn't want to do that to her, she was honestly my entire world-- she still would be if I hadn't fucked up* 


There were tears in my eyes as he cleared the emotion from his throat, and I shovelled my dessert in faster. I couldn't understand how this was going to make me feel better.


*Sorry.. That's not the point. I'm here to admit what I've done, beg for forgiveness, maybe even hope that you'll take me back in the end. I'll do anything to make this up to you Rebecca.*


The true tears came when he said my name, and Amanda put her arm around me as Matthew described his mistake" in complete detail. His parents pressuring him to leave me, friends and family alike urging him to go back to his ex, urging him to stay home and start a family there. He revealed everything, up to the morning that his ex woke him up with a kiss, and when he realized she also happened to be half naked Well, we all know what happened. 


He was pressured, he was seduced, he felt awful, and none of that made me feel any better. I felt nothing but a deep ache in my chest by the time he ended the video.


*That's the truth. It will always be my biggest regret, and I'm going to do everything I can to get you back Rebecca. I swear I'll make this right.*


I sat in my seat and cried. I was miserable, my dessert was gone, and the person I was in love with still wanted to fix my broken heart. I couldn't imagine what he could do that would fix anything, it all seemed like such a lost cause. What was stopping him from doing this all over again? He was a good guy, but there was so much negative pressure in his life. He was the one who left me after all, though I might have made the choice myself if I was given time to process.


Amanda gave me a small smile and a squeeze as the video ended, then slid over her half finished dessert. I took the silent offer, and continued trying to drown my feelings in the sugary dish. 


Another video started playing on the screen, and I steeled myself for more heart-rending messages created to give me closure. 


The video started with the camera being set up in a room with a concrete floor. Everything was clean, the walls white, and the lights bright. The camera panned over to a previously unseen corner of the room, where a man sat latched to a surgical table. 


Several doctors enter the room, surgical masks and gloves already in place. Not a word was spoken by the surgeons throughout the video, but they handed around a sheet of paper that seemed to be a list. 


The man on the table apparently was undergoing this procedure without anesthetic, since he started screaming when the scalpel touched his skin. 


I looked to Amanda in shock, *what is this?* She said nothing, and we both couldn't help but turn back to the screen. 


We watched in morbid awe as the surgeons removed sections of fat and muscle from the stomach and thighs of the man. The camera would zoom in at those parts, so that you saw in explicit detail as the scalpel sliced neatly between layers of flesh. 


The man screamed in agony, but whatever words he was trying to get out were unintelligible through his pain. Around the time that they opened up his midsection, he passed out. They removed what I believe was a kidney, then closed him up. 


I was still confused about seeing this, other than the man being awake this seemed to be an expertly done surgery. I absently picked at a fruit peel that was stuck between my teeth while the video continued, and took a horrifying turn. 


The surgeons had all his other wounds closed, the monitors showed everything to be going great, and that's when they did an amputation. The camera was painfully close as the scalpel moved between the mans thighs, and his body twitched when it made contact with his tender area. He remained unconscious, but not for long.


He screamed in the most agonizing way, a sound full of true pain and despair. The surgeons ignored the sounds, and expertly removed his appendage and stopped the bleeding. Once it was removed one of the surgeons brought a mask to the patient's face, his head fell back within moments once the relief of medication hit him. 


The screen cut to black for a moment, but it wasn't over. I didn't look away, but I was confused. It was a slideshow of pictures, all in a kitchen. It showed different ingredients being prepared and cooked. The images flashed by quickly, but something had caught my eye. It was familiar but I didn't have time to pinpoint it. The slideshow ended with a picture of each complete dish, all of which we'd eaten that evening. 


I gave a concerned glance in Amanda's direction, but a voice came from the TV before she noticed. I looked back to see Matthew, lying in a hospital bed. He was in tears.


*I know.. It was too much, I didn't know what they were planning. I just wanted to help you. I'm so sorry Rebecca, I hope you can forgive me even after this*


I was dumbfounded for a moment, and then the slideshow replayed. Slower. 


I soaked it in. A familiar looking piece of meat being seasoned, a strange organ being sliced into strips and sauteed, a fleshy looking object being delicately skinned by an apple peeler. I felt sick. 


The video ended and the waiter was suddenly there, before he could say anything I demanded to speak to someone in charge. I was repulsed, I couldn't believe the conclusion my mind came to. 


The woman in charge wasn't much help when I accused her of torturing people. She assured me that contracts and fine print went a long way in this world, and that if I had a complaint this place would disappear within hours. I didn't know how to respond, but she filled the moment of silence.


Which dish did you enjoy the most? It's usually the dessert, they do say that revenge is a dish best served cold, she smiled at that, before turning and walking away. 


I tried to go after her, to scream about how I didn't want vengeance in the first place, but a set of burly men drug both Amanda and I out. We screamed and tried to fight back, we were outraged at what we saw, but it was to no avail. We were shoved into the back of the car we had arrived in, and it sped off as soon as the doors closed. 


I cried into Amanda's arms throughout the drive, we whispered about how this was surely the end. I was almost relieved when the car stopped and the door opened, the first thing I saw was the hospital sign. We crawled out of the car as fast as possible, and flinched away from the man who stood outside the vehicle. 


He did nothing except toss our phones on the ground in front of us, then got back into the car and sped away. 


That was our last interaction with that business. We found Matthew in the hospital, he had no idea how to track down who had done this. He had no memory of the surgery, or anything that had happened after he filmed his apology video. Amanda has tried to find the emails, but they're entirely gone. We have no way to catch the people who did this. 


Matthew is still in the hospital, it's been about two weeks from the incident. He's missing a kidney and a fleshy sword, but he's healing really well. I visit him every day, and I feel horrible that I caused this. Somehow, he still wants to be with me, and I'm more than willing to work on things after all he lost for me.


Plus.. I know it's wrong, but I just can't help having this reoccurring thought. 


He can't cheat on me this time.


------


[HF](https://www.facebook.com/subject374/) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-04 22:48:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Poor little dog :c  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-04 21:10:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm oddly just very sad after reading this  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-04 20:59:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I actually have moved since this experience </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-04 20:56:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm assuming dental records or something similar, this is just the information as it was given to me  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-04 18:59:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The only reason he didn't kill me was because I lived next door, or else I would be an ideal victim  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-04 16:47:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hmm so you might have some humanity and feel bad for me, if I hadn't thrown rocks towards birds. Nowhere did I state I was hurting or killing birds, and the first time I spoke of them I threw the rock at the fence. I threw stones into the yard to scare them away, not bludgeon small creatures to death. 

I hope a serial killer impersonates your neighbor and murders you. 3 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-04 16:32:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Wait, what? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-04 16:31:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'll see you in hell I guess 3 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-04 16:30:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Not to hit them, just by the fence to make them fly away and stop picking apart the yard.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-04 16:29:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm pretty glad about that too
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-04 16:27:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I did move away, but it was the birds man. They never entirely left.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-04 06:28:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I think she'd try, she truly has always been my only protector out here.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Too Close To Home </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-04 04:25:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Every night at exactly 11:45pm my dog barks at my neighbor. He gets home from work at the same time each night, and it's been this way for the year that I've lived in this neighborhood. It bothered me the first few weeks, but eventually I grew used to it. It's kind of comforting to know that the old man next door is home for the night. 


He was a nice man, my parents quickly befriended him. They had helped me move in my meagre possessions last year, and they ended up sparking a conversation with the neighbor while he checked his mail. 


His name was James Barton, and he'd lived in that house his entire life. He was the same age as my father, and apparently they had graduated high school together. They hadn't been friends back then, but James said he thought he recognized my parents. My mother graduated two years later, so they would still have been attending at the same time. 


My parents didn't recognize James, but he seemed like a great guy. My mother had planned to cook a nice family meal to celebrate my new home, and she invited James to join us for the housewarming. It was nice, there were laughs and pleasant conversation. James didn't speak a lot, but when he did it never ceased to bring out at least one smile. 


Over the last year James has attended a couple of our dinners, and we make pleasant small talk when we see each other outside. He's become great friends with my father, and often enough I think Dad visits me just as an excuse to make plans with James. It's nice though, I feel safe when my neighbor is around.


He's kept me informed about the neighborhood, about how to stay safe when I have to go to work or walk my dog. I didn't mention it to my parents, but often enough there was somewhere within ten blocks featured on the nightly news. They already thought the place was dangerous, but I didn't need them to reel me back home after I'd only just decided to make it on my own. More than enough people survive bad neighborhoods.



My dog, Jade, loves our neighbor. She's always excited when he's around, and he always had treats because he had his own dog as well. His dog was a small lap dog, nothing like my larger Pitbull-Mastiff mix. His little Smokey was cute at least, but definitely not my type of dog. 


Jade was not only strong and protective of me, but she seemed to just be the perfect dog. She kept me safe and in good company, an ideal pet for a woman in her early twenties. She knew the daily routine, and she was smart. My dog was part of the reason that my parents agreed to let me use my savings to move into this one bedroom bungalow. The rent was relatively cheap, and it was close to where I worked, but it was in the bad part of town.


I think my parents were put slightly at ease about the neighborhood once they saw it didn't look entirely destroyed, and having a friendly neighbor nearby in case of an emergency was a plus. I was happy, finally out on my own and working towards building my life. For the longest time I felt entirely safe, as though nothing could get to me through my neighbor and dog. 


Things in the neighborhood could be crazy, what with the news of a supposed serial killer roaming the city, and the sheer amount of criminal activity that surrounded this area on a regular basis. I kept to myself for the most part, made friends with a few neighbors and James. Some of the people are odd, but James was never one of them. The oddest thing about James was something he often mumbled to himself.


Sometimes, after we'd have a conversation I'd hear Mister Barton talking to himself quietly. Usually it was nonsense, some small tangent of a memory replaying in his head because of something we'd spoken about. I think that I must have reminded him of someone, because I heard one phrase quite often after we spoke.


*Too close to home.*


He sometimes seemed sad after we spoke to each other, and sometimes I felt bad that I may be triggering a painful memory from his past. He was my best friend in the neighborhood though, since so many of the other neighbors were *creepy*, they all seemed to blend into the shady environment we lived in. My dog kept me safe from them, and so did Mister Barton. 



One night I stopped feeling so safe. I was dancing around my kitchen, music playing and water set to boil on the stove. It was dark, but my house seemed warm and cozy. The kitchen light was bright and it made it hard to see out the windows, but I knew Jade was somewhere sniffing around our small backyard. It was nearly midnight, and I'd been advised by multiple neighbors to avoid walking the streets alone around here. Sure, Jade is pretty tough, but a gun can always beat a dog. 


So Jade was confined to the yard until she commenced her nightly ritual of barking at Mister Barton's car when he pulled in. Those were actually the only times I ever let her out in the small yard instead of going for a walk. The barking didn't happen though, I put the pasta in the pot, skipped to the next song in my playlist, and then noticed the time. It was a few minutes after midnight, and Jade hadn't barked. I walked into the small living room to look out the window and see if Mister Barton's car was there, but it wasn't. I figured he must be late, and decided to leave Jade outside until I had eaten. 


I strained, served, and ate my midnight meal, but still hadn't heard any barking. When I went to the back door to let Jade in I found her staring into Mister Barton's yard, just standing still and looking at the lawn. There was nothing there that I could see. It took a minute before she noticed me calling and came lumbering in the house, but she stopped and looked back at his yard as she got to the door. I stared into the yard, then picked up a stone and threw it at the chain fence. 


Several birds flew from the overgrown grass of my neighbors yard, and I was satisfied with the result. Jade had been transfixed on them. There was no barking at all that night. Jade wasn't a loud dog, she only barked when a stranger came near the doors of the house or when Mister Barton got home. Neither of those things happened. 


Over the next few days I found myself bored, Mister Barton wasn't around to talk to while I was outside. I tried to occupy the free time, but things were odd without the usual presence. We lived in a part of the country with fair weather pretty much year round, and I tried to fix up my backyard to deal with the boredom. 


I'd cleaned out the yard months ago, like nearly every other yard in the neighborhood it had been full of junk. I remember the days I spent cleaning out the yard fondly, because occasionally Mister Barton would see me and help. He was always good conversation while we got rid of useless items left behind by old renters.


Sometimes I'd see him planting things in his yard while I was busy, but it never ceased to look like a jungle. His grass was tall and overgrown, plants and flowers grew at random. It was pretty in a natural way, and that's exactly how James Barton had wanted it. 


I'd asked him once if he wanted me to mow his lawn, but he declined the offer. 


This space is the one place that holds true, natural freedom. It belongs this way, he had spoken with a smile on his face, his eyes seeming lost in a memory. 


After a two days of working in my yard alone I couldn't take it, I felt so alone and unsafe in the neighborhood. My dog was too quiet, my neighbor had disappeared, and I resorted to stoning birds. It was my only way to fight back against my growing paranoia about the dangerous location I resided in.


Occasionally I have enough spare change to have some recreational fun, and with my neighbor being gone I found myself able to freely have such fun. I didn't want my smoking habit to get back to my parents, so I usually kept it to my bedroom when I needed to. With my neighbor being gone I was free to sit on the cracked concrete ledge that my landlord dared to call a patio. 


So that's what I did, I sat in my yard. A stoned girl throwing rocks at the birds who landed in the yard next door. I'd stare at the yard and wonder if James Barton was dead, buried in a cemetery under flowers that were arranged neatly. I felt like he'd rather let his grave become overgrown, hidden among natural beauty. 


I didn't like thinking that way though. He was the same age as my parents, only in his mid-fifties. I didn't like knowing that someone that age could suddenly drop without a warning, Mister Barton couldn't be dead. 


It was four days after my dog stopped barking, a warm morning. I got up, got dressed, poured a coffee, and put Jade on the leash for her morning walk. We walked to the mailbox where I stood and looked through my mail, and then Jade whimpered. I looked to her, then to the driveway she was staring at. Mister Barton's car was back.


I was excited, I wanted to know the reason behind his sudden absence. I went and knocked on his door, Jade jumping around excitedly at my feet. No one answered, and I left to take Jade on her walk after several minutes of waiting. Perhaps he was asleep.


After work I knocked again, only to find the same thing. I was disappointed. He had been gone for days, but it seemed that I would have to wait to figure out why. Before dinner I sat in my yard and smoked, the sun was setting. All the lights in Mister Barton's house were off, and it still felt empty to me. 


I threw stones at the birds and watched a cluster fly up and circle overhead, I felt myself make a face of disgust-- I hated birds flying over my head. I watched as they came back down, and for some reason it sent a chill through me. My friend and neighbor had been replaced by a flock of beady eyed creatures. Maybe it was because I smoked too much, but the birds made me feel afraid. What if they were mad about the rocks? 


I shut myself into the house for the night, planning on discussing the birds with Mister Barton the next day. I didn't want them to hurt the garden he loved so much. Unfortunately the next morning was the same as the last, and I found myself spending another few days wondering why Mister Barton was avoiding me.


Sunday came along, and with it brought my parents. They asked about Mister Barton, apparently my father had been trying to get in touch and make plans. I told them what I knew, and my mother took it upon herself to knock at his door. She received the same response as I did, and we all questioned the strange behavior of James Barton over dinner. 


Another few days of smoke, stones, birds, and dogs that didn't bark. That's when the woman who lived on the other side of James Barton called someone. She had noticed the car remain still, and the mail overflow from its box. She was concerned, worried that the old man might be trapped in his home and hurt. I hadn't thought of it that way, I had taken the first part of his absence heavily into consideration and assumed that it was all connected, which made it seem like he was avoiding everyone.


They didn't find an injured Mister Barton, but they found many other things. They found Smokey, Mister Bartons small terrier-mix. I was horrified when I heard the news, someone had actually strangled the dog. I still can't understand how anyone could be so cruel. 


Someone at the scene noticed the curious amount of scavenger birds circling the backyard, and it wasn't long until they decided to look deeper. Deeper as in, they dug up the overgrown yard. They destroyed the wild beauty and revealed organized decay. Neat rows of bodies were buried in the yard, most of which have been identified as people who were suspected victims of a local serial killer. 


One body in particular stood out, the body of James Barton. James Barton, who had lived in the house next to mine for his entire life, who had attended the same high school as my parents. James Barton, who still kept the yearbook from his senior year in his house, the same year that my father graduated. James Barton, who should have looked familiar to my parents, because he was actually on the football team with my father. James Barton, who was murdered in his home and buried in his backyard. James Barton, who had his identity stolen. 


I've seen pictures of the real James Barton since then, and the imposter was quite accurate in his impersonation. The true James had been dead around three years, and the man I knew had kept his cover all that time. The person who had made me feel safe in an unsafe place happened to be the most dangerous person possible. 


They haven't found the imposter. He seems to have moved on to his next set of victims, or maybe into permanent hiding. If you're a young woman in your early twenties, then you match the type of victim that he seems to favor. When I heard the description of his victims it made my blood run cold, and sent a wave of realization through me.


I understood what he meant when he walked away from me muttering under his breath.


*Too close to home.*


-----

[HF](https://www.facebook.com/subject374/) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-03 20:34:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The most memorable one I remember seeing when I was around 7, the Amityville Horror remake had just come out and I was watching it in the living room with my parents. That was followed by some horror movie about werewolves that I fell asleep after. Woke up in the middle of the night terrified and thinking the dead girl was in the house.

The first one though, was a few of the nightmare on elm Street movies. My parents sent me to a friend's house when I was fine or six, he was a few years older so he picked the movies.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-03 20:01:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It all started with us going there to drink the Crystal Pepsi, without that this never would have happened.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-03 19:59:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> My apologies, I meant to state that it did stop. I never heard it again after the incident at the Price house, which is why I assume it was some sort of tactic to guilt me. I have no idea how it relates at all to the final outcome of things, but it was just something that occurred in such perfect timing that I assumed it must be related.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-03 17:31:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Okay?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-03 05:21:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I definitely will if anything progresses, it just seems too strange to have found this suddenly </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-03 05:20:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'll definitely work on getting a gun, I swear this keychain has to be recent. I only packed these boxes and bought them here a few weeks ago, and I definitely didn't pack that. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Fading Faithless </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-03 05:08:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Once a world of black and white 

Now a plane of greys

Gone is all the vibrant light 

Missing sun-bright rays

Things are dim

Numbness sets in 

Playing a game that I cannot win 

I'll say sorry every time 

I'll let you hurt me 

I'll accept your lies 

I'm sorry, my dear 

It's all my fault 

Sorry for my tears 

I can't help that they fall 

I wish I was better 

I'm doing everything wrong 

I try to be enough 

But I guess I'm not strong 

Strong like you, 

The fighter, the yeller

My love, it's true

I'd let you love me black and blue 

I'm in love

It's not fair

Yes it hurts

I don't care 

I'm sure I will 

One day

I'll have my regrets 

Things could get better

But I'm nearly faithless

I want things to be fine 

I want things to be right 

But my hope fades more

Every time that we fight

I'm sorry, I'm sorry 

For bringing it up 

I'm sorry for staying 

I'm just trying to be enough





 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> I Shouldn't Have Tried Crystal Pepsi </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-03 04:07:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Remember a while ago when there was some big thing about people having Crystal Pepsi? I don't remember exactly when, or what the big deal was, but I remember when my friend offered me a can. 


Apparently his dad had several cases sitting in his work shed.


Now the thing about my friend Dominic is that his parents are *weird.* It was a little off-putting. His mother collected porcelain dolls and fancy plates. His father collected soda merchandise and coins. They were really intense about their collections, but they were never ones to waste money. 


I don't think anyone else in the neighborhood had near the same amount of savings as the Price family. They were extremely responsible with their money, and weren't against selling valuable pieces of their collections. They both worked steady, well paying jobs, and they lived in a house well below their means. They didn't spend frivolously just because they could, they planned to have a nice sum to guide them through retirement. 


Dominic Price wasn't as serious as his parents though. Part of why we were friends was his amazing sense of humor, he was one of the funniest people I knew. He was adventurous, and throughout the years we'd gotten into all sorts of trouble together. We were infamous among the neighborhood.


That's besides the point though, because on this day all our infamous duo was doing was taking one can of Crystal Pepsi from one of the many cases that were stacked in the back corner of the work shed. 


To keep a short story short, we drank a can in the shed. It tasted weird, and it was just a general waste of time. There was one interesting thing I noticed in the shed while we looked around, it was an old keychain with the Pepsi logo on it. It was pretty cool looking. 


Dom suddenly picked up the keychain and tossed it at me, Want it? Dad's got a million, he'll never notice. 


I nodded and pocketed the keychain as we left. I knew I shouldn't have taken it, but I did anyways. It was almost like it was a gift from Dom. Anyways, I walked out with a neat trinket, and Dom finished off the gross pop. I didn't think much of our little shed escapade, except to worry that Mr. Price would find out and be upset. 


It was a week later when I sat down with the Price family for dinner, and my anxiety over being caught was validated.


Have you two been in my work shed recently? Mr. Price spoke casually, as though he was used to people entering his shed without permission.


I looked to Dominic for his reply, because I had no idea if we planned on telling the truth. 


Yea, we tried out one of the Crystal Pepsi's last weekend, he admitted.


His father nodded, and asked that we get permission before going into his shed. The rest of dinner went smoothly, but I couldn't help but still feel nervous that Mr. Price knew about what I'd taken. 


When I left the house that night I could swear Mr. Price glared at me as we said goodbye. I didn't sleep well that night. I brushed it off as guilt over the petty theft, but the sounds freaked me out. I kept hearing a noise which sounded like someone pacing outside my bedroom window. 


Over the next week I wished my room was located on a higher floor, because I swore that something was outside. It tapped and scratched at my window, and several nights I saw a silhouette standing out on the lawn. I was afraid, I thought that maybe Mr. Price was trying to scare me into a confession. 


If that was the case, it worked. I showed up at their home on a Saturday afternoon, but Dom was out. I admitted that I was actually there to see Mr. Price. We walked into his living room together, and each sat in a chair. I pulled the keychain from my pocket.


I'm sorry Mr. Price, I took this from your shed a few weeks ago, I spoke nervously, rushing to get the words out. 


I know, and you kept it from me. You lied about what you took from my shed, his voice was low and stern, it sent a wave of fear through me.


I-Im sorry, I stuttered out the apology, in no place to correct him on exactly who had told the lie. 


Listen, his tone softened, I normally wouldn't care about a small theft, but this thing is cursed.


I stared at him for a moment, waiting for the punchline to this joke. He remained calm and serious, so I just nodded at his statement. Mr. Price was weirder than I'd thought. 


There's something inside it, he continued, but quickly broke into a fit of laughter, I'm sorry, it's just you almost seemed to believe it. This thing does have a history of being stolen, but that's all. 


I was confused, and honestly didn't find the joke very funny after the week I'd had. I was polite as possible for the rest of the conversation, and left as soon as I could. As I was leaving I heard Mr. Price call out a final statement to me.


Returning it doesn't change the fact that it was stolen, and that you lied to my face.


I was stepping out the front door as he said it, I turned to apologize once more but his wife closed the door in my face.


I thought the weird noises and strange figures would go away once I returned the keychain, but nothing changed. I spent another week nearly sleepless before I found myself back at Dom's house for dinner. 


His mother let me in and led me to the table, Dom was already seated and nodded towards me in a greeting. Mrs. Price left to go to the kitchen, and Mr. Price sat imposingly at the head of the table. There was an odd tension in the air, and I felt uncomfortable sitting there. I noticed that the table hadn't been set, which made me realize how unusual it was for everyone to be seated for dinner so early.


When Mrs. Price came back into the room she was holding a hammer, and her husband suddenly stood. I sat in shock as they walked over to me. I wasn't expecting the hammer to slam down on the hand Id left resting on the table. I heard the crunch of bone before I screamed. It was the worst pain I'd ever felt, and I was too shocked to move. 


The hammer came down a few more times, landing squarely on each of my knuckles. I flinched each time I heard my bones breaking, but by the last one I wasn't sure if I could feel it. My right hand was a useless, mangled mess. 


Mrs. Price gripped my shoulders as her husband moved away from me. She wasn't very big or imposing, but she was strong enough to keep me in place while I groaned in agony. I don't think I could have moved very much if she hadn't been holding me, the pain was intense. 


I wanted more than anything to leave, but I couldn't understand why Dom hadn't moved from his seat. That's when Mr. Price pull his son's seat away from the table, and I saw that his hands were bound. 


In some places, the punishment for stealing is very costly, Mr. Price smiled, you two are lucky. 


I stared in disbelief as held the hammer above Dom's hand. That was the moment when Mrs. Price leaned close and whispered to me.


*Run, don't tell anyone what you saw. There's a similar punishment for spreading rumors, she giggled at that, and it sent a chill through my body, No one would believe it either.* 


She gave me a slight shove, and I ran out of the room as the first of Dom's screams rang out. The street was busy, loud. I couldn't hear any screams once I was outside, but I still ran. I ran until I got home, feeling guilty for leaving Dom. They were his parents though, and I was a skinny teenager. I didn't know how to help. 


When I got home my parents were waiting for me, they weren't surprised by my bloody hand. They received a call from Mr. Price where he explained that I had gotten into a fight with Dominic. Today was the day they had planned on moving out of the state, and according to Mr. Price I was mad that no one had told me they were leaving. 


My parents were disappointed in me, assuming my broken knuckles were from a wall I had supposedly put a hole through at the Price home. We went to the hospital about it, and even the doctor told them that it didn't appear to be caused by punching something. They didn't really acknowledge it, too deep in their acceptance of what Mr. Price had said. He was their friend, a fellow parent in the neighborhood, of course they trusted them. 


Dominic wasn't in school on Monday, and when I walked by the Price house at the end of the day it appeared empty. I steeled myself and walked up to the door, knocking softly. No answer. I peeked in a window and found the house devoid of furniture. They really had moved away. 


It's been years since then, but I've never found a trace of them. I don't know why they believed in such severe punishment I for theft, or why someone was outside of my home. Maybe thinking I'd tell my parents and make myself less credible in the end? Regardless, no one has ever believed my side of the story. The only reason I even thought to tell anyone about this is because I found something in an old jacket of mine today. 


It was an old Pepsi keychain that I *know* I returned.


-----


[HF](https://www.facebook.com/subject374/) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-01 04:02:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I can only hope she's somewhere out there. 

If I hadn't delved into the liquor cabinet after posting this I would address the rest of your wonderful message, but thank you for your excellent insight on the subject.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-01 03:59:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Anytime c:  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-01 03:12:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The authorities are doing their best to find her, and my wife is very hopeful. I'm not sure if I'm quite so optimistic after my experience.. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-01 02:44:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I wonder now, if this creature called Guilt is the reason that the elderly act as they do. Either consumed by the past and withering away, or determined to live a happy life despite what happened before.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-01 02:11:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Would we be so prone to dwelling on past mistakes if we knew that thinking too deeply would lead to worse things? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-01 01:52:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Lol how dare you promote yourself on *your own* content! Shameful, what a travesty. How dare you get credit for what you've done! How *dare* you make finding your content easier for other people. 

How dare you indeed  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-01 01:49:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I have never cringed so much at a description but God that grossed me right the fuck out  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Guilt </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-01 01:39:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Usually, when a person describes a day using the metaphor *worst day of my life*, they've had a rough day. Be it due to work, an embarrassing moment, a regrettable choice, or a tragic event, some days seem to deserve this title. Of course, it's usually exaggerated, but everyone is guaranteed to experience the worst day of their lives at some point. The issue is, there's only one day that exists where it's accurate to label it that way, and almost no one alive has experienced it yet.


After all I've been through, I've realized how casually we throw around the title of *Worst Day Ever*. Prior to the recent events, the worst day of my life was easy to recall. 


I was young, and admittedly not the most attentive to the feelings of others. You can't always expect great things from 17 year old boys. I thought I was a pretty sensitive guy, I was nice at least, and I'd never had any issue with another student. I had my few close friends, and everyone else I was just friendly towards. For the most part, high school held minimal teenaged drama for me.


Then came the second half of senior year, where Prom and Graduation sat happily waiting mere weeks away. At the time my friend group had narrowed down to only the two people I was closest to, and senior year was amazing for us. We drove around on late night adventures together, wandered the woods at the edge of town, and attended every party that would have us. 


Most of or party attendance was a few minutes where one of us would grab a bottle of liquor from the kitchen, while the other two spoke to the party host. In less than ten minutes we'd be in and out of a party, and off to spend our Saturday nights drinking stolen bottles by the creek in the woods. It was Ashley, Riley and I, the three musketeers. 


Ashley was one of those girls who didn't get along well with other girls. She wasn't exactly a tom-boy, but she'd rather not deal with all the drama that groups of girls seemed to be clouded in. We became friends in our sophomore year, after she tore apart some guy in our English class. He had been spouting random nonsense about how everyone on Welfare was a lowlife, and she ran up one side of him and down the other over his ignorant claims. She was pretty outspoken when she was annoyed at someone. 


We were fast friends, without any of us really having to say it. Riley and I had lived down the street from one another since birth, but didn't realize we had a lot in common until middle school. Ashley may have been a few years late into the friendship, but from the first day we had lunch together it was like she had always been there. She accepted two random boys sitting with her at the lunch table without question, and spoke to us like we were already old friends. 


It was perfect, it was easy, and I couldn't ask for better friends. Then I went and ruined it. I could go on and on about the great times we all had, but the biggest event in that friendship was not a happy one. That's my fault though, it should have been the best night of our high school careers. 


Now, I don't mean to sound cocky or anything, but the three of us were an attractive group. We'd each had our fair share of relationships throughout school, but two weeks before prom hit we found Riley to be the only one in a relationship. Since Ashley and I couldn't lock down dates who actually *wanted* to go, she asked if we could go together. It was a platonic thing of course, we'd been friends for so long.


The big thing about it was that Ashley *really* wanted to go to prom. She had gotten an expensive dress and shoes when her ex had asked her months ago, but his way of breaking up with her was publicly asking another girl to prom. Very publicly-- as in, he did it during the middle of an assembly in front of the entire school. She was devastated considering they had been together for a year, but she thought going to the dance would prove something. I agreed, honestly in the last three years she had become a better friend to me than Riley. He had been slightly hard to track down since senior year began and he started dating a girl named Leslie. 


So that was the plan, I'd go to prom with Ashley so that she could look amazing in front of everyone who saw her huge embarrassment two months prior. The only issue with the plan was that I was late.


Prom was on a Saturday, and I had a plan for my friends and I. I woke up later than expected, nearly 2pm. I had more than enough time to arrive by 7. Riley and Leslie were taking a limo-- the perks of having well-off parents-- and Ashley was going to be arriving with them. I told them I'd meet them there. 


I had a plan to make a little after-party for the four of us, at our favorite spot. I spent the day collecting the things we'd need, and setting things up at the location. By the time I was finished it was just after 7, I was already late. Thankfully I had preordered our tickets, so Ashley could get in without me. I felt bad for being late, and I planned to head directly over to the prom. That's what I did, but there was a distraction.


I got a phone call on my way, which I answered while driving, a quick glance showed my ex-girlfriends face on the screen.


Sabrina? 


Um.. I'm sorry, I know it's late, but are you busy? She sounded nervous through the phone.


It's not that late, I'm just driving, I told her.


Oh, well that's the thing. Do you think you could stop by and give me a ride to prom? My um.. my ride cancelled, She stumbled over the words, and I felt a little bad for her.


I agreed to stop by, it wouldn't be too far out of my way. If I'm honest, I missed her. We had broken up back before Christmas because she was somehow convinced that I'd never make the effort to see her once she left for college the next year. I felt awful over it because I had actually applied to the same schools as her so we could stay together, but it was supposed to stay a surprise until I learned if I had been accepted.


Let's just keep it short and sweet. I got to her house and she was still in her room, her mom has always been fond of me and sent me upstairs. In her bedroom I made a choice, and I didn't realize how important it was. I suppose she missed me as much as I missed her, because by the time we got in the car and left we were nearly two hours late to prom. Sabrina had told me on the ride that it was actually her date who had cancelled, but she didn't expect me to go with her since she had friends waiting. 


I was prepared to head into prom and give an embarrassing explanation to my friends about my tardiness, but it didn't happen quite like that. Sabrina left me as soon as we entered, immediately finding her friends. I roamed the room, looking for a glimpse of the deep red that Ashley had recently colored her hair. I saw Riley and Leslie dancing, but Ashley was nowhere in sight. I asked them if they had seen her, but they said she had disappeared a while ago.


It was nearly 10pm before we left to find her, she wasn't answering her phone and we couldn't find her anywhere in the building. We took my car, checking her house first, and assuring her parents that she had probably gone home with a friend. We searched everywhere obvious, before thinking of heading to our favorite spot in the world. It was around 10:30 when we got there. She had left prom less than two hours before.


We found her, at the creek where we all hung out. With the blankets I had brought earlier in the day set up in a nice spot to hangout, and battery powered lights tied to branches in the surrounding trees. Then there was the backpacks, filled with pop and snacks, and enough alcohol to fill a pool. The bags were open, and so were several bottles. The amount missing from each bottle varied, but it was more than enough for any single person. 


Then there was Ashley. Her floor length blue dress was soaked from the creek water, it made the dark color look nearly black. Her makeup ran haphazardly down her face, and she looked so sad and cold. I didn't know what to say, Leslie and Riley hadn't arrived yet. I didn't move towards her, I knew that this was all my fault. 


She was so still, her neck bent at an unnatural angle against a sharp rock in the creek. I saw the nearby plank of wood that we had used as a makeshift bridge, a piece had rotted through. I had just noticed that Ashley's shoes matched her dress when suddenly a hand grabbed my shoulder. Riley and Leslie broke me out of the trance, but I'll never forget finding her there.


When the official report came out, it wasn't surprising. She had a very high amount of alcohol in her system, her ankle was fractured, and her neck was broken.


I missed a lot by being late to prom, the night pieced together from other students memories. Like seeing Ashley fight with her exs date. She didn't fight though, she was attacked. Apparently this girl didn't take kindly to her date staring at his ex, Ashley had looked astounding at the dance. In the time before Ashley left, the girl managed to pour a drink down her back, and step on her dress so that it tore. No one noticed this escalating, and when she consulted a chaperone she was told that these were likely accidents in a crowded room. 


She got sick of it, she had spent so much money on a dress that was ruined, for a night that was ruined. Her ex and his friends laughed as she walked out. Then she went to our spot in the creek, and she found my plans for an after-party. She had the party alone, took a drunken walk in high heels, and twisted her ankle as she fell through rotted wood. She died alone when her neck snapped upon impact with a sharp rock. 


That day I found her, that was the worst day of my life. I shouldn't have been late, I could have kept her away from the things that made her leave the dance. I could have gone to the creek with her. I always knew it was a horrible decision that I made which led to her death, and the day was never forgotten. This is probably as close as anyone has ever been to feeling like the kid from *Bridge to Terabithia*. 


Years have gone by, I've tried putting the past behind me. I did end up getting back together with Sabrina, she helped comfort me after Ashley's death. Life has been going fine, I feel like I've made all the right choices since that day. Finishing college, getting a job, marrying Sabrina, having a baby. It's been almost 11 years since Ashley died, and I've almost gotten past the guilt. 


I have been very conscious about my choices for the past 11 years, I didn't want to carelessly cause any harm. That's what everyone does, right? We all make the best choices we can to help ourselves without hurting too many others. The thing is, you never really know how many choices you've made that caused unnecessary harm. 


So there I was, 28 and believing my life was wonderful, other than one choice I made as a kid. I had a decent paying job, and the apartment we live in is a mere 25 minute walk away. I don't mind the walk, it's a good time to destress. That's what I was doing when a stranger suddenly fell into step with me, when I glanced over to see who had come so close I only caught a glimpse of *something* before it sped up and walked ahead of me. 


Trying to think about it I can't think of how to describe what I saw. I'd say that it was like seeing nothing, the absence of air around a space which contained an unseeable object, but that wasn't quite it. I knew something was there, but it was hard to see or focus on. Not like it was nothing, but like it was *everything*. It was all that surrounded us, displayed in such a way that it blended almost seamlessly with the street around me. I'm sorry if that doesn't make much sense, but you'll know what I mean when you encounter it. 


It seemed to disappear once it was a few steps ahead of me, and I felt confused about what I had just experienced. I thought about what it could have been, and ended up assuming it was some sort of side effect from being stressed out. I assumed it was something I'd imagined, and my walk went along as normal. I reached the entrance to the path through the park and stopped.


It was dark, but there were still a fair amount of people walking through the streets and the park. The path I stared at was wide and made of stone, trees lined the sides and the foliage overhead made the path appear like a dark tunnel into a haunted forest, but it was actually kind of beautiful. I walked through this path every night, but tonight I saw two men who appeared to be arguing.


Not wanting to walk by the argument, I decided to go around the park. It would add ten minutes to my trip, but I didn't mind. As I took my first steps away from the park I felt it, that *thing*-- the one made of everything and nothing-- was beside me again. Then I heard a whisper that sounded like hundreds of child-like voices at once.


*Every choice has a consequence, don't forget.* 


Then suddenly the feeling was gone, but the whispers seemed to echo through my head. I stood still for a moment before taking another step forward, a step that felt deeply *wrong.* The thought popped into my head forcefully, *go the usual way.* I paused again, standing still to think. *Maybe theyre done fighting.* 


I don't know why it had felt so wrong to try and avoid the park, but I decided to listen to that instinct. I felt better as I stepped towards the park, but that was a short-lived feeling. 


There were two distinct sounds as I stepped onto the stone pathway. One was the sound of a man groaning in pain, and the other was whispering children.


*Too late.* 


I stared down the pathway, at a man lying in a puddle of blood. Of course the police were called, I had to give my statement-- which wasn't very helpful at all-- and the man who had been stabbed was being sent to the hospital. I was talking to him before they took him to the ambulance, he told me something that brought me back to the feelings I'd had when Ashley died.


He was old, maybe 50, and I wasn't sure if he would live until the authorities arrived. I tried to help, and he thanked me for it. Then he apologized, because this was his fault. He thought it would be smart to bring a knife to defend himself against a debt collector, but it was used against him. The part that made me feel awful? He told me that he wished I'd gotten to the park sooner, because he wouldn't have pulled the knife if someone else had been in the park.


I didn't know what I was supposed to do with that information, but I decided to keep it to myself that I had actually seen them fighting and walked away. I felt awful when the ambulance left, and when I was told I was alright to leave I stewed over it. A man might have been spared several punctures if I had changed one simple decision. A decision that shouldn't matter at all in the grand scheme of things. My walking route shouldn't have been such a large factor in whether that old man bled out in the park or not. 


I was almost out of the park, but I sat down on a bench to clear my head. I had already sent a text to Sabrina explaining that there had been some trouble at the park and I would be getting home late. I didn't want to bring such a heavy weight when I walked in the door, I felt guilty. I shouldn't have, it could have happened to anyone. 


I almost didn't notice when the strange *thing* sat next to me. The whispers came back then.


*Every choice has a consequence.*


I spoke aloud to the odd space next to me, I don't understand why you're here. 


I didn't want to dwell on the incident in the park, I already felt bad about it. I wanted to get straight to the most important issue, why was a creature like this suddenly following me? Of course I wanted to ask what it was, but there's really no polite way to ask that of an inhuman entity whom you've only just met.


*There are those who have made so many choices that appear to hold no consequences, so many times they picked an option they did not need to. You have done just that, and now we bring you one more choice. You may decide how you feel over all that you have caused.*


I sat there, completely astounded by what the voices of children were telling me. I could think of only two things that I'd done which held high consequences, surely there were people with a far greater collection of mistakes? I nodded in the general direction of the barely visible creature, entirely unsure of how to respond. 


There was a moment of silence, the kind that you never experience anywhere. There was no sound of traffic, no buzz of electricity, no voices, nothing. The air around me was entirely devoid of sound, and then I felt something touch my hand. Pins and needles shot up my arm, and the inside of my skull was shaken by a loud ringing noise. 


*How do you feel over the choices you've made?* The children still spoke in a whispering tone, but it sounded deafening inside my head. 


My vision faded into a blank white state, and I could think of only one word.


*Guilty.*


The feeling spread up my arm, and change from the pins and needles to knives and acid. It felt as though my flesh was melting off. There was a sudden flash of black, and I was numb. As though I was dreaming I watched several scenes play out. 


There I was, arriving at Sabrina's house. The entire night played out the same as it does in my memories, but then there are parts I didn't see.


I was a ghost, an invisible character in the lives of my friends. I watched as Riley and Lelsie went home after leaving the crime scene. I watched as they discussed how the death was partly my fault. Time skipped forward, to their decision that they couldn't be friends with a person like me, though we had all planned to go to college together they decided to go out of state instead. 


I watched as Riley grew distant with everyone throughout the months after Ashley died. I watched Leslie leave him out of frustration. I watched as he killed himself. It was about two years after Ashley's death, a year after we had fallen entirely out of touch. 


After watching Riley hang from the rafters of his garage, everything turned black again. The darkness lasted five seconds, but it felt like an eternity where the pain of my flesh falling from my bones returned. 


The scene flicked back to Sabrina at prom. Someone was telling her about the death. She was devastated. Skip forward a few days, and I discovered something I wish I'd known before I picked her up that night. It wasn't just her date that had cancelled on her, it was her boyfriend. 


This boyfriend had been told about someone else driving her to prom, and arriving so late. Things didn't go well for her there, and based on what I saw in my third person form she was used to it. After a few weeks of her taking it like a champ, he left her. She seemed shocked, but relieved. That was around the time she started to visit me and comfort me, but she never talked about her ex. 


That scene was short, I already knew what happened with Sabrina and I after prom. The darkness and pain returned tenflold. I hadn't realized how much my choice that day affected. A flash of white blinded me.


I was suddenly standing on Sabrina's front porch all dressed up. Her mother opened the door and I stared at her in confusion.


Daniel? Sabrina's still in her room if you want to go up, I have to leave in a moment, she smiled at me, seeming pleased that I was here for the first time in months. 


No, I'll wait here, I replied with a smile.


I was finding it hard to catch my breath though, was I honestly getting a chance to fix my mistakes? 


The night went on. Sabrina came downstairs and I drove her to the dance, she told me that we should hang out some time. I danced with Ashley, her ex stared. His date didn't come near my group of friends, we all spent the night happy. 


About an hour into the dance Sabrina's date barged in. He was obviously drunk, and everyone in the room witnessed as he grabbed Sabrina by the arm and tried to pull her out of the room. People stepped in, including myself, and we removed him from the building while Sabrina told him that they were through.


Time went on, I had a fun little after-party with my best friends, and Sabrina spent the night with her friends. We all graduated, we all went to the same college. I ran into Sabrina there, and we got back together. Everyone was happy, we all had our lives on track. The darkness returned. 


I'm sure I screamed out loud as the pain rocketed through my body, but I couldn't help it. When I opened my eyes I was staring at the odd entity on the park bench. My phone was vibrating in my pocket over and over, and I was very confused. 


*You should not be consumed by guilt over past choices. Too much guilt keeps you from being able to make better decisions in the future.* 


The child-like voices spoke in a way that sent a deep sense of dread through my body. I looked away from the creature to see why my phone hadn't stopped going off. 

It had been hours since I sat on this bench. So many missed calls, all from my wife. So many voicemails. I listened to one, forgetting that there was something inhuman sitting next to me. Something was wrong.


The voicemail shook me to my core, our daughter was missing. She thought maybe she had gone to the park to find me. I needed to get home now, I needed to find her. I stared at the creature, it stood as I hung up the phone. 


*Sometimes it's better to choose not to feel guilty, dwelling on mistakes wastes so much time,* the voices spoke softly before the creature stepped away, disappearing. 


I could swear I heard children laughing as I sprinted through the park, yelling my daughter's name. 


We haven't found her, it's been over a week. That day has taken up residence as the worst day of my life. The day where I got to see how horribly I ruined my friends lives 11 years ago, the day where I let my guilt keep me from choosing to run home. 


I could have run away, I could have been afraid of the inhuman thing and avoided it. I could have been spared the true worst day of my life. Instead I was enteanced from the moment those childish voices whispered about consequences, because I knew I hadn't faced any harsh enough for the wrong I'd done. 


What is the consequence of too may mistakes that go unpunished? Guilt. 


I think that's what I'd call the creature that visited me, Guilt. So, from me to you, here is some advice.


Don't let it get to you, don't let your guilt over the past cause you to choose wrong in the future. Don't choose to feel guilty when it comes for you, because it comes at a cost.


------


[HF](https://www.facebook.com/subject374/) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-30 19:52:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Probably within the next two weeks or so ~ </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-29 21:55:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> **Previous D31 Stories:**



3/1: [Last National Pig Day](https://www.reddit.com/r/shortscarystories/comments/5wvmuk/last_national_pig_day/) - /r/shortscarystories     
  **Pig Day**

3/2: [Not Your Average Sibling Rivalry](https://www.reddit.com/r/nosleep/comments/5x5cpc/not_your_average_sibling_rivalry/) - /r/nosleep   
**Rivalry**

3/3: [Natural Filicide](https://www.reddit.com/r/youpoetried/comments/5x8r6m/natural_filicide/) - /r/youpoetried  
 **Natures Fury**

3/4: [Best Kept Family Secret](https://www.reddit.com/r/nosleep/comments/5xl8oz/best_kept_family_secret/) - /r/nosleep  
 **First Time**

3/5: [In a Dying World, The List of Things I'll Never do Again is Growing Each Day](https://www.reddit.com/r/cryosleep/comments/5xpiqd/in_a_dying_world_the_list_of_things_ill_do/) - /r/cryosleep       
**Never Again**

3/6: [You Don't Do That To Family](https://www.reddit.com/r/nosleep/comments/5xtytg/you_dont_do_that_to_family/) - /r/nosleep                         
**Bitter Silence**

3/7: [I Tried Out a Dating Site](https://www.reddit.com/r/shortscarystories/comments/5y4f6u/i_tried_out_a_dating_site/) - /r/shortscarystories           
**Dating Sites**

3/8: [She Is My Eternal Inspiration](https://www.reddit.com/r/nosleep/comments/5yayg0/she_is_my_eternal_inspiration/) - /r/nosleep            
**Inspiration**

3/9: [Suicide Town](https://www.reddit.com/r/nosleep/comments/5yi7eo/suicide_town/) - /r/nosleep          
**Panic Day**

3/10: [Suicide Town (Part Two)](https://www.reddit.com/r/nosleep/comments/5yp9sf/suicide_town_part_2/) - /r/nosleep                         
**The Letter B**

3/11: [My Daughter Loves Playing Games With Me](https://www.reddit.com/r/nosleep/comments/5yx900/my_daughter_loves_playing_games_with_me/) - /r/nosleep                 
**Hide and Seek**

3/12: [Careful What You Wish For](https://www.reddit.com/r/shortscarystories/comments/5z1mnp/careful_what_you_wish_for/) - /r/shortscarystories               
**Magical Beasts**

3/13: [I Witnessed A Murder That I Didn't See](https://www.reddit.com/r/nosleep/comments/5z4ovi/i_witnessed_a_murder_that_i_didnt_see/) - /r/nosleep                  
**Festival Of Colors**

3/14: [For The First Time In My Life I Wish I Had Said No](https://www.reddit.com/r/nosleep/comments/5zgx5d/for_the_first_time_in_my_life_i_wish_i_had_said_no/) - /r/nosleep               
**Just Say No**

3/15: [Almost Your Time](https://www.reddit.com/r/libraryofshadows/comments/5zmmmg/almost_your_time/) - /r/libraryofshadows               
**Missed Connections**

3/16: [I Tried To Force My Husband Into Losing Weight](https://www.reddit.com/r/nosleep/comments/5zrocn/i_tried_to_force_my_husband_into_losing_weight/) - /r/nosleep               
**Breakfast**

3/17: [Seeing Green](https://www.reddit.com/r/youpoetried/comments/605utv/seeing_green/) - /r/youpoetried                
**Saint Patricks Day**

3/18: [Listen to What Your Kids Say](https://www.reddit.com/r/shortscarystories/comments/607pls/listen_to_what_your_kids_say/) - /r/shortscarystories                 
**Kid Logic**

3/19: [Mr. Cooke's Last Chemistry Class](https://www.reddit.com/r/nosleep/comments/60epj1/mr_cookes_last_chemistry_class/) - /r/nosleep               
**Chemistry**

3/20: [Clich](https://www.reddit.com/r/youpoetried/comments/60l9mp/clich/) - /r/youpoetried             
**Cliche**

3/21: [Take Me](https://www.reddit.com/r/youpoetried/comments/60shpk/take_me/) - /r/youpoetried                    
**Onomatopoeia** 

3/22: [The Good Shade Hotel](https://www.reddit.com/r/nosleep/comments/6104g9/the_good_shade_hotel/) - /r/nosleep                 
**Hotel**

3/23: [My Beautiful Roses](https://www.reddit.com/r/libraryofshadows/comments/61abwe/my_beautiful_roses/) - ~~shortscarystories~~ /r/libraryofshadows                
**Symbolism**

3/24: [We Learn From Experience](https://www.reddit.com/r/nosleep/comments/618ite/we_learn_from_experience/) - /r/nosleep                
**Writer's Block**

3/25: [Tasteless](https://www.reddit.com/r/youpoetried/comments/61kgpo/tasteless/) - /r/youpoetried                  
**Cravings**

3/26: [I Was Almost In The Lucky 47 Club](https://www.reddit.com/r/nosleep/comments/61oydb/i_was_almost_in_the_lucky_47_club/) - /r/nosleep              
**The number 47**

3/27: [Our Hotel Celebrates The Strangest Holidays](https://www.reddit.com/r/nosleep/comments/61xh3y/our_hotel_celebrates_the_strangest_holidays/) - /r/nosleep              
**Make up your own Holiday**

3/28: [Perhaps I Took My Gambling Habit Too Far](https://www.reddit.com/r/nosleep/comments/624rej/perhaps_i_took_my_gambling_habit_too_far/) - /r/nosleep             
**Gambling**

3/29: [Orbit](https://www.reddit.com/r/youpoetried/comments/62brlj/orbit/) - /r/youpoetried            
**Narcissist**

3/30: [Strange Things Happen in Louisiana](https://www.reddit.com/r/nosleep/comments/62qvct/strange_things_happen_in_louisiana/) - /r/nosleep           
**Serendipity**

3/31: [Loyal To The End](https://www.reddit.com/r/shortscarystories/comments/62tg2h/loyal_to_the_end/) - /shortscarystories       
**Doggo Day** </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-29 21:53:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I shouldn't but I will anyways  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-28 17:07:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thank you c: There should be a new story out and added to the nosleep list within 24 hours c:  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-28 17:05:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That's pretty much exactly what I was looking for! Thank you so much </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-27 23:05:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> We already have employees that do so c:  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Need a "spooky" Snoo for a new subreddit. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-27 22:53:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Think of spooky however you please. I'm not picky, anything from a ghost looking snoo to one with a witch hat. Though a simple ghost would be really nice! 

Apologies for not being specific, but this Snoo just needs to be easily identified as representing something creepy.

Thank you very much!

subreddit is r/HylianHorror </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Library {Story Master Post} </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-27 22:10:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Welcome to the library, here we find the links to the different lists of stories. Enjoy your stay among the dusty shelves, dim corners, and eerie silence. 

-----

[Stories by Subreddit](https://www.reddit.com/r/HylianHorror/comments/67y5gr/stories_by_subreddit/?ref=share ref_source=link) 

[Short Horror](https://www.reddit.com/r/HylianHorror/comments/67xvs6/short_horror_stories/?ref=share ref_source=link)

[Nosleep Stories](https://www.reddit.com/r/HylianHorror/comments/67xrgw/nosleep_stories/?ref=share ref_source=link) 

-----

*This page will grow in the future, feel free to comment with suggestions for additions.* </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Stories By Subreddit </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-27 21:59:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> **This page is still under construction.**

Here, all stories listed below go by which subreddit they belong to, so that you can see the entire collection of stories with ease. If you have a preference for a specific subreddit, this list may help you.

-----

*Subreddits listed alphabetically. Subreddits containing few posts  will have links to those posts below them. Subreddits with numerous posts will link you to a complete list of stories posted there.*

------

r/cryosleep

* [Voicemail](https://www.reddit.com/r/cryosleep/comments/666beu/voicemail/?ref=share ref_source=link) *originally written for r/nosleep*

* [In A Dying World, The List Of Things I'll Never Do Again Is Growing Each Day](https://www.reddit.com/r/cryosleep/comments/5xpiqd/in_a_dying_world_the_list_of_things_ill_never_do/?ref=share ref_source=link)

-----

r/libraryofshadows

* [My Beautiful Roses](https://www.reddit.com/r/libraryofshadows/comments/61abwe/my_beautiful_roses/?ref=share ref_source=link) *originally written for r/shortscarystories*

* [Almost Your Time](https://www.reddit.com/r/libraryofshadows/comments/5zmmmg/almost_your_time/?ref=share ref_source=link)

------

r/nosleep

*see [Nosleep Stories](https://www.reddit.com/r/HylianHorror/comments/67xrgw/nosleep_stories/?ref=share ref_source=link) for complete list*

------

r/shortscarystories

* [I Tried Out A Dating Site](https://www.reddit.com/r/shortscarystories/comments/5y4f6u/i_tried_out_a_dating_site/?ref=share ref_source=link)

* [Careful What You Wish For](https://www.reddit.com/r/shortscarystories/comments/5z1mnp/careful_what_you_wish_for/?ref=share ref_source=link)

* [Loyal To The End](https://www.reddit.com/r/shortscarystories/comments/62tg2h/loyal_to_the_end/?ref=share ref_source=link)

* [Listen To What Your Kids Say](https://www.reddit.com/r/shortscarystories/comments/607pls/listen_to_what_your_kids_say/?ref=share ref_source=link)

* [Last National Pig Day](https://www.reddit.com/r/shortscarystories/comments/5wvmuk/last_national_pig_day/?ref=share ref_source=link)

-----

r/SLEEPSPELL

* [The Quest That Was Not](https://www.reddit.com/r/SLEEPSPELL/comments/54ziap/the_quest_that_was_not/?ref=share ref_source=link)

------

r/twosentencehorror

* [Hidden Daughter](https://www.reddit.com/r/TwoSentenceHorror/comments/5vq1nb/after_15_years_ive_become_used_to_my_daughter/?ref=share ref_source=link)

-----

r/youpoetried

*see [this list of depressing poems]() for posts in this sub* </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Short Horror Stories </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-27 21:18:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This list contains horror stories that are 500 words or less, for those of us who only want to taste the human-bacon, but don't want to swallow the whole piece. 

*Split up by sub, ordered from least to most upvotes.*

-----

r/twosentencehorror *(the smallest nibble you can take)*

[Hidden Daughter](https://www.reddit.com/r/TwoSentenceHorror/comments/5vq1nb/after_15_years_ive_become_used_to_my_daughter/?ref=share ref_source=link)

-----

r/libraryofshadows *(Regular bites of horror, 500 word MINIMUM, this story just hit that)*

[My Beautiful Roses](https://www.reddit.com/r/libraryofshadows/comments/61abwe/my_beautiful_roses/?ref=share ref_source=link)

-----

r/shortscarystories *(bite-sized horror)*

[Last National Pig Day](https://www.reddit.com/r/shortscarystories/comments/5wvmuk/last_national_pig_day/?ref=share ref_source=link)

[Loyal To The End](https://www.reddit.com/r/shortscarystories/comments/62tg2h/loyal_to_the_end/?ref=share ref_source=link)

[Careful What You Wish For](https://www.reddit.com/r/shortscarystories/comments/5z1mnp/careful_what_you_wish_for/?ref=share ref_source=link)

[I Tried Out A Dating Site](https://www.reddit.com/r/shortscarystories/comments/5y4f6u/i_tried_out_a_dating_site/?ref=share ref_source=link)

[Listen To What Your Kids Say](https://www.reddit.com/r/shortscarystories/comments/607pls/listen_to_what_your_kids_say/?ref=share ref_source=link) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
