<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject8211</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-10 16:30:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Strap a jet engine to the back of a truck... what could go wrong... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-10 16:26:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Not sure, I usually don't follow the controversy unless it's something huge. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-10 15:50:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> TBH, I'm okay with this. Spending money efficiently is a slow process. And they've got a LOT of money to spend. In the end it's gonna buy a lot of game. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-10 15:20:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Honestly, I'm fine with this situation. It's consumer choice. Pay with adds, a buck or press Ctrl-W. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-10 12:51:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Is there even a mobo behind there? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Sunglight [Afterlaughs] </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-10 12:38:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-10 04:13:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That's true. They were built for greyhawk I believe.

Now, I know Red Hand of Doom isn't a 1-20 deal, but it does cover a fair range of levels and is one of the better adventures out there. What it does have, is a thread over on GitP, which details the work other people have done to adapt it to other settings - the Eberron adaptation being a particularly interesting one(though, this admittedly this is a rather uninformed opinion since I've not played Eberron to any significant degree).  
Also, sadly, the GitP forums are currently down, so the [link](http://www.giantitp.com/forums/showthread.php?171284-The-3-5-Red-Hand-Of-Doom-Handbook-for-DMs-Major-spoilers!-WIP-PEACH!) won't work, but I'll leave it here for reference. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-09 23:27:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You might fudge a roll or two, but do not cheat on rolls chasing some bullshit idea of balance or fairness like "50% chance of success" - this completely invalidates the idea of character progression(which is where a fair number of people derive their enjoyment of D D from - seeing your character grow from a scrub to a hero). </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-09 23:20:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hm... I was generally aware they buffed sneak attack(and that it could be used against undead), but now I went ahead and dug into the gears and cogs and it turns out, most types that were immune to sneak attack and critical hits in 3.5 are no longer immune in PF. In fact, type-wise, only oozes are still immune.

Also, elementals and giants are no longer their own type, but subtypes.

Undead are d8 instead of d12, but use Cha for HP and mid BAB instead of low. Mon. humanoids are d10 instead of d8 and 4 skill points instead of 2.

That's... all changes I highly approve of as a DM. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-09 21:25:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> They were published in Dungeon Magazine during the 3rd edition years. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-09 21:23:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That's the kind of DM that causes me to foam around the mouth and rain expletives.

I'd call bullshit immediately. It's one of my biggest DM red flags.

Good ways: Qualitative cheating  
Bad ways: Quantitative cheating </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-09 21:12:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> There's are in fact 3 of them. They are called "Adventure paths" and were usually published a chapter at a time, each covering a couple of levels.

1. Shackled City  
2. Age of Worms  
3. Savage Tide

All pretty awesome. I'm partial to Savage Tide. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-09 17:55:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Let's hope not. I know first hand how many people fail to keep backups, but losing the entire forums would be a disaster.

There's a new message that the forums will be down for a few days. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-09 14:55:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Now they only need kung fury too. :) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-09 13:06:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yea... it has. Now the site's up, but the forums are 404ing.

I was expecting a tweet, but eh... Don't know if any of the admins have a twitter to ask. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-09 13:03:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Not as a rectangle on a flat plane. It isn't *mathematically* possible.

There a great deal of [map projection techniques](https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Map_projection) to choose from in general, depending on how you intend to use the map. There's probably also tools to convert from one to another floating around. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-09 02:46:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The elf bard would sit down, treat everyone to a mug of cheap ale and either sing or start recounting tall tales of his misadventures. Like that time he got trapped on a floating island full of amazons. Or that time he got crowned(briefly, but they don't need to know that).

The large noble warrior lady will take him up on the offer and rebuff all his advances, cuz her ladyship is a recent development. She might arm-wrestle him though. Which he will summarily lose.

The surly thri-kreen ninja will sit alone in a corner playing with his pet. He is shy, but deadly...

Until the half-lizard, half-lovecraftian-monster, half-a-bunch-of-other-things girl sees the cute little kitty and tries to befriend it(actually a rather vicious lesser basilisk, though when you look like her your notions of 'cute' tend to get somewhat skewed). They'll probably end up playing dragonchess.

The half-dragon drow priestess will stare at them from afar and scoff at such pointless pursuits like as merriment. When she eventually gets bored, she might start pulling petty pranks with her magic. Or sharpening her scythe. One of those. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-09 01:27:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The entire premise of my campaign is giving a spotlight to every other race except Humans(they get one teensy kingdom in a world larger than Earth).

I've literally not seen it done by *any* DM so far(including the responses to this or other similar threads from the past). </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-09 01:09:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Many of these are surprisingly usable.

Also, 22 is the plot to Red Hand of Doom. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-09 01:01:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Being, what it seems an equirectangular projection, "fact" might be stretching it a bit.

Plaster it on top of [this](https://www.maptoglobe.com/) for a better idea of how it actually is.

If it's earth sized, the distance between your Keyhill tower and Caer-something is 440 miles. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-09 00:38:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [Not exactly subtle.](https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=jtgA0jvhp2A) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-07 03:35:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Dresden Files #12: Changes

Also, fuck this thread cuz I now spoiled part of the plot for myself just cuz I went to check which number that book was. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-07 03:30:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> One who admits mistakes. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-07 03:26:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Sing with me, sing for the years  
Sing for the laughter, sing for the tears  
Sing with me, just for today  
Maybe tomorrow, the good lord will take you away </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-07 03:19:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> He ain't no Hatebeak though. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-07 02:52:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That time has come again, eh?

Every year, around siggraph I go on a video hunting spree to see what awesome new goodies we can await in upcoming years.

I can't wait for believable elasticity and viscosity simulation in games. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-07 02:29:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Wow... that's like, the most clear-cut example of gravitational lensing I've seen. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-07 02:25:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Probably mostly a case for the dire necessity of the EFF(who saw this as an opportunity to do some good). </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-07 02:18:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That's an o(d|l)d thing to say... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-07 02:17:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This is me in my group. I got an b-day incoming and they keep asking if they should...  
But I keep wondering how much use a repetitive multiplayer shooter is gonna see on my part.

League also, but that I tried and it didn't stick either. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-07 02:06:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeeep. Not smaller, but definitely enough to get underfoot.

Plenty of ingame and cinematic cutscenes in both games provide reference for size.

I think I was most surprised by the size of the science vessel(which you can gleam from that brood war cinematic with the nuke). </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-07 01:45:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's hard to hate random nickname-shaped words on the internet, but those who downvote to express opinion, those I do hate. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-07 01:27:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> But not 4K. Not even 60FPS. Bleh. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-07 01:06:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yea, that's him. Kinda distinctive face. :) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-06 23:52:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It is, for these reasons, and more, my favourite Pixar movie ever. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-06 23:44:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm kinda boring in that regard. Functional though.
https://i.imgur.com/xgxTdeE.png

What you see here accounts for all 6 of my MoBo's Sata ports(D: is a RAID0 of 2 drives). I literally can't plug more drives even if I wanted to. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-06 23:44:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Aligns neatly Mr. F: as well. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-05 17:32:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If only more muslim were as lucky as you. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-04 22:44:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It was very easy for me - I got tired of **every** other DM's samey setting and decided to do em one better.

The core idea is a world where monsters are not sacks of HP for human PCs to massacre, but are actually full-fledged members of society. The majority in fact. Humans are relegated to a small nation on a tiny continent and frequently seen as slimy and opportunistic.

In fact, if look through this thread, you'll see that not a single response challenges that most basic premise of a human-dominated world. There's a reason I bolded that word.

Beyond that I aimed for a certain set of aesthetics that would create the ideal D D world as I see it. Such as the ability to have epic adventures(epic as in the *literal*, historical meaning of the word), the ability to let the players be powerful and do cool shit. The notion of a marked progression from lowly adventurer to mythical hero(which automatically excluded 5e as a system). The idea that magic is rare and special, while allowing the setting to remain high-magic and full of mystery and wonder. Another core concept in my continuing design of the setting is "the rabbit hole ALWAYS goes deeper"; or "there's always a bigger fish" if you will. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-03 17:59:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> IMO the Uncertainty principle becomes obvious if you look at everything as a wave. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-03 01:24:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Kill the emperor. Then the great dragon who was using the emperor as a puppet. Then the dragon king who ordered the great dragon to do so. Then head of the extraplanar organization the dragon king was a member of. Then the demigod who was the true mastermind behind said organization. Then the demigod's dad. Then the king of the demigod's dad.

I mean come on... the ladder goes way up high and they've just stepped on the first couple of rungs. Gotta keep on climbing. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-03 00:26:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> *A game happens.*

That's what. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-02 17:08:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So... this thread is basically a failure. First fifty responses and about 2 guys who understood it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-02 17:06:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'd go for bluff, but eh... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-02 02:32:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Anything on actual TV at this point.

I catch glimpses when I go to my parents. Not a single second of what I see is actually watchable. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-02 01:41:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The rules themselves are free, on the [pfsrd](http://www.d20pfsrd.com). Time investment, that's up to you.

But you might wanna explain that to him. I'm sure he'll be more understanding of that, than a simple unqualified "no". </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-02 01:02:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Or you know... you could do Pathfinder. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-02 00:58:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Were they trying to get through interdimensional customs or something? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-01 22:13:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yea... the resemblance isn't exactly subtle.

But wow... this image fits crazy well to a prominent character I just made up for my game. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-01 22:03:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> In my group that name would have a completely different connotation.

If the DM dropped that name, no PC would even dare think of messing with that NPC.  ^^^^^Hint: ^^^^^Dresden </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-01 21:52:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I think the title should go  
**"I am become DM, the roller of dice!"** </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-01 14:53:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I was gonna say CDPR, mostly because of gog.com, but it seems they're their own company.

I also just found out they sell movies too. :) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-28 20:35:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Would you make another game in GMS or are you ready to move on to bigger and better things? What would those things be? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-28 01:56:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This was positively awesome. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-28 01:47:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Let them fail in a way that moves the plot forward.

Look at [#4](https://www.brainpickings.org/index.php/2012/04/03/kurt-vonnegut-on-writing-stories/). Replace "sentence" with "action".  
In fact only all of these are strongly applicable to D D. Only #7 perhaps needs its subject changed from "person" to "party". </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-28 01:39:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Ah, there we go... Can't have high-magic without mentioning Tippy. TV goes well beyond that single post. Here is a massively long discussion on the [economics of high-fantasy settings](http://www.giantitp.com/forums/showthread.php?36788-Build-Me-An-Economy!-\(General-Challenge). Also a good demo of Good vs Evil. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-28 01:30:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Most characters(NPCs) I make start with me picking an image from my library that inspires me and running with it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-28 01:25:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Uh... There is Shaktari... The queen of Mariliths, a minor demon lord, by circumstance not lack of power or malevolence.

Otherwise they are most likely bound to one of the major Demon Lords. Graz'zt, Lolth and the like. Who don't easily tolerate slights upon their authority.

See Dragon #359. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-28 00:55:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yea, it was just a joke. :) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-28 00:42:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That's what the rules say. In at least in one edition. Look [here](http://www.d20srd.org/srd/magicOverview/spellDescriptions.htm#aimingASpell). </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-27 17:43:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> TBH I think you are part of the problem. And people lacking in critical thought and western culture in general. I'm not sure if I should find it amusing or sad this notion of trying to pass infanticide or *genocide* as something less evil than rape. Have you actually stopped to think what genocide actually means. Go read some stories and look at some pictures of the german concentration camps and try the same spiel with a straight face.

And in case your approach merely relies on shock, as in "oh, look we think rape is worse than these other extremely horrific things",  
a) western culture strikes again  
b) it never works

Mind you, this is not a defense of rape, merely an argument for proper contextualization. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-27 16:15:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Amusingly, in D D if you are unconscious you are considered willing. :) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-27 10:39:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Generalizations such as this one are meant to cover only the lowest common denominator DMs. It is not a universal truth, but it should appear such to those who would not look past the surface(both this statement and fumbles). Here's a terrible secret: I use fumbles. Mine also come up an upside. I also pity your horses... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-27 00:47:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You know... this isn't a new idea.

I can't recall where exactly I've come across at least 2 instances of such relics/artifacts - one in the 3.5 Weapons of Legacy book, where a pair of bones from a legendary monk were made into a nunchaku, the other I can't rightly remember where(maybe the Book of Exalted Deeds, or some obscure dragon magazine or something).

But this is so totally going into my item compendium. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-26 23:21:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Bioshock + Civ 4... There's probably a mod for that. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-26 23:20:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> DM: You seduce the unicorn instead. Your parents wonder where they went wrong. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-26 22:54:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [You're in luck.](https://docs.google.com/document/d/1YVapC-VhuKDQ5vx4T2go8v4HdY6vX7U_FUA-IEn_yrM)  
Go sing your praises to Mr. Squirrel Dude over on GitP. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-26 20:58:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Skill checks do not even have auto-fails(or successes), let alone fumbles. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-26 20:22:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's practically always a better idea to play with veterans unless you suffer from misplaced nostalgia or you want to coast by with your DMing. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-26 19:58:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> #Fumbles

I want to play a **hero**, not an incompetent jackass or a slapstick comedian. Seriously. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-25 21:42:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If you can't beat em, tax em.  
-- Every government ever. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-25 14:52:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [Man of Steel, Woman of Kleenex](http://www.rawbw.com/~svw/superman.html) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-21 20:21:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Why not a prison ship disguised as a tavern... in a dungeon? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-21 20:21:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Well of course it's a poll. How else do you collect data? :)

I'm not looking for all the special cases here, just the statistical mean. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-21 17:32:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I suppose I missed "In the dungeon" as an option, but I'm specifically interested in seeing how pervasive that "You meet in a tavern" or "You all wake up in prison" cliche is. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> DMs, where did you start your first campaign? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-21 17:26:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-20 23:17:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Learn drawing and high-level math.

Renaissance men were onto something. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-20 23:11:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I see a distinct lack of the "Serious" tag. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-20 23:01:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I believe this is a great summary of all the reasons:  
https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=r4jCTiGSuwU </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-20 21:19:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I actually approve of this practice in straight up dungeon crawls. Ones that play out more like a board game.  
I do however find it inappropriate in any extended or more narrative-driven campaign. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Some bugs/feedback </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-20 20:04:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> https://imgur.com/a/A4vNQ

Just discovered this nifty(if it worked) tool. Except it doesn't properly.

1. There's a difference between where I drew the blob and where it got put on the globe.
2. Notice the tiny little artifacts on the globe projection?
3. To get any changes to appear I have to toggle the lag/long grid on the globe, just to get the render to update semi-properly.
4. Notice how the buttons with the drawing tools are missing.
5. When/if the rendering issue is fixed, can we please get a hotkey for switching between the views and for the drawing tools.
6. A non-zero axial tilt makes the mesh show through the texture on top.
7. Edit: Noticed the misalignment of the image I posted is due to the axial tilt.

This is on chrome 58(though same issues in firefox). </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-20 19:35:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You can hint at things. Rumors, news from far-away lands, bards singing of the exploits of *OTHER* heroic parties.

Having your PCs occasionally just end up in the wrong place at the wrong time can be fun for all sides - you, for showing the story, and them for being glad that for once they're not smack in the middle of the shitstorm. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-20 19:17:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It is, with absolute certainty, **correct**.

Pelor knows why the calculators get it wrong. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-20 18:25:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Oh, for the love of... this **time**. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> New Geek and Sundry GM tips (This type with Satine Phoenix) </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-20 18:24:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-20 18:22:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> TBH it was mostly a Family guy reference. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-20 15:08:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You underestimate yourself. Don't you know about the 4th hole? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-20 15:03:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Nu... though it might just be a case of high expectations. Like I was expecting there to be much more FF porn :) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-20 13:44:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's actually surprisingly hard to find porn. I tried. For science. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-20 11:32:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You do have a point. While Create food and Water is 3rd level, and a caster ratio of 1:15 (with casters of CL5+ no less) is mighty high for an army, Purify food and Water is L0. So is Prestidigitation. This makes it easy to salvage ruined stuff.

Though I don't think supply by fly would work as easily as you imagine. The *fly* spell simply won't cut it. *Overland flight* is 5th level and personal(meaning you'd require expending resources on carrying capacity, i.e. bags of holding or similar). Natural flight would work, but hey, if they have enough big flying beasts for that, the party has bigger problems. Ring gates are another failed idea(they have a weight limit).

So while magic works marvellously on small scales, army-scale magic is extremely expensive and/or high-level. To the point of, if the PCs face such an army, they're better off going looking for allies who can measure up, rather than trying to go up against that kind of might. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-19 22:46:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This exists: http://www.d20pfsrd.com/gamemastering/tools/critical-generator/  
(also links at bottom of page) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-19 22:34:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If you are facing overwhelming odds: [Scorched earth](https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Scorched_earth)

Fielding and supplying armies for extended periods is a logistical nightmare. Make it worse. In D D you can even go as far as enlisting the support of druids in making it harder for the army to live of the land.

You *should* have fly by now, so go behind the army's back and cut off supply lines. Hit em where it really stings. Evacuation is a waste of your abilities by this point.

I mean, here:
https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/List_of_military_tactics  
Go wild! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-19 19:33:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> 1. Be wizard.
2. Profit. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-19 19:02:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Of course not. Populating everything from scratch is not feasible(my setting is quite young).

World gets 'rendered' in decreasing detail radially outward from my players. When preparing I decided the adventure would start somewhere on that large continent and placed the major powers there, then a couple dozen major cities/regions.
Those are developed in the "Why does it exist? Who rules it? What's it's thing?" formula. When my players decided they wanted to be pirates/have an aquatic adventure, is when I started going into more detail. For example I already knew the primary political and sociological tensions of the area they are starting in. I knew the coast was peppered with a loose collection of city-states, instead of a single unified nation. I knew the strength of the fleets of the neighbouring island nations and their economic interests, and the aspirations of the militaristic empire that's over the hills from said collection of city states. Then I started working on the "free cities" themselves.

The other continents are less developed for obvious reasons of me not being god, but enough that if the players should suddenly find themselves over yonder, I can sketch up something on short notice. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-19 13:26:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> With games it's different.

Games many times use proprietary middleware, such as sound or animation libraries or what-have-you, which carries different licences, which makes it impossible to open source. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-19 02:07:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> TBH I was expecting thread title to be a rhetorical question and this below it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-19 02:00:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Orbital characteristics included?  
*Fine.*

My world is a super earth, orbiting a G0V main sequence yellow star with a perihelion of 140 mil km and aphelion of 150, 3rd among 5 planets, mean radius of 6,988 km, axial tilt of 20, gravity = 1.04g.

It has 2 moons, the size of the Moon and Ceres. Both are tidally locked.

Surface is 64% water, 35% land(this means ~50% more land area than earth).

It has 4 major land masses, the biggest of which is approx. 90x10^6 km^2.  
It has 2 large island chains(think oceania) and 2 ice caps, the southern being much larger.

The connected surface area of the underdark is equal to ~25% of above ground land area. Unconnected/isolated portions account for another 30%.

The highest mountain is about the height of Mars's Olympys. The largest one is about the twice the size of the Himalayas.

It is fully circumnavigateable by sea.

Subject to both plate and magical tectonics.

Geography, climate and demographics maybe another time... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-19 00:45:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> 1. Heroes
2. High magic
3. Humans a minority
4. Both
5. Both
6. Everywhere
7. See above
8. Many enemies
9. Both
10. Alert

My world.  
The unfortunate implication of which, I believe, one easily can spot. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-18 22:34:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> But he wasn't. It was the DMs choice. There is a significant difference between "If you don't rez my hero I leave" and "I found that one fun and can't think of anything else I'd find nearly as fun, so I'll just leave".

This sub keeps reiterating that (admittedly not untrue) cliche - **"No D D is better than bad D D"**. And you just bashed on a player *following* that advice. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-18 22:27:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Typically, spellcasters vs sword-swingers. Have not actually ever played 5e 20th level, but in 3.5/PF that starts happening by about L5(no ifs and buts, straight up my class is this, you lose, let's go home). </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-18 22:20:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Having the terrain be a factor in the battle should be standard practice.

There is very little incentive to have a fight on open ground if one side can gain advantage by choosing more favourable terrain.  
This means that very few battles, outside of large army confrontations are ever fought that way. And in D D not even those, cuz an open field battle is just an invitation to unleash all manner of area of effect magic. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-18 20:14:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Sweet. Now can we please get anisotropic filtering and antialiasing? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-18 19:51:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> 9gag's a little faster... like just 1-2 days :D </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-18 16:23:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Ah, the old guys.

Good art has become... well, a lost art. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-18 16:23:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> THAC0 is like anathema to modern nerds. You show them the table and they hiss and back off.

Good riddance tho. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-18 15:20:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Er... English+German... Gerlish? Engman?

It's possible, I suppose, but it erases all manner of terminology that has become common place in english. That's A LOT of work that language would have to redo, just to get on par with modern english in expressiveness. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-18 13:37:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> F=ma is a bitch </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-18 01:56:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Why, yes, [there are](http://www.d20pfsrd.com/gamemastering/other-rules/called-shots/). </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-17 22:49:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Good god man... it's the manifester's familiar.

It starts off by giving neat bonuses and only gets better from there. It can scout for you. It can deliver messages. It can deliver touch powers. Then there's the tricks. It can share powers with you. For example sharing vigor. And share pain. And if you wanna get advanced, your crystal is half your HD. HD carry certain benefits. Not the least of which is a feat progression. How convenient then, that there exists the leech feat power. Though, you must first eliminate the construct immunities somehow.

As for the egoist, in combat situations he's all about buffing himself and others physically. You can blast easily too. And before yet another tables suffers the fate of "OMG, PSIONICS OP, BAN THEM!!11!", let me remind you of the cardinal rule of psionics(which, judging by this question, you most likely missed):  
**You cannot spend more power points on a single power than your manifester level!** </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
