<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject3180</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [I ate] Guay Tiew Kua Gai in Bangkok (chicken and wide noodles fried in pork fat, topped with a runny egg) </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-09 23:31:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-21 02:27:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Do you have any particular occasion or event in mind? There is going to be a huge difference between, say, a birthday party with some friends and a formally planned massive white party with a pool and a DJ, for example.

How much room do you have? How many people would be there? Etc. I think that will help people contribute better.

Hot tubs and pools almost always make for a fun party, but that's not realistic for lots of folks. The kinds of decorations, food, and drinks I recommend will be totally different based on the occasion and the theme! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-13 19:35:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Sorry, I went on vacation after this - how did it go though?? (or has the party still not happened yet?) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Summer taco and piata party </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-13 17:32:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Any great ideas for a weirdly themed bridal shower? We're thinking about doing "Christmas in July"... </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-13 17:09:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> My sister is getting married this fall and we're planning to do a bridal shower with the extended family during our usual family reunion in July.

She doesn't want much in the way of gifts since the wedding is shortly after and she and her fiance already live together in a well-stocked tiny apartment, but she DID express some interest in having everyone bring a Christmas ornament as a gift, so that they'll be able to decorate their own Christmas tree.

So I was thinking of making the shower "Christmas in July" themed, but I don't want to go FULLY cheesy. Any thoughts on how to make that work? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-13 16:58:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> LOVE THIS idea. I would definitely involve some Lisa Frank-inspired temporary tattoos and/or stickers, maybe scattered on some tables like confetti. And yes, I think an obnoxiously ranbowy cake or cupcakes is also a must.

I've also been shamelessly plugging the sub I just took over, /r/partyplanning. I would love to see posts/discussions like this happening over there too - maybe you can post some pics of the party afterwards to share with other people?? :D </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-13 16:53:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I love making a big batch of cocktails for theme parties in particular! IMO beer and wine are great (and usually I have those too) but cocktails are fun and refreshing and can really add to the party theme.

The only downside/difficult part is usually finding recipes that make a full pitcher. So here's a list of a few. I've also made [these cranberry ginger cocktails](http://www.foodnetwork.com/recipes/dave-lieberman/ginger-cranberry-cocktail-frozen-vodka-or-gin-recipe) for Friendsgiving and [these margaritas](http://cookieandkate.com/2012/fresh-margaritas/) for a summertime taco party.

I recommend making them the day of the party, not too far in advance, and then keeping them chilled right up until the party starts (or if possible, keep the pitcher on ice during the party). I've also read that it's a good idea to add a little bit of water to large batch cocktails to mimic the role of melted ice you'd normally get in individual cocktails. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Here are some large batch cocktail recipes so that you don't have to do math to make a whole pitcher </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-13 16:46:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-13 15:42:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I just went to a weekend bachelorette party - we did a cooking class one night (SO fun) and an improv show the next night! Of course, we involved drinking in both of these activities but that is totally not required.

Also, shameless plug... I just took over the /r/partyplanning because planning parties is my jam (and I'm working on a bridal shower and bachelorette party right now!). I would love to have people post there for party help too!! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The new /r/partyplanning </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-13 15:23:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hi everyone,

I just took over this sub after it had been largely left alone, and I'm doing my best to revitalize it. I think I've removed all the spam so that we're down to just legitimate content, and I'm doing my best to contribute to that as well.

Thoughts, ideas, and feedback for the sub are all more than welcome at this point. What would you like to see here, in terms of content, features, or otherwise?

Also, spread the word! Let's get more people here! :) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-01 22:58:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Sounds fantastic so far.

In college we had one of those spinning light up disco ball things... Not even sure what to call it but it made every party better. Seems like it would feel very Miami ([something like this?](https://www.amazon.com/GLISTENY-Changing-Rotating-Activated-Ballroom/dp/B01BBRB0KO/ref=zg_bs_5486431011_2?_encoding=UTF8 psc=1 refRID=0R1RMECGS2ENFCDMQS44)).

What about food and drinks? Can you make/have someone make little cuban sandwiches? Not sure about cocktails, but maybe something rum-based?

You could also get some of those plastic striped sunglasses and scatter them around to have people put on. 

And don't forget the Miami playlist, including plenty of Will Smith obviously... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-01 17:39:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> /r/monalisaclan just got started up </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-01 17:38:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> /r/monalisaclan just started </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-01 17:23:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This is the official reference being used:

http://i.imgur.com/UtVcdW6.png </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-01 17:17:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Agreed, but I say we primarily focus on filling in the canvas as best we can first and then go back and fix the little mistakes here and there. It's a complicated design. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-01 02:22:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> No! Preserve the flag. Surround it with lattice but don't write over it. We're preserving art, it helps us win over allies too. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-01 01:52:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Can we put green borders around art we want to keep, just to make it nicely incorporated into the lattice? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-01 00:39:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> /r/greenlattice </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Homemade decor, party favors, and activities for a "Lingerie   Cardigans" themed bachelorette weekend </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-27 21:39:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-24 14:56:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The pink cupcakes are frosted with vegan raspberry "buttercream" (frosting texture was a little weird, but seems to taste good, so whatever). The white are frosted with regular vanilla buttercream. Decorated with homemade lingerie   cardigans cupcake toppers (an inside joke). :) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> I made vegan cupcakes for a bachelorette party! </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-24 14:55:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-23 20:39:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Just wait til you discover coconut and salted caramel! It's basically how I eat dessert for breakfast without feeling guilty. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-22 12:30:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I only weigh in once a week and since I was just under 161 last week, I was so hoping/excited to see finally see the 150's again this morning... nope. 160.0. I couldn't even get 159.9! Ugh! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-21 18:32:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Not exactly, I make chili all the time so I just kind of make it up as I go, but it's really easy! 

I basically just throw an onion, a bell pepper, some jalepenos, and lean ground turkey into a pot and cook them. Then add some seasoning, tomato sauce, and diced tomatoes (different recipes use different tomato options, but I like a little texture, and I usually use Rotel to get some extra flavor). Let it simmer a bit and then add a can of beans. That's it! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-21 18:10:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> They are surprisingly not too bad! Obviously not low carb if that's what you're going for, but Google says a "medium" one (173g) is 161 calories. You can weigh them for better accuracy, or I sometimes just guesstimate 200 calories to be safe.

I used to just assume potatoes were terrible too, but then I realized it's just because I associate them with mashed potatoes, french fries, tater tots, etc. You could also replace with a sweet potato or some mashed squash (I'm weird but that's actually my favorite).

It's honestly so filling that I can barely eat the whole bowl, which is perfect because I'm a notorious night snacker. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-21 16:03:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I actually do use greek yogurt, but I also add white vinegar (in addition to the seasoning packet). I find that it thins it out a bit and adds some tanginess so it tastes less like it's just flavored yogurt. I also recommend letting it sit in the fridge for a bit to let the flavors mingle. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-21 15:49:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What I'm eating this week:

* **Breakfast:** Oikos triple zero (I change it up, but banana creme is my favorite!) + half a scoop of vanilla protein powder + a small handful of blueberries. Also, tons of black coffee. **~228 calories**
* **Lunch:** Homemade "broccoli salad" (blanched broccoli topped with reduced-sugar craisins, sliced almonds, and homemade vinaigrette). **391 calories**
* **Snack:** Apple. **~80 calories**
* **Dinner:** Homemade turkey chili over a baked potato. **433 calories**
* **Dessert:** 2 caramel corn rice cakes, and usually some hot tea. **100 calories**
* **Total: 1232 calories**

I change my lunch salad and my dinner every week, but more or less my days always follow this kind of "template". Right now my struggle is to eat more protein without getting bored of my meals or eating too many calories...
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-21 14:19:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's normal to fluctuate during the day (and even during the week) due to eating, drinking, going to the bathroom, etc.

For consistency, I only weigh myself in the morning before eating any breakfast (though I might have coffee first). </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-21 02:13:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So cool, I love this!!

[It reminded me of the spaghetti cake my mom made once, I had to go back and find a picture!](http://imgur.com/a/PJ97e).

I'm really impressed that you were able to hold up the chopsticks somehow! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-18 14:23:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yes, it's [right here](http://www.lifeloveandsugar.com/2016/12/19/baileys-chocolate-cupcakes/)! I added a little extra Bailey's to the frosting because why not? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Happy St. Paddy's! I made Chocolate Bailey's cupcakes (and realized I have no idea how to properly frost cupcakes!). </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-18 14:17:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-14 15:39:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This was my second annual Galentine's Day party. I like to make this party as cheesy as humanly possible by making just about everything pink and heart-shaped and by including a party craft. Last year we made shrinky-dink wine charms. This year I let everyone vote and we settled on cookie decorating! 

Working with royal icing takes a bit of practice (I did a test run a week before the party) but it turned out great! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> This year we decorated cookies at my Galentine's Day party! Here's an album of the (heart-shaped) food, the decor, and of course the cookies. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-14 15:31:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Requesting /r/partyplanning - it's a single mod who hasn't been active in 4 years </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-14 14:27:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-13 14:14:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> In addition, OP may want to do some further research into what a sanctuary city actually is, since it really only relates to law enforcement turning immigrants over to federal authorities, and has nothing to do with welfare. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-13 03:43:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Midnight in Paris. It popped up on Netflix with a high rating so I thought I'd give it a shot... I barely lasted 10 minutes because fucking Owen Wilson is so awful. Then I googled it thinking I must not be alone on this and the Netflix rating must be a fluke... Nope, got great reviews in general. I don't understand. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> I had to sneak slices out of the box when he wasn't looking </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-13 01:14:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-10 00:25:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Well depending on what you decide to cook, it's really not a lot of time or very complicated! You can still cook something really simple and just make several days worth - that's all I do. It actually saves more and is simpler compared to making 3 different dinners on 3 different nights!

I'm talking a big pot of chili, or baking 4 chicken breasts instead of 1-2 for example. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-09 20:18:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So that stressed/overwhelmed snacking you're doing when you can't figure out what to eat for dinner is *exactly why* I like to meal prep - that way I only have to think about it once per week, and every night my food is pre-made.

I don't go super crazy with it. I always have some sort of yogurt for breakfast, some sort of salad for lunch, and then dinner is different every week. For me, having a basic structure makes it easier to plan.

Throughout the week I'll use things like Tumblr or Pinterest or just google-searching things that sound tasty to me to find possible recipes. I save anything that looks good so that I always have a big stockpile of options.

Then on the weekend, I pick one salad and one entree from my stockpile, plug them in as recipes in MFP (it does most of the work for you) to make sure they fit in my calorie goals, and then use the recipes to build my grocery list. I only buy what I need at the grocery store, so that I don't have a bunch of extra food to use up or snack on.

I try to make my entree that weekend (usually something simple, like soup, or chicken and roast veggies). I divide it up into individual tupperwares so that when I get home for dinner, all I have to do is microwave it. I make my salads every day so that they're fresh and so I don't have to do a ton of meal prep up front.

That's it! Like anything, it takes time to make it a routine, but my life actually feels so much easier and less stressful overall when I do this. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> I should buy a boat. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-09 18:35:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-08 21:25:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I can't stop laughing at this. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-08 12:31:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Always. (Really, he hates when I take his photo.) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> My handsome man </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-08 02:39:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-08 01:31:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That sounds awesome. I would check out Denver - I googled quickly but looks like it has all of those things. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Someone spent a lot of time on this apple bin </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-01 23:04:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Unisex baby shower from a few years ago </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-01 17:54:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> I'm sad this subreddit doesn't seem to get used much - I love party planning! Here are pics from 2016's Friendsgiving to try to revive things. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-01 17:29:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-15 19:51:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Wow, this is beautiful! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-15 19:47:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Just a heads up that it looks like you posted this twice. :) They look great though! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Last week I posted my failure of a first attempt at royal icing and got lots of help. Round 2 was much better and the Galentines Party was great! </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-12 18:24:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-11 04:10:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Haha it's disgusting and I love it!! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-09 14:02:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Gorgeous!! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
