<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject8455</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-09 17:56:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Probably, this is one of the options I thought of as well! I am a scaredy cat, that's why I got scared, it doesn't necessarily mean it was something sinister. It was just creepy and I sincerely have no explanation of it! It could have been a person, of course, but come on... Too weird! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Strange Voice in the Dark </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-09 14:45:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hey guys! I rarely post here as not many scary or weird things happen to me, things with no explanation, but last month such a thing did happen and I would like to share in hope that you can help me figure out what it might have been (though I'm not sure we'll find out ever).

So, me and my boyfriend were on our way to his hometown for Easter. He picked me up after work, which was a little after 7 PM and by the time we drove off it was past 8. His hometown is three hours away by car, so... yeah.

Somewhere after we passed the capital and continued to the little villages, the heavy rain had ceased and we were looking for a secluded place on the road to take a pee. We found a spot that was a bit aside from the road and he pulled over. The spot was on a lonely part of the road between two villages. 

We came out of the car and were just breathing the fresh rainy air, when, out of the woods, we hear a man's voice singing. 

Now, I'm from Bulgaria. When I say "singing", it sounded like a folklore singing typical for our homeland. The voice just echoed through the woods and it sounded very close. We just looked at each other in dismay as it kept going for like 15 seconds. My first thought was, here's a drunkie celebrating the holiday, but somewhere in the middle of listening I started getting creeped out. 

We are in the middle of the road, with forest on both its sides. The street lights are like 5 meters away from one another and, so far, only one car had passed us by. Who the hell could be outside, in the forest, in quarter to midnight, in a cold and rainy weather?!

My boyfriend did his business, but I was freaked and almost refused to go. But I did, and it felt like a man would jump out of the trees at any second, with old gun and knife, big moustaches and clothing, like it was when we were under slavery and such men were hunted through the mountains while fighting for freedom. I honestly tell you I did think that!

It sounded as a person who had come back from the ages and was roaming the forest. It was scary!!!

When we got back in the car, my brain started working. First, it was almost midnight, and I know that because my mom had called me to check on us little before we got off to pee and I checked the time. Second, if that man was drunk, he was singing way too accurately for a drunkie. In fact, he had not a single wrong note. And third, I saw no light, not a single sparkle of flickering light through the trees. If there was a person there, and they were even a bit close, we'd see flashlight, house lights from windows, something. But no. 

We reached our destination safely and searched the history of the area. We found only like two sentences about a warrior, a haydut, as we call them, by the name Milenko who was slaughtered in one of the villages. He was part of the opposition back then.

On our way back, during broad daylight, we took the same very road in search of any sign of home life. We saw that the trees weren't as thick as they appeared at night, and we could actually see through the other side. There was a field with a small den. No houses. No tents. No signs of life. There's nothing there but open air. 

It still boggles my mind. It was absolutely real, we could both hear it and, given the circumstances, it could have been something else, but not human. I mean, what are the chances of two random people stopping by to pee in the middle of nowhere and someone decieds to sing just then?! And may I add, it never sung again apart from those 15 seconds.

What do you guys think? If any of you have any suggestions, that would be awesome. We'll never find out for sure, but still. Thank you.

I'll leave here a link to illustrate how the voice sounded, minus the instrumental music. This manner of singing is authentic to us, it's our musical heritage.

https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=jCepk9gF1AA
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-11-04 23:36:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Wonderful. Be on your guard, stay safe. Anything else happening? haven't been on here for a while, I hope all is good! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-10-19 02:12:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I know, right?! I don't now if you guys are kidding but my phone is on silent and I keep checking it for missed calls :D </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-08-30 08:09:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Forgot to add - this story should win a monthly contest. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
