<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject7988</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-08 01:19:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Very good points and thank you for bringing them up! I thought mostly about Myshkin but Nastassya does seem to be the more interesting character now that you mention it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> I just finished The Idiot by Fyodor Dostoyevsky and it did not quite resonate like I'd hoped! </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-07 20:49:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The Brothers Karamazov is tied for my favorite book of all time (with East of Eden) so I was excited to finally delve into more Dostoyevsky. The Idiot seemed intriguing so I read through it and once again Dostoyevsky was wonderful prose and thought provoking sections. I believe his theme is that Prince Myshkin is the epitome of a human being and character but cannot survive or change the debased society we exist in. He enters it knowing nothing and leaves it in shambles.

My only complaint is that I never really got the sense that Myshkin was anything more than just a normal guy living in a rich social group. He doesn't do anything exceptional or even out of the ordinary. He just had common human deceny and respects others and I'm from the Midwest so that's just the average person. Any thoughts or more perspectives to help me see more into this book? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-07 00:12:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I hardly ever reread books. I have loved some and would enjoy a reread but there's just so many new ones out there I want to experience! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-02 23:05:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I have received over 50 books from thriftbooks with only one acceptable book being a little rough. Their very good and like new and exceptional quality for cheap and the shipping usually is only a week for me. I love thriftbooks! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-30 01:19:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It seems like it's just me but I just don't get it.. discworld is not very fascinating to me at all! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-28 04:18:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I have this edition and love it! It's my favorite book cover. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-19 20:29:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Timshel in East or Eden is the only book I can think of where one word represents the entire book and extrapolates to an entire life! We have the choice to do good in our world or to do bad. Such a beautiful word </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-18 03:06:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This book has been on my list for a while and now I defintely will check it out! Cheers! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
