<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject9425</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Shattered worlds is incredible! </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-02 13:22:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Absolutely amazing update. Brings me back to my POE days. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> LPT Request: how to stick to a schedule when your weeks are erratic? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-20 13:13:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hi, i struggle to stick to a schedule. I am supposed to be studying 20 hours a week for my maths, but i work nights on a flexible contract, this basically means they can just say i need you to work this night.

The work i do prevents me from going regularly to the gym, and i just want to relax and sleep whenever i get in.
On days off i have to rearrange my sleep pattern to cater to be awake throughout the day, this in itself is a challenge.

What pro tips do you have that will help me stick to a schedule? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-08 21:35:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thank you, it's Tescos frozen cooked and sliced everyday value chicken (500g bag) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-08 12:39:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hey guys, this was my first attempt at prepping. It will last me 3 days.

Chicken Meal

* **Sliced Chicken** *(Frozen, Pre Cooked)* - 166g
* **Green beans** - 125g
* **Cherry Tomatoes** - 5 (I didnt weigh it, I just added a number)
* **Green Pesto** - 40g

This is my favourite meal, inspired by the gif (will link) recipe. Super delicious, super cheap.

Steak Meal

* **Sliced Steak** - 80-100g (got a pack of four at 365g)
* **Asparagus Spears** - 4-6 Spears
* **Cherry Tomatoes** - 5

If you guys have any advice with this meal I'd really love it, it was quite a boring one, so anything will help.

All in all, it will last me 3 days. Ill have the Chicken for lunches, and the Steak for dinner.

All cooked in one pan :) (Yes i washed it)
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Hey MPS, I finished my first meal prep, and i gotta say I'm quite proud of myself :) </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-08 12:29:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Me irl </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-07 09:09:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> me_irl </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-01 13:33:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-28 09:59:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Aha look again, there's an apostrophe as well as a quotation </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-27 15:18:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Ice JJ fish - On the floor </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-27 15:15:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I was also doing a night shift, but we just went by the analogue clock, so we still worked the full 9 hour shift. Start at 10 finish at 8. My dad was adamant that i worked for the extra hour though. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-27 12:57:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I noticed when i went out one night and my mate said, dude your back looks fucked, you look about 5'7". I'm 6'". 

I began by focusing on my back and cervical spine more, as well as doing 'back to wall arm raises'. I also really wanted to do handstands and I couldn't with the back i had. So shoulder strengthening and trapezius strengthening helped massively.

All in all i owe it to the /r/bodyweightfitness community as they have a TON of help on this sort of stuff </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Need help with current situation </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-23 06:38:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What's up MPS. I'm in a bit of a predicament at the moment, I'm living at home with my parents and am very involved in fitness, absolutely love it, however my diet hasn't always been the best.

Last week i asked my mum and dad if we could actually start eating cleanly as i want to gain weight, I'm 75kg at the moment aiming for 85kg. Long story short i got told "no."

Now the only way to help keep my diet in check is to cook for myself which means buying everything of course.

Now i live in the UK and i have a budget of about 60 a week as I'm saving up to go to college. I have pretty much all the equipment to cook with at home, but i want to know;

What cheap and healthy plates can you prepare with a low budget, and what would the shopping list look like?

Many thanks. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> A small guide for people starting UVHM as Gunzerker </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-22 13:49:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Before beginning UVHM continue to play through PT 2.5 by farming Boll and Savage Lee for the fastball and the Unkempt Harold. Try get a corrosive shock and fire version of the Fastball.

Start UVHM and immediately start the Tiny Tina DLC. Progress to get the mission The Beard Makes The Man for the Grog Nozzle.

You may be about level 53 by now but don't worry.

Make sure you're specced into:

  Down not out

  Yippee ki yay

  Double your fun

  I'm ready already

  Got some

  Money shot

The Grog Nozzle will scale to your level so all you have to do is farm a new UH and FastBall whenever they become obsolete.

A sham shield will help sponge some damage but it isn't too important as you'll be getting tonnes of heals from the Grog Nozzle.

Hope this helps :)

Edit:

Class mod: blue suave renegade
Relic: Sheriff's badge (i got this in nvhm - relics don't scale well) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-08 12:33:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This is my fault but I took a month off and had come back to the gym on Monday. Could barely manage 3 pull ups but was able to hold a handstand for 30 seconds, a complete opposite of what I used to be able to do. So now I'm annoyed.

On top of that, all of my form is gone, and I have a fitness instructor exam on the 20th. RIP </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-04 17:25:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Wrong thread lol </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-03 12:29:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Been out of the game for a while, are we able to emulate or download DS games to the 3DS yet? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [Discussion] Why do we complicate fitness so much? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-01 18:09:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-26 10:23:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Nah boy, sounds fine </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-21 00:08:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> No, for now, until I grow confidence I avoided it completely because of that exact reason </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> I spoke to 8 random people today... </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-20 12:53:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> ... well, partially random... Let me explain

So I am involved in a multi level marketing business, and part of that involves talking to people, but I'm not good at that. Been in the business 5 months have made 0 progress. Today I decided to take a step forward.

Okay so here's what I did. I went to my local town centre, went into random shops and stopped people while they were working.

Now you might say what if they had a lot of stuff to do? Well here's the thing, people on shop floors are very much there to help!

Here was my script "hi, can I just stop you for a minute" now usually they'll say - sure! Or "How can I help?"

I always respond with "I know it's very random, but I'm trying to talk to 10 people today." Now it is important to stop and listen to them too as a conversation takes two people. Stopping there will prompt them to respond with something. Usually they'll ask why you want to talk to ten people - fantastic!

"I'm just doing some hands in personal development to help me talk to people and come out of my shell." Now I'm being very honest here, I am doing exactly that. And you would be surprised what could spark from that little answer.

Now it is important to always wish them a good day, you want them to feel good too! The first person I spoke to looked very happy after I said "have a fantastic day!".

So that's 8 people today, not quite ten, but it's 8 more than I would've thought I could've spoken to. You just got to say "Fuck it" really.

If the formatting is a bit awkward, apologies, I'm on mobile.

Have an amazing day everyone! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-19 18:06:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Im not bothered about DXP, if you want, i can help :) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-19 11:49:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> wot </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-18 09:33:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> There's a whole album full of Elizabeth killing her mother </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-16 08:14:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> With what tool? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-08 17:21:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I love how the purple makes a Zaros symbol </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> How to install lots of mods very quick! </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-03 11:55:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hey everyone,

So the point of this guide is for those who want to play with lots of mods but your computer is too old/slow for Curse client to run.

What you will need:

* **Curse Client**
* **Minecraft Mods Folder** 
* **Mods** (Downloaded through Curse)


Okay.



1. Open Curse and navigate to MInecraft

2. Click Create modpack (Name it whatever, and use the version you want to install your mods to.) The client will automatically install forge, but you may need to install it on your original.

3. Click the image to view the profile

4. In the top right corner it says **"GET MORE CONTENT"**, click that and search for mods you want. If the mod requires a core, it will automatically be downloaded

5. Go back to the overview of the profile you just created.

6. Next to where it says **"GET MORE CONTENT"** there is an ellipses button, click that then click **Open Folder**

7. Have the created modpack folder and your original minecraft folder open.

8. Drag all the mods from curse folder into your original

9. Enjoy :)

**NOTE:** Curse does not have Optifine, so it will have to be installed normally.

Done. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-30 11:25:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I can only answer your first question, but, it doesn't matter how many sets it takes as long as you do it for the time. For example, cans do 18 sets of 10 seconds, or 6 sets of 30 seconds </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-25 21:34:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I can sort of relate, went for my first run in about 2 years on Saturday, did 5.5 km in 27 minutes but omg I couldn't walk properly until today. Always do a proper cool down </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-13 17:26:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> They still add to kc as aviansie :/ </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-13 04:26:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Please make aviansie tasks last longer like greater demons.
Currently killing Kree'arra requires you to lose 40 kc. This means the task will last 30-45 Kree'arra kills. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-12 22:27:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Dude, some people don't start building well into their game. I like to build a hit, get everything done first then start to build, that alone will take me to day 100. Some people play at different places. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> me irl </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-05 17:28:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> meirl </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-02 13:50:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-29 11:22:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Okay, but they had access to my steam account, put 40.2 hours on Dota 2 (Which Ive never touched) changed everything to russian, changed my name, email address, and profile picture. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Steam Account hacked, now weird stuff is happening with my email. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-29 10:53:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hey PCMR

A couple weeks back i got a message from my mate telling me my steam account got hacked. This was my fault as i didnt have Steam Guard. I have it back, and have reenabled steam guard.

Now weird stuff is happening to my email. Im receiving emails with message undelivered, but nothing has been sent from my email. I Have liked the imgur posts to see what im on about. I didnt block the other email addresses simply because they dont exist. [Album](http://imgur.com/a/fLwwn)

I have logged every other computer out from my account, and changed all my passwords. What should I do?

Thank you </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The arriva bus app is as unreliable as the buses they track </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-20 20:05:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Been waiting half an hour and apparently three buses have gone by.... Bollocks </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-20 10:38:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Actually, its rarer than that. Assuming you dont mind which piece of 3a you get; a clue with 5 rewards has a chance of 1/3380 to drop. This makes the Zaryte bow from a nihil 295x rarer than getting 3a from an average clue. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> LPT: Butter your bread before toasting! </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-14 11:13:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-11 11:03:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Mine would be machine supremacy. Their. Music is so good but the singer is just under par which ruins it a bit for me </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What band/musician would do really well if they improved one aspect of their music? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-11 08:47:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-07 22:57:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I don't know what you exactly mean, but blue light does make the eyes strain. Try installing f.lux, it lowers the blue light making it less painful for your eyes </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
