<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject7426</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-16 21:30:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This is great and a really fun to boot! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-14 17:14:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This is amazing! Even better that's its cropped to size! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-13 23:16:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The header should have a 10:3 aspect ratio. The minimum size should be 640x192 px and the maximum Reddit can support is 1280x384 px. Obviously we can crop images that don't meet the aspect ratio but if you did it beforehand it would allow you to make sure the most important parts of your submission are represented. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-13 23:14:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This looks great! Unfortunately, I think it would we are looking for a map or banner that uses the new textures and icons. As much as many of us loved the old style, they are no longer an accurate reflection of Inkarnate and the banner should reflect the most current and accurate state of the program. If you have a submission in the new style, we would love to see that too! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-04 21:53:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Omg I was thinking the EXACT SAME DAMN THING!!!!! I turned to my husband (who shares my love of J Coolz) and was like "Are you living for Jaymes right now?!?" Simply the best and made parting even harder. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-04 20:50:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I like being able to browse lots of different brands at once, so my go-to is usually [International Jock](http://www.internationaljock.com).
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-30 23:44:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hahaha that's basically my dream too. But we shall see - I'm not going to make any guarantees but if I can figure out a somewhat easy and stylistically compatible way to do that, I may give it a whack. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-30 23:21:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Oh for sure I totally agree with you! And you're welcome! Let me know if there are any colors you don't see but would like to as well! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-30 23:15:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You can upload them using the texture uploader! Granted, you can only upload ten custom textures at a time, but at least you don't have to wait for them to add them for you! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-30 20:19:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> These are compatible with whatever is currently live in the site. I'm pretty sure it's still in beta unless I missed an update. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-30 19:46:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Howdy everyone! Here's the (much belated) update to the texture gallery I've been working on. This includes the core textures, as well as textures by myself and /u/Spadie. Credit is given for each texture in the gallery.

I had to delete my old gallery post in order to post this one because it used the same link. Fullest apologies to anyone who had saved/bookmarked/etc the old post.

As always, I am looking for further color suggestions and submissions to broaden the scope and depth of the gallery. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Inkarnate Texture Gallery: I'm Back Y'all! </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-30 19:44:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-30 18:25:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This is so great to see some of the textures in my gallery put to use!! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-17 16:53:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Jesus I've been trying to figure out for a while how to get onto the roof with the Ragged DVD chest. Now that I know what's there it was easy for me to search for an answer but before I was shooting in the dark!  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-15 17:39:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thanks, you're a peach! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-15 16:55:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I've seen your posts before, so I know you've been asked this before as well. However, that won't stop me!  What program(s) do you use when making your maps? If you have the time, I would love an insight into your process. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-14 22:02:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [WE  AS WELL SHALL BECOME AS GODS!](/spoiler) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-07 18:09:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Howdy! As of now, I have not uploaded them. The last couple weeks have been a stressful surreal blur at work and I haven't had a lot of free time to work on fun stuff like this. Expect to see a new post hit the front page when I update the gallery though. Fingers crossed I will have some time to work on it this weekend, but no promises. Thanks for your patience everyone! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-05 00:11:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> A little late in responding to this but here's my ten cents. As of now, that's a bit beyond the scope of what I want to do. I think it would be amazing if we had some textures with actual differing textural designs though. Maybe someone will pick up the baton in that regard. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-04 17:54:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> There is a box with a plus sign in it in the textures drop down menu. Clicking this will allow you to import new textures from your own files. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-24 17:17:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> *Trudeaus-Bubble-Butt* </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Question about goal funnels </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-22 17:26:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I am trying to set up goal tracking for rfq forms embedded in my client's product pages. They would like tracking for form completions from each page but they all direct to the same thank-you page url. I have tried setting up conversion funnels for each goal with the product page as a required starting point for the funnel, but I ran into an issue. When an rfq was submitted on one product, other products would also appear to fire for the goal completion.

My question is this - Let's say a user clicks into a product page, triggering the first step in the funnel for that page's rfq goal. The user then clicks into another product page, triggering the rfq for that product, completes the form and lands on the thank-you page. When the second funnel is triggered, does the first one remain triggered? If so, this would explain why my goals were double-counting. I would love confirmation on this aspect of goal funnels.

Thanks! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-21 23:53:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'll drop some unpopular advice for FFXIII for the series as a whole. Take some time out of playing the game and read the datalogs as they are given to you/updated. Seriously, do this. While I disagree with this as a world building and story forming technique, the story being told is really freaking amazing and it's a shame it was hidden behind large walls of text. It also helped me to really like Hope (which I know is another unpopular opinion). I know XIII-2 and Lightning Returns get a lot of flack (in addition to all of the normal flack) for how heavily involved Hope was in all of it. Aside from his name being a VERY clumsy metaphor, he is one of the best developed FF characters IMHO. At the start of XIII he is a young boy that throughout the series is forced to grow up and mature rapidly in response to overwhelming tragedy, loss, and "destiny" forced upon him. Sure, the other characters have to deal with this too, but they are much older and to an extent (looking at you Snow) more mature. Hope and Light's relationship is one of my favorite FF pairings due to how much they force each other to grow. This relationship is at its best in XIII and I feel is a necessary component to making the most out of their interactions in Lightning Returns.

So I digress. TL:DR Read the datalogs. And I really love Hope.

Edit to add: Anyone that tells you the story was hard to follow clearly didn't pay attention. Once you figure out the four or five pieces of jargon (L'Cie, Fal'Cie, Cocoon, Pulse, Cieth, etc) the story isn't really hard to follow. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-20 15:47:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I think the original intention for these textures was to be used in a map like [this](http://forum.profantasy.com/extensions/InlineImages/image.php?AttachmentID=2010). You would then use other colored textures to draw out lines and add in icons, etc to fill it out. As things stand right now, I think the colors are more useful being used like the other textures because line drawing is a pain and the features make creating a parchment style map a real labor of love. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-20 15:37:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Parchment is an antiquated form of paper, made from either tree/plant pulp or from thin layers of tanned hide. There are three parchment textures that are default right now in Inkarnate. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> How long would it take for a body to dissolve in a pool of pineapple juice? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-18 16:51:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-17 18:14:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I can definitely do that. Maybe we could get that link stickied in the side nav as well so that people don't have to hunt it down. Either way, I will include that when I post the update next week. I am wrapping up a few...let's call them experimental textures and I want to have them hammered out before pushing everything out. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-16 17:40:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This sounds like an issue that needs to be addressed by development. Try logging an error report with them. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-16 17:31:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Something like a sandy shallows where one might snorkel? I'm envisioning those Sandals vacation commercials. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-16 17:31:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Are you thinking of a shade that would matches/complements the current brown mountain icons that the program uses? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-16 14:46:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Maybe we can butter up /u/igagen....Because that would be amazing! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-16 14:45:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'll see what I can do! This type of suggestion is super helpful to me so let me know if you have more! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-16 05:50:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Howdy y'all! I'm in the process of adding a big update to the texture gallery I've been compiling - here's a preview. I want to get at least 7 more colors added so here's where y'all come in. If you have a texture color you've been dying for and you don't see it here, shoot me a comment on this post and I'll try my best to match your vision to one of the textures in the update. I aim to roll out by the end of next week at the latest. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
