<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject7781</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-10 15:32:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Another reason these numbers are notableeven if they seem a bit high. Politico/Morning Consult is the only poll that ever showed a plurality of the public supporting the AHCA. Back in March, when some polls had support for the bill in the teens, this poll had it at 46 Support/35 Oppose (3/13) and later 40/37 (3/19). This is a significant reversal.       </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-10 15:08:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Trump has been signalling his authoritarianism for some time now in various waysranging from his fearmongering demagogy on immigration and crime, to how he praised Putin as a more effective President than Obama. You don't say that unless you mean to be *more like Putin* and *less like Obama* in your own leadership style.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-10 14:57:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It would be useful to have him on staff based just on his knowlege of the full FBI investigationthough query whether that knowledge would raise issues that could disqualify him. But, if feasible, this would make Trump's head explode. That alone makes it worthwhile.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-10 14:50:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Whether the FBI will be run by a Trump crony depends on GOP Sens troubled by this firing. If they are serious, they can hold up the confirmation as leverage to get a select committee and special prosecutor. Comey's deputy is acting FBI director in the meantime. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-10 14:34:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm not sure Trump has the self-awareness or humility to think "Hmm. Maybe I'm being unwittingly influenced." He appropriates others' ideas as his own so he can feel smart. Thinking about this as him being influnced would make him seem weak in his own mind.

And that's the charitable interpretation assuming that he doesnt have direct knowledge that his campaign colluded with Russia. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-10 14:27:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm aware of this. That's why I called it backfilling.

Good comment on the Rosenstein memo:
https://twitter.com/lawrencehurley/status/862127236480200704 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-10 14:10:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Perfect, accurate headline as far as the nominal reason goes. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-10 13:38:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The 6 issues:

1. Does Trump have any business ties to Russia  including real-estate holdings or outstanding debt  that could pose a conflict of interest in his dealings with Russian President Vladimir Putin?

2. How deep and far back do Trump associates' Russia ties go?

3. Why did Trump associates' contact with Russians in late 2015 raise red flags among European intelligence agencies?

4. Why did the White House wait 18 days to fire former national security adviser Michael Flynn, after being warned by the Justice Department about his susceptibility to Russian blackmail?

5. How reliable is the collection of memos compiled by former British spy Christopher Steele that details the alleged collusion that occurred between the Trump campaign and Russia?

6. Why did a Russian bank with ties to Putin try to reach the Trump Organization during the campaign? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The Trump-Russia probes are not going away  here are 6 things to watch as they move forward </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-10 13:33:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-10 08:37:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I've [been arguing](https://www.reddit.com/r/politics/comments/5ayble/z/d9kctvb) that the US has been flirting with banana republic status since the federal policeled by one James Comeysaw fit sabotage Clinton's presidential campaign 11 days from the vote. That action compromised the integrity of the election. 

This is just a further step down that pathaway from democracy and the rule of law, and toward authoritarian rule by the powerful and well-connected, according to their corrupt whims.

Today's step was brought to you by the Orange buffoon who sits the throne. But he only sits there because of Comey's earlier arrogant meddling and violation of investigatory norms designed to protect against this very thing.

    </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-10 06:51:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Let me push back on this. The Rosenstein memo is a pretextual attempt to backfill the legal rationale for Trump's earlier, already-formulated decision to fire Comey. In other words, Trump didn't decide to fire Comey based on the memo's recommendations. I'd be surprised if Trump has the attention span to even read it. Rosenstein cites Comey for improprieties that Trump praised and shamelessly exploited during the 2016 campaign. So, in that sense, the memo is a lie. Procedurally, it also doesn't have factual findings, citations to precedent, or other indicia of a rigorous investigation and anlysis (like I presume the I.G. report will).

Yet, as far as legal rationales go, Rosenstein's substantive conclusions concerning Comey's misconduct are spot-on (with the exception of some weasel wording that may give Trump an opening to try to argue to his base that Comey was fired for clearing Clinton). Comey shat on normal investigatory protocol, torched long-standing norms concerning disclosure of ongoing investigations, and ran the Clinton email probe according to his whims. And then, to top it off, he made false statements to Congress last week in an attempt to justify it all. 

Obviously this has nothing to do with why Comey is being canned *now*.  If this were genuinely why Comey was going to be fired, he should have been fired on January 20th, or October 29th, or July 6th. This firing reeks of cover up.

But Comey's supreme self-assurance and lack of care at multiple stages of this process *did* give Trump the opening he needed. And that now has the potential to bite us all in the ass. With a bit more humility on his part, this Orange buffoon wouldn't even be President. 

Hopefully Comey will meditate on tremendous damage he's inflicted on this country during his unexpected unemployment.

Thanks Comey. 
           </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-10 06:13:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> We don't know how the public will react. If Trump's approval drops sharply, this plan may not work.  

Comey is an idiot for giving this opening with the false statements and mishandling of the Clinton investigation. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-10 03:23:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The world is a complicated place.  As [I said today before Comey's firing](https://www.reddit.com/r/politics/comments/6a2v0h/z/dhc8p6t):

It doesn't have to be black or white.

It ~~could~~ can simultaneously be true that: (1) Comey badly mishandled Clinton email investigation; and (2) Comey ~~will~~ would have looked into the Trump-Russia affair more thoroughly than anyone Trump could possibly appoint.

Trump obviously has just been waiting for an excuse to do this. He reportedly asked Sessions (who should not have participated because of his earlier recusal from anything related to Russia) to find a rationale for the firing.

My educated guess is that Sessions or Rosenstein must have gotten wind of the preliminary findings of the ongoing Inspector General investigation of Comey's actions during the election. Rosenstein's memo probably tracks those findings so it looks like they were ahead of the curve. And that's possibly how Trump thinks he can beat this and distinguish Comey's firing from the Saturday Night Massacre. If the I.G. also finds misconduct, Comey's prextextual firing looks more defensible.

By making false statements to Congress last week and doubling down on the idea that he didn't do anything wrong with the editorializing or letter, Comey further weakened himself.

The irony here is that although Comey *probably did* commit fireable misconduct, he should have been fired on July 5, or October 28, or possibly January 20not now, while he's investigating Trump. Beyond the highly suspect timing, the legitimate rationale is totally incoherent and hypocritical in light of Trump's shameless exploitation of Comey's improper disclosures during the campaign.

I hope this won't be able to derail the Russia election interference investigation. Perhaps the reestablishment of the investigatory norms that Comey violated, which Rosenstein explicitly mentioned in his memo, will now be used to shield the dirty shit Comey's potentially uncovered about Trump's connections to Russia.

Imagine that the DoJ, at Rosenstein's discretion or that of a special prosecutor he selects, declines to pursue criminal charges against Trump Regime officials. All the investigatory material would be shielded from public view. Thats why a special prosecutor is not enough. There needs to be an genuine Congressional investigation by a bipartisan select committee, or else an independent comission, with full access to the FBI/DoJ's investigatory files. Anything less than that, and these bastards could.get away with this.





         </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-10 00:56:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Trump's passive-aggressive letter terminating Comey:

Dear Director Comey:

I have received the attached letters from the Attorney General and Deputy Attorney General of the United States recommending your dismissal as the Director of the Federal Bureau of Investigation. I have accepted their recommendation and you are hereby terminated and removed from office, effective immediately.

**While I greatly appreciate you informing me, on three separate occasions. that I am not under investigation, I nevertheless concur with the judgment of the Department of Justice that you are not able to effectively lead the Bureau.**

It is essential that we find new leadership for the FBI that restores public trust and confidence in its vital law enforcement mission.

I wish you the best of luck in your future endeavors.
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-09 23:32:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This claim was [rated 3/4 Pinocchios in a WaPo Factcheck](https://www.washingtonpost.com/news/fact-checker/wp/2017/05/09/trumps-pointing-of-the-finger-at-obama-for-failing-to-vet-flynn/?utm_term=.4fd5ec6d2914) yesterday:

---

[Trumps pointing of the finger at Obama for failing to vet Flynn]

... **Flynns clearance was a routine matter**, said Jim Kudla, a DIA spokesman. **Flynn had left the agency but the practice there is that all former DIA directors should keep a clearance so the current director is able to have a discussion with former directors about classified matters that might require insight from a previous director.**

**Flynns clearance at DIA comes up for renewal every five years, and so in January 2016, he filed the necessary paperwork. Kudla said the clearance was** ***only for Defense Department matters.*** **It was not so General Flynn could go to other agencies asking for classified information, he said. Each agency would be required to determine whether to allow access to classified materials.** ***Kudla noted that at the time it was being renewed, early in 2016, he was not in the political sphere he subsequently became.***

Flynn in February told CNN he had been advising Trump on a range of issues. At one point, Trump even seriously considered tapping him as his running mate.

As part of the clearance renewal, Kudla said, an applicant is asked about foreign travel and foreign contacts. Kudla said that **there are a couple of questions about foreign financial interests, such as stock investments, but asking about payments for a foreign speech is not part of the clearance process.**

Separately, he noted, Flynn as a former Army officer is supposed to receive permission from the secretary of the Army and the secretary of state before accepting payments from foreign governments. Flynns lawyer has said that as part of the clearance review he disclosed his attendance at a 2015 event in Moscow organized by Russia Today, a government-linked news organization that U.S. consider to be a propaganda front. **But lawmakers have charged that Flynn probably broke the law when he did not disclose $45,000 that he received from RT.**

Most of the security clearance process deals with questions of character and trustworthiness (though it also includes consideration of possible foreign allegiance), said Steven Aftergood, director of the project on government secrecy at the Federation of American Scientists. **It does not address questions of competence or policy judgment. He noted that in light of concerns about Russian election-tampering, General Flynns record of interactions with Russian entities took on a new significance that they did not have in 2015.**

White House officials acknowledge that ***Flynn was still awaiting a CIA clearance when he was fired by Trump***. At the time he was fired, Flynn had an interim clearance in order to allow him to do his job.

I know what I went through as a political appointee twice, in a Republican and a Democratic administration, said James R. Clapper Jr., the former director of national intelligence, in testimony on May 8. **And the vetting process for either a political appointee or someone working in the White House is far, far more invasive and far, far more thorough than a standard TS/SCI clearance process. (TS/SCI refers to Top Secret / Sensitive Compartmented Information, the clearance level Flynn held at DIA.)**

---

Flynn retained his routine clearance as a former head of the DIA and was able to renew it in April 2016. This clearance related only to DoD matters, and existed mainly for the benefit of later directors of the DIA. He did not have general clearance to request classified info from other agencies, such as the CIA or NSA. And he was never given the highest level of clearance for political appointees and White House staff, which was required for him to serve as the [National Security Advisor](http://thehill.com/policy/defense/332399-flynn-never-completed-cia-background-check-for-trump-white-house-job-report). </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-09 23:08:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I didn't say cease all life. I said "end human civilization." Lookup nuclear winter, fallout dispersion patterns, and EMP. There's no such thing as a limited nuclear war between major nuclear powers. The incentives compel escalation. 

Even if some humans did manage to survive a full nuclear exchange, you'd likely have billions of deaths and a decline back into pre-industrial technology at a point where we've used up most of the easily reachable fossil fuels. No sane person wants to even risk this scenario. 

Here's a good flowchart showing [how WW3 could start in eastern Europe](https://www.vox.com/2015/6/29/8858909/russia-war-flowchart). </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-09 22:34:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Nothing would stop the investigation from proceeding under a Clinton administration. In fact, you'd arguably have a lot less interference with whatever the Justice Department wanted to pursue. 

Again, the standard operating procedure would have been not to disclose the emails. I don't see how breaking protocol and damaging Clinton's campaign (for something that it would not be at fault for under this scenario) would ever put the investigation on better footing.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Michael Flynn kept security clearance after warning of Russia blackmail risk </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-09 22:29:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-09 22:24:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Putting aside the national security implications, this is also terrible politics. 

McMaster is universally respected on both sides. If Trump continues to undermine or sideline him, McMaster could simply resign in protest. The press and public opinion would almost certainly side with him. 

That would be a canary in the coal mine moment for the Trump Regime, and they'd struggle to find a replacement of comparable stature. Of course, that would leave the ideologues with free reign--and we'd have to survive that interim period without the world ending. But this is the sort of event, like the Saturday Night Massacre, that can quickly get out of control and topple a Regime.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-09 22:04:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I agree with you 100% about the gravity of the situation--and am not brushing off the seriousness of subverting our elections by any means. It's a hostile act, arguably an act of war that's on same spectrum as staging a coup to overthrow the government. 

But we can't--and shouldn't--attack Russia militarily. It would pose an unacceptable risk of escalating into WW3 and ending human civilization. A mutual defensive pact like NATO strikes the right balance because it doesn't obligate interlocking alliances to join in their allies' offensive wars (ala WW1), but takes away any advantage a potential aggressor, like Russia, would have to gain if it attacked any member of the alliance. After the two most devastating wars in human history, NATO has helped keep peace in Europe for almost seven decades through this basic mechanism.

A similar commitment from every democratic country to treat Russian cyber-attacks as attacks on their own sovereignty and democratic processes could work for the same reason.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-09 21:50:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I don't know if it's possible to completely sever them from the internet, and there would be various work-arounds. But we could conduct proportional counter-cyberattacks and escalate the economic sanctions--like cutting them off from western banks, targeting their financial and energy sectors with boycotts and tarriffs, possibly even looking at expelling them from the WTO. 

Russia has a fairly undiversified, highly petroleum export dependent economy. If there's a concerted effort to cut them off from the benefits of the international system they're trying to undermine, they will suffer disproportionately. This may encourage internal opposition to Putin or at least self-interested restraint on his part to avoid these effects. 

The key is to announce these retaliatory measures in advance and have it on an automatic (or credible) trigger if Putin does the thing that we pre-declare as unacceptable.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-09 21:20:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Exactly. And the weakening of NATO is precisely why I think there's [a plausible case for treason](https://www.reddit.com/r/politics/comments/69yo5l/z/dhasdls) under the "aid and comfort" prong of the [18 U.S.C.  2381](https://www.law.cornell.edu/uscode/text/18/2381) statutory definition *provided* it can be established that there was a *quid pro quo* and direct coordination with the Kremlin to subvert the 2016 election. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-09 21:05:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Right. Because Putin already hit the jackpot. Until we can remove his stooge (or useful idiot) from power, it will mainly be up to the leader(s) of the free worldMerkel (or Schulz) and possibly Macronto deal with Putin. It would be great to get the whole EU onboard if the Orange One prevents action by NATO.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-09 20:55:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> There has to be some form of retaliation, preferably by NATO, for this ongoing campaign of Russian cyber attacks. Maybe amend the North Atlantic Treaty to specify that attempts to subvert democratic elections will be subject to Article 5.

I'm not saying military force should be usedbut this certainly warrants increased and coordinated sanctions, and possibly cyber counter-attacks on Russian IT infrastructure.

Announcing this policy publicly and following through if Putin persists with his campaign will raise the financial and domestic political cost to him and his allies of doing this in the future. That may help deter future cyber attacks.

If this continues to be costless, what does Putin have to lose? It won't always work, but when it does, he can sow internal political divisions among his adversaries, and if he hits the jackpotlike with Trumphe can tarnish their international reputation, obtain favorable policies, or damage them economically. Hypothetically, the US could even suffer a "lost decade" as the result of Trump's presidency if we get a full-blown trade war, recession, repeal of healthcare, and budget-busting tax cuts.

    </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-09 20:42:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> See [this comment](https://www.reddit.com/r/politics/comments/6a6c42/z/dhc8bdv). </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-09 20:37:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It doesn't have to be black or white.

It could simultaneously be true that: (1) Comey badly mishandled Clinton email investigation; and (2) Comey will probably look into the Trump-Russia affair more thoroughly than anyone Trump could appoint.
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-09 20:30:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> After you give Congressional testimony under oath, especially in an official capacity, it's routine to review everything line-by-line and correct or supplement any innacuracies or misstatements. Here, there was a weekend in between the day of Comey's testimony and this report. It's totally plausible that someone caught this on Friday or yesterday, and upon learning of the FBI's suspended plans to supplement Comey's testimony, decided to take it to ProPublica, which broke the story late yesterday.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-09 20:26:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> No, the federal police's improper and decisive interference into the Presidential electionwhich is the subject of an [ongoing inquiry by the DoJ's Inspector General](https://www.washingtonpost.com/news/post-nation/wp/2017/01/12/justice-department-inspector-general-to-investigate-pre-election-actions-by-department-and-fbi/?utm_term=.b26ed896da4a) and which now may involve false statements to Congress under oathis *not* a distraction, especially given the legacy of the FBI's abuse of power under Hoover.

Is it simultaneously true that Comey will probably look into the Trump-Russia affair more thoroughly than anyone Trump could appoint? Yes. But that doesn't excuse Comey's mishandling of the Clinton email investigation.


  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-09 20:13:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Comey did tip the election, and the way he handled the letter violated long-standing norms of investigative procedure. 

Moreover, he foresaw Chaffetz's leak and the "significant risk of being misunderstood" (his words). Yet, he sent the letter anywayand at his discretion, becsuse he wasn't required to. So he can't put the blame on Chaffetz.

If interested, see [this exchange](https://www.reddit.com/r/politics/comments/67fgm6/z/dgr8jk5) (two long posts discussing Comey's handling of the Clinton email investigation).   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-09 19:39:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Heh. Fixed. Try typing one handed w/ a toddler running around and an infant babbling "da da pa ga gu" in the other arm. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-09 18:23:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Assuming for the sake of argument that this were true, you don't destroy the frontrunner's presidential candidacy, or calculate that she can take the hit, in order to protect the source. You review the emails first. If the emails *had* been planted, pretending they weren't would help whomever planted them.     </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-09 18:10:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This isn't a distraction:

FBI Director James B. Comey said at a hearing last week that it made him mildly nauseous to think that he may have influenced the outcomeof the 2016 campaign.

New revelations about his apparently botched testimony are liable to make Democrats  and Comey a little more than mildly nauseous. And they are going todamage Comey's best defense of his actions.

The Post's Devlin Barrett has confirmedProPublica's reportingthat Comeymisstated key details of an investigation into HillaryClintonat a hearing last week.

Specifically at issue are Comey's statements that:

1) Top Clinton aide Huma Abedin forwarded hundreds and thousands of emails from Clinton's private email server to her husband, disgraced former congressman Anthony Weiner, as part of a regular practice of forwarding emails for Weiner to print out for Clinton, and 

2) These emails contained classified information.

Barrett reportsthat this first claim is just not true and the second one obscures the fact that the few classified emails weren't marked classified at the time:

Neither of those statements are accurate, according to people close to the investigation. The investigation found that Abedin did occasionally forward emails to her husband for printing, but it was a far smaller number than described by Comey, and it wasnt a regular practice, these people said. None of the forwarded emails were marked classified but a small number  a handful, according one person said  contained information that was later judged to contain classified information, these people said.

To be clear, these weren't just small details that emerged from Comey's testimony on Wednesday; they weretheheadlinefor manynew outlets that covered Comey's visit to the Senate Judiciary Committee, including The Post.


They werealso keyto Comey's testimony, in that he used them to defend his decision to disclose the new Clinton emails just 11 days before Election Day. Facing questions from Democrats about why he did what he did, Comey cited these facts as proof of the seriousness of the email discovery and the need to say something. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> James Comey just stepped in it big time </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-09 18:05:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-09 15:36:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This wasn't even a concrete question like that. It was a simple followup to his answer about why he was checking IDs to make sure they were constituents.    </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-09 15:34:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The footage really is striking. A GOP lawmaker just off a tough vote gets so frustrated he walks out of an interview he agreed to do, on a week where his main job is to go home and explain why he supported the controversial health-care bill that narrowly passed the House. Cameras captured the whole thing.

And boom, it becomes an instant national story, a microcosm of how conservative Republicans, especially in swingy districts, are struggling to defend why they voted for a bill many of them despise.

Also worth noting: The reporter hadn't even gotten to ask Blum about his health-care vote! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-09 15:30:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I hadn't seen this before. It's terrible. Poor wittle snowfwake. A reporter asked him questions based on his actions. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Just took a tough vote? This GOP congressman shows how NOT to conduct yourself back home. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-09 15:22:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-09 15:01:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> There weren't votes to pass even a watered-down public option. He would have had to have the Senate nuke the filibuster right at the outset, then impose single payer without consensus.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-09 10:21:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Well Comey explicitely [sic] had told a Senate panel that Abedin broke the law and there were laws about them not sharing classified materials with civilians, which she did. 

And Comey cited **lack of criminal intent not that what she did wasn't illegal** as the reason they weren't prosecuting. **Considering our legal framework claims ignorance of the law is not an excuse I'm pretty sure she was let off the hook.**



You're conflating two distinct concepts: (1) **mistake of law** and (2) ***mens rea***.

Mistake of law would be doing something unlawful while sincerely believing it's legal. This is almost never a valid defense outside of some very specific situations that are irrelevant here.

*Mens rea*, on the other hand, is the [culpable mental state](https://en.m.wikipedia.org/wiki/Culpability) that [**must exist concurrently**](https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Concurrence) for a voluntary action to constitute a crime. 

People who arent legally-trained often dont understand that a criminal offense consists of **both** an *actus reus* (a voluntary wrongful action) **and** a requisite degree of *mens rea*. Even criminal statutes that don't explicitly mention mental culpability are construed to contain a *mens rea* requirement. [*See*, *e.g.*, *Morissette v. United States*]( https://scholar.google.com/scholar_case?case=787130527265701764 q=342+U.S.+246,+251 hl=en as_sdt=2006), 342 U.S. 246 (1952) (Crime, as a compound concept, generally constituted only from concurrence of an evil-meaning mind with an evil-doing hand  As the states codified the common law of crimes, even if their enactments were silent on the subject, their courts assumed that the omission did not signify disapproval of the principle but merely recognized that intent was so inherent in the idea of the offense that it required no statutory affirmation.)

Indeed, almost every misdemeanor or felony has a *mens rea* elementwhereas certain "strict liability" infractions, like speeding tickets, don't. This is an essential protection of substantive criminal law, and is encapsulated by the Latin maxim:

*Actus reus non facit reum nisi mens sit rea*

Which translates to:

 An act does not make a person guilty, *unless the mind is guilty*.

Many people understood that Clinton (or Abedin) had committed a crime but "got off" on some technicality, when in fact the absence of *mens rea* completely negates the crime. 

Intent, as used in this context, doesn't mean you need to intend to violate the law. It just means that you must be **aware of** and **consciously disregard** a substantial and unjustifiable risk that you are disclosing classified information, or else *knowingly or purposely* disclose classified information. 

That's not the same as negligence*i.e.* you *should have known* that you were risking careless or inadvertent disclosure of classified information.

By declining to refer the investigation to a prosecutor (which Comey isn't), Comey was saying that there was insufficient evidence of the requisite *mens rea* to even indict on the charges, let alone establish them beyond a reasonable doubt for a conviction.

In other words, no crime. Although, possibly, rules, guidelines, or best practices for information security may have been violated. There may be some civil remedy for that. But that's different from a crime.        </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Fact checker: Trumps pointing of the finger at Obama for failing to vet Flynn </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-09 09:12:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-09 05:19:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This is a huge storyfar from a distraction from today's bad headlines for Trump. We need to have bandwidth for this as well.   

Comey relied on Abedin's misstated conduct portray the significance of the supplemental investigation that precipitated his letter.


So this is a fairly important thing to get wrong under oath. From the article:

FBI director James Comey generated national headlines last week with his dramatic testimony to the Senate Judiciary Committee, explaining his incredibly painful decision to go public about the Hillary Clinton emails found on Anthony Weiners laptop.

Perhaps Comeys most surprising revelation was that Huma Abedin  Weiners wife and a top Clinton deputy  had made a regular practice of forwarding hundreds and thousands of Clinton messages to her husband, some of which contain classified information. Comey testified that Abedin had done this so that the disgraced former congressman could print them out for her boss. (Weiners laptop was seized after he came under criminal investigation for sex crimes, following a media report about his online relationship with a teenager.)

The problem: Much of what Comey said about this was inaccurate. Now the FBI is trying to figure out what to do about it.

**FBI officials have privately acknowledged that Comey misstated what Abedin did and what the FBI investigators found.** On Monday, the FBI was said to be preparing to correct the record by sending a letter to Congress later this week. But that plan now appears on hold, with the bureau undecided about what to do.


The idea that Comey and the FBI don't know how to deal with correcting Comey's testimony is also notable. This is not routine correction for a wrong date or figure. It goes, at minimum, to Comey's basic understanding of what happenedhis stated basis for sending the letter that tipped the election. Accordingly, it could potentially even raise issues in the ongoing Inspector General investigation of Comey's pre-election conduct and handling of the Clinton email investigation.
      </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-09 05:11:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> FBI director James Comey generated national headlines last week with his dramatic testimony to the Senate Judiciary Committee, explaining his incredibly painful decision to go public about the Hillary Clinton emails found on Anthony Weiners laptop.

Perhaps Comeys most surprising revelation was that Huma Abedin  Weiners wife and a top Clinton deputy  had made a regular practice of forwarding hundreds and thousands of Clinton messages to her husband, some of which contain classified information. Comey testified that Abedin had done this so that the disgraced former congressman could print them out for her boss. (Weiners laptop was seized after he came under criminal investigation for sex crimes, following a media report about his online relationship with a teenager.)

The problem: Much of what Comey said about this was inaccurate. Now the FBI is trying to figure out what to do about it.

FBI officials have privately acknowledged that Comey misstated what Abedin did and what the FBI investigators found. On Monday, the FBI was said to be preparing to correct the record by sending a letter to Congress later this week. But that plan now appears on hold, with the bureau undecided about what to do.

ProPublica is reporting a story on the FBIs handling of the Clinton emails and raised questions with government officials last week about possible inaccuracies in Comeys statements about Abedin.

It could not be learned how the mistake occurred. The FBI and Abedin declined ProPublicas requests for comment on the directors misstatements.

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Comeys Testimony on Huma Abedin Forwarding Emails Was Inaccurate </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-09 05:09:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-09 02:40:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's potent because Medicare is both popular and relatively easy to understand since it's not an abstraction. 

When faced with the concrete choice of the garbage system the AHCA is seeking to implement as a replacement to the ACA, Republicans are inadvertently making the Democrats' political arguments for them. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-09 02:35:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Sooner or later, we will have universal, single-payer health care in this country  sooner if Republicans succeed in destroying the Affordable Care Act, later if they fail.

**The repeal-and-replace billpassedby the House last week is nothing short of an abomination. It is so bad that Republicans can defend it only by blowing smoke and telling lies.** You cannot be denied coverage if you have a preexisting condition, House Speaker Paul D. Ryan (R-Wis.)said true in the narrowest, most technical sense but totally false in the real world, since insurance companies could charge those people astronomically high premiums, pricing them out of the market if, as often happens, they let their coverage lapse. There are no cuts to the Medicaid program, Health and Human Services Secretary Tom Pricesaid a bald-faced lie, given that Republicans want to cut$880 billionfrom Medicaid in order to offset a big tax cut for the rich.

...

**I cant think of a more effective way to drive the nation toward a single-payer system.** In their foolish haste to get rid of Obamacare, Republican ideologues are paving the way for something they will like much less.

...

**When President Barack Obama decided to tackle health care, he chose a framework that had been developed at the right-leaning Heritage Foundation.** The ACA is based on what began as Republican ideas: **maintain the basic system of employer-based health insurance provided by private-sector companies; set up exchanges to service the individual market; provide subsidies to help the working poor afford insurance; expand the reach of Medicaid; guarantee reasonably priced coverage to those with preexisting conditions; and impose an individual mandate to ensure that younger, healthier people either buy insurance or pay a fine.**

Its a complicated scheme but it can work, as Republican Mitt Romney proved when he enacted a similar plan as governor of Massachusetts. And because the ACA maintained the basic private-sector structure of our health-care system, Obama reasoned that surely it would win some GOP support in Congress.

He was wrong. Only Democrats voted for the ACA, and Republicans turned its repeal into a partisan crusade  leading, eventually, to Thursdays vote.

I have always believed, however, that **Obamawas prescientin seeing that the ACA would have a larger impact that would be difficult if not impossible to erase**, no matter what Republicans did to the law itself: **It established the principle that health care,** as Obamasaidin accepting theProfile in Courage Awardat the John F. Kennedy Presidential Library and Museum on Sunday, **is not a privilege but a right for all Americans.**

**Ryan and other House Republicans obviously disagree**, but polling suggests they **are increasingly out of step with the nation**. In Gallups most recent survey, the ACA had an approval rating of55 percent, its highest to date. Perhaps more significantly,52 percentof those polled a few months ago agreed with the statement that it is the responsibility of the federal government to make sure all Americans have health care coverage, vs. 45 percent who disagreed  a sharp turnaround in the past couple of years.

Those majorities may seem less than overwhelming, but the trend lines are clear. If tens of millions of Americans lose their insurance coverage and the most popular provisions of Obamacare are nullified, how do you think opinion will evolve?

If nervous Senate Republicans refuse to walk the plank, Obamacare will remain in place. But President Trump and the GOP majorities in Congress now own the health-care issue, and if they dont stop trying to sabotage the ACA and instead try to make it work, voters will be angry. ... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Republicans are accidentally paving the way for single-payer health care </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-09 02:25:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-09 02:10:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> From what I understand based on public reporting that I've read, is that it was managerial incompetence, erratic, contradictory behavior as well as abuse of subordinates. Up till then, particularly while working under McChrystal, he had a model career and earned 3 starsno small feat. He was permitted to retire and discharged honorably. 

I imagine that the sort of offense for which your security clearance would be stripped would involve intentional mishandling of classified info or an offense for which you'd be dishonorably discharged in a court martial. 

I also would expect that security clearance would be a marketable asset for former military officers wanting to start or join private defense/security contractors after their retirement. There's probably a norm for not stripping security clearance unless there's something specific to justify it. Maybe that needs to be looked at.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-09 00:41:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That's a pretty big claim to make when Clinton would have carried MI, WI, and PA if just 39K Trump votersmany of whom voted once or twice for Obamaswitched sides. Those states are certainly in play in 2020.       </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-09 00:19:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I think your analogy captures one of Trump's guiding principles, to the extent anything he does can be called principled and not impulsive. He's trying to be the opposite of Obama, and thinks he knows better. 

But on the other hand, the image of Obama as Trump's sober, experienced future self made me chuckle. This might be one case where doing the opposite might actually be a good rule of thumb.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-08 22:23:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> As I've argued before, a formal declaration of war isn't necessarily required. And I think there's a colorable case of treason to be made on this fact pattern without it. That's not to say that key terms wouldn't get intensely litigated and there isn't an easier charge to pursue for strategic reasons.

The Constitution sets the outer limit of what can be considered treason at [Article III, Section 3](https://www.law.cornell.edu/constitution/articleiii#section3), which provides:

----------

Treason against the United States, shall consist ***only*** [1] in levying war against them, *or* [2] in adhering to their enemies, giving them aid and comfort. **No person shall be convicted of treason unless on the testimony of two witnesses to the same overt act, or on confession in open court.**

**The Congress shall have power to declare the punishment of treason**, but no attainder of treason shall work corruption of blood, or forfeiture ***except*** during the life of the person attainted. (Emphasis and numeration added.)

----------

The statutory definition of treason, codified at [18 U.S.C. 2381](https://www.law.cornell.edu/uscode/text/18/2381) pursuant to Congress's constitutional power to punish treason, defines the offense as:

---

Whoever, owing allegiance to the United States, [1] levies war against them *or* [2] **adheres to their enemies, giving them aid and comfort within the United States or elsewhere**, is guilty of treason and shall suffer death, or shall be imprisoned not less than five years and fined under this title but not less than $10,000; and **shall be incapable of holding any office under the United States**. (Emphasis and numeration added.)

---

Here, no one levied war against the U.S. (though some have called it an act of war), so we're left "adherence to the enemy, giving them aid and comfort"--a separate basis for treason.

Note that the key phrase "aid and comfort"which appears in both definitionshas a narrow, restrictive meaning. But it doesn't appear to require that Russia be a wartime enemy. In [*Cramer v. United States*, 325 US 1 (1945)](https://scholar.google.com/scholar_case?case=2809896451252158562 q="18+u.s.c.+2381" hl=en as_sdt=2006), the U.S. Supreme Court explained that:

---

 Treason of adherence to an enemy was old in the law. It consisted of breaking allegiance to one's own king by forming an attachment to his enemy. Its scope was comprehensive, its requirements indeterminate. It might be predicated on intellectual or emotional sympathy with the foe, or merely lack of zeal in the cause of one's own country. That was not the kind of disloyalty the framers thought should constitute treason. They promptly accepted the proposal to restrict it to cases where also there was conduct which was "giving them aid and comfort."

**"Aid and comfort" was defined** by Lord Reading in the Casement trial comprehensively, as it should be, and yet probably with as much precision as the nature of the matter will permit: **[a]". . . an act which strengthens or tends to strengthen the enemies of the King in the conduct of a war against the King, that is in law the giving of aid and comfort"** *and* **[b] "an act which weakens or tends to weaken the power of the King and of the country to resist or to attack the enemies of the King and the country . . . is . . . giving of aid and comfort."** Lord Reading explained it, as we think one must, in terms of an "act." It is not easy, if indeed possible, to think of a way in which "aid and comfort" can be "given" to an enemy except by some kind of action. Its very nature partakes of a deed or physical activity as opposed to a mental operation.

**Thus the crime of treason consists of two elements: [1] adherence to the enemy; and [2] rendering him aid and comfort.** A citizen intellectually or emotionally may favor the enemy and harbor sympathies or convictions disloyal to this country's policy or interest, but so long as he commits no act of aid and comfort to the enemy, there is no treason. On the other hand, a citizen may take actions which do aid and comfort the enemy  making a speech critical of the government or opposing its measures, profiteering, striking in defense plants or essential work, and the hundred other things which impair our cohesion and diminish our strength  but if there is no adherence to the enemy in this, if there is no intent to betray, there is no treason. (*Numeration and emphasis added*.)

---

From this definition, it doesn't seem like a state of war is necessarily required, because aid and comfort also encompasses overt acts which "weake[n] or ten[d] to weaken the power of the ... of the country to resist or to attack the enemies of ... the country." 

The key term that would be litigated, I think, is "enemy," which isn't defined. Generally, that means you'd use the ordinary meaning. 

Merriam-Webster [defines enemy](https://www.merriam-webster.com/dictionary/enemy) as:

1:  one that is antagonistic to another; especially :  one seeking to injure, overthrow, or confound an opponent

2:  something harmful or deadly 

3

a :  a military adversary

b :  a hostile unit or force

Under these definitions there are good arguments for deeming Russia an enemy for purposes of treason based on their subversion of the election. 

Alternatively, you have the definition of enemy at [50 U.S. Code  2204](https://www.law.cornell.edu/uscode/text/50/2204), which states:

As used in this chapter [*i.e.*, [Chapter 39 of Title 50](https://www.law.cornell.edu/uscode/text/50/chapter-39)]

...

(2) the term enemy means any country, government, group, or person that has been engaged in hostilities, whether or not lawfully authorized, with the United States;

(3) the term person means

(A) any natural person;

(B) any corporation, partnership, or other legal entity; and

(C) any organization, association, or group

By its own terms, this definition does not control uses of the term "enemy" in Title 18 (where the statutory definition of treason appears)--only Chapter 39 of Title 50. But assuming this definition *did* control Title 18, the meaning of "enemy" depends on the meaning of the word "hostilities," which is not defined in the statute. 

So we'd again go to the plain meaning. 

Merriam-Webster [defines hostilities](https://www.merriam-webster.com/dictionary/hostilities) as:

a :  deep-seated usually mutual ill will 

b

(1) :  hostile action

(2) hostilities plural :  overt acts of warfare :  war

2:  conflict, opposition, or resistance in thought or principle

There's a decent argument under the plain meaning that "hostilities" does mean "overt acts of warfare." So if the 50 U.S.C.  2204 controls, you might be able to defeat treason charges provided that subverting an election isn't an act of war. 

Under either meaning of the term "enemy," but especially the first (non-statutory), it's not clear that Russia would be held *as a matter of law* NOT to be an enemy for purposes of treason. I haven't done a comprehensive overview of the caselaw on this issue, but I don't see anything in *Cramer* suggesting otherwise. 

If Russia isn't precluded as a matter of law from being an "enemy," I think that there's a good argument to be made that emnity can be inferred from a factually intensive inquiry into the nature of the act itself--especially if we go with the first plain meaning of enemy as "one seeking to **injure**, **overthrow**, or confound an opponent." 

This understanding of enemy is fully consistent with *Cramer*'s definition of aid and comfort as "weake[ning] or ten[ding] to weaken the power of the ... of the country to resist or to attack." And subverting an election for the highest federal office arguably meets this test--provided there was an explicit *quid pro quo* to secure illicit Russian campaign assistance (and possibly funding) in exchange for U.S. foreign policies desired by Putinincluding a weakening of NATO, the U.S.'s principal military alliance, and consequent impairment of the U.S.' ability to "resist or to attack [its] enemies."

The agreement to subvert our election would also likely satisfy the "**adherence to the enemy**" element of treason (which could be further inferred from the delivery of pro-Putin policies detrimental to U.S. national security and use of the hacked information knowing that it was unlawfully obtained and disclosed under this illicit deal). Enacting pro-Putin policies and speaking favorably of Putin would likely satisfy the overt act of "**aid and comfort**" element. Russia has long been an adversarial power, and the hostile act of subverting our democratic election to promote its objectives and weaken our principal defensive military alliance would likely be sufficient to establish **emnity**. So assuming you had **two witnesses** to the overt acts, you might be able to convict for treason in the strict [18 U.S.C.  2381](https://www.law.cornell.edu/uscode/text/18/2381) sense. 

Of course, there are much easier charges to bring and prove. Bribery. Fraud. Conspiring to commit or aiding and abetting the computer hacking. Violation of campaign finance laws. Possibly espionage, as well as cover-up related charges.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-08 21:45:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I was talking about the short to medium term. I doubt the GOP Congress will hold him accountable. I tend to think that we may have to first deal with him politicallysuch as through impeachmentbefore he can be held accountable criminally.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-08 21:38:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Financial sanctions targetting the Kremlin and its backers' wealth have potential to give second thoughts. Yes, there are unintended consequences for people who aren't responsible. It's preferable to war, though. And we can hope that by being transparent about the reasons for sanctions, it will increase domestic Russian opposition to Putin.

We have to make this interference strategy a lot more costly for the Kremlin going forward.

Trump's Presidency could inflict a "lost decade" on the US, even if we assume for the sake of argument that there was no treasonous quid pro quo or ongoing favors.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-08 21:32:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> To counter Russias online operations, we should adopt a strategy that focuses on two pillars: deterrence and resilience. Its essential both to discourage Russia from launching attacks and to harden our defenses for the next salvo.

Successful deterrence combines clear intentions and demonstrated capabilities. Put simply, we must articulate which Russian cyber-actions will trigger a response, and we must prove that our response will be very costly to the Kremlin.

The West can solve the first half of this equation by issuing a joint NATO-European Union declaration affirming that using cyber-subversion to undermine the democratic process of any member state will be treated as an attack against all. That way, the Russians will understand that the West intends to respond collectively and forcefully should their meddling persist.

The West can address the second half of the equation by agreeing to impose broad economic sanctions against Russia if its red lines are crossed. As a closed society, Russia is less vulnerable to political intervention than is the West. But Russias economy  feeble and dependent on the West  is an appropriate target.

The United States and Europe should go beyond the Obama administrations approach, which directed cyber-sanctions at the actual perpetrators of digital malfeasance, and plan to hit Russia where it hurts most: in its financial, energy and technology sectors.

The United States and the E.U. should broadcast that continued cyberattacks will lead to sanctions against Russian firms in those sectors  and they should agree on measures in advance so that sanctions can be enacted swiftly when needed. If Moscow knows that electoral interference will cause one of its largest banks to be blacklisted by the West  a move far more severe than any taken thus far on Russia sanctions  it will think twice before launching its next attack.

Meanwhile, the West must make itself more resilient to Russian attacks. The Homeland Security Department was right todeclareelectoral systems critical infrastructure in January. But Congress must take it a step further. This begins with supporting an independent investigation of Russian cyber-interference in the 2016 election. Thefactis that Russia tried to penetrate our election systems and influence the outcome. This is not a partisan issue. It is a threat to our national security that demands a thorough investigation.

Additionally, the White House should make it a priority for the government to share cyberthreat intelligence with the private sector. Many institutions that are critical to the functioning of our democracy, from media outlets to telecommunications firms, make tempting targets for Russias cyber-operators. They should not be expected to defend themselves against a nation-state foe such as Russia without proactive assistance from the U.S. government.

Social media companies such as Facebook and Twitter must also do more to prevent Russia from using their platforms as accessories of subversion. Facebooks recentpaperon information operations, which proposes ways to stem the spread of fake news, is a good start. The U.S. government should encourage these efforts, collaborating with social media firms to identify disinformation campaigns and to weed out fake news planted by foreign intelligence services.

With Le Pens defeat on Sunday, the West dodged a bullet. But if we proceed without a comprehensive strategy to counter Russias subversion, we may not be so lucky next time. The United States and Europe must act now to defend themselves against Moscows digital threat to democracy.

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-08 21:28:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> +1 Your dry impression of Trumpian sycophancy is a little too good. You almost had me second-guessing. Props for leaving off the /s, which would have defused the joke. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Russia is still waging cyberwar against Western democracy. Its time to push back. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-08 21:17:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-08 19:28:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Agree that this tends to rule out incompetence, leaving willful, reckless contrarianism or, alternatively, an intentional ulterior purpose. 

Either could have damaging political consequences. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-08 18:44:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That's slowly erroding. And not everyone who voted for him did so because they affirmatively supported him.   

If he loses enough people, it won't matter that his base continues to back him. Recall that he started without even a plurality of the electorate, having won the decisive states by 77,744 votes.

If about 39K people change their minds in those states, he could be toast. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-08 18:38:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If there was a *quid pro quo* and direct coordination between the Trump Campaign and the Kremlin to subvert the election, in the process violating laws on bribery, prohibitions on foreign campaign finance, computer hacking, fraud, and possibly even treason, there'd be a great argument that the election itself was hopelessly tainted and should be anulled.

Possibly that annulment in itself would require a re-vote.

But even if not, it'd be worth challenging every governental action stemming from the tainted election as null and void. 

This would potentially invalidate every law, CRA-based repeal of administrative regulations, executive order, and Presidential appointment into question. If this made it up to SCOTUS, Gorsuch would under normal principles of judicial ethics have to recuse himself, since he has a direct stake in the outcome. Query whether he actually would.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-08 18:17:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> They would have been fine if they simply used proportional delegate allocation rather than winner-take-all or winner-take-most delegate rules meant to help the front-runner and end the primaries quickly. Trump wouldn't have broken 50% and there would have been a brokered convention. Possibly, someone else could have stolen the momentum and gotten a plurality of delegates. But in either case, Trump would likely not have clinched the nomination.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-08 18:12:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If Trump and Pence are impeached for the Russia affair, the idea that he'd nominate his successor would be highly objectionable, since they would presumably be tainted by the misconduct that got them impeached. And assuming it happens after Democrats potentially re-take the House, they'd be in a position to block the confirmation, which has to go through both the House and Senate.

Republicans won't want President Pelosi. So what should happen at that point is a bipartisan amendment to the Presidential Succession Act providing for a special election to fill the vacancy. Under Article II, Section 1, Clauses 4 and 6 of the Constitution, Congress has authority to pass a law to do determine who becomes President when both the Presidency and Vice-Presidency are vacant. That's where most of the current line of succession comes from. There's no need to go through elaborate process to put people in positions such as Speaker or President Pro Temp of the Senate so they can, in turn, ascend to the Presidency under the current law. Congress can and should simply change the law. 

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-08 17:53:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Done. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> It sure sounds like John Kasich might primary President Trump in 2020 </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-08 17:43:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-08 17:19:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> *Not only* did Obama fire Flynn (a yuge red flag), *not only* did Yates and Cummings warn the Trump Transition about Flynn, *not only* did the Trump Transition actually vet Flynn and discover the undisclosed foreign work and contacts, but Obama also *explicitly* warned Trump*in person*, during their *first meeting* after the electionnot to hire Flynn. 

And yetafter shitting on Obama's sound advicethe buck-passer-in-chief is still making half-assed excuses and trying to blame Obama for giving Flynn security clearance *before Obama fired him*.

Trump may actually believe he's never wrong, and he will never admit it even if he doesn't. But there's no way he can disown this decision in the eyes of the public.


                  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-08 15:20:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Acoording to the results page linked above, there were 3,019,724 (6.35%) Blank votes, and 1,049,532 (2.21%) Null votes.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-08 14:48:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Aren't abstentions just what the French call not voting? They're not the same as the blank and null ballots actually castdistinct categories ("blancs" and "nuls") within the  portion of the electorate that turned out to vote ("votants").  It's my understanding that they know the precise number because they have universal voter registration (the proper way to handle this). 74.56% turnout is high for us, but the lowest since 1969 for them.            </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-08 14:38:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Well, states *can* withdraw, but not after July 20 for a Presidential election taking place in the same year. Since the NPV compact is a binding inter-state contractual agreement, and the other states also gave something in value in exchange, it's fair to prevent unilateral disorderly withdrawalparticularly if the objective were to game the system at the expense of other signatory states who allocated their electoral votes in reliance on the other signatories' allocations.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-08 04:09:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You should be thanking Comey for [bringing this about to begin with](https://fivethirtyeight.com/features/the-comey-letter-probably-cost-clinton-the-election/?ex_cid=538twitter).
  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-08 03:49:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [See this comment](https://www.reddit.com/r/politics/comments/69rhrq/why_doesnt_anyone_know_were_incredibly_close_to/dh9mi5v). </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-08 03:46:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> A compact is in fact a legally binding contract on a signatory state. And under the federal Constitution, states can't pass laws retroactively impairing contract rights, which is what a law purporting to withdraw a signatory state from the NPV compact outside of the terms of the withdrawal provisions would do. If a state were to try to enact a law that conflicted with the compact's withdrawal procedures, the other signatory states could sue it to seek a court order compelling specific performance or the compact.    </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-07 20:21:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> IN SEPTEMBER 1941,the German army drove Soviet power from Kiev, the capital of the Soviet republic of Ukraine. The Nazi secret police, the Gestapo, took over the building that had housed the Soviet secret police, known as the NKVD. Natives of Kiev soon appeared to denounce their neighbors to their new Nazi masters, just as they had done under Soviet rule.

The main enemy defined by Soviet power before the war had been the Polish spy, so Kievans informed on neighbors of Polish origin. Under the Nazis, the enemy was the Jewish communist, and so now it was Jewish neighbors who were in peril. The two regimes, different in so many ways, were alike in their cultivation of, and indeed their reliance upon, denunciation.

**The scene seems distant, the perpetrators exotic. But are we so different? If we could denounce our neighbor with impunity, would we recognize the danger to ourselves?** Denunciation is a great temptation. You can destroy lives on a whim.

**Our own Department of Homeland Security has just announced an American denunciation program, known as the Victims of Immigration Crime Engagement office.** The stated purpose is to aid the victims of undocumented migrants.VOICE declaresthat any person who is affected by criminal activity allegedly perpetrated by criminal aliens in the United States should consider himself or herself victims of immigration crime. An online form encourages Americans to name names and check off the violation that best applies from a list that ranges from benefits fraud to terrorism  and includes other. Did you have additional businesses/individuals to report on? the questionnaire concludes.

**Did you catch the trick? Did it strike you that the due process of law had been abandoned in favor of classic denunciation politics? Or did you accept that the person doing the denouncing was automatically the victim, and the person being denounced automatically a criminal?** There is no reason to believe that someone is the victim of a crime just because he or she goes online and denounces a member of an officially stigmatized group. **In a country where the rule of law prevails, it is the courts that decide whether a crime has been committed.**  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The VOICE office enables citizens to denounce their neighbors </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-07 20:15:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-06 13:59:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> And they acheive this nationalist goal by backing foreign interference in the national elections of various countries.

There's no coherent principle of national sovereignty here. It's about undermining the liberal democratic order and achieving right-wing policies through increasingly authoritarian means.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-06 13:51:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Aprilwas the safest monthin the history of New York City. Murdersare down 13 percentcompared to this time last year. Last month saw 20 homicides, versus 28 in April 2016. Overall, the city has seena 5 percent declinein serious crime from last year  and New York had already achieved historicallylow crime in 2016.

NYPD officials attribute the most dramatic drops to precision policing, where cops identify crime patterns and investigate and target the key offenders. Police build strong cases over time with the goal of making meaningful arrests  quality over quantity  that more often lead to prosecution.

And as officials promoted New York as one of the safest big cities in America, they managedto quietly throw shadeat the Trump administration. Last month, the Justice DepartmentdescribedNew York City as soft on crime in a memo warning so-called sanctuary cities that they risked losing funding for failing to cooperate with federal immigration authorities. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-06 13:17:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Remember when Trump or the elf start fearmongering about crime. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> New York City Has Another Record-Low Crime Month </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-06 13:16:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-05 06:18:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Read your comment. Will respond at length when I get in front of a computer later.

Will just note a few things for now.

First, the link to my comment re: ShareBlue was an error on my part. I copied over the link when responding to someone else's comment to a sepparate article. I actually intended to link to this Chicago Tribune article:

[FBI leaders knew about new emails for weeks before Comey letter](http://www.chicagotribune.com/news/nationworld/politics/ct-fbi-emails-investigation-20161102-story.html)

Second, there's plenty of evidence that Comey's actions affected the election. 

[Ive argued the point at length](https://www.reddit.com/r/politics/comments/5nmxob/z/dcctqr2) and it seems clear to me that letters effect was decisive. Its actually harder to see how the letter *didnt* matter than how it did, when a swing of just 39K votes allocated among three states would have changed the outcome.  

[I'm not the only one](http://m.motherjones.com/kevin-drum/2017/04/lets-talk-about-bubbles-and-james-comey) with [this assessment](http://www.vox.com/the-big-idea/2017/1/11/14215930/comey-email-election-clinton-campaign). [Not by a longshot](https://twitter.com/NateSilver538/status/855798547505180673).

Here's Nate Silver's excellent, detailed article from yesterday:

[The Comey Letter Probably Cost Clinton The Election](https://fivethirtyeight.com/features/the-comey-letter-probably-cost-clinton-the-election/?ex_cid=538twitter)

The fact that Comey's letter likely tipped the election doesn't, by itself, establish negligence. Rather, i contend that his failure to take adequate precautions after expressly acknowleging the "significant risk of being misunderstood" does that. I linked you to a detailed pre-election comment where I lay that out. You didn't respond substantively to the comment, and instead focused on your perception of my partisan biasincluding through your suggestion that ShareBlue and Rolling Stone are telling me what to think about Comey. 

Will continue discussion later. Thanks for reply. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-05 05:50:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This is good. Pelosi was ready to go in the 2007 and 2009. This is necessary preparation for a return to Democratic House control that Trumpcare's partial passage just made a lot more likely. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-05 04:30:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Are you referring to the stock footage shoot for the 2018 attack ads? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-05 03:44:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Heckle him or his staffers at their office. Hold town halls in absentia. All sorts of ways to deal with this.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-05 03:32:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> With more haste, less transparency, greater public opposition, and no attempt to compromise across the aisleall in order to enact a bill that is substantively much worse policy.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-04 23:58:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> He needs to be heckled at a town hall. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-04 21:54:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Agreed. Laws have consequences, and there's only so much the playing field can be tilted. Go for the juggular. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-04 21:51:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> In 2010, Democrats who voted for Obamacare paid a huge price in the midterms. Just how big a price? **A2011 studyby FiveThirtyEight contributorSeth Masketand another political scientist, Steven Greene**, found that Democrats who voted for Obamacare lost 6.6 to 7.6 percentage points of the vote, depending on which model they used. Note, however, that these totals refer to theshareof the vote the Democrat lost and not to themarginthat the Democrat had against the Republican. Since third-party candidates are rarely major factors in House races, almost every vote the Democrat loses is one the Republican gains. **Thus, the effect on the Democratsmarginagainst the Republican was roughly twice that  13 to 15 percentage points. Thats a huge effect; it means that a Democrat who was on track to cruise to re-election by 12 points would lose if theyd voted for Obamacare.**

**Alater studyby Masket, Greene and three other researchers found impacts of a similar magnitude**, estimating a 5.8 percentage point Obamacare effect on the Democrats vote share using one technique, and an 8.5-point effect using another. Again, these are voteshares,not votemargins. (We usually think in terms of margins here at FiveThirtyEight). **The margins would be roughly twice as high  in the range of 12- to 17-point penalty for a Democrat who voted for Obamacare.**

**If Republican members should suffer a similar penalty for voting for the AHCA  somewhere in the neighborhood of 15 points  it could put dozens of GOP-held seats in play.** Some 33 Republicans won their seats by 14 percentage points or less in 2016Or in 2017 in the event of Rep. Ron Estes of Kansas, who won his seat in a special election last month.

Republicans in the next tier or two down could also be vulnerable, however, because the overall political climate is likely to be a lot worse for Republicans than it was in 2016. In 2016, Republicans won the aggregate popular vote for the U.S. House byabout 1 percentage point. Democrats currently have a 5- to 6-point lead inpolls of the 2018 House vote, however. Moreover, the numbers for the presidents partyusually get worseover the course of the midterm cycle as more voters tune into the political process. **There could easily be an overall partisan swing of 5 to 10 percentage points against Republicans, therefore**. **Its not quite clear how this partisan swing would interact with the AHCA penalty  whether youd add them together or whether thats double-counting  but it should be enough to make a lot of Republican incumbents nervous. There are 58 Republicans who won by less than 20 points inwho voted for the AHCA.**


...

Theres even a chance that Republicans could suffer a bigger penalty than Democrats did. Asunpopular as Obamacare wasas it was being debated by Congress in 2009 and 2010, the AHCA ismore unpopular still. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The Health Care Bill Could Be A Job-Killer For GOP Incumbents </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-04 21:37:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-04 20:40:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The hope is that if the Senate passes a bill, it will be too moderate for the Freedom Caucus. But we shouldn't depend on that. It would be better to kill it altogether, because now that the entire House GOP caucus has painted targets on its back, they may feel pressure to pass something.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-04 20:38:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> He's made noise opposing it from the right, along with Mike Lee, and is probably the third most vulnerable Senator in 2018 after Heller and Flake. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-04 20:34:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Key Senators to pressure:

Susan Collins, Lisa Murkowski, Mike Lee, Bill Cassidy, Dean Heller, Jeff Flake, Rob Portman, Cory Gardner, Shelley Moore Capito, Tom Cotton, Rand Paul, Mike Lee and even... Ted Cruz.

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-04 20:33:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The fact that it's moving to the Senate doesn't mean we should let you the pressure on House Reps who voted for this. [Great Twitter thread arguing precisely why such pressure is important.](https://twitter.com/benwikler/status/859838674258755584)


We need to do both simultaneously.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-04 20:30:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Also Susan Collins, Lisa Murkowski, Mike Lee, Bill Cassidy, Dean Heller, Jeff Flake, Rob Portman, Cory Gardner, Shelley Moore Capito, Tom Cotton, and even... Ted Cruz. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-04 20:26:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Have to do *both* simultaneously. Exert maximum pressure on GOP Senators *and* give hell to the House Reps who voted for this.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> House Sends Health Care Hot Potato to Senate </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-04 20:23:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-04 19:58:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If it's losing, they may keep the vote open for hours like they did with Medicare Part D under Bush. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-04 19:54:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [Per CBS](https://twitter.com/MajorCBS/status/860190228698497024) conversation with WH official, current whip count is 217 in favor, with 216 needed for passage.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-04 19:46:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Pelosi is a badass. Can't wait to call her Madam Speaker again on January 3, 2019. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Live Vote Count: The House Health Care Bill </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-04 19:33:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-04 19:29:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I don't give half-a-fuck what Republicans subjectively "like." They're objectively voting to implement this as policy against the express desires of their constituents. They own every word of it as if it were their own baby. Because it is. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-04 19:18:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Exactly. 

[Great thread arguing precisely this](https://twitter.com/benwikler/status/859838674258755584).

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-04 18:35:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The CBO is [run by a guy handpicked by the Republican leadership and praised by Tom Price](https://thinkprogress.org/price-belittles-cbo-director-he-picked-to-save-trumpcare-921acebf28bd). Nevertheless, it still has some independence and will "show its work." The CBO estimated that 24 million people would lose coverage over 10 years under the previous version of Trumpcare, and this in any ways the current bill is *even worse*.  If Republicans somehow try to tamper with the CBO analysis, it would leak pretty quickly and explode in their faces.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-04 18:01:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  "crouching behind their desks with the phones unplugged".


Don't give them so much credit for owing up to what they've done or actually working. Their *staffers* will be doing that. 

The bastards themselves will just [run away to Universal Studios](http://m.dailykos.com/story/2017/4/12/1652432/-Paul-Ryan-is-spotted-vacationing-at-Universal-Studios-avoiding-town-hall-meetings-for-over-550-days) in the meantime.

But they won't be able to run from the voters on November 6, 2018.

     </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-04 17:31:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Dead on:

House GOP leaders are confidently forging ahead with the repeal-and-replace vote today, and **they are laughing off questions as to why they would go forward despite their willfully premature and dim understanding of how the measure might impact millions of Americans and one-sixth of the U.S. economy.** They are doing this without seeing a nonpartisan analysis of their new bill from the Congressional Budget Office  which will, conveniently, allow them to conceal the full truth of what they are voting for from their constituents.

**But this is likely to backfire**. Heres why: The Congressional Budget Office score of the bill is coming, anyway  as soon as next week. And it will land after an untold number of House Republicans have committed themselves to the bill.

**This means moderate and vulnerable House Republicans who are already worried about explaining to their constituents why they voted for the bill"*  which guts protections for the sick and rolls back coverage for millions of poor and working-class people while delivering a huge tax cut to the rich  **will have to justify it again, in light of a nonpartisan analysis spelling out the grisly details of what they really voted for.**

...

If this happens, it will put moderate and vulnerable Republicans who supported the bill in an odd spot. They will be at home on recess, hearing from their constituents, and they will have to justify their vote for something that threatens to inflict all the harm that the new CBO score has now projected it will inflict.

**Whats more, they will also have to explain in retrospect why they rushed the vote in advance of a CBO score detailing its impact, even though it was only a few days away**  and is designed to help them make a more informed choice about what it is they were truly voting for. **At that point, though, it will be too late. They will already be on the hook for it.**

----

The CBO score will be a real problem. It frames the context and big picture. But even more problematic, narratively, for vulnerable Republican incumbents are the individual substantive provisions of the bill that lend themselves to compelling attack ads.

Besides gutting essential protections for pre-existing conditions by [making it unaffordable for anyone who actually needs to purchase coverage](https://www.americanprogress.org/issues/healthcare/news/2017/04/21/431019/premium-increases-pre-existing-conditions-latest-aca-repeal-plan-state/) (and [exempting Congress from this change](https://www.vox.com/policy-and-politics/2017/5/4/15542314/republican-health-plan-loophole-exemption)), it was [reported by the WSJ just today that this bill also removes protections from employer health plans](https://www.wsj.com/articles/little-noted-provision-of-gop-health-bill-could-alter-employer-plans-1493890203) (which is how the mast majority of people get healthcare). Others have noted that the bill [cuts special education funding as well](https://mobile.nytimes.com/2017/05/03/us/politics/health-bill-medicaid-special-education-affordable-care-act.html) by preventing schools from getting Medicaid reimbursement for services provided under [IDEA](https://en.m.wikipedia.org/wiki/Individuals_with_Disabilities_Education_Act).

As people comb through the statutory language, expect to find more of these gems. If the AHCA clears the House today, it will be up to us to discover and hang them around the necks of every single Republican who backs this billregardless of whether it eventually becomes law. 

By voting for a bill packed with these cruel and ill-conceived provisions, they're giving a costly signal of their partisan loyalty and showing their willingness to put it above the needs and express desires of their constituents. How ever they try to excuse it in 2018, costly actions speak far louder than words. These Republicans can be depended on to fuck people over in the future.

Vote accordingly.

 



           </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The GOPs strange, ugly strategy of rushing todays vote will backfire. Heres how. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-04 17:23:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-04 17:07:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Clearly not. 

Besides gutting essential protections for pre-existing conditions by making it unaffordable to purchase coverage (and exempting Congress from the change), it was reported by the WSJ just today that this bill also removes protections from employer health plans. 

Others have noted that it cuts special education funding as well.

As people comb through the statutory language, expect to find more of these gems.

If the AHCA clears the House today, it will be up to us to discover and hang them around the necks of every single Republican who backs this billregardless of whether it eventually becomes law. 

By voting for a bill packed with these cruel and terrible provisions, they're giving a costly signal of their partisan loyalty and showing their willingness to put it above the needs and express desires of their constituents. How ever they try to excuse it in 2018, costly actions speak far louder than words. These Republicans can be depended on to fuck people over.

 



     </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The Daily 202: 10 storylines to follow as the House votes on health care </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-04 16:43:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-04 09:31:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Also a response to /u/dfecht.

I *am* casting doubt on the propriety of  Comey's *observable conduct*. This is not revisionism. I've argued consistently, since [a week before the election](https://www.reddit.com/r/politics/comments/5ayble/z/d9kctvb), that Comey's actions failed to comport with investigatory protocol and DoJ guidelines, fell short of the basic precautions and standard of care we'd expect from someone in Comey's situation facing the scenario he did, and evidence the application of a troubling, seemingly arbitrary double standard. 

I've *never* suggested and don't believe, however, thay Comey was in any way intentionally assisting or coordinating with Wikileaks or the Russian government. 

Rather, I interpreted the final part of the excerpted New York Times articlewhich I obviously didn't write, but *did* select and emphasizeas showing the concrete adverse consequences of Comey's failure to endorse the October 7 Statement. If Comey and the FBI had endorsed the Statement, and it we ere understood as reflecting the unanimous assessment of the IC, there would have been significantly less tolerance for Trump's sophistry concerning the perpetrators of the hacks. It's notable that the Statement was put out on the very day that the Podesta email dumps beganabout an hour after the the Access Hollywood tape leaked.

Further, the timing is also significant given that Comey's rationale for not endorsing the Statement was that October 731 days from the electionwas too close and politicized, even though the Statement didn't specifically mention that Russia was helping Trumpa fact known at the timeor disclose the existence of the FBI's collusion investigation. Recall that the first letter to Chaffetz was sent on October 2811 days from the election. Evidently, in Comey's inscrutable judgment, that *wasn't* too close to the vote, even though [the FBI had known about the emails since early October](http://www.chicagotribune.com/news/nationworld/politics/ct-fbi-emails-investigation-20161102-story.html). 

As for Comey's motives, I don't really care as much. It seems like one could prove culpable negligence at a minimum. We know, based on his own internal memo to subordinates (which, of course, leaked), Comey sent the letter to Chaffetz knowing full-well that the letter would likely leak. He contemplated and accepted the risk and that it could influence the election. Yet, he failed to take even basic precautions to minimize the damage such a leak could do. Such precautions would not have required the disclosure of investigatory or classified information. If he felt compelled to say something, he could simply have said, "there's approximately X number of emails, Y/X are duplicates of emails that we have already reviewed, and we anticipate based on the established rate of review that the new emails will take Z days."

De-duplication is not complicated with modern off the shelf e-discovery software. Moreover, Comey would not have breached any ethical duty to supplement his Congressional testimony by waiting until a preliminary review had taken place first. All that his purposely vague initial letter did was fuel speculation and innuendo. Trump promptly seized on the resulting uncertainty to play up wildly-exaggerated scenarios where Clinton was about to be arrested. This had a measurable effect on the polls *while people were already voting*.

As noted, the way Comey handled all of this didn't only violate basic investigative practices and common sense, but it was also against long-standing DoJ policies. Indeed, the very fact that Comey's actions did break so drastically from normal protocol fueled further speculation about the gravity of what might be in the laptop emails. 

Now, if you ask me to speculate on further motives or aggraving characteristics, I think that Comey's legendary [self-righteousness](http://www.nytimes.com/2016/11/02/opinion/campaign-stops/james-comeys-self-righteous-meddling.html?smid=tw-nytopinion smtyp=cur) and obsessive [fixation with *appearing* impartial and protecting his reputation](http://www.rollingstone.com/politics/features/how-the-fbis-james-comey-fumbled-the-clinton-email-probe-w447597) probably played a role, and are more persuasive than Comey merely being a run-of-the-mill partisan hack.


       </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-04 08:25:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [I did](https://www.reddit.com/r/politics/comments/66byny/sean_spicer_cant_name_a_single_legislative/dghcbz4). 

Your substantive point? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-04 03:22:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I've called Trump the Orange One as a term of endearment since he was installed in last year's *perevorot*, because he's... well... sporting a chemical orange tan that's as fraudulent (and toxic) as he is.

It's more convenient than dealing with Cyrillic text to refer to his title,    (Gubernator of the Trumpistan Oblast).

And his formal style in English is bit of a mouthful:


[**Donald John "Yugehands" Trump, *il Douche* of Orange**](https://m.imgur.com/a/nArsi), the first of his name; the Tremendous; the Unschackled and Unpresidented; Commander-in-Chief and Emperor of the United States; Supreme Leader and Lord Protector of the American Empire; Tribune of the People and Speaker of the House; Senator for Life and President of the Imperial Senate; Chief Justice of the Emperor's So-called Bench; Registrar and Scourge of Muslims; Spinner of Tales; Builder of Walls; Deporter of Mexicans; Breaker of Budgets; Grabber of Pussy; and Restorer of Greatness.     </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-04 02:29:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> There were more Senators opposed based on the Medicaid Cuts. But the focus should be on defeating it in the House. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-04 02:28:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> There's an open question whether the plan can meet the requirements for reconciliation.  But assuming it can, it will still be a tough fight to get 50 votes.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-04 02:15:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The only reason this is even a fight is that the House Democratic Caucus, led by Pelosi, has been absolutely unified. 

If the [whip counts](https://www.nytimes.com/interactive/2017/05/01/upshot/health-care-vote-whip-count-comparison.html) are accurate, we need 4-5 more GOP voteswith over 30 GOP members still having undecided/unclear public positions. Of those undecideds, 22 are members of the more  moderate Tuesday Group or else are from districts that Clinton won, and 2 are Freedom Caucus holdouts, [according to the NYT](https://www.nytimes.com/interactive/2017/05/01/us/politics/health-care-whip-count.html?_r=0) (which has the most conservative/pessimistic whip count). 

**Bottom line:** ***we can do this***. 

The public is on Democrats' side. Call your Rep if they are potential GOP votes against this, or even if it's just to thank them for standing firm. Overload the Congressiinal switchboards. If this can be defeated in the House a second time, the damage to the Orange One's legislative agenda going forward could be profound. And even if they ram it through in the House, they're voting their seats away. So don't give up even if things momentarily seem dark.  

    </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-04 01:24:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The FBI's leakiness doesn't provide any justification for Comey's actions. If anything, it calls his management of the Bureau into question. You don't make decisions that important on the assumption that your subordinates will mutiny and undermine you. Comey should have followed through with the proper investigatory protocol and held leakers accountable after the fact if they leaked. 

The tone of mainstream coverage would be completely different, with less coverage focusing on the extraordinary nature of Comey's actions being an indication of a shoe about to drop for Clinton. And the impropriety of the leaks would become apparent once the email review was complete. If Comey did this and Clinton still lost because of the leaks, it would not have been because of his misconductas it is now.
  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-03 23:44:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The way that Comey sent the letter without having a warrant calls the rationale he gave for needing to send the letter into question. As does the fact that the FBI knew about the emails for weeks before Comey was ultimately briefed on October 27. There was enough time to complete the full review of the emails during that delay. Comey still hasn't adequately explained this gap. If FBI agents were hiding the emails from him in order for the renewed investigation to have maximum political impact on Clinton, the letter should not have been sent. At minimum, the timing of his briefing should have given him serious pause before sending the letter.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Senator dismantles Comeys excuse for sending Clinton letter days before election </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-03 23:35:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-03 23:31:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> A criminal conviction and up to a year in jail for laughing at the elf. Yet the elf still hasn't been called to task for his perjurious testimony. MAGA, I guess?

A jury on Wednesday convicted three Code Pink activists on charges related to a protest at the confirmation hearing of Jeff Sessions for attorney general  including a Virginia woman who said all she did was break out in laughter.

Each of the three protesters faces up to 12 months in jail, $2,000 in fines, or both, depending on the outcome of a June 21 sentencing hearing.

The woman with the laugh, Desiree A. Fairooz, 61, of Bluemont, Va., said she was undeterred. Well face the music when we get to that, she said.

A two-day trial in District of Columbia Superior Court in Washington ended on Tuesday. All three had pleaded not guilty, rejected a plea deal and demanded the trial.

In an April court filing, the office of the U.S. attorney for the District of Columbia had argued that all three protesters shared a common goal to impede and disrupt the hearing. Ms. Fairooz, the office said, had created a scene.

It was early in the hearing when Senator Richard Shelby, Republican of Alabama, said that Mr. Sessionss record of treating all Americans equally under the law is clear and well-documented, Ariel Gold, the campaign director of Code Pink, said on Wednesday.

Ms. Fairooz said that, on hearing that, she let out a giggle.

I just couldnt hold it, she said on Wednesday. It was spontaneous. It was an immediate rejection of what I considered an outright lie or pure ignorance. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Code Pink Protesters at Sessions Hearing Could Face Year in Jail </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-03 23:28:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-03 22:42:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thanks for correcting. And sorry that I was a bit curt initially. I'm frustrated with the effort by some to lionize Comey.

His decision regarding the October 7 is puzzling to me. I don't know if he was pressed on it today. But the too close to the election justification rings hollow and is incoherent in light of his later actions. 

I wonder if it was contrarian petulance. In other words, "I didn't get to do it my way, so I'm not going to do it your way either." He seems to have an inflated and self-righteous sense of his own judgment and importance. Even if it wasn't retaliating, if he decided to not endorse the October 7 statement for some idiosyncratic reason and wouldn't take feedback from others who thought it was a good idea, I find that pretty inexcusable.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-03 22:33:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The point is that Comey was *not* legally required to send the letters--certainly not by the Constitution. He mishandled the Clinton email investigation from the outset by [failing to follow standard investigative protocols that exist for a reason](https://www.reddit.com/r/politics/comments/69032x/senate_dem_ill_ask_comey_why_he_talked_about/dh2pzto/). That failure put him in a position of giving testimony and potentially having to supplement it when the laptop emails were discovered. But even then, he could have properly relied on standing DoJ protocol against election interference--as well as discussions with superiors who advised him strongly against sending the letter--and waited at least until the investigation was complete before disclosing it to Congress.

He made a discretionary judgment, and it was miscalibrated. When you are utterly convinced of your own integrity, refuse to take input, and think know better than anyone else, that tends to happen.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-03 22:05:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Props for correcting. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-03 21:46:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Sorry, but that's revisionist bullshit. **Comey wanted to write an op-ed where** ***he*** **personally warned of Russian interference**. But he later refused to endorse the [official October 7 statement from ODNI and DHS](https://www.dhs.gov/news/2016/10/07/joint-statement-department-homeland-security-and-office-director-national)supposedly because it was too close to the election. And he persisted in this stance even after Trump used the FBI's non-endosement to call the validity of the October 7 statement into doubt.

Here's a [key excerpt from the April 22 NYT piece](https://www.nytimes.com/2017/04/22/us/politics/james-comey-election.html?_r=0 referer=https://t.co/gU4pdevSXc):


As the F.B.I. plunged deeper into that investigation, Mr. Comey became convinced that the American public needed to understand the scope of the foreign interference and be inoculated against it.

**He proposed writing an op-ed piece to appear in The Times or The Washington Post, and showed the White House a draft his staff had prepared**, according to two former officials. (After the Times story was published online on Saturday, a former White House official said the text of the op-ed had not been given to the White House.) **The op-ed did not mention the investigation of the Trump campaign, but it laid out how Russia was trying to undermine the vote.**

**The president replied that going public would play right into Russias hands by sowing doubts about the elections legitimacy.** Mr. Trump wasalready saying the system was rigged, and if the Obama administration accused Russia of interference, Republicans could accuse the White House of stoking national security fears to help Mrs. Clinton.

**Mr. Comey argued that he had unique credibility to call out the Russians and avoid that criticism.** After all, he said, he had just chastised Mrs. Clinton at his news conference.

***The White House decided it would be odd for Mr. Comey to make such an accusation on his own, in a newspaper, before American security agencies had produced a formal intelligence assessment. The op-ed idea was quashed. When the administration had something to say about Russia, it would do so in one voice, through the proper channels.***

...

[B]y fall, the gravity of the Russian effort to affect the presidential election had become clear.

The D.N.C. hack and others like it had once appeared to be standard Russian tactics to tarnish a Western democracy. After the WikiLeaks disclosures and subsequent leaks by a Russian group using the name DCLeaks, agents and analysts began to realize that Moscow was not just meddling. It was trying to tip the election away from Mrs. Clinton and toward Mr. Trump.

**Mr. Comey and other senior administration officials met twice in the White House Situation Room in early October to again discuss a public statement about Russian meddling**. But the roles were reversed: Susan Rice, the national security adviser, wanted to move ahead. **Mr. Comey was less interested in being involved.**

At their second meeting, ***Mr. Comey argued that it would look too political for the F.B.I. to comment so close to the election, according to several people in attendance. Officials in the room felt whiplashed. Two months earlier, Mr. Comey had been willing to put his name on a newspaper article; now he was refusing to sign on to an official assessment of the intelligence community.***

Mr. Comey said that in the intervening time, Russian meddling had become the subject of news stories and a topic of national discussion. He felt it was no longer necessary for him to speak publicly about it. **So when Jeh Johnson, the Homeland Security secretary, and James R. Clapper Jr., the national intelligence director, accused Russias senior-most officials on Oct. 7 of a cyber operation to disrupt the election, the F.B.I. was conspicuously silent.**

***That night, WikiLeaks began posting thousands of hacked emails from another source: the private email account of John Podesta, chairman of the Clinton campaign.***
          </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-03 21:04:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> At least two problems with that.

1. Trump made an issue of the FBI's conspicous non-endorsement of the October 7 statement in order to cast doubt onto the validity of the underlying Intelligence assessments upon which that statement was based. Comey remained silent thtoughout this. That gave a misleading impression.

2. Again, the supplemental testimony from Comey via the letter was given at his discretion. Putting aside the question of Comey only being in that position due to his earlier improper editorializing, Comey could have easily relied on standing DoJ policy to rebut any charge of impropriety had he first waited to complete the review of additional emails or at least done a preliminary review to exclude duplicates. The extraordinary nature of Comey's own actions became evidence that something extraordinary was about to happen (when in reality it just showed his gross departure from investigatory norms).

As we know, nothing new came of the investigation. But even if you look at it with foresight, rather than hindsight, Comey should have been much more concerned with the two to three week delay in briefing him after the emails were discovered on the laptop. That delay was potentially enough time to complete a full reviewwhich took 9 days, including obtention of the warrant. Delaying the start of the review caused the letter to be far more damaging than if it had been sent in early October. Comey needed to factor the timing of his letter far more than he appears to have done.

        </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-03 20:27:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Some people do question it.

But beyond that, the "it shouldn't even have been close" line of criticism is asinine. We live in a closely-divided country. Partisan tribalism is a thing. And to top it off, this would have been the third term for the Democratic Party, which historically is a very difficult feat to pull off (Clinton actually outperformed the vote share one would expect based on the historical average dropoff and Obama's 2012 vote share by 2.9%). Likewise, the polisci models based on fundamentals (rather than polls) had the race as a tossup to a slight GOP advantage.

If Clinton would have managedin the absence of Comey's interferenceto win slim but a hard fought victory and retake the Senate in the process, that should have been the outcome. 

Comey's actions improperly thwarted the conclusion to which the election was building. If we believe in free democratic elections as the way to choose our leaders, that should trouble us. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-03 20:08:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm linking to a comment containing citations and further elaboration of the point.  

You're wrong about the Trump investigationwhich is itself a misnomer here because what would have been disclosed is Russia's interference, not the investigation into the Trump campaign's potential collusion.

Obama didn't think it was appropriate for Comey to write a newspaper op-ed on his own concerning Russian interference. Yet, it was Comey who refused to sign on to an October 7 statement by the ODNI and DHS attributing the hacks and interference campaign to Russiasupposedly because 31 days was too close to an election (but the letters 11 and 2 days out apparently weren't).  

From [the NYT piece cited in the comment you take issue with](https://www.nytimes.com/2017/04/22/us/politics/james-comey-election.html?_r=0 referer=https://t.co/gU4pdevSXc):

Mr. Comey and other senior administration officials met twice in the White House Situation Room in early October to again discuss a public statement about Russian meddling. But the roles were reversed: Susan Rice, the national security adviser, wanted to move ahead. **Mr. Comey was less interested in being involved.**

At their second meeting, ***Mr. Comey argued that it would look too political for the F.B.I. to comment so close to the election, according to several people in attendance. Officials in the room felt whiplashed. Two months earlier, Mr. Comey had been willing to put his name on a newspaper article; now he was refusing to sign on to an official assessment of the intelligence community.***

Mr. Comey said that in the intervening time, Russian meddling had become the subject of news stories and a topic of national discussion. He felt it was no longer necessary for him to speak publicly about it. **So when Jeh Johnson, the Homeland Security secretary, and James R. Clapper Jr., the national intelligence director, accused Russias senior-most officials on Oct. 7 of a cyber operation to disrupt the election, the F.B.I. was conspicuously silent.**

***That night, WikiLeaks began posting thousands of hacked emails from another source: the private email account of John Podesta, chairman of the Clinton campaign.***


This is incoherence at best, and pure hypocrisy or an improper ulterior motive, at worst. Comey could just have said, "actually, we agree with this assesment," because he did agree. Yet, he stood by and did nothing while Trump used the FBI's non endorsement to cast doubt on the statement. This is the precise reason its why Comeys refusal to defer to others is so dangerous. Were at the mercy of his whims, and that undermines the rule of law.    </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-03 20:07:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Just mildly? 

What he should be experiencing is severe nausea and profound remorse. 

He changed the outcome of presidential and downballot elections fought over the course of two years, and affected the course of our country's historyand by extension the world's.

That was not his role as an investigator. His ongoing failure to own up to his misconduct is disturbing. Hopefully, the DoJ Inspector General will get to the bottom of it.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-03 20:00:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Calling it the "Chaffetz letter" absolves Comey of responsibility for his mishandling of the Clinton email investigation, starting with the improper editorializing on July 5 that got him dragged before Congress and ultimately convinced him that the letter was necessary. 

Contrary to his current claims, Comey was *not* forced to write the letter and would have been on solid ground updating Congress after the fact. And he himself foresaw that the letter would leak and expressly acknowleged the ["significant risk of being misunderstood"]( https://www.washingtonpost.com/news/post-nation/wp/2016/10/28/read-the-letter-comey-sent-to-fbi-employees-explaining-his-controversial-decision-on-the-clinton-email-investigation/?utm_term=.9fdecdb695cc tid=a_inl).

Comey cared more about his *reputation* for impartiality than actually doing the right thing (regardless of the criticism he'd take for it).   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-03 19:06:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Comey is not a "messenger." He's not even a prosecutor. He's an *investigator.* Investigators aren't supposed to editorialize about investigations they're conducting*especially* when they admit those investigations haven't turned up enough evidence to warrant a criminal referral for an indictment by an actual prosecutor. 

The fact that Comey can even be perceived as a messenger is *itself* an indication of how badly he mishandled this investigation. 
        </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-03 19:01:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Well-reasoned and empirically-supported analysis. Get this to the front. 

Unless we understand all the principal factors in Trump's electoral victory, we can over-diagnose the problem and implement faulty remedies while leaving other problems ([like Comey's misconduct in violating investigative protocol](https://www.reddit.com/r/politics/comments/69032x/z/dh2pzto), or the media's speculation- and innuendo-driven coverage of the letters) completely unaddressed.

Clinton deserves her share of blame. But there's also a lot that was done right and was sabotaged at the last minute.    </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-03 17:11:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> There may be some federal constitutional or statutory basis for bringing a suit, which could potentially be used to get around this. 

Would have to look into it.

In any event, it's outrageous that the water co could get liens to enforce payment for a contract that they clearly breached while relying on state sovereign immunity to escape liability themselves.

At minimum, the Court should deny enforcement of the water bill debts using something like unclean hands. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-03 16:16:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What we already know doesn't justify Comey's actions. Quite the opposite. The [deep-dive NYT piece on Comey from April 22](https://www.nytimes.com/2017/04/22/us/politics/james-comey-election.html?_r=0 referer=https://t.co/gU4pdevSXc) lays out the key problem:

Mr. Come[y] ... handled [the two investigations] in starkly different ways. **In the case of Mrs. Clinton, he rewrote the script, partly based on the F.B.I.s expectation that she would win and fearing the bureau would be accused of helping her. In the case of Mr. Trump, he conducted the investigation by the book, with the F.B.I.s traditional secrecy.**

Essentially, Comey erred by editorializing at the July 5 press conference and only exacerbated this error with other decisions he made. Comey actually would have been doing the the right thing by not disclosing the FBIs counterintelligence and criminal investigations of Trump*provided he had afforded Clinton the same by-the-book treatment*. Having made extraordinary disclosures about the Clinton investigation, which he shouldnt have done to begin with, Comey now arguably had an obligation to make further disclosures about Trump in order to ensure that what he had said about Clinton would not be misleading. Instead, Comey allowed Trump to perpetuate a narrative that Comey knew was false and was enabled by Comey's selective disclosures.

I don't think Comey is a garden variety partisan hack who pulls for one team or the other. Rather, he looks out for himself and what he perceives the FBI's interests to be. Over time, he has carefully cultivated a reputation for being impartial and he guards that reputation zealously*too zealously*, to the extent he forgets that his reputation isnt an end in itself. I think his press conference was an attempt to show his work and try to establish that he had reached his decision not to refer Clinton for prosecution based on the merits of the evidence he considered, without outside political pressure.

This strategy backfired spectacularly. 

Not only was Comeys decision criticized anyway, but he provided powerful ammunition to Clintons opponents when he criticized her for what he characterized as extreme carelessness. Rather than reassuring Republicans that he was not carrying water for the administration and Clinton, the fact that he was so willing to commentwhen investigators *almost never* do in these situationscreated the appearance that there *had indeed* been interference, either because people independently reached different conclusions than Comey (which doesn't mean that Comey's decision not to recommend prosecution was unreasonable), or because they inferred that Comey might be signaling that Clinton *had* committed crimes but his hands were somehow tied. 

Compounding matters, people who arent legally-trained often dont understand that a criminal offense consists of [**both**]( https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Concurrence) an *actus reus* (a voluntary wrongful action) **and** a requisite degree of *mens rea* (culpable intent). Even criminal statutes that don't explicitly mention intent are construed to contain a *mens rea* requirement. [*See*, *e.g.*, *Morissette v. United States*]( https://scholar.google.com/scholar_case?case=787130527265701764 q=342+U.S.+246,+251 hl=en as_sdt=2006), 342 U.S. 246 (1952) (Crime, as a compound concept, generally constituted only from concurrence of an evil-meaning mind with an evil-doing hand  As the states codified the common law of crimes, even if their enactments were silent on the subject, their courts assumed that the omission did not signify disapproval of the principle but merely recognized that intent was so inherent in the idea of the offense that it required no statutory affirmation.)

This is an essential protection of substantive criminal law, and is encapsulated by the Latin maxim:

*Actus reus non facit reum nisi mens sit rea*

Which translates to:

 An act does not make a person guilty, unless the mind is guilty.

What many people understood from Comey's extraordinary press conference was that Clinton had committed a crime but got off on some technicalitywhen in fact the absence of *mens rea* completely negates the crime. Put differently, Clinton didn't *unintentionally* "commit a crime"which requires a criminal conviction upon proof, to a jury, beyond a reasonable doubt, of all the elements of the offense, *including* culpable intent. 

People yelling "lock her up!" or calling for Clinton to be disqualified from the election based on her purported criminality were basically calling for punishment without a criminal indictmentlet alone a trial. 

The Trump campaign did everything to encourage this misunderstanding of criminal law and procedure. And the strategy was highly effective politically. Recall that the aftermath of the Comey press conference was [the first time Clintons poll numbers sank sharply](https://projects.fivethirtyeight.com/2016-election-forecast/national-polls/#now), and that they didnt fully recover until *after* the Democratic National Convention. At one point, Trump took the only lead of the campaign in the 538 forecast, which is further indirect evidence of how much Comeys letters (and the media's sensationalist coverage of them) likely mattered.  

Just as importantly, the press conference presented all this derogatory information about Clinton outside the context of adversarial legal proceeding where it could be challenged and various defenses could be presented. 

Now, this is the sort of procedural issue that might concern a lawyer a lot more than a non-lawyer. But think about what you'd want to happen if you were in the shoes of the person being investigated. Would you want the FBI using its coercive investigatory powers to obtain evidence, ultimately finding that the evidence *wasn't* enough to warrant a criminal referral, yet still publicly criticizing your alleged actions that, *by the FBI director's own admission*, could not support a criminal indictment? 

This is basically what Comey did. **At his discretion.** And it was wrong.

**In his capacity as FBI director, Comey is not a prosecutor. Hes more like a senior federal police detectivean investigator**. Investigators almost always dont disclose derogatory information about the subjects of their investigationsthat is, unless and until theres a public indictment *by a prosecutor* who relies on the information. Comey had every right to give his most brutal assessment to the prosecutor with jurisdiction and ultimate discretion of whether to pursue charges against Clinton. But its not Comey's place to publicly scold *anyone* for admittedly non-criminal conduct. These rules and norms exist to ensure due process and curb the immense potential for [abuse](http://articles.chicagotribune.com/1991-09-08/entertainment/9103070622_1_hoover-legendary-fbi-director-secret-files) through extrajudicial disclosure of investigatory or surveillance information.  

Riley Robert's excellent profile of Comey, from September of last year, is worth reading in full because its turned out to be prescient of the pitfalls of Comeys obdurate[e] self-assur[ance]:

[The Case Against James Comey](http://www.politico.com/magazine/story/2016/09/james-comey-fbi-accountability-214234)

Having fueled a firestorm of innuendo with his extraordinary press conference, Comey was then hauled before Congress multiple times to give testimony, where he further discussed investigative information that would normally not be disclosed absent an indictment. And when the laptop emails came to light months afterward, he felt compelled to supplement his initial testimony (again, at his discretion, because it was not required and against DoJ guidelines, in any event). Comey shouldn't be excused for the later errors when they were brought about by his earlier self-righteous defiance of investigative protocol. 

All of this is made worse by double standard in how the Russian hacking and investigation into potential Trump campaign collusion were handled. 

Recall that Comey specifically refused to sign the FBI onto the Department of Homeland Security (DHS)/Office of the Director of National Intelligence (ODNI) [statement on October 7, 2016 that publicly attributed the attacks to Russia](https://www.dni.gov/index.php/newsroom/press-releases/215-press-releases-2016/1423-joint-dhs-odni-election-security-statement)even though he agreed that Russia was behind the hacks and [had wanted to write an Op-Ed to that effect](http://www.newsweek.com/fbi-director-james-comey-russian-tampering-election-576417)supposedly because the October 7 statement was being issued too close to the election. But recall that 3 weeks later, to the day, from the initial release of the October 7 statement on Russian interference (which didn't explicitly say the interference was to help Trump), on October 28, Comey sent the letter that sabotaged the Clinton Campaign. **Apparently 11 days wasn't too close to the election, but 31 days was.**  (Whatever Comey's motives, his decision to do this against others insistent advice embodies the "I know best" attitude that I  find absolutely infuriating.) 

The DHS/ODNI statement even [came up at the third debate on October 19](http://www.politifact.com/truth-o-meter/statements/2016/oct/19/hillary-clinton/hillary-clinton-blames-russia-putin-wikileaks-rele/) and Trump questioned it in front of millions of people. 

Despite now vowing to do [everything in his power "identify, investigate and then call out foreign efforts" to influence an election](http://hosted.ap.org/dynamic/stories/U/US_TRUMP_RUSSIA_COMEY?SITE=AP SECTION=HOME TEMPLATE=DEFAULT CTIME=2017-04-13-12-52-45), Comey couldn't even be bothered to say a quick "actually, the FBI agrees with the October 7 statement" to refute the disinformation and innuendo Trump was spreading by mischaracterizing the FBI's non-endorsement of the statement as an indication that it was unreliable.
           </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-03 15:09:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Are you a foreign despot who has just purged his opposition or authorized a deadly war against your nation's drug dealers? Normally, you would expect at least a mild rebuke from the leader of the free world. Depending on how egregious your violations, maybe even a tough speech from the Rose Garden or a U.S.-sponsored United Nations resolution.

Not anymore. In the Donald Trump era, it's springtime for the world's authoritarians. ...

...

It's clear that much of this is improvisational. After the first 100 days, all of us are getting used to a president who says and tweets whatever is on his mind, regardless of how it coheres with his administration's foreign policy. We saw this previously when it came to Russia's political influence operation last year. Trump this weekend told CBS News that hestill wasn't sureRussia was behind the hacking of leading Democrats (even though he had acknowledged as much before his inauguration).

... [A]ny argument that Trump really cares about human rights or democracy in foreign policy is undermined by his sweet words for Duterte, Erdogan, Sisi and China's leader, Xi Jinping.

Past presidents have also looked the other way at times for authoritarian allies. And often presidents who made support for human rights a rhetorical priority didn't back up those words when it came to policy.

The difference is that when former presidents cozied up to authoritarians, there was a strategic purpose. Obama needed Egypt to be stable while its neighbor Libya descended into civil war. Clinton wanted North Korea to agree to a deal to abandon its long-range missile program. Franklin D. Roosevelt needed Stalin to defeat Hitler. With Trump, it's unclear whether his obsequiousness to despots is part of a larger plan or just popping off. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Trump's Springtime for Despots </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-03 15:00:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-03 02:37:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Meanwhile, a racist elf is *not* being [tried for perjury](https://www.reddit.com/r/politics/comments/61vc6s/z/dfhlti7).  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-03 02:26:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> 
My point is that it's a mistake to dismiss Clinton's criticisms of Trumpparticularly as as direct participant with first-hand knowlege of the electionjust because of one's personal views of Clinton. But you're certainly free to make that mistake. So groan and eyeroll away.  For my part, I think it's worth evaluating her arguments on their merits.       </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-03 02:06:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> No. The conspiracy I was referring to was the long-running [something something evil George Soros something something](http://www.vocativ.com/412237/george-soros-right-boogeyman/).  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-03 00:12:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's not wrong not to trust him. The Turtle is a consummate hypocrite and liar. But keeping the filibuster [likely helps Republicans in the long run far more than Democrats](https://www.vox.com/policy-and-politics/2017/5/2/15515834/filibuster-kill-abolish-nuclear-option-trump-mcconnell). Hopefully, Democrats will oppose nuking it without going on the record with public statements that make it hard to abolish going forward. The filibuster makes Congress dysfunctional and our politics less accountable (it's easy for the electorate to blame the majority for the opposition's obstruction, as happened in the 2010 midterms). The only twinge of regret I have is at seeing the abolition happen under Trump--rather than a normal Republican or Democratic President. But if it takes Trump to finally be rid of this anachronism, then so be it.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-03 00:00:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I see two (and if I stretch, three) persons who I can plausibly interpret as people of color among the 31 people I count in the stands, and they're not necessarily black. Since they aren't even real people, there's no way to know their ancestry. It's totally subjective.

In any event, even the 5 people you counted as potentially black would be well under the percentage of non-whites in the U.S. electorate.






 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-02 22:24:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The indefensible fail was just too strong today. Come back tomorrow... Maybe. 

In the meantime, carry on discussing [outrageous tweet](https://twitter.com/jonkarl/status/859473987012894723).  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-02 22:02:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The [empty podium](https://twitter.com/jonkarl/status/859473987012894723) is an apt but unhelpful metaphor for the entire Trump Regime.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Reporters confounded as Sean Spicer flees White House briefing without taking questions </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-02 22:00:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-02 21:51:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Interestingly, look at how white he drew the stand of Trump supporters. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-02 21:41:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Love her or hate her, as a citizen, Clinton is totally within her rights to speak out against the Orange One. 

She got 2.86 million more votes than him despite her campaign being targeted by Russian interference (with potential coordination by the Trump campaign) and sabotaged at the last minute by James Comey's improper letter while people were already voting. 

If she were more personally popular, she'd be a natural leader who the resistance would look to. But regardless of Clinton's popularity, her criticisms of Trump during the campaign were spot on (including about Russia), she trounced him in all 3 debates, and so she should not be dismissed by anyone who genuinely opposes Trump. 

Whether you'd vote for Clinton again (or at all) is a totally separate question from whether she's worth listening to on the issue of why he's been disastrous for this country. And, in any event, she's said she's not running for anything in the future. 

Some might prefer Clinton to retreat from the national stage into obscurity. Strategically, that sentiment may not even be 100% wrongbut it's her call to make.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-02 20:59:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Lol. The nationalist right was [already saying Kushner is a globalist who's getting his father-in-law to betray the commitments that got him elected](http://grrrgraphics.com/uploads/7/4/7/3/74734153/tug-of-war-ben-garrison_1_orig.jpg). (Warning: the level of delusion here is staggering.)

With Kushner tied to *anything* related to Soros, their tinfoil hattery should now reach a fever pitch.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-02 19:45:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> All signed by Obama. 

You can cross reference the Wikipedia links below with Congress.gov to double check if you wish. 

Again, I'll concede the point with a single counter-example (which has yet to be provided). 

-----

**2013**:

-----

https://en.m.wikipedia.org/wiki/Continuing_Appropriations_Resolution,_2013

-----

[H.J.Res.117 - 112th Congress (2011-2012): Continuing Appropriations Resolution, 2013 | Congress.gov | Library of Congress](https://www.congress.gov/bill/112th-congress/house-joint-resolution/117)

-----


09/28/2012	Became Public Law No: 112-175. 

**09/28/2012	Signed by President.**

09/25/2012	Presented to President.

-----

https://en.m.wikipedia.org/wiki/Consolidated_and_Further_Continuing_Appropriations_Act,_2013

-----

[H.R.933 - 113th Congress (2013-2014): Consolidated and Further Continuing Appropriations Act, 2013 | Congress.gov | Library of Congress](https://www.congress.gov/bill/113th-congress/house-bill/933)

-------

03/26/2013	Became Public Law No: 113-6. (TXT | PDF)

**03/26/2013	Signed by President.**

03/22/2013	Presented to President.


-----

**2014**:

-----

https://en.m.wikipedia.org/wiki/Continuing_Appropriations_Act,_2014

-----

[H.J.Res.59 - 113th Congress (2013-2014): Continuing Appropriations Resolution, 2014 | Congress.gov | Library of Congress](https://www.congress.gov/bill/113th-congress/house-joint-resolution/59)

-----


12/26/2013	Became Public Law No: 113-67. 

**12/26/2013	Signed by President.**

12/19/2013	Presented to President.



-----

https://en.m.wikipedia.org/wiki/Making_further_continuing_appropriations_for_fiscal_year_2014

-----

[H.J.Res.106 - 113th Congress (2013-2014): Making further continuing appropriations for fiscal year 2014, and for other purposes. | Congress.gov | Library of Congress](https://www.congress.gov/bill/113th-congress/house-joint-resolution/106)

-----

01/15/2014	Became Public Law No: 113-73. 

**01/15/2014	Signed by President**

01/15/2014	Presented to President.

-----

**2015**:

-----

https://en.m.wikipedia.org/wiki/Continuing_Appropriations_Resolution,_2015


-----

[H.J.Res.124 - 113th Congress (2013-2014): Continuing Appropriations Resolution, 2015 | Congress.gov | Library of Congress](https://www.congress.gov/bill/113th-congress/house-joint-resolution/124)

-----

09/19/2014	Became Public Law No: 113-164. 

**09/19/2014	Signed by President.**

09/19/2014	Presented to President.


-----

**2016**:

-----

https://en.m.wikipedia.org/wiki/Consolidated_Appropriations_Act,_2016

-----

[H.R.2029 - 114th Congress (2015-2016): Consolidated Appropriations Act, 2016 | Congress.gov | Library of Congress](https://www.congress.gov/bill/114th-congress/house-bill/2029/)

-----

12/18/2015	Became Public Law No: 114-113. 

**12/18/2015	Signed by President**

12/18/2015	Presented to President.

-----


*See* [Article I, Section 7 of the Constitution](https://www.law.cornell.edu/constitution/articlei):


All bills for raising revenue shall originate in the House of Representatives; but the Senate may propose or concur with amendments as on other Bills.

Every bill which shall have passed the House of Representatives and the Senate, shall, **before it become a law, be presented to the President of the United States**; if he approve he shall sign it, but if not he shall return it, with his objections to that House in which it shall have originated, who shall enter the objections at large on their journal, and proceed to reconsider it. If after such reconsideration two thirds of that House shall agree to pass the bill, it shall be sent, together with the objections, to the other House, by which it shall likewise be reconsidered, and if approved by two thirds of that House, it shall become a law. But in all such cases the votes of both Houses shall be determined by yeas and nays, and the names of the persons voting for and against the bill shall be entered on the journal of each House respectively. If any bill shall not be returned by the President within ten days (Sundays excepted) after it shall have been presented to him, the same shall be a law, in like manner as if he had signed it, unless the Congress by their adjournment prevent its return, in which case it shall not be a law.

**Every order, resolution, or vote to which the concurrence of the Senate and House of Representatives may be necessary (except on a question of adjournment) shall be presented to the President of the United States; and before the same shall take effect, shall be approved by him, or being disapproved by him, shall be repassed by two thirds of the Senate and House of Representatives, according to the rules and limitations prescribed in the case of a bill.**

*And see* [*INS v. Chadha*](https://scholar.google.com/scholar_case?case=2221871582286121199 q=ins+v.+chadha hl=en as_sdt=2006), 462 US 919 (1983):

The records of the Constitutional Convention reveal that the requirement that all legislation be presented to the President before becoming law was uniformly accepted by the Framers. Presentment to the President and the Presidential veto were considered so imperative that the draftsmen took special pains to assure that these requirements could not be circumvented. During the final debate on Art. I,  7, cl. 2, James Madison expressed concern that it might easily be evaded by the simple expedient of calling a proposed law a "resolution" or "vote" rather than a "bill." 2 Farrand 301-302. As a consequence, Art. I,  7, cl. 3 ... was added. 2 Farrand 304-305.

...

 We see therefore that the Framers were acutely conscious that the bicameral requirement and the Presentment Clauses would serve essential constitutional functions. The President's participation in the legislative process was to protect the Executive Branch from Congress and to protect the whole people from improvident laws. The division of the Congress into two distinctive bodies assures that the legislative power would be exercised only after opportunity for full study and debate in separate settings. The President's unilateral veto power, in turn, was limited by the power of two-thirds of both Houses of Congress to overrule a veto thereby precluding final arbitrary action of one person. ... **It emerges clearly that the prescription for legislative action in Art. I,  1, 7, represents the Framers' decision that the legislative power of the Federal Government be exercised in accord with a single, finely wrought and exhaustively considered, procedure**.

...

**Whether actions taken by either House are, in law and fact, an exercise of legislative power depends not on their form but upon "whether they contain matter which is properly to be regarded as legislative in its character and effect."**  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-02 17:41:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You can't amend a statute, retroactively or otherwise, without Presidential approval. If Congress appropriates money, the President has to sign off. Give me one concrete counterexample of a continuing appropriations resolution enacted into law *without a Presidential signature or veto override* and I'll gladly concede the point.    </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-02 17:28:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah, exactly. And it'd be happening even closer to 2018, after Trump's popularity has had more time to fall, when it's obvious that he is the one being unreasonable and the cuts themselves are spectacularly unpopular. 

"Vote for us and we'll shut down our own administration" isn't much of a sales pitch. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-02 16:58:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yes they do. Anything that requires both Houses of Congress to act and will have binding legal effect once enacted requires presentnent to the President. If he vetoes, then you can do it without him. But the threshold increases to 2/3rds. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-02 16:43:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The Democrats' ability to filibuster exerted some influence on the deal. But I think the reality is even more basic than that. Republicans needed Democratic votes to even get a bill out of the House. They can't seem to hold their caucus together for anything other than killing internet privacy and repealing environmental rules.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-02 16:34:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Well, the Orange One was already going to be blamed for any potential shutdown when Republicans have unified control of Congress and the Presidency. Vetoing this funding bill after Dems reached a deal would make it even harder than already was to somehow pin blame on them. The only reason Dems even have a seat at the table is that Republicans can't hold their caucus together for basic governing functions like funding the government. 

Edit: and Trump already signed this funding bill in any event, so this is just posturing to keep him from looking as weak and innefectual as he actually is.
         </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-01 09:37:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> President Trump is the most fact-challenged politician that The Fact Checker has ever encountered. He earned 59 Four-Pinocchio ratings during his campaign as president. Since then, hes earned 16 more Four-Pinocchio ratings.

But those numbers obscure the fact that the pace and volume of the presidents misstatements means that we cannot possibly keep up. The presidents speeches and interviews are so chock full of false and misleading claims that The Fact Checker often must resort to roundups that offer a brief summary of the facts that the president has gotten wrong.

....

So here are the numbers for the presidents first 100days.

488: The number of false or misleading claims made by the president. Thats an average of 4.9 claims a day.

10: Number of days without a single false claim. (On six of those days, the president golfed at a Trump property.)

4: Number of days with 20 or more false claims.(Feb. 16, Feb. 28, March 20 and April 21.) He made 19 false claims on April 29, his 100th day, though we did not include his interview with Face the Nation, since that aired April 30.

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> President Trumps first 100 days: The fact check tally </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-01 09:35:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Dems inch closer to House takeover with Miami Republican's retirement </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-01 01:35:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-01 00:25:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Re-read it carefully. Article I, Section 7 doesn't just deal with vetoes, but rather, defines the process for passing legislation generally:

Simple majority to pass a bill into law with a President's signature, or 2/3ds (67 votes) to override a veto with a mandatory roll call. 

Nowhere is there a 3/5ths requirement (60 votes) for the Senate to end debate on a bill. That comes from Senate Rule XXII.     </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-01 00:11:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Even under the First Amendment, Trumpand any other public figurecan *already* sue a newspaper for libel if the newspaper prints a false story about him with actual malice (*i.e.*, if the falsity of the story is known to the newspaper, of if the newspaper shows reckless disregard for the truth or falsity of the story).

If Trump wants to make it easier than this to sue, he'll have to either abrogate the First Amendment or get SCOTUS to overturn its bedrock 1st Amendment precedents creating the public figure doctrine (like *New York Times v. Sullivan*).  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-30 23:29:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Compare what you're saying:

It's a consequence of the requirement of the Senate needing 60 votes to pass something, **defined in the US Constitution**. 



With what I said:

The filibuster *isn't* a constitutional rule, but rather the consequence of **a rule and tradition created by the Senate**

-----

Here's what the [Constitution has to say on the subject](https://www.law.cornell.edu/constitution/articlei):

Article I, Section 7

All bills for raising revenue shall originate in the House of Representatives; but the Senate may propose or concur with amendments as on other Bills.

Every bill which **shall have passed** the House of Representatives and the Senate, shall, before it become a law, be presented to the President of the United States; if he approve he shall sign it, but if not he shall return it, with his objections to that House in which it shall have originated, who shall enter the objections at large on their journal, and proceed to reconsider it. **If after such reconsideration two thirds of that House shall agree to pass the bill**, it shall be sent, together with the objections, to the **other House, by which it shall likewise be reconsidered, and if approved by two thirds of that House, it shall become a law.** But in all such cases the votes of both Houses shall be determined by yeas and nays, and the names of the persons voting for and against the bill shall be entered on the journal of each House respectively. If any bill shall not be returned by the President within ten days (Sundays excepted) after it shall have been presented to him, the same shall be a law, in like manner as if he had signed it, unless the Congress by their adjournment prevent its return, in which case it shall not be a law.

Every order, resolution, or vote to which the concurrence of the Senate and House of Representatives may be necessary (except on a question of adjournment) shall be presented to the President of the United States; and before the same shall take effect, shall be approved by him, or being disapproved by him, shall be repassed by two thirds of the Senate and House of Representatives, according to the rules and limitations prescribed in the case of a bill.

Article I, Section 5

Each House shall be the judge of the elections, returns and qualifications of its own members, and a majority of each shall constitute a quorum to do business; but a smaller number may adjourn from day to day, and may be authorized to compel the attendance of absent members, in such manner, and under such penalties as each House may provide.

**Each House may determine the rules of its proceedings**, punish its members for disorderly behavior, and, with the concurrence of two thirds, expel a member.

Here's [Senate Rule XXII (provides the procedure for ending debate)](https://www.rules.senate.gov/public/index.cfm?p=RuleXXII).











 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
