<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject1166</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Surveillance footage captures last days of boy fed to pigs. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-10 07:04:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-10 04:49:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Im 18, i am new to swimming though.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-09 04:06:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This inspires me to draw, could ya draw my fav, Clefable? :D </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-07 20:37:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I know i was trying to beat some chick in my heat that was on my team, maybe the goal of having something to beat made me PR I feel like it was the wrong time though as if someone messed up, maybe it's just me being low in my confidence in myself.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Hit a good PR, can't quite reach close to it again. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-07 18:15:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So I hit a PR of 10 seconds in 100 Breast and im not sure how because now I cant even come close, I got a 1:32.50 ONCE and now im back at 1:42.34 finishes... Does this happen to anyone else?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-07 18:12:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You got out of your emo scene kid and now approaching the pop punk pizza kid.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-07 17:35:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I wouldn't doubt it because in middle school i got tagged on Facebook of a weed leaf and i got searched at school. Fun times. Then they had to call my mom and my mom works as a police dispatcher and all the calls are monitored, even more fun of times.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-07 05:24:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I do as well but far too lazy to redo it. Lol </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-07 05:24:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I heard from my high school counselor that adding a picture of yourself on a resume helps out. What's your opinion on that?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-07 05:04:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You look like you try too hard to be edgy  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
