<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject7495</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Penn State frat pledge's skin had turned gray by morning after fall, prosecutor says </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-10 09:04:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-10 03:40:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Because cheating came up. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-09 22:14:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Employees not reporting. College town. They don't want that money train to stop.

Killing animals-even a high school kid would get charged and committed for that. Just because it involves or is associated with college does not make it right.
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-09 20:36:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> In the US anyway one literally has to politic or lobby for most government jobs especially administrative ones. Meaning the job applicant is already behaving like professional politician seeking government work and/or making deals. Along with the people they are associating or making deals with.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-09 18:38:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> In life in general people including professors or management at a job want consistency. And look for achievers. They also want and frequently reward high numbers in regards to productivity. That being said the second cheating or anything with a scandalous connotation comes up you are done.

Was this a form letter?

 Also in the day an age of tech anything you say even in e-mail is part of the permanent record. A record that could be supoenaed by a lawyer one day.

I'd speak to the professor in person first. And ignore and see if there is a follow up email.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> At Penn State, critics claim, there's no handle on hazing </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-09 18:27:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-09 18:18:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Two hazing incidents prior to this in 2009 and 2013. 170 instances of chapter misconduct since 2015. Penn State said it has a vigorous anti hazing policy and private security is used to help monitor fraternity activities.

Throw in the Sandusky scandal and rioting students as late as last fall after a football game Penn State seems to be looking the other way on bad pr issues. There's obviously an alcohol problem yeh yeh I know college students drink but how many riot after football game. And one must wonder many un or under reported incidents there have been over the years.

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-09 17:54:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That's nice but homelessness isn't just about shelter. The next step is a job and/or self reliance. The motivation to get a place on their own. Some need help and should have help especially with kids. But without the next step this donation will be spent and the conditions and issues will still be there. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> At Penn State, critics claim, there's no handle on hazing </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-09 17:30:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-09 17:25:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The drug war, confiscations, imprisonment etc is bad enough but the supply and distribution was such that it enabled so much use that it help decriminalize what should be frowned up behavior. It enabled the drug culture period. What should be a behavioral exception is now the norm. It helped "normalize" drug abuse.

 I get the rights issues with various substances but the desire to get high fueled by the party culture of the 1980s and cocaine smuggling is the most troubling literally and figuratively. 

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-09 17:13:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Theoretically that sounds ok but if one controls the supply of ballots they can control the outcome.

Are there generic or write in ballots in case they run out? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-09 17:00:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yes the figure heads, the CEOs, the President have issues. But it's the people that they delegate to or put in charge that tend to be more dangerous and actually push   implement their biased agenda. Along with being unscrupulous  sociopathic pieces of crap. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-09 16:53:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Big bankster Macron was already a professional politician. Who the establishment "wanted" is no surprise. 

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-09 16:49:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> How come all the candidates are not on one ballot and the voter checks a box. Just for privacy sake it should be indistinguishable who a voter is voting for. By having to request or get a ballot from a particular candidate that shows how a person voted. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-09 16:46:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> How come ballots are not guarded, monitored or distributed by election staff. There should be someone sitting at that table.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-09 16:44:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What's the election over sight in France-EU? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-09 09:21:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Insurance is a method a payment. Actually an optional form of payment that happens to be preferred by providers and patients alike. Both want the public believe that is the only way to go. Insurance is third party money. Third party money perpetuates inflation due to somebody else is paying for syndrome.

These insurance bills ACA and/or Trump Care just find ways to get money to the care industry. In the meantime the actual cost of care issues are rarely touched.

 Efficiency, waste, greed and ways health CARE is delivered are what needs to be discussed. Not method of payment. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-09 09:15:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Universal, single payer etc are just ways to pay the health care industry. It's third party money for the providers. If somebody else is paying for it there tends to be less incentive to control costs or change what one is doing for more business   profit.

Nailed it on ER type care. Anything else is cya price gouging care. I know people with good insurance all pilled and procedured up being the compliant patient and their health is worse than people who see a doctor a fraction of the time they do.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-09 09:08:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Obamacare is/was an insurance bill. Both the ACA and Trump Care are insurance bills designed to throw third party money at the health care industry will perpetuates inflation because somebody else is pay for it.

The real programming or myth is that insurance is they only way to pay for health care and little has to be done to reduce the actual cost of care.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-09 09:01:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The real estate, legal and union lobby seems to love her.

https://www.opensecrets.org/politicians/summary.php?cycle=Career type=I cid=N00006690 newMem=N

A question would be legislation has she impeded if she is not passing bills.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-09 07:28:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What can one say. Maybe it is time to quit pretending. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> EXCLUSIVE: State Rep. claims DSP trooper's killer was a "budding jihadist" Muslim </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-08 21:59:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-08 21:47:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Because those who became used to subsidized INSURANCE would go into withdrawal.

 Also until people learn to differentiate between insurance and actual care this will be an issue. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-08 21:36:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> In 1999 they instituted a system of free health care. They considered health care a right.

 What's government subsidized free health care called then or just consider it single payer, universal or free-all three require subsidization. 

https://venezuelanalysis.com/analysis/4566 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> More details emerge in horrific Penn State fraternity death </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-08 17:49:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Penn State frat brothers knew dying pledge needed serious help </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-08 17:45:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-08 17:41:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> A lot of non fraternities can   do raise money. Many colleges have a community service requirement that all of their students do charity work before they graduate.

One of the issues with fraternities in general is that it can send the wrong message that one has to be in with a certain clique to succeed career wise or socially. That's probably why many pledges go through these rituals. They want in.

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-08 09:13:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I thought they called them shelters. Although they still are in a prison of sorts
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-08 08:42:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Someone just posted today about fake facebook accounts and likes. Social media is prone to bot posting/commentary. Doesn't have to pithy just enough to reinforce a narrative. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-08 08:39:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Doesn't he have a banking background-lots of numbers in play there. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-08 08:34:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That's what will happen with single payer basically turning doctors into government workers because they all will be paid the same. Single will payer will cover the same as well so if a patient want's some extra or less that might cause some billing consternation.

I want to see the abuses in over billing or gouging insurance companies/the premium and tax payers BUT I'm also for a business/practice pricing what the market will bare ie fee based pricing, not just the standard medicare/medicaid reimbursement.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-08 01:10:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Laws and/or policy apparently don't mean much to Penn State. They already got sued for a hazing incident in 2012.

http://www.cnn.com/2015/06/08/us/penn-state-fraternity-hazing-lawsuit/index.html </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-08 01:04:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The case needs to remain high profile as example of hazing and ignorance. The case should be part of student orientation. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-08 01:02:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This week Joe Paterno's son gets elected to the Penn State Board of Trustees. He's been crying how his father was framed and scapegoated by the Penn State itself. If they ignored child abuse I must wonder how many hazing or alcohol related incidents at Penn State they ignored or covered up.

Don't forget the riots/victory celebration last fall or riots after Paterno was dismissed. The campus culture is obviously has an alcohol problem. 
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-07 21:58:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Not all are happy.

http://thebiglead.com/2017/05/05/penn-state-clearly-doesnt-care-about-appearances-as-jay-paterno-is-elected-to-board-of-trustees/

I'd figure both the son and college would want to quietly get away from the Paterno years. 

This vote or appointment comes as news of a new scandal and tragedy at Penn State. The negligent hazing death of a fraternity pledge at Penn State where 18 students and fraternity members charged.

What really has changed at Penn State since the Sandusky scandal and Paterno years.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-07 20:45:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> One would figure the son would want to quietly distance himself from his father's legacy as would Penn State.

 Instead the son has publicly defended his dad/ Joe  Paterno crying cover up and frame job. And many Penn Staters are still whiny about the sanctions being too harsh when many thought they were too lenient.

In a disgusting yet fitting twist Paterno gets his board seat the same week 18 were charged in the hazing death of a student on Penn State campus. Things have not changed at this school, the only reason this incident made a prosecutors office   news is that there was a fatality. But out of control fraternities, hazing, alcohol abuse etc apparently fell into the sights of the look the other way mindset   crowd at Penn State.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-07 18:20:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Pathetically ironic that this 'elected' to the board comes out the same week Penn State is hit with another criminal scandal-18 charged in hazing death.

Is he there to cover up or live off the family name.

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Penn State Clearly Doesnt Care About Appearances As Jay Paterno is Elected To Board Of Trustees </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-07 18:09:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-07 17:26:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> One would figure after other hazing incidents around the country alone Penn State would've banned hazing period or toughened up it's rules against. Or after the Sandusky scandal Penn State would've gone out of there way to be on their best behavior at all times but it didn't. 

Nor can I believe with a lot of drug and alcohol information out there now a days that these pos college kids didn't call 911 but that's exactly why they were charged. Those boys will finally grow up. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-07 17:17:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Drama queen crying the sky is falling .

Actually the financial hardships and stress caused by trying to pay exorbitant premiums for someone else's care might do exactly that. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-07 17:13:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I guess the right to health care also includes the right to put the tax and/or premium payer into financial hardship paying excessively high prices to pay for somebody else's poop then.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-07 17:05:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I thought it was the other way around. 

One of the news shows basically described her father as a lunatic, a rage machine of sorts. Showed pictures, lots of pictures of raised fists. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-07 17:02:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Controlling information damages democracy, not disclosing it. All goes back to who and why the information is being controlled.

And as with the US msm where was the investigative reporting of Macron. They seemed to have no problem getting or leaking stories like EU ivestigations of LePen but yet Macron who was already in politics and with "a history" did little.

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-07 16:55:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If they can find a way to pay for it go ahead. Romney Care already failed in Mass with mandates, taxes and regulation modifications allowing things like pas to do what the drs did. 

Unless California addresses cost of care issues, not just who is going to pay for it single payer will be nothing but a failed attempt to throw money at a problem.

California stands a better a chance of becoming a single state/country before getting single payer to work. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-07 16:49:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> 'Temporary' measures that were already extended in several countries. Because they know shortly after the mass migrations will start up again. 

https://euobserver.com/justice/135647

Hungary is building a second fence because the first one worked.

http://www.latimes.com/world/la-fg-hungary-fence-20170227-story.html

Rather than tell countries just let the mass migrations flow into their country the EU needs to work harder on controlling the flow of immigrants/refugees going so far as to help the refugees in their own country.

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-07 04:29:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah but the timing. Obama probably grabbed much of the remaining major news headlines about the election days prior to the blackout. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-07 02:34:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What is En Marche! then? Founded by Emmanuel Macron in 2016.

 Maybe you got confused since he is not a member of a major political party.

https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/En_Marche! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-06 23:56:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> One would hope France has impeachment or even nullification procedures but best guess the opposition will wind up attempting to delegitimize him for a while if not his entire term.

Does France have one final rubber stamp for their elections like the electoral college vote? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-06 23:44:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The EU just moved to keep their time table up to speed mandating member nations remove their border controls in 6 months, the same ones they used and that actually worked to control and reduce the flow of mass unvetted immigration.

http://www.express.co.uk/news/politics/799292/European-Union-EU-orders-member-states-drop-migrant-crisis-border-checks  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-06 23:40:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Centuries late but better late than never. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-06 23:38:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Humans rights concerns and the concern or fact the Saudi government enabled or participated in 9/11. This is one of those countries if something is needed there it should just be taken. If we need an airport, strip or any land for any purpose it should be ours. If not face full fledged invasion along with regime and culture change-take it or leave it.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-06 23:35:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  EU members just given a 6 month notice to get rid of border controls.

http://www.express.co.uk/news/politics/799292/European-Union-EU-orders-member-states-drop-migrant-crisis-border-checks

Macron is the favorite-to keep 'the plan' on track. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-06 23:14:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The election law has been there. 

The state of emergency wasn't declared until after the Charlie Hebdo attacks. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-06 23:03:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Some single payer v police funding differences

For the most part police, not federal law enforcement is funded at the local level and their costs for the most part are clearly spelled out in budgets and proposals. Police Departments are free to pay their officers as they please and local governments tax for them as needed. Some towns give one a bill straight up for emergency services, it's cost is not hidden in one big tax number. Also local policing frequently share duties along with backing each other up at the county or neighboring town level. Single payer would need a federal tax increase along among other things including reallocating and locating resources.

With policing, the officer gets paid hourly for the most part, maybe some overtime or comp time along the way. The police get paid the same wether they rescue a cat or have a shoot out or chase a suspect. Doctors, health care providers want or are paid by the procedure which would be like the police charging extra for a robbery vs a noise complaint. 

Also to make single payer government enforced health care work not only would require new taxes but it would wind up allocating resources meaning one's now convenient hospital might move it's services 10 miles away. In our county the regional hospitals are already designated during off hours ie a burn patient goes here, a broken leg goes there etc. meaning one could pass a hospital on their way to the ER. Also more importantly  doctors and/or health care workers become defacto government employees meaning many will become hourly or salaried employees rather than billing by the job. Also means more clinic style medicine which might not be as bad but people want the convenience of an appointment. Wait times will go up to see the doc and get a non emergent procedure done. 

Also in many countries with single payer their population numbers, demographics, politics, culture, economics, other systems/services are different. It's not  just a matter of unplugging US health care and plugging in single payer. It would NOT be plug in and play. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-06 22:42:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Partly because of the "not me" or "I'm not doing anything wrong so what do I have to worry about" mindset.

http://www.economist.com/news/europe/21695368-france-realising-its-state-emergency-may-last-long-time </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-06 22:28:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Book tour and tv appearances. Sounds like he is desperately trying to become the new(not young) face of the Republican Party or the other "professional establishment politician.

Blah blah blah, Sounds too whiny and fake for my taste </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-06 22:23:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> More a precisely a news blackout a the day prior to and of the election. 

France has been under a state of emergency since the Paris attacks as well. I think that gives them a lot of free reign to do what ever as well. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-06 21:14:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Any info on the memo on who it was sent to and for what purpose?

Should add that this comes out as it is alleged a newspaper was bribed to cover up asylum seeker crime by the police in the Netherlands.

https://wentworthreport.com/2017/05/05/dutch-police-bribe-newspaper-to-bury-data-on-criminal-asylum-seekers/

Seems many government types in Europe consider censorship just another tool in the box. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-06 21:11:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Maybe more of a byproduct. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-06 20:28:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The show with most disgusting thing being tax payers frequently wind up funding their stages. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-06 20:11:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If true this might workout better for LePen if she loses because she too can do the delegitimize the winner thing.

If false this could be LePen's one and only chance, no redos if it came from her camp. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-06 20:08:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Except Macron's emails should've been leaked before the preliminary elimination election. The DNC leaks started to flow before their convention with the rigged/DWS issues. 

Timing is odd but 'timely' enough so either side can exploit it causing confusion, doubt, rage-what ever they want.

When was the actual hack date, not content of this material?-is this a job for the French election commission officials? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-06 18:18:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Blackout or censorship anywhere is a dicey proposition but in France it's the law.

 At what point is 'a' news story deemed election related and not allowed? Who makes that decision? 

That being said the opposition will use it after the election to delegitimize Macron and Party. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-06 17:20:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Cost issues keep getting lost in these insurance bills. The source of the problem needs to be treated and Rand Paul knows that being a doctor. The real issue is 'somebody else is paying for it syndrome'

Both the insurance and health care industries have made a living billing a third party for money. 

Insurance and/or bills throw money at the problem. Costly health care, drugs, medical supplies, facilities etc.
COSTS are the real problem, not who is going to pay for it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-06 17:14:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I've read reports from 24 hours to 2 days a blackout of stories that 'could' sway the election are banned as well. 

If the email story pans out then what. A recall election, impeachment in France or straight up civil or criminal charges. In the meantime the opposition will write him off as a cheat or criminal

That being said the Obama endorsement of Macron this last week was no coincidence. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-06 17:08:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Their drug dealer abandoned them. They finally sobered up. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-06 08:31:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The lobbies. 

Was there a provision to allow drug imports? Notice how these bills just look for ways to pay insurance premiums but don't try to reduce the actual cost of care.  
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-06 08:23:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I think there are some anarchist hackers/hacks among those with specific targets. Look at the attention these 'hacks' get.

Disinformation, spun stories and narratives were around long before the internet. Are these "projects" routine old fashioned activities with different tools or is this a truely different tact. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-06 08:01:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> In the article the proof maybe the blurry web page the top, it is a blurred out spreadsheet. France does impose a blackout on campaign news 24 hours prior to vote that may sway the election.

http://www.newstimes.com/news/crime/article/French-campaign-watchdog-examines-election-eve-11125984.php

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> French Government Shuts Down 4Chan links of Macron Illegal Agitation at Le Pen rallies, Tax Evasion #MacronLeaks - Geller Report </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-06 06:58:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> French Government Shuts Down 4Chan links of Macron Illegal Agitation at Le Pen rallies, Tax Evasion #MacronLeaks - Geller Report </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-06 06:56:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-06 02:41:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Different culture, politics and economy. Per capita comparisons  doesn't always translate like for lik because of the different variables. 

The larger population will stress service budgets more. Resources are finite but with more people using them their costs will increase.

 Australia is much closer to socialism than the US. Australia probably taxes more along with a more centralized government. That's exactly want very few want or will accept in the US.

There are different spending needs in the US. The US has more and older infrastructure that needs to be maintained. The US spends more on military good or bad but that allows many others countries to not spend on their military. 

In the US independence, not dependence is emphasized.

   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-06 02:20:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Socialism. Look at Venezuela today. Inflation and food shortages started up as there supreme leader died. 

Socialism. Look at how fast the old Soviet Union broke up

The problem now is with a larger immigrant population legal or not and the instant gratification culture socialism will get a much closer look than it did several years.

The key is get the younger workers into the work force as soon as possible so they have motivation to see what their job allows them to afford on their own without bureaucracy. 

Independence, not just physical freedom but free of government and dependence on a program needs to be emphasized. 

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-05 21:01:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Should note this is nothing new to Soros funneling money to local prosecutor campaigns of late.

http://dailysignal.com/2016/12/19/the-staggering-campaign-of-liberal-billionaire-george-soros-to-swing-local-prosecutor-elections/

Why local elections, DAs/prosecutors in particular. For starters they would be the ones charging and prosecuting protestors(many employees) and associated violence   mayhem. Along with giving him favors should he need one in a particular locality. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-05 19:47:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> No wonder Philadelphia being one of the sanctuary cities. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Soros dumps $1.4 million into Philly DA primary </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-05 19:46:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-05 19:24:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Silly, he's not 'the' president even though he still holds the title and influence and power etc

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-05 19:20:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> One of the radio guys got into a dispute about doctor supply. 

 There have been stories for years that the AMA, a large   powerful lobby worked to control the supply of doctors for decades. Many doctors say no, maybe today but decades of this practice could've help bring the cost issues we see today.

Insurance companies/lobbies are help shorting the supply the insurers with no cross state insurance selling.

Funding medical education and residency could help along with reducing some doctor debt which many use to justify their pricing. I don't want a hospital or school to exploit that though-tuition inflation is about as bad as anything out there. Third party money perpetuates inflation. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-05 19:12:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This is what happens when an insurance bill is touted for care let alone considered "affordable" </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-05 19:08:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> How much surveillance do these governments really need. To top it off they put them a person of interest or no fly list they still wind up committing attacks. And this stuff will come or not go away in the US either. 

Setting aside the amount or kind of intelligence unless it's properly analyzed and then acted on all that spying isn't worth a darn. And is open to being stolen or exploited later.

 People are sacrificing their privacy for what again? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-05 18:58:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> And yet couldn't take the time to travel to Paris or send his Secretary of State for a global memorial service after the Charlie Hebdo attacks.

http://nation.foxnews.com/2015/01/12/shameful-obama-and-america-mia-skip-paris-march-against-terror-world-stage </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-05 18:44:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> But it's controlled immigration. Tougher vetting and border controls help ensure a more viable immigrant citizen candidate getting to live the country. 

Judging by the chart population growth has been steady which is partially from controlled immigration. 

http://www.tradingeconomics.com/australia/population

Eroding health care system-is care quality going down or are costs increasing? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-05 18:29:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Trigger words being exploited.
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-05 18:20:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Trump beat everyone to it.

https://www.yahoo.com/news/trump-australia-better-health-care-015300468.html </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-05 17:53:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Mr Gruber. 

The perfect example of how many professional politicians and administrations conduct themselves.

Business as usual </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-05 17:29:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Being professional politicians doesn't help but a little smaller but repackaged Obama Care doesn't help either. 

The minute they saw a repeal wasn't going to fly they should've and probably still could work on getting sunsets and reduced funding on Obama Care. In other words work on phasing it out and/or letting it die. 

Some how for non catastrophic events especially we have to reduce big insurance's role as the preferred method of payment. That also means incentivizing lower cost health care service, not subsidized care but find ways to reduce the actual costs of physical care.

Just an example for arguments sake I'd give incentives for these urgent care clinics for services and pricing that can compete with ERs in some cases. A $300 trip to an urgent care is cheaper than a $3000 trip to the ER that wasn't needed. Some trips to the ER are poor planning and cya recommendations by another doctor. But insurance covers them. The providers know it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-05 17:14:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Population is a critical variable but Somalia also has a different culture, politics and economy. Different variables are why what works in one place might not work in another.

 If the variables in Somalia were much closer to a country like Australia that smaller population could be given health care much easier. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-05 17:05:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Many used to do exactly that. But then the insurance companies would play you didn't fill out the forms right etc, administrative games.

The problem is third party money wether it's insurance or the government. Third party money perpetuates inflation. Inflation from to be exact simply because they know that money is there.

  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-05 17:00:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The higher quality of life comes from things the US doesn't have including a much smaller population and a even tougher immigration policy. 

If it works and is accepted in Australia fine but it doesn't mean that system would work in the US even people wanted it to. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-05 16:31:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I was lucky to have one of the last old school doctors where I could pay for an office visit out of pocket with cash or check.. I was referred when needed and if a problem caused a return visit it was free or $20-40 tops. I'd rather pay a doctor in full a couple of times a year than pay double every month in insurance premiums. 

Insurance should be left and used for what it was ment- A catastrophic event or hospitalization and/or procedure. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-05 16:21:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Multi culturalism isn't the issue. If immigration is controlled, slow and steady which it seems to be in Australia the standard of living can stay high or increase. If I'm reading Australia  too tough on immigrant stories year round that's a reflection of a tough   controlled immigration policy. Everytime I read quality of life or standard of living surveys Australia comes out in the top 10

https://www.numbeo.com/quality-of-life/rankings_by_country.jsp

http://www.mapsofworld.com/world-top-ten/world-top-ten-quality-of-life-map.html 

A smaller population is much easier to service. In the US the hospital emergency room(EXPENSIVE) winds up being the doctor for immigrants and poor which leads to unpaid bills and money issues(just one issue of many).  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-05 16:05:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Multiple surveys/studies have shown Australia in the top 10 when it comes to quality of life. These are touted at least once a year by various organization. The stories I've read about the housing market  is a reflection of growing economy.

https://www.numbeo.com/quality-of-life/rankings_by_country.jsp

And again, controlled immigration makes a huge difference in quality of the life for everyone. The immigration policy considered too tough by some.  The job and housing don't get out of control. Slow steady growth in population and economy enhances quality of life. 

I'll be first to admit that not everyone's life fits into a touted statistical category but the numbers can't be ignored.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-05 15:54:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Then surveys   studies showing Australia in the top 10 countries in regards to quality of life are wrong?  

https://www.numbeo.com/quality-of-life/rankings_by_country.jsp </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-05 08:55:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Again? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-05 08:53:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Probation? 30 days in a cell at least. I doubt if a citizen did a less aggressive act on just one woman the sentence would be less severe.

How can he not know that it was wrong or not legal. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-05 08:49:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Because they're all hooked government subsidized insurance like a junky on crack. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-05 08:31:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Australia's population is about 1/10 the size of the US with different politics   tax system, different demographics and a much tougher immigration policy which can enable a more gentrified population and life. 

It was nothing but an ill thought out comment and dig at Obama Care and cheesy attempt to keep "his" health care bill passage in as much of the news cycle as possible.

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-05 08:23:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The Republicans need to spin this to sell less government. Freedom is not having a big entity like government in your daily business like health care and finance. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-05 07:49:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I understand they have and should have the right to pick their own candidates by what ever process they want. BUT aren't they defrauding party members by encouraging voting and/or promoting voting. They could potentially pull votes from another candidate in open primaries as well. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-05 07:45:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Is this extreme vetting they were talking about? I don't know. Over time this would be easy to build and fake. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-05 07:43:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> A heist? No hacking? An A for effort, literally effort other than typing.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-05 07:39:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The house repackaged Obama Care giving ownership to impotent Republicans.

All they had/have to do is phase it out incrementally by reducing the subsidies and put sunset on what ever provisions they can. 

In the meantime they have to work on alternatives including more clinic style medicine, interstate sales of insurance and demand full disclosure upfront pricing for starters. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-04 23:00:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Even more scary is that too many in their audience use them for their news   opinion. Fair or balanced-what's that?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-04 22:27:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Oh goody another INSURANCE bill for health CARE issues </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-04 22:25:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If it wasn't a "joke" I'd be a little more bothered by it. The viewing public and consumers who are exposed to his advertisers products have to decide with to patronize his show or buy those products. Come down too hard and nobody will be able to say or joke about anything.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-04 22:21:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Unemployment is a little different and is proportional(good or bad) to last salary. Other programs the user winds up with more than they put in. But monies were put into those programs for those who really need it, not those who 'want' to use it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-04 22:14:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  I've known alot of out of work non union   union members who never had to go on food stamps, welfare, medicaid, government grants, loans etc. Some unemployment at most. I also know people who used alot of their savings   credit trying to avoid government programs. Granted there are some that really really need assistance but not needing or using government programs does not make them elite I wish. 

Government programs should be for those who only really really need and cannot provide for themselves or family. If you want a government service but don't really need it you should pay. And once on or using a government program there needs to be incentives including education, training and/or penalties to get off those programs.

Another one trying to perpetuate us against them.  

    </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-03 22:00:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's about necessity. The professional politicians really need that insurance with all the deals they make in smoke filled backrooms.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-03 21:49:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Republicans can now join the ranks of cupcake nation. College students get radical while Republicans push policy to get re-elected. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-03 21:32:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If the politician or party takes lobby money from the health care or insurance industry they ARE part of the problem. Insurance is a, one method of payment which actual physical care seems to lose out to-for a reason-the insurance industry and/or lobby.  All the focus is on INSURANCE an optional form of payment preferred by providers and patients alike. Finding ways to fund insurance coverage is nothing but a somebody else is paying for it game, who plays the game the best; the Democrats.

The focus needs to be on controlling costs and finding other wayS to deliver actual physical care. Instead we get insurance middle man funding bills. Single payer or a government health insurance plan should be an option, not the only form of payment. The government would be another middle man as well. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-03 19:10:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Establishment politicians Democrat or Republican. Again it's about the status quo and money train. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> May Day clashes in Paris leave police officer with serious burns </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-03 18:41:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Police officer set on fire with petrol bomb during riots in Paris </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-03 18:28:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-03 17:48:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's not just Feinstein. There are establishment politicians but there are also establishment industries-insurance and health care. It's all about maintaining the status quo and money train running. There are no advocates here, just shills for the status quo.

Those same establishments have perpetuated the myth that insurance based health care is the only way to go and have indoctrinated generations of patients and providers that INSURANCE is the only way to deliver health CARE. Third party money perpetuates inflation which is profit for both the health care(including big pharma) and insurance industries.

Myth, image, perception etc but little or no solutions and/or alternatives. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-03 17:21:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hellooo, mediocre comedian gives an emotionally driven psuedo political commentary.

Another somebody else's money liberal. And yes he should've focused more on his child's condition for awareness rather moan about a method of paying for actual care-insurance. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-03 17:11:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yes and no. Third party reimbursement or sources of money help perpetuate inflation as well.  

Both provider and patients are treating health INSURANCE ment for a catastrophic event like a service plan year round. Problem is too much focus is on the method of payment-(insurance) rather than working on reducing actual costs of care. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-03 02:49:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The throwers punishment should include working in the burn ward of a hospital. 

Basically a version of home made napalm. Aren't Napalm and other flammables considered a weapons treaty violation now. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-03 00:37:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Not yet, just a messy trap ie oozing, dripping or leaking fluids and/or poor performance from dirty or failing fittings or components. 

Many manufacturers say basically all of your fluids need to be changed out by the end of the 5th year because they lose effectiveness.

Big thing is when you drive just don't think about the final destination pay attention to the way the car is actually driving, check out any alarms and pay attention to the stresses the car has been through like desert heat, artic cold, tropical humidity, road conditions ,road or sea salt, sand, 15mph city traffic or 60 mph highway driving etc. Again pay attention to the way the car is driving or performing. 


 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-03 00:23:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I've had cars give trouble within months of the 3 year mark and of course end of the 3 year or 36K warranty. The rubbers   plastics start drying out and changing shape, at least the older rubber parts did. I only had one electronic part give out in less than 4 years but hoses, belts, fittings I'll usually lose the first one by the end of the fourth year. They have planned obsolesence down pretty good now a days.

Environment is huge as is the driving/conditions and driver. Hot cold hot cold hot cold not great for parts either.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-03 00:14:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> In the form of a joke and satire, not a personal diatribe on a comedy show. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-02 23:26:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Colbert's Democrat sister must have run for office again.

http://www.csmonitor.com/USA/Elections/Vox-News/2013/0509/Stephen-Colbert-stung-by-sister-s-loss-to-Mark-Sanford.-Will-he-seek-revenge-video </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-02 23:02:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Read one report the bottle hit the officers helmet which means flaming liquid dripped down his body. If that was during a war the protestor could've been charged with a war crime.

I hope they get the thrower and lock them away for ever. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-02 22:59:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You helped bring up an important point. 3 years is about the point in which many cars start needing repairs other the normal maintenance. Many people don't want to deal with repairs period. I guess it's like renting an apartment rather than buying a house. Ownership comes with cost along with work/commitment. Leasing is practical for many. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> May Day clashes in Paris leave police officer with serious burns </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-02 22:52:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> May Day clashes in Paris leave police officer with serious burns </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-02 22:51:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Police hope video will help ID anti-gentrification vandals </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-02 22:33:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-02 22:20:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> How many infants    children, not older adults or teens died pre Obama Care because of no insurance or actual care. Most states have had medical insurance for kids under 13 if not  free medical care for uninsured children. The medical insurance industry is a problem. But is a comedy show, not a political commentary show the proper forum for a political   emotional driven vent/rant?   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-02 22:08:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Unless a business is aiding and abetting a known and declared enemy of the US nobody should be sanctioned for doing business with anybody. This will be grounds for appeal as well. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> French Would-Be President Macron Says Would Seek Poland Sanctions </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-02 19:10:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-02 18:50:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Instead of land locked many drivers are lease locked. Nobody wants to buy and own for 5-10 years, they want to lease for 3. Must be a lease saturation point in the market. Even though 3 years seems short depending on when everyone signed the contract which could reflect current sales.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-02 17:12:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Any third party would be in the same position or face many of the same issues facing Republicans today but a more hardline stance would've at least come up with a compromise bill that wouldn't be a cave-in. A third party would've fought for every line and word in the bill and more importantly the numbers. The Libertarians would've fought for more reductions because it is about the size of government and it's budgets. 

Why aren't the Republicans fighting for incremental reductions in budgets and programs. A 25% reduction might be easier to accept than elimination. Put a sunset on these programs even if it's specific things. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-02 17:05:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I get that but in the class action lawsuit the DNC said they can pick their candidate the way they want to even if it's in a "back room" Meaning the primaries are just a show and hopefully a validation of party management's choice. This is where some of the fraud happened in the 'validation' process including timed stories, rigged caucuses and super delegates.

It's not just about accepting a loss. There needs to be follow up on the issues from the 2016 primary season and party practice.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-02 16:37:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> In other words she took voters for granted and did not account for the bad taste left in many Obama voter's mouth from the 2008 primary. She ASSumed the Clinton and Democratic names would carry her. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
