<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject9926</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-10 11:40:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I really hope, that I am never hard up enough, to need to, use the kind of  hookers you pimp out of that thing.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-10 10:52:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hmm I love cheese fries, and I love garlic fries, but not sure how I feel about the two together.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-10 10:46:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Looks yummy. Sous vide? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-10 10:43:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> New go to vegetarian dish.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [homemade] Spiced Kabocha sqaush smoked over pecan wood. With hapa rice, and a vegan lime aioli </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-10 10:43:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-10 07:10:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah he stole that thing </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-10 04:04:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> There was a legitimate window, in the beginning. There was a lot of momentum. 

That window has closed.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-10 04:01:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I just want to make absolutely sure that no one here is shedding a tear for James Comey. 

Fuck that guy. 

Obama should have put his ass out on the street after:

**he threw the fucking election!!!**

First by insinuating that there was any possibility of a criminal case over the non story emails, and then his letter that cost Clinton the election. 

This cunt can rot in hell, he is personally responsible for this mess. I am hearing a little revisionist history, and conciliatory tones in these threads. 

I would like to remind people

**James Comey had more impact on the elections then the Russians did. If you are not happy with this administration this is the sad sack POS who got us here**

 There is only one thing that could make me happier then the events of today. It is great seeing the man's career in tatters, a pariah on both sides of the aisle. Sitting at home for the 8th day straight, watching the price is right, staring a his phone that only buzzes when someone mentions him negativity. 

That one thing would be a group of FBI agents doing a perp walk, and stuffing him handcuffed into a car leaving the court house where he was just indited, for treason. 

He is not our friend, and he could not be trusted to run this investigation. Bask in the news today, do not shed one tear for this rotten scumbag.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-10 03:18:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I cant believe you use, a FM modulator in 2017 lol. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-10 03:17:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I think it is no coincidence that this photo looks like it was taken with a old disposable film camera. You found this photo in a drawer somewhere, and scanned it in. No way this POS is still on the road. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-10 03:14:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> All this time has metallic beige been tactical camo, for meth lab country wind blown praries? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-10 03:12:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Pretty good deal for $75,000, only 116,000 miles under 100,000 and you would be looking at used Lamborghini money.

 I see you opted for the much sought after Barney lurking in the shadows purple. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-10 03:08:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You know what colors don't go well together? Haven't washed my car in months black, and taco bell, after tequila shit brown </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-10 03:05:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Rule #1 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-10 01:13:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Please make sure to be recording when you get stuck not even 100 feet down the first trail.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-10 01:11:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Roughly how many inches is your penis gonna shrink when a guy pulls up in a demon?

Oh and take this shipping guards off the spoiler you are making a fool of yourself </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-10 01:00:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> How's that throwing the election for Trump going you fucking cunt Comey...

**HAHAHAHAHA**

If you would have done the right thing you would still have a job, now you are kryptonite, and your career is in shambles. Couldn't have happened to a worse guy.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-09 20:08:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> For me the only real use case I see for this is the handsfree YouTube videos. That would be nice for cooking. Then again I do have a iPad, and a laptop.  

I guess for shopping it would also be nice to have visual confirmation as well. 

If I didn't already own a echo this is the one I would buy. It will be interesting to see what kind of skills people concoct. I can't really think of any other visual device that was controlled totally by voice. 

The more I think about it this will probably be a absolute god send for disabled people. The echo was already amazing for sight impaired people, but this could be great for quadropalegic people or those with Parkinson's. Not having to type to get content will hopefully help people out.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-09 19:57:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah 90% of the Echo is the mic </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-09 18:56:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> He looks resigned to his fate, that a boop on the snoot is imminent  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-09 18:53:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Looks like a mini dj khaled </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-09 18:38:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I came in just to try and warn you guys </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-09 14:22:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Jesus 1100 upvotes? Looks tasty, but tons of people post up Ansel Adams level photos of unique things, and get like 15. This underexposed homemade dish is oddly popular. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-09 14:16:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Quite possibly the only idea worse then Turo </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-09 12:36:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I don't get it. I s this a cliff? I doesn't look that high from this perspective. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-09 12:34:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> :( </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-09 11:41:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> yep. by far </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-09 11:37:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I always ride my bike hammered. You can technically get a DUI though so I probably should uber. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-09 11:36:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> These things cost $200,000 you can afford to buy your way out of trouble, if you can afford this. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-09 11:34:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> There is no way to ride this thing, and not look like the biggest cunt of all time...


I want one desperately  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-09 08:22:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This entire article is based on a farcical idea. If actually read the claims it is BS.

 When connecting wirelessly, Schneiderman writes, subscribers on the 300 Mbps plan typically received 15% of the promised speed; subscribers on the 200 Mbps plan received 20% of the promised speed; subscribers on the 100 Mbps plan received 39% of the promised speed; and subscribers on the 50 Mbps plan received 58% of the promised speed.

The key to this is wirelessly. I have 500 mbps internet. I also have a top of the line highly reviewed Asus router, and anything that is on wifi is 80211.ac rated, and the best in class. I scanned my channels with a professional wifi analyzer, and chose my channel after careful deliberation.

The best speed I have ever reached over wifi even with all the best stuff available on the market is 150mbps. Now is it fair to say that I am only getting less then 1/3 of my speed I pay for? Fuck no it isn't if I plug in hard wired I get the full 500 every single time. I get 100% of what I pay for, but internet speeds have vastly outpaced wifi's ability to deliver them.

Does the author expect ISPs to invent some new wifi standard, or force everyone to buy top of the line enthusiast gear? Also this is NYC where the airwaves are super crowded. No even if everyone gets the nighthawk cable modem, and buys a sweet computer you will still see a small fraction of the speed.

There are limitless reasons to trash the ISPs but this is a hit piece, and founded on BS. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-09 07:58:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Just remember never watch a trailer for a movie, you are positive you will see. I will be completely blacked out on this movie until I see it in the theater, I will be surprised about everything, and I will draw my own conclusions.

Then I will come on the internet, and see what you lot think. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-09 06:31:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I always wonder when what it is like to be boring </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-09 05:23:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This is not a huge hub for SE Asians, in the same sense as Japan, China, and Korea. That being said I have met many Thais, Malaysians , and if their is one cuisine that is overrepresented vs population it would be Vietnamese. There are 4 Vietnamese restaurants within walking distance of me (Kaimuki), and 8 within a mile. I know for thais, and Vietnamese people there is a tight knit community. 

 If you are any flavor of asian you will blend in here. The other great thing for me as a mixed race person, is that people have been crossing racial divides for generations here as well. So While there are many people who are 100% this or that, chances are if you stay in hawaii long enough you have that one Grandma who ran off with a white guy, or the one grandpa who shacked up with a african American girl. It isn't that big a deal here, and that is awesome.

Back to the Asian thing though. Just having the majority of people being some flavor of Asian has put a lot of out of state transplants, at ease in a way they didn't realize was possible.

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-08 22:40:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The crux of the issue is that T-Mobile bills themselves, as a consumer first company. Their implementation of their promotions for the past few years have continued to set bad precedents. With the one plan customers are technically getting even access to most providers, however video is throttled, unless you jump through a convoluted process to unlock HD. ATT saw them getting away with it, and launched DTV now which is 0 rated against your data, in flagrant violation of NN.

When speaking on NN it is hard to have a conversation on every factor, since the definition is a constantly shifting. With the zero rating of spotify vs daves music streaming service, then the compression of videos from big companies that was on by default, and now the byzantine process of watching a HD video with day passes Tmobile continues to find ways to interject themselves between you and the digital diaspora. They throttle this, and promote this as a partner, they make big shows about providing more for less but 1,000 ft view a lot of these policies are very consumer hostile. 

Devils advocate, no one was ready for the onslaught of people finally realizing the power of their phones to watch tv, listen to music, and podcasts, upload live videos etc. In some sense a lot of these policies were enacted as a compromise, to alleviate congestion on a network not yet robust enough to suddenly handle 10 times more traffic. I get it.

That being said, we are now in a world where Tmobile leads the industry. It is safe to say that they have turned the wireless industry upside down, and where they go everyone is forced to follow. That is why I find it disheartening that they are on the other side of this issue. Bottom line for me, what I want is NN legislation written into law, that my ISP, wireless or otherwise, does not have the ability to throttle, or speed up any content that I request over their network. If I exceed my data allotment so be it, but it should be my decision what video is in HD, and which is constrained to 1.5mbps. It should be my decision what audio I listen too, and at what quality it comes to me. 

The ISP has no business tinkering with my data, and while things are at a tollerable level now, be prepared to be extremely outraged in the future. History shows that there is no industry more apt to be given a inch, and take a mile then ISPs. They have a whole gameplan, on how to divide up the internet into nothing but entrenched players, and split the profits. The unlimited data on ATT only for direct TV customers, was only the opening salvo.

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-08 22:15:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Aw our nickname for our lab is Nugget as well </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-08 21:32:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Sure you can. After a few years of home ownership, and on time payments your credit is excellent, and you have equity in the property. You also can count the rental income towards your yearly take home. In my case it Jack's me up by $24,000

I went back to my same loan officer, and she didn't bat a eyelash at giving me a second mortgage for my personal property.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-08 21:29:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> No. As far as I know you will still not get deprioritized for watching binge on video.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-08 21:24:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> We can get it lower! Just keep on calmly explaining facts to the rational people in your life, and we can turn the tide. 
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-08 21:15:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah I would take a bullet, or crawl through broken glass for my wife, but if she were a fervent trump supporter, it would probably be over.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-08 21:13:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I think they need to move past Flynn. He is already out. I'm sure he didn't act alone. We need to go after the others as well </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-08 20:53:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Lol </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-08 20:40:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I am very lucky on both counts. 

We go hiking all the time, and he hasn't slowed down much at all from the early days, although he is a tuckered out guy after these days. Hope to keep him active as long as possible.

Some of the best times of my life in these hills with this guy </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-08 20:31:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Countrymans always looked distressed, and shocked/surprised with their giant headlights. 

In this picture it looks like the blue one farted right in the grey ones face. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-08 20:27:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Plenty of room in the boot for your straight from China counterfeit streetwear collection, vape accessories, and half filled out GED applications. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-08 20:24:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Supercharged, and still has less power then a base Camry. SMH </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-08 20:21:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Ajit Pai is going to save all the comments for his spank bank, and read them like erotic stories, all while he continues his plot to destroy the open internet </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-08 20:19:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Tmobile is leading the way to destroy net neutrality with binge on, and 0 rated data. You can argue that their flavor of violating the spirit of NN is more consumer friendly, but the fact is they are picking winners, and losers. They were at the forefront of this as well, and implemented it long before VZ, and ATT.

In case you are not clear on why allowing you unlimited netflix, and spotify is a bad thing. It is not the company you do business with today that is at stake, it is the new company who you would have done business with tomorrow that can be damaged, by ot having their data prioritized, or included for free. The logical conclusion of 0 rating is that big companies will end up paying ISPs to be included in premium tiers, and upstarts will be locked out.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-08 20:09:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I can see this easily happening. We were trying to get to Eurpoe last year. They changed gates on us 5 times. I think they were boarding for 5 minutes before the screen reflected the final gate, and there were still people confusedly wandering around.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-08 19:46:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm sure they were aware of the powder issue all along, and were petrified someone would call them out on it.
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-08 12:54:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> https://youtu.be/zfD7agP1yxw

:Danzig learning the lesson of talk shit, get hit. 

Never forget </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-08 12:47:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Even on phone calls I have been getting a bunch of complaints about voice quality on my s8+. I have taken to  carrying my earpods everywh to make calls.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-08 12:42:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I bought one for my GF, and sent it back. The camera is certainly not anywhere close to a flagship, or her current one plus 3. Especially in low light it was quite smudgy. 

It also feels extremely cheaply made. 

If you only have $299 to play with then it is a nice option, however for $270 I ended up getting her a pristine  open box S7 on swappa with 11.5 months of Samsung warranty.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-08 12:28:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm not a analyst or anything, and I am going strictly on anecdotal experience, but I find this hard to believe. I know literally 0 people with LG phones. I am into phones so I will always find out what type of phone people have, to see if it is a area we can small talk about. 

I haven't met a single person in the past year with a LG phone, and I chit chat with people from all walks of life, and socio economic backgrounds at work, and in my personal life. 

I find it hard to believe that one in five people bought a LG phone last year. The G5 was such a flop that all of it's add ons we're 80% off at the TMobile store, not even six months after launch. The V20 certainly picked up a percentage of note 7 refugees (myself included). However it was certainly a niche product, and you had to be 100% committed to phablet life, because it was huge, and ugly. 

I suppose there is a huge subset of people just buying the budget versions, but it still seems like a dubious claim since in my personal experience most people have whatever the budget Samsung of the moment is, or just buy year old flagships.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-08 11:15:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Interesting thank you. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-08 09:03:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I would give you shit for driving a car that is only suited for depends adult diapers runs, going 10mph under the speed limit in the fast lane, and paralyzing unsuspecting cyclists in designated bike Lanes. However living in NYC you made the right call, although I may recommend a mad Max style lifted hearse with machine gun turret for your next upgrade.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-08 08:58:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Looks like a cro magnun e30 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-08 08:56:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The v6 mustang is like those dummy cellphones they have at Sam's club, or buying a MacBook pro box with a brick in it from a guy on Craigslist. 

At first glance it looks like it has a function, but it is all a elaborate ruse.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-08 08:54:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Stick your dick in the tailpipe. Assert your authority, and mark your territory.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-08 08:51:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Looking at a picture of the new Mazda 3 vs the original, is like looking at healthy black Michael Jackson, vs bothed plastic surgery old white lady MJ.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-08 08:47:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Lamborghini doors on a car that is slower to 60 then a base Camaro SS. What a poser.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-08 08:41:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It is just annoying to me, since I would gladly just order a 7 layer burrito, and a bean taco supreme for my order Everytime but that is $6-7. Whereas I can get a box meal with the promotionalitem, 2 tacos, and a drink for the same price.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Age ain't nothing but a #. My man Henry crushing a 5 mile hike on his 10th birthday today. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-08 08:37:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-08 06:10:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Going to make a big difference if you live in a gigabit LTE market. For the most part speeds around me are trash, but I have been a few places that I assume are enabled for gigabit, and got over 100 for the first time ever with T-Mobile </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-08 06:04:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I want one but I dont like any of the colors </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-08 06:00:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Pretty cool </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-08 05:39:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Still tasty with the other flavors in the salad </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-08 04:21:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Out of curiosity I wonder if you could answer a question? I have noticed that there is a huge amount of Indian reviewers of technology who do everything in english. Who are they marketing to? It is nice that if I am looking at a relatively obscure product, that a Indian guy took the time to post a video, but I'm curious why they don't do things in their native language? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-08 04:17:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  ield: family entertainment and game streaming...hopefully replace only after a long time
 

I need a phablet for looking at schematics in the field. I would go even bigger then s8+ if it were availible.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-08 03:54:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Honestly their southwest salad is one of the best things you can get from a drive through(near me at least). It has sauted chicken, corn, and a little bit of cheese. Just go easy on the dressing, and it is damn healthy as well. 

http://www.cookinglight.com/eating-smart/nutrition-101/healthy-fast-food/healthy-fast-food-mcdonalds-southwest-salad </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Phone won't fast charge even with factory charger. Any ideas? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-07 23:04:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> At first my phone wouldn't fast charge on any of my third party fast chargers from Anker, or aukey(both of which I have verified to work on many other devices). Every time I plug in I get a message saying, that my device is slow charging. 

Forgot to plug in last night so threw it on the charger at 9am this morning. Came back at 10:30am and I was only at 65%, and it wasn't indicating fast charging. I was using included charger, and included USB c cable. 

I also had a day this week when I plugged in over night, and was only at 85%the next morning. 

Is my phone defective? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-07 11:55:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> the white millenials voted for trump too though.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-07 06:34:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Right in the cooter! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-07 06:07:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Looks like a russian E30 knockoff </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-07 04:15:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I totally agree, I'm sure without graft they could have built it for the same price as the projections. They should appoint a committee dedicated strictly to auditing the contractors, and watching the budget. 

That being said this has become a political hot potato, and everything is black and white. You are either for, or against, and there is no room for shades of Gray or nuance.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-07 03:04:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Not sure how I feel about this. As a rail supporter is her ousting going to be better for rail's prospects? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-07 03:02:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I think the other posters are underselling it  This place is heaven on Earth for Asian Americans. Almost everyone you deal with from the cops, to the bank teller, to the cable guys are going to be predominantly Asian. Wherever your family comes from there will most likely be a wide variety of restaurants catering to your cuisine, and a rich community of people who celebrate your traditions  Asian culture has been intertwined with Hawaii for many generations, so you will be a insider and have a advantage over others based solely on being Asian. 

Plus the weather is nice 

However if you bring negative vibes, then people will call you out here just like anywhere else.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-07 02:28:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The og Mazda 3 hatchback is actually a underrated design. Even today the lines are really gorgeous, and timeless. It has some of the best proportions ever to Grace a small  hatchback  

The sedan however from the rear looks like it got sat on by a elephant with explosive diarrhea  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-07 02:12:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This is the car that started it all. 

When these were new they gave the owners such delusions of grandeur, that they thought their wrong wheel drive 180hp were exotic cars. 

With nothing more then a fart can, some konig wheels and some Chinese body mods the owners self esteem, and egos were so conflated that they would call just about anybody out. 

Life came at them fast if they ever did race people though. It turns out noise doesn't equal power, and those Chinese coilovers will put you in a ditch instead of enhancing your handling.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-07 01:40:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If you have access to a good quality large monitor you can see for yourself. Cue up a photo in apple photos, and then toggle to a Google photos backup. On face value they are quite similar, but look at the fine details, and you will find lots of artifacts. Also in my experience they appear to be less vivid, and have less dynamic range after compression. 

Taking a file from 12 MB, to 2 MB will have ramifications no matter what. 

I am a outlier now with large high resolution monitors, and a big 4k tv, but in the future it will be totally mainstream to have wall sized screens, and every bit will count. Not to mention that there will sometime come a day where it will be common place to strap on VR goggles, and really gaze deeply into photos. 

2 of the biggest mistakes I ever made was ripping my impossible to find CD music collection in 128kbps, and buying a crap point and shoot camera for the most pivotal summer of my life. In both cases even in 2017 I wish I had a time machine to go back and tell past me to do it right the first time, and not cut corners. Instead I am listening to low quality mp3s, and looking at blurry photos on my high end modern gear.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-07 00:37:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I have apple photos backing up all my dslr, and iPhone shots. I pay the $10 per month, and have rough 250 gb worth so far. 

 I also have Google photos, as a back up.  Even for iPhone shots, the compression is noticable when looked at critically. 

Fine for perusing on a phone, but my photos are the only physical possession I actually care about. One day I will be old, and paging through the memories of my youth. I want them in the highest Fidelity possible.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-06 22:25:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Wow a blue camry, Grandpa was feeling a little saucy when he was picking this thing out. Unfortunately you could paint a Camry neon green, with tiger print racing stripes, and it would still be metallic beige underneath.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-06 22:21:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I know that this is a big sign of status in Philippines. Here in the states you couldn't get a date with a peg legged lady boy in that car.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-06 22:17:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Must get annoying changing the water pump every time you fill up gas.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-06 19:55:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You can certainly tell on a big 4k screen. I'm not willing to permanently degrade my photos to save a few bucks. Years from now when I am.looking at my vacation photos on my 120 inch 12k resolution screen I will be kicking myself. 

I already have regrets about going for a cheap camera, over a really nice one years ago. I wish my photos were crispier.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-06 17:42:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I enjoy the videos. It is 2017, this is how information gets disseminated  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-06 17:07:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> how do you make the text shake like that? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-06 11:24:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> 2 is more then enough for me. I have probably had a total of 6 or so... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-06 11:19:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> For me it is the taco burrito, beefy Frito, or loaded griller. Any combination of the 3 and I will leave full, and have dropped under $5 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-06 11:17:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This is actually a stroke of genius. I will try this next time.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Why are the old standard menu items so expensive (supreme taco, 7 layer burrito etc)? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-06 11:16:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Relative to a lot of the more modern menu items the old ones really have a lot less ingredients, yet they are some of the most expensive things on the menu. I love me some 7 layer burritos, but for the price of one I can usually put together almost a whole meal. Around me a burrito supreme runs almost as much as a xxl stuffed burrito with higher quality meat, and way more volume of ingredients. 

Why does TB jack the prices up on ye old faithful menu items? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-06 11:10:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> you'd be working so much you wouldn't have a social life.... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-06 11:06:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Loaded potato griller, and beefy Frito crunch burrito. Gets me full for $3.50. 

If they are running a box promo and I am famished I will usually get that, buy it usually ends up being too much food.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-06 09:43:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I bet the payload is exactly one 30rack of Natty ice. Which is fine by you since that is all the bed will be used to transport.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-06 09:40:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> As a owner of a bicycle I take offense to that statement.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-06 09:39:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If you have given up on life enough to drive a Kia Rio, then you might as well just get it over with, and down a whole bottle of sleeping pills </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-06 09:35:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> **follow up** had margaritas. All is well </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-06 09:32:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That video from earlier today of the guy driving through the mist and flying dismembered limbs of his brother (who just crashed) moments before crashing into the car filming and dying himself was enough to reaffirm my decision not to get a motorcycle.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-06 04:36:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If you think that Hawaii has cronyism, you apparently have never done business on the east coast. 

I personally love the laid back work culture out here. People get enrichment from their lives, and don't take work to seriously. 

If you are ambitious, and career minded Hawaii is certainly not the place for you. Your skills will wither, and being around so many people just phoning in their work for a check will drive you mad. 

If you are like me, and are lazy, then this is the promised land.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-06 04:29:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> /thread </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-06 04:28:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Amazon, and whatever trash Walmart carries is your only choices </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-06 04:24:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Something spooky about the woman who comes into frame and just stands there with her hands on her head for a few minutes. Must have been a brutal scene she was observing </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-06 00:22:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Nvidia shield has Amazon, and it does 4k HDR. I also have the Apple TV but won't be using it for Amazon since it only does 1080p </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-05 23:00:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Good luck </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-05 20:17:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> 10/10 would hang out on stairs with </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-05 20:15:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> All work, and no margaritas makes subject9926, a dull boy </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-05 11:59:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Dang I could care less about the gear VR. Between this and the costco deal I regret my preorder. 


Thanks guys </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-05 06:23:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I did not. 

However I did have it off the market for 4-5 months as I DIY renovated it. Although it is technically breaching the contract to get a loan under the auspice of using it as a rental, there is 0 enforcement. You can buy a property and rent it out the next month. If anyone asked you could just say that circumstances changed. 

The beauty of this setup is that you can build equity while still living comfortably in a rental that fits your needs. All the while writing off tools, gas money, and depriciation on appliances. You can even write off your association dues. 

Then after paying it off you either have passive income, or have built a bunch of equity you can trade for a house of your dreams without much sacrifice.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-05 04:37:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Italian hero on Italian herbs, and cheese bread. **Double meat** lettuce, tomatoes, and onions. Oil, and vinegar S/P and thats it. 

Miss me with that salad sandwich shit. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-04 19:32:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I certainly don't support snitching on people to get them fired/so I can feel morally superior. You apparently have never worked in a kitchen. Everyone gets as high as possible, as often as possible. 

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-04 19:22:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Kinda dick calling out his workplace IMO </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-04 19:16:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Painting a Audi a3 wheels blaze purple is like Al Roker in a racy leopard skin thong.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-04 18:43:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> How can you not look at adorable puppies all day? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-04 12:04:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I use it across a wide range of different computers from poweful modern i7 macs, to archaic 10 year old workstations, and don't have many issues. The only time it ever bogs me down is if I leave the never ending scroll on, and open all images. By page 5-6 you will run out of ram. 

However day to day it is a excellent companion to Reddit, and makes it extremely convenient to use, vs clicking every link individually. 

Highly recommend everyone give it a try.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-04 11:26:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Have sex with a bunch of prostitutes and arrest them after I get my nut. 

/S

http://www.foxnews.com/us/2014/03/21/hawaii-law-allows-undercover-police-officers-to-have-sex-with-prostitutes.html </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-04 11:17:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> One word of advice is to look at investment property before you buy your home. I didn't plan it this way, but I ended up buying a rental property long before I bought a house for myself. It was the best move I ever made. 

As far as tax benefits go I am much better off with the rental property. 

Essentially you buy a property that may not fit your standards, but you can easily afford. Let someone else pay your mortgage on it, and reap all the tax incentives. If times ever get tight you can live in it for a while.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-04 11:10:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Harsh reality is that you need to choose between kids, and a comfortable lifestyle here in Hawaii. If you have kids, you not only need a extra bedroom for them ($$$), your school district will play a huge roll in their education. Obviously the wealthier schools will be better, forcing you to buy even more expensive housing. Or you could send them to punahou...

We decided against the crotch fruit, and live comfortably on dual income no kids salaries. Own property, and are on top of all bills. However my co workers with kids are sometimes pay check, to paycheck bringing home $85-100k. That is far from fuck you money, but save for the Bay area, and NYC you can carve a comfortable middle class existence out with $100k anywhere in the country. 

If kids were in the cards for me I would be leaving Hawaii ASAP. Which really is a shame because this seems like a great place to raise a family. It is safe, and culturally diverse. Just the kind of environment that would foster some well rounded offspring.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-04 10:51:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Just a heads up for those who use a browser. Download a plug-in called RES (Reddit enhancement suite). It makes Reddit 100 times better in a lot of ways. The most important being that in the top row you will now see a option to expand all images, or you can use key command shift+x. No more clicking on links everything is displayed on the page, and you can go into only the content that is worth it to you. 

It will also allow you to browse a never ending stream of Reddit pages in line. (this does become resource intensive) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-04 10:46:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> triple deckers 

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-04 10:44:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Reddit is mostly image based though? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-04 10:43:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Boost is the best Android Reddit app IMO, and narwhal on iOS is killer.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-04 07:40:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Green is lowkey the hear and soul of the warriors </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
