<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject9366</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> How do you read books? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-08 01:47:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I know this might sound stupid at first, but please bear me for a while.

There are two ways to read. First, go word by word. Second, read fast, while soaking in the general idea and not worrying about every emotion or detail.

I tend to take the first route, but at the expense of consuming fewer books. For e.g., in Pride and Prejudice, I have to reread lot of sentences to exactly understand what's going on, because of its archaic style. The same happened with me when I had read The Great Gatsby and Midnight's Children, because of their high-end vocabulary. I limit the second approach for *lighter* novels, such as those by Sidney Sheldon.

At this point, I should clarify that I am not a newbie reader. It is just that I am slowed down by my attempt to soak in everything that the author has to say, and I am now wondering if I should read faster, albeit with lesser comprehension.

So, what do you suggest? How do *you* read books? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Today I watched 2 terrible movies in a day: Independence Day Resurgence and Insurgent. What about you? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-08 00:38:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-27 01:38:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I registered at 4 pm. Do I have any chance of getting a ticket? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-22 05:03:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The book - that's all. Trust me.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-22 01:29:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I quit smoking after being at it for 8 years. In case you didn't know about it, read Allan Carr's book called The Easy Way To Quit Smoking. It literally is what it says and it helped me and a friend to quit - HIGHLY recommended.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-21 16:39:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I find it hard to believe that some college graduates still can't find jobs after 2008. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-21 08:40:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> And you thought Amazon wasn't a *cool* company?! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-13 16:51:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Holy shit.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-08 08:14:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Damn, you put this song in my head. And now I can't get it out. I am fucked.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-07 09:49:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I have taken lot of interviews for my company. Two instances stand out:

- I was having a dull day at a recruiting event, because the candidates were all poor. Suddenly, I was sitting in front of this guy from Walmart Labs. I had heard that Walmart Labs asks really difficult questions in its interviews. And since this guy was an employee, and so must have cleared their interview in the past, I couldn't ask him the usual simple questions I was asking all day long. I brought out the big guns, even one difficult question that I had never asked before  The candidate didn't disappoint and handled all of them comfortably.

- One of my favourite questions is how to design a monitoring and automated alerting system, on a high level. The problem isn't as easy as it sounds. Needless to say, I have seen lot of folks flounder in it. And I remember a guy who used a stream, such as Kafka, to build the system. He also handled failure scenarios properly. I was impressed! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-07 06:05:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Awesome! I would have given you a gold, if I had any!

Anyway, keep it up.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-06 19:39:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Agreed. Start with the ones that are lowest in your order of preference, just to get a hang of things. Keep the difficult ones for a little later. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-06 19:30:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I agree with everything *except*:

 I'd chat with the engineer tomorrow and tell them you're interested, talk about road map, etc. And see if you'd be a good fit.

I'd suggest you first talk to the hiring manager: either ping him to meet you over coffee or setup a short 30 minute 1:1 with him. Find out if he indeed has open positions in his team and what kind of prior experience he is looking for. If you sense he is interested, ask him if there's anyone on his team you could talk to further.

In other words, reach out to the hiring manager *before* talking to someone on his team. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-04 14:53:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Oh fuck, this is one crazy story! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-03 12:25:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  overwrite them all in my Google account and access them via Signal

What do you mean by this? I too wish to get rid of Google Contacts, but haven't come up with a way yet. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What has been your love-hate relationship with Facebook and Instagram? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-31 23:30:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-31 07:02:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I am moving to United States soon. Adding this to my bucket list.

Thanks for sharing.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-30 13:11:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I switched to DuckDuckGo some time ago, but its search results sucked so bad that I had to return to Google Search. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-30 12:52:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I use Authy- it is an awesome extension of Google Authenticator that syncs codes on various devices, both mobile and desktop.

2FA makes things difficult, but that is so for anything that betters security. Authy simplifies things a bit.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-28 20:20:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> - The first scene of Kill Bill 1, in which Bill shoots Kiddo.
- The docking scene from Interstellar.
- The last meeting between Lauda and Hunt in Rush. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
