<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject7498</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-10 04:28:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I just started IJ. I'm only on page 22 during the introduction of the marijuana addict, but I'm really liking it already. I don't find it all that hard to follow quite yet, just a lot of vocab and references that require some looking up, but the IJ wiki page is perfect for that. Really looking forward to this long ride! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-10 00:49:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You're welcome! Let me know what you decide to go with. I'd love to help you get into the mindset of the book and see what you think. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-10 00:45:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> t/y </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-10 00:39:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It may depend on what you're into but these are all pretty easy to read and don't require as much extra thought. They all get you into the story pretty quickly and are relatively short.  

- And Then There Were None by Agatha Christie (mystery, page turner)
- The Giver by Lois Lowry (dystopian, young adult)
- The Long Walk by Stephen King (dystopian, thriller, page turner)
- The Outsiders by S.E. Hinton (coming of age, young adult)
- The Perks of Being a Wallflower by Stephen Chbosky (coming of age, young adult)

possibly these as well...they're short and you will be able to tell fairly quickly if it's for you or not. 

- Animal Farm by George Orwell (dystopian, symbolism, dark humor/satire)
- Of Mice and Men by John Steinbeck (friendship)
- The Hitchhiker's Guide to the Galaxy by Douglas Adams (sci-fi, comedy)
- Fahrenheit 451 by Ray Bradbury (dystopian) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-10 00:16:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thank you! Yes, I rated them all on Goodreads, and wrote reviews for the majority of them. I created a shelf with the list above as well. Here's my [Goodreads](https://www.goodreads.com/user/show/2829998-ian) profile. If you want to add me feel free! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-09 22:35:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That's very true! I might look into doing that.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-09 22:06:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thank you! Yeah, you're right. I do want to make more an effort to read a variety of authors to expand my perspective. We didn't really put that much thought into this list, to be honest. We were totally new to the whole thing. If I were to do something like this again I would definitely put more thought into who I'm reading and where they are from, etc to make it more diverse.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-09 21:39:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm debating rewarding myself with a nice quick simple read -- Infinite Jest :D

They're doing a reading of it right now on r/infinitediscussion and i've been wanting to read it for a long time. 

Either that or I will read A Gentleman in Moscow or Rabbit Run, both I got as Christmas presents but haven't been able to read yet! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-09 21:24:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah it was tough at times, but there was one point I wanted to let my buddy catch up so I ended up reading a couple books on the side which acted as a kind of break. But still it was definitely tough. My to-read list has become insanely long. There's no doubt in my mind if I didn't do it with a friend I would have given up. We both fed off each other. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-09 21:17:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thanks </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-09 21:15:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I just removed the link! Thanks for the heads up. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-09 20:55:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thank you! I really liked The Giver as well.

It is very tough for me to pick just one favorite book from here but I think the ones that have stuck with me the most are East of Eden, To Kill A Mockingbird, The Catcher in the Rye, and The Outsiders. I usually go for books with memorable characters and I think that's why I love these so much. 

As for which book surprised me the most, man these are tough questions, I'd say Catch-22 because of the hype on here and it's non-linear narrative gave me doubts, The Stranger because I didn't know anything about it and it peeled my eyelids back, and Watership Down because I did not expect a story about rabbits to be so engrossing and so real. I thought it would be simply a children's story and I was wrong. 

My future reading plans: I want to continue with classics but incorporate a lot newer literary fiction as well. I also have been wanting to tackle Infinite Jest for a long time because it just appeals to me, so maybe I will try to give that a go before jumping into shorter reads. Really I just look forward to being free to choose whatever I feel like, maybe even read a couple things at once! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [UPDATE] I have just completed a list of 40 popular books after not reading any books my entire adult life! </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-09 20:34:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Almost nine months ago a friend and I decided we wanted to start reading more books. I had recently read a few books that got me into reading, but before then it had been about seven years since I last read a book in high school English class. Since then it was almost as if I never read any of these required books at all. I forgot most of the popular modern classics and had no knowledge of their influence on literature. My friend felt the same way. We questioned if we really read them or simply used SparkNotes to get by. To change this, we decided we had some catching up to do. We each picked 20 books from lists that were heavy on modern classics, put our lists together to form 40 books, shuffled the list, and got started on the journey intending to read them in the order they fell. Of course, this didn't go exactly as planned as we did alter it a bit later on. Two weeks into the journey, I ended up posting in this sub shortly after to share our story with Reddit.

[Original post and story](https://www.reddit.com/r/books/comments/51phev/after_rediscovering_my_love_for_reading_i_will_be/)

The list ended up having a mix of modern classics, popular reads, and a few that were completely random. We kept the list relatively simple because we were still new to reading so we didn't want to get burned out by creating a monster list of old classics. 

The overall experience was unforgettable. I now love to read more than I ever did. Not only that, I now look forward to doing it whenever I have the chance. I love the learning experience and simply taking in the stories that other people have shared in their writing. I used to think of the act of reading a book as this tedious, daunting task that would require a significant amount of time and effort. Yes, it takes some time to finish a book. But it also takes time to partake in any activity. At least this activity is one worth spending time on. In the past, instead of wasting two hours watching a movie on television that I've already seen, I could have picked up Of Mice and Men and had an entire book finished. Instead of spending an hour blindly browsing Twitter on my phone, I could have put a dent in To Kill A Mockingbird. This experience forced me to put aside my phone for a few hours and get carried away in a story. 

I would be lying if I said every step of the way was a blast. Sure, there were some books I felt bored with or I just wanted the get to the end. In these moments I learned to put the book down and come back to it another time, even if it meant holding up my progress for a while. For the most part, I enjoyed the majority of the books we decided to read. Some more than others, of course, but I had an appreciation for each one. Honestly, there were no books that I could say I "hated". One struggle I came across about halfway through the list was thinking about how long our list was. I kind of regretted making the list 40 books instead of only 20 at times. It wasn't that I didn't like the book I was reading, it's just that at a certain point I wanted to branch off and do my own thing and not be tied down to a certain book. Sometimes I just felt like reading a particular book I found that wasn't on my list, but I couldn't read it cause I wanted to get through this darn list first. Because we both felt this way, we did end up changing the list a little bit. We removed a handful of the tougher, longer books we originally had on the list and put in some shorter ones. But in all we made it! Now I look forward to picking up and putting down any book I damn well please at any moment. 

I ended up tracking all of my progress on Goodreads and have become addicted to the site. I've written many short reviews for the books I've read, which has helped me reflect on each one. Everyone is so friendly and I constantly find great ideas for new books that interest me. I'm always looking for new friends to share experiences with on there. If you want to link up feel free to send me your profile in a private message and I will add you! 

I wanted to share my story and start a discussion about my experience with the books I've read, discuss reading in general, and maybe even inspire some new readers to form this positive habit. Reading regularly is something I believe I will continue to do throughout my entire life. 

If I get a lot of similar questions I will try to answer them up here.

**AND here is our completed list in the order that we read them:**

- Cats Cradle by Kurt Vonnegut
- The Old Man and the Sea by Ernest Hemingway 
- Brave New World by Aldous Huxley
- All Quiet on the Western Front by Erich Maria Remarque 
- American Psycho Bret Easton Ellis
- The Perks of Being a Wallflower by Stephen Chbosky 
- Fahrenheit 451 by Ray Bradbury
- Man's Search for Meaning by Viktor Frankl 
- And Then There Were None by Agatha Christie
- The Call of the Wild by Jack London
- Sirens of Titan by Kurt Vonnegut
- The Hitchhiker's Guide to the Galaxy by Douglas Adams
- Any human heart by William Boyd
- East of Eden by John Steinbeck
- Animal Farm by George Orwell
- A Clockwork Orange by Anthony Burgess
- The Giver by Lois Lowry
- Of Mice and Men by John Steinbeck
- One Flew Over the Cuckoo's Nest by Ken Kesey
- To Kill A Mockingbird by Harper Lee
- A Farewell to Arms by Ernest Hemingway 
- The Great Gatsby by F. Scott Fitzgerald
- A Wrinkle in Time by Madeleine L'Engle
- Walden by Henry David Thoreau
- Watership Down by Richard Adams
- Mrs. Dalloway by Virginia Woolf
- Death of Ivan Ilyich by Leo Tolstoy
- The Catcher in the Rye by J.D. Salinger
- The Handmaids Tale by Margaret Atwood
- The Long Walk by Stephen King
- Lord of the Flies by William Golding
- The Stranger by Albert Camus
- Slaughterhouse-five by Kurt Vonnegut
- The Curious Incident of the Dog in the Night-Time by Mark Haddon
- Post Office by Charles Bukowski
- Fear and Loathing in Las Vegas by Hunter S. Thompson
- Catch-22 by Joseph Heller
- The Outsiders by S.E. Hinton
- Ragtime by E.L. Doctorow
- The Things They Carried by Tim OBrien


**FAQ:** 

**Which was your favorite book?** 

Very tough to answer so I will give you a few. East of Eden, To Kill a Mockingbird, The Catcher in the Rye, The Outsiders, The Stranger, Animal Farm, Of Mice and Men, Watership Down, Catch-22, The Things They Carried, The Death of Ivan Ilych. I love memorable characters and I think a lot of these did that. 

**Which was the book you were most surprised about?**

Catch-22 because the hype gave me doubts and the non-linear narrative was tough at first, The Stranger because I knew nothing about it and it peeled my eyelids back, and Watership Down cause it had so much depth and was so real which I did not expect after seeing the cover. 

**What are my future reading plans/what will I read next?**

I plan on continuing with classics but incorporating more recent literary fiction and non-fiction. I also want to diversify my reading more in regards to authors and even genres. I may start reading Infinite Jest because I've wanted to tackle it for a long time. I know, there's another 9-month journey :D. If not, I will read either A Gentleman in Moscow or Rabbit Run because I got them as Christmas gifts and have not been able to read them yet! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-09 06:24:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Let us all take a minute to appreciate how careful this person was with their craftsmanship. It's impressive they got down to the lead without snapping it in half.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-09 06:09:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I haven't read this so I can't confirm how similar it is to what you're looking for but [Battle Royale](https://www.goodreads.com/book/show/57891.Battle_Royale) popped into my mind when I read your post.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-08 17:21:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Good to know! I'm quite persistent so even if i'm not enjoying something I usually inquire more about the subject to gain a better understanding or take a break and come back to it the next day. But the subject matter, from what ive heard, is really interesting to me. Plus, i've watched many interviews with DFW and find him fascinating. I know this doesn't mean I will like his writing, but it at least I know i'm reading it because i'm genuinely curious, and not because I feel like I have to read it just to say I did.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-08 15:59:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Sounds good. I have post it flags to mark portions and also a notebook if I need it. I suscribed to r/infinitediscussion to help me stay motivated. They are doing a reading right now that they started on the 1st in case you weren't already aware. Thanks for tips. I think i'm as ready as I will ever be.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-08 15:23:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I haven't read these yet, but i've heard amazing things about both of them. I seem to love Steinbeck myself from what i've read so far. Enjoy.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-08 15:20:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> **The Things They Carried, by Tim O'Brien**

Then i'm thinking it's time to crack open **Infinite Jest, by David Foster Wallace** </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-07 06:34:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The Outsiders by S.E. Hinton  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Dark humor in Ragtime by E.L. Doctorow </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-06 22:37:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Spring! Spring! Like a mad magician flinging silks and colored rags from his trunk the earth produced the yellow and white crocus, then the fox grape, the forsythia flowering on its stalks, the blades of iris, the apple tree blossoms of pink and white and green, the heavy lilac and the daffodil. Grandfather stood in the yard and gave a standing ovation. A breeze came up and blew from the maples a shower of spermatozoic soft-headed green buds. They caught in his sparse. He shook his head with delight, feeling a wreath had been bestowed. A joyful spasm took hold of him and he stuck his leg out in an old mans jig, lost his balance, and slid on the heel of his shoe into a sitting position. In this manner he cracked his pelvis and entered a period of health from which he would not recover. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-06 19:16:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Napoleon Dynamite. Don't judge me, it gets better with time. Speaking of, its been awhile.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-06 18:06:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The MTV Unplugged performance of [Down in a Hole](https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=QLTFgo2Z1EE) by Alice in Chains is a song I always come back to. It just has so much emotion pouring out of it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-06 18:00:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Scrolling down this thread I keep seeing songs that I've loved in the past but they slipped my mind and say to myself "wow, yes, yes, yes." 

God, I love music.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-06 17:46:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Since most of the classical music that came to mind has already been mentioned I'll go with something a little more recent. 

[Bridge Over Troubled Water](https://youtu.be/GYKJuDxYr3I) (Live Version from 1969) by Simon   Garfunkel. 


I can cry on demand hearing this song. 





 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-06 17:32:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Omg yes </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-06 05:31:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> - I'm reading **Ragtime** by E.L. Doctorow right now; It's wonderful. It's like injecting the feeling of the turn of the 20th Century in America. Reading the writing feels like how I imagine jumping in a pool of marshmallows feels like. 

- **Any Human Heart** by William Boyd is another good one with a very sprawling timeline. This time set in Europe. It follows one man's incredible life as he grows older. Taking place from post World War One to all his years beyond. Very touching. 

- Both the above are similar in the sense that they have a ton of huge historical figures that act as themselves but are surrounded by fictional characters. They both deal with a large scope as well. 

- My favorite is **East of Eden** by John Steinbeck. Might not be that dense with historical events, but it's as good a book as someone can ask for. 

- **The One Man** by Andrew Gross is another one worth checking out. It's a historical thriller they call it. It takes place during the Holocaust. It's quite the page-turner.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-06 04:12:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I still really liked the show even though they had to change some things. It kinda gave me some new suprises. But yeah it's nearly impossible to surpass your own imagination formed from the book. It was really cool to see the sets and everything on screen though. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-06 03:50:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> 11/22/63 by Stephen King. It got me into reading books, something I hadn't done since elementary school. Shortly after finishing about 8 months ago, a friend and I started a reading challenge and now I've read a total of 52 books in that span. It's a hobby that I intend on keeping for the rest of my life.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-04 20:14:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm not sure at this time how to make books completely invisible, but that doesn't mean it can't be done. Maybe someone else could be of better help with this. I'd have to take a look at the site on my desktop when I get home.

I know you can at least prevent books from appearing on your feed when you rate them. I think either by going into your settings or another way is to go to your profile page and click x on the right side of your post to remove it from your feed quickly, although that could be risky. It will still show up in your shelves though either way.

Maybe you could play with the date read so it appears as one of the first books you've read? This way it gets buried at the bottom of your read shelf. I would test these out with books you don't mind sharing. 

Good luck with everything! Best wishes on trying to add a new little member to your family :)  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-04 13:50:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> These look amazing. I've only heard of a few of them too. For some silly reason I thought A Fine Balance was an older book. Thank you! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-03 19:16:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm currently reading The Outsiders and they mention Gone with the Wind quite a few times in it. Now, I'm just seeing your post and really want to read it! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-02 18:06:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Oh i've heard The Nightingale is a good one. I've heard of A Thousand Splended Suns but didn't know anything about it until now. Thanks for the recs! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-02 16:09:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I've heard of this one but haven't looked into it really. Looks exactly like the sort of thing im into. Thanks!  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-02 06:11:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Great, Thanks! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-02 04:00:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I haven't! I'm still pretty new to the reading game. The reading list of classics i'm finishing up has been mostly the only stuff i've read so far. 

Any particular books by Auster that gave you Steinbeck vibes or are a good place to start? 
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-02 03:55:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Perfect. I've heard some good things about this one, I will look into it.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> I'm looking for some "must read" 21st century literature </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-02 03:11:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm finishing up a reading list soon that mostly consists of classic/modern classic fiction. I'm looking to branch out afterwards and incorporate some high quality literature that was written closer to present day. Lets say *roughly* from 2000-2017. So what are some fiction books written in recent years that you feel are enjoyable, well written, and contain lessons that everyone should experience? Either those that will be considered classics sometime in the future or hidden gems. They don't have to take place in the 21st century necessarily, just as long as they were written in more recent years. 

If I put my book interests in a blender it would likely contain the following characteristics: Distinct characters and relationships, nostalgic,  historical, emotional, immersive, philosophical, flowery prose, and simple prose. 

Heres some of the classics that I really liked for your reference:

- East of Eden by John Steinbeck
- Of Mice and Men by John Steinbeck
- To Kill A Mockingbird by Harper Lee
- Flowers for Algernon by Daniel Keyes
- The Stranger by Albert Camus
- The Catcher in the Rye J.D. Salinger

Thanks all!  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-02 02:29:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I haven't read any Coatzee yet, so I can't say if they are anything alike , but *The Stranger* by Albert Camus gave me that hopeless, wandering feeling from the main character.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-02 02:20:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I thought the adult interpretation was that Holden needed an adult to talk to and never got it until after he almost went off the rails. 

Books are a funny, yet beautiful thing  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-02 02:12:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Try *The Curious Incident of the Dog in the Nighttime* by Mark Haddon if you loved Flowers for Algernon.

 Flowers for Algernon is one of my favorites so I didn't like it quite as much, but it reminded me of it as I was reading.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-02 01:58:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Try *The Long Walk* by Richard Bachman aka Stephen King </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-02 01:52:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Finishing **Catch-22, by Joseph Heller** I really love it. Different than what I usually go for. It's all over the place but the scenes are hilarious and absurd. It's now slowly starting to come together and getting really deep, so the humor kinda hurts as its woven in. 


**The Outsiders, by S.E. Hinton** Read this over 10 years ago while in middle school I believe. Really looking forward to reading it as I don't remember much.


**Ragtime, by E.L. Doctorow** I'm a big fan of historical fiction so this has a strong appeal to me.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
