<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject8631</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-10 09:30:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> OMFG. It took me 3 seconds. After that I swallowed back a bit of vomit and had a vomit eatin' grin on my face. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-10 03:36:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> well. you know. at least Josh will never have the chance to get his frat boy hands on her now! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-09 10:22:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Man, I keep warning all of y'all about these apps.

does anyone listen?!??!?!

#NO </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-09 09:52:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> anytime! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-09 09:51:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> r/nosleepworkshops :)

I can take a look at it there as soon as you post it! ^er ^well ^if ^I'm ^not ^being ^the ^lazy ^bum ^I ^usually ^am. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-09 02:05:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hm I'm not sure if it's super common but thanks! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-08 22:06:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Man. I almost left in the middle of that explanation </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> A New Techy Horror Story?!? Let's Go! </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-08 17:14:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> A Site Called "Cash for Confessions" Has Changed My Life </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-08 17:12:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Im not usually the type of person to click on ads, but I was completely broke and still living with my parents. Before a bunch of you guys come at me and tell me to get a job and to stop being a bum. I want you guys to know. I do have a job. I work 55 hours a week and I give all of my money to my parents. They are the ones that dont have enough to pay their bills. After everything is said and done, I have maybe 40 dollars a month to spend on myself. Fuck, they are my parents, but I make sure they have enough to eat before I feed myself. 

That is why when I saw a simple black square take up the bottom right corner of my screen with the words Cash for Confessions inside of the box I clicked it. I was using an old beat up tablet and hooked up to really shitty Wi-Fi coming from the modem and router Comcast rents out to us, but the site opened up on my tablet in an instant.

Like I said, Im not normally the type of person to click on ads so my guard was up high, but the website seemed completely safe. It was pretty much solid white with a small tan box in the middle of the screen. On the box were two generic words. **Create Account** I quickly made a throwaway e-mail address and clicked on the box. It took me to the next screen. It only asked me for three things.

*User Name*

*E-mail Address*

*Currency Desired*

My favorite superhero is Flash so I made my username BarryFlash, I typed in my e-mail address, and then typed in USD on the last slot. As soon as I finished typing the screen turned black. It stayed that way for a couple of seconds before two words appeared on the top of screen. ***Thank You.*** The two words faded away and were replaced by a series of rules.

***Cash for Confessions***

**1) All of the confessions must be completely true.**

**2) Do not use the money to help others out. This is your money that you have earned.**

**3) You may tell others about Cash for Confessions, but you cannot send this into anyone that will cause us any type of trouble.**

I impatiently tapped on the screen until the screen flashed a completely white screen before transitioning to a gray screen. An endless list of confessions filled my screen. I wasnt really interested in anyone elses confessions. I wanted to see if this thing actually paid us. After a couple of seconds of searching around I finally found what I was looking for. 

Once you click this you must confess.

Without a second thought, I tapped on the link the other confessions disappeared from the screen and was replaced by an empty white box. I tapped on the box and my keyboard came up on my screen.

After a small sigh of anticipation, I typed out I was a virgin till I was 22 years old. Right after I finished typing the keyboard disappeared and the screen went completely black. I waited for a couple of seconds before the tablet vibrated. After a couple more seconds of waiting, I pressed the power button and my tablet came to life. There was a new e-mail. I tapped on the notification and the e-mail app came up and slowly started to load. 

I almost let out a scream of joy when I saw that the e-mail was from Cash for Confessions. I tapped on the e-mail and quickly became sketched out and slightly pissed when all it said was, $15 has been deposited into your bank account. If you would like more money please give us a better confession.

Shit. I would have been happy with just $15, but I knew that there was no way they could have deposited the money into my bank. They didnt have my account number, they didnt even know what bank I used, shit, they didnt even know my name. After letting out a depressed groan, I turned my tablet off and went to sleep. 

I woke up in the middle of the night to the sound of my tablet vibrating continuously. Once I got out of bed, I nervously walked up to my tablet and turned on my tablet. E-mails. Thousands of e-mails from Cash for Confessions. I nervously clicked on the first e-mail and almost dropped it on the ground. I closed out of the e-mail and looked through the rest. They all said the same thing.

*Dont doubt us, Samuel Harrison. We know who you are. We gave you the money. Please check your bank account and see that we are a legitimate business. We miss you and we hope you come back.*

Curious and scared out of my mind, I clicked on my bank app and logged in. I had 14 cents in my bank account before (I checked earlier to see if I could eat Taco Bell the next day) but I now had $15.14. I was scared. I really was, but I was also excited. I mean, it was the first opportunity I was given to actually make a little pocket change for myself.

I dont really know when I fell asleep, but I do know the sun was rising when I finally did. I kept writing out confession after confession. I mean, they knew who I was, but the people that were reading it had no idea who I was. All they saw were my confessions. I didnt really put anything juicy, but a couple of them managed to make me around 30 dollars. That was 4 days ago. 

I woke up the next morning and realized I was already 4 hours late to work. I dont know why I was so dumb, but I called my manager and told him that I quit. In the middle of his rant, I hung up on him and checked my bank account. My jaw dropped when I saw that $1560.14 in my bank account. 

For the next three days, I wrote as many of my confessions as I could, but yesterday morning I realized something. I was out of things to confess. 

That is when I started to mess up my entire life in the span of 24 hours. I broke one of the rules. I started to make up confessions.

It started off with small shit like I stole 100 dollars out of my grandmas wallet when I was 12. and quickly escalated to I have a gun in my drawer. I am going to kill my parents tonight and they wont be able to do anything about it.

Right after I made that confession I checked my e-mails. A couple of my made up confessions made in between 15 dollars to 750 dollars, but my newest one made me $15,000. 

I was ecstatic. Everything finally felt like it was perfect, but about an hour later, my tablet started blowing up again. Nervously, I checked it and saw that I had over 800 e-mails waiting for me. I opened the first one and instantly knew how bad I fucked up. I knew they all said the same thing, but I spent the next hour clicking through all of the e-mails and checking to see if it was maybe just a warning. It wasnt. They all said the same thing again.

**Samuel,**

**Why would you lie to us? You knew we would figure out if you were lying or not, but there is a way to fix it. If you look in your first drawer you will see a gun. Kill your parents if you want to live. Fulfill the confession or we take your worthless life.**

I checked my drawer, and sure enough, the gun was in the middle of my drawer. I picked it up and felt goose bumps cover my body. 

When my parents sat on the couch for our weekly movie night I took the gun downstairs. I sat next to them for the last time. I enjoyed every single second, every single laugh at dumb moments from the movie, and every single smile we gave each other. 

As the movie ended I took the gun out of the back of my pants. Tears filled my eyes as I knew what I needed to do. 

I placed the gun behind me and ran out the front door. I didnt look back at them. I didnt want to see their confused and concerned faces as I ran off into the night. 

I went to my friends house that night. I knew I was putting him at risk, but I was honestly hoping they would kill my friend and me off, but unfortunately, I woke up this morning. I woke up and saw my friend cooking breakfast. With a feeling of dread and sadness, I turned on his tv and turned it to the news.

The main story was about my parents. They were found in our house. Both of their heads were mutilated by several bullets. I choked back my tears and sobs. I know they are after me now. 

Im writing this out on my tablet and leaving it at my friends house while I try to get as far away as possible. Its my fault that my parents are dead, but it is now up to me. Its up to me to get revenge for their deaths. 

Until then. I want to leave you guys a warning.

Please be careful if you use Cash for Confessions. It is fine if you need a bit of money, but please dont be like me. Dont [make up confessions.] (https://www.facebook.com/subject8631NoSleep/)
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-08 14:07:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Haha i love your username origin XD </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-08 13:09:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Oh that is awesome! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-08 13:09:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Ohhhh did not know it was straight from demonology! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-08 13:07:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If i dont like it -.- i will be sad but cant really do anything since i live in korea </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-08 10:41:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> P.S. Get a Portable Battery the next time you go out! Super life saver. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-08 10:38:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Good. Remember to keep us updated man! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-08 10:31:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Not to be a stick in the mud or anything, but I am highly confused right now.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-08 10:30:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> ohhhhh see that's what I wish I had! A username with a meaning :( </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-08 10:29:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Man. Speaking from my experiences with phones. I would say just trash that shit.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-08 10:15:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> oh that is really cool! I figured it had something to do with the Oxford dictionary haha </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-08 09:04:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> ###YES </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-08 09:04:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> #benevolent dachshund overlord </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-08 08:46:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I shall take your name then! and forever hear the same joke. "I thought it said poopy at first" </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-08 08:37:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> but i'm more boring because I never even watched SleepyHollow :/ </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-08 08:31:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> ohhh that is actually really cool O.o 

Fun fact: subject8631 is actually a girl's name. Kinda makes me wonder if my parents really wanted a girl instead of a boy. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Meaning Behind your Usernames </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-08 08:09:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Basically as the title states.

What is the meaning behind your username? Past experiences, What you find the most scary. Just genuinely curious!

Mine is just my first name. *(boring. I know)*
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-08 07:51:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Lmfaoooo XD </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Oh, Bath Bombs and Rotting Skin?! </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-07 17:13:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Don't Trust The Bath Bombs From Ugly Duckling Project </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-07 17:12:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I walked into the hospital an extremely attractive man two days ago. I am now a lump of decaying flesh. The doctors have no idea what could have caused it, but I do. Telling them wouldnt help anything. I mean. They already know the important details. I have thousands of tiny parasites eating me from the outside. They even managed to get two of them off of my body, but the more they examined the parasites the more confused and scared the doctors and I have gotten.

The doctor gave me a description of what they look like about 2 hours ago. They have worm-like bodies, but the face of the parasite has a lot of similarities to. Um. To yours. Both of them. I dont really know how else to describe it. No arms but small limbs that resemble legs and. Well. Feet. Thats all they really told me, but they will continue to examine them and hopefully find a way to get them off of you. For now. Just relax.

I really tried relaxing for an hour, but every time I stopped completely moving I could feel those things go in and out of my flesh. That is why I decided the most productive thing I could do now is to give everyone a warning. 

So I dont really know how I should start my introduction, but I guess I could just act like Im talking to you. 

So hi!

My name is Chris. I am a 28-year-old man. I live in a two bedroom house and when Im not dying on a hospital bed I am spending most of my day at the small Italian restaurant I own. I have two cats that I love very much. I live in Fayetteville, North Carolina. Never been a really attractive person, but I was far from ugly. Of course, I wished I was the guy that made people take double takes, but I knew that was completely impossible when I couldnt even afford the most basic plastic surgeries. 

That all changed 9 days ago. 

It was around 1 in the afternoon when I heard a knock at my door. Slightly annoyed by the unknown visitor, I let out a sigh and walked to my front door and looked through the peephole. A woman was standing patiently outside. Even from the peephole, I could tell that this woman was fucking gorgeous. I straightened out my clothes and my hair and opened the door.

With the first glance, I was awestruck. She was the most attractive person I have ever seen in my life. With a confident smile, she stuck out her hand and said, Hello sir. Have you ever heard of Ugly Duckling Project? Slightly confused and curious, I shook my head at her and asked, Um no, but Im not really trying to buy anything ri- She cut me off and said, Oh no. Im actually going around and giving people one week trials! I dont even have anything to take payments. With a quick motion, she took out a ball the size of a baseball and stuck it out to me. I took it and looked at it. 

After giving me a second to look at the multi-colored ball, she continued to speak, Thats a bath bomb. Have you heard of those? Well. They basically go into the bath and slowly they dissolve into the water. Its a lot of fun to watch as well as making your bath smell a lot better, but ours are different. If you just use the ones I give you for a week I can promise you that you will look like someone I would drool over. She took out a small box and handed it to me along with the bath bomb that was in her hand.

I took it and nodded at her. 

Before she left she said, Use the bath bomb I gave you first and then use the other ones. You will see a change within the first day. Its important you dont go past 30 hours before using the next bath bomb or else it will stop working. Ill be back next week. You can place your order with me and then take me out to dinner after. 

Im normally not a bath kind of guy, but curiosity got the better of me that night. I threw in the bath bomb and got in. 

She was right. The bath bomb was nice to watch. It dissolved and slightly fizzed in the water. Blue and red foams started to cover the top of the bath. I leaned back and relaxed. I woke back up a couple of minutes later and it felt like I had bugs all over my face. No matter how many times I rubbed my face the feeling of having something crawling all over my face didnt stop. Out of desperation I threw the bath water on my face and tried washing it off.

It finally stopped. I quickly dried myself off and checked the bathroom mirror. 

Nothing changed, but I wasnt really that disappointed. I mean. She almost had me. Of course, she would use her beauty to seduce me into taking the trial and hopefully convince me into making a purchase by giving me the sliver of hope that I could take her out on a date. 

I went to sleep that night around 11 pm. 

When I woke up the next morning I checked my alarm clock and realized that I completely overslept. It was already 8:45 and my restaurant opened at 9. I rushed out my house and drove as quickly as I could to the restaurant. When I got there I rushed out of my car and opened the doors. As soon as I got opened the doors I felt someone tap on my shoulder.

It was one of the waitresses. With a small cough, she asked, Um do you know Chris? I never got the memo that someone else would be opening today. 

I let out a laugh and said, Cmon Stacy. I know I didnt have enough time to get ready today, but that joke is a bit harsh. Her mouth dropped as well as the other six employees. They rushed inside except one of the cooks. He looked at me for a second before saying, Sheesh man. You look like a fucking model now. How did you do it? That must have cost a fortune. I gave him a confused look and ran to the restroom. I stared at myself in the mirror for over 2 minutes. I couldnt help it. I was now the best looking guy I have ever seen. I still looked like myself, but shit, the perfect version of myself.

The rest of the week was a blur. I did the bath bomb every single day at the same time. I didnt get any better looking, but I still felt somewhat obligated to continue using them.

Before I knew it, it was the next week. I took the day off so I could wait for the lady to come back and I could place my order. 

She came at around 1 in the afternoon again. I opened the door and she didnt even bat an eye. With a smile, she said, So I know for a fact you used them. Good. Im not drooling like I promised, but I would really like it if you could take me out to dinner, but first, you need to place your order. I gave her a nod and asked, So how much is it? Without skipping a beat she said, Well for a week its $14,000 and for a month its $50,000. I recommend the month because you save $6,000. 

My jaw dropped. I didnt even have enough to pay for a week. Shit. I didnt even have $5,000 in the bank. I shook my head and said, Im going to be honest with you. Im happy with what I have now. Besides, I dont even have close to that amount. I was just going to buy more so I could take you out on that date. With a sigh, she said, Are you sure you cant buy anymore? I highly recommend not skipping a day. I mean. You know that the looks will only be maintained with those bath bombs. I shook my head once again and said, Like I said, I dont have close to the amount to pay for a weeks worth. Shit. I own a restaurant, but I make just enough to pay the bills and have around 2 grand a month to spend on myself. 

She gave me the saddest look I have ever seen and said before leaving, You need to know. The first bath bomb is filled with tiny parasites. They eat away the impurities of a person. The other bath bombs after that give those parasites enough mock flesh to feed off of for around 30 hours. Once they run out of the mock flesh they will start to eat the rest of your flesh. 

I dont know why, but I laughed at her. I mean, at that time, it was completely ludicrous, but I shouldnt have doubted what she said. 

She gave me a final sad look before handing me a bath bomb. 

Before she walked away she said, This bath bomb is the same as the first. For when you want a quick death. 

That was three days ago. 

The next day I woke up and saw patches of exposed flesh all around my body. I didnt feel pain, but I could feel those little creatures traveling inside of me constantly. 

I rushed to the hospital. 

Like I said earlier, the doctors havent found a solution for me. I know there isnt a solution. 

Well, there is one last solution. 

I asked the nurse to bring in the bath bomb that was in the left pocket of my hoodie. 

Luckily, she found it and brought it in.

Once I send this warning out to you guys I am going to eat this fucking bath bomb. Its going to taste gross, but I want it to end now. There isnt any hope for me anymore, but there is hope for you. If anyone asks you if you know about the Ugly Duckling Project walk away from them or shut the fucking [door in their face.] (https://www.facebook.com/subject8631NoSleep/) 

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> My mother really does know best </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-07 02:48:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> My Mother Really Knows Best </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-06 17:05:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Did you have enough to eat? Are you sure you studied enough for the test? Have you practiced the guitar, piano, and trumpet for an hour each tonight? Do you have any updates on your test scores? 


Those would be the starter questions my mother would ask me every night. If I couldnt say yes to every single question, I would have to stay up a little later and finish whatever task I did not complete. 


It annoyed me greatly at the time, but now that I am 25 and live around 3 hours away from my mother, I am forever grateful for how she treated me. I did not graduate college or start a business, but I was the general manager of a store that generated around 2.5 million dollars a year. I made enough to live somewhat luxuriously, and that was all thanks to all of the times my mother made sure I had every single task completed. 


For my age, I have accomplished a lot. I was making 4 times I thought I would ever make in a year with my job. I was dating a girl that was absolutely perfect to me. Her name was Carolyn, and I knew I wanted to spend the rest of my life with this funny, sweet, caring, and fiery woman. She had beautiful short brown hair, eyes that changed colors, and a face that made me smile every time she walked by my side. I loved her, and I knew that I wanted to marry her. 


That is why when my mother gave me a phone call and asked if she could move in with me, I said, Yeah! Just give me a call when you get close to my house. She let out a sigh of relief and hung up the phone without saying another word to me. 


My girlfriend was living with me at the time, but I really thought she wouldnt have any sort of problem living with my mother. I mean, even when I told my girlfriend that my mother was coming to live with us for a while she just gave me a smile and told me that I was a good son. I also knew my mother would be excited I found a woman so perfect for me.


My mother came to my house two days ago. Carolyn and I were watching a movie on the tv when I got a call from my mother. She told me that she was around 30 minutes away. It was 8 pm, but I didnt care. I was excited. I wanted my mother to see how happy and successful I was, but when my mother walked into my house she immediately started talking about how dirty my house was. I tried telling her that we werent expecting her to come so soon, but with a glare, she said, This isnt how I raised you. You used to be such an obedient and good child. Now you are some rebellious punk.


I gave her a small laugh and showed her to our spare bedroom. She started unloading her luggage in her room and I walked back out to the living room. Carolyn looked at me with a face of concern, but with a reassuring hand on her shoulder, I told her that my mother would quickly get used to our house. She gave me a small nod and walked to our room. I called out to her to tell her that the movie wasnt over yet, but she ignored me and continued to walk into our room. 


Yes. My feelings were hurt, but I knew why she would feel insulted. I mean, we both cleaned our house twice a week after work. We fucking busted our ass to make the house seem as immaculate as possible, but what my mother said, was pretty much a slap in our face. 


I finished the movie and walked into the bedroom. Carolyn was already asleep. I lied next to her and tried to fall asleep, but right as I started to drift off to sleep I saw a figure standing in front of our room. 


It was my mother. 


I tried to get out of bed and guide her back to her room, but before I get out of bed my eyelids became heavy and they slowly closed while my mind fell into a deep slumber. 


I woke up yesterday morning and saw that our room was a complete wreck. Every single drawer of our dresser was lying on the ground. Everything that was inside of the dresser was now covering pretty much every inch of our room. I got out of bed and heard Carolyns voice coming from the living room. With a sigh, I walked out of our room and saw that my wife and mother were having a very heated argument. 


Despite feeling slightly disappointed that there were already problems between my girlfriend and mother, I got in between them and did my best to settle them down. Once they managed to stop yelling at each other, I turned to my mother and asked her, Why did you go through all of our stuff? Were you trying to look for anything? 


After letting out an exasperated huff, my mother said, I was just looking for your test scores. I know you studied so hard for the test. Why wont you show them to me? 


Carolyn let out a snort and walked out the room. 


I put my hand on my mothers shoulder and sat her down on the couch. Feeling concerned, I asked her, What are you talking about? Its been almost 8 years since I took my last test. Are you feeling okay? 


Tears started to fall down my mothers face as she started to sob. 


I patted her shoulder and told her that I would find her some help, but she smacked my hand and started to scream, You need to go take the test that you have studied so hard for. I cant let you throw your life away like that. Go take the test and tell me how you did.


I started to tell her that I didnt have any upcoming tests and that we were fine but I couldnt let a word out. Hell, I couldnt even fucking breathe. I reached out to her, but everything blacked out on me. 


I woke up to the sound of my wife screaming. I couldnt really make out what she was saying but my mother sat next to me. When I tried getting up she pushed me back on the couch and told me to remain calm and relax until the paramedics arrived. 


When the paramedics got to my house they loaded me up on the gurney and pretty much threw me into the back of the ambulance. I tried asking them what was happening, but all I could really get out was a series of unintelligible mumbles and gurgles. Everything went black again and I didnt wake up until around 6 am this morning.


In the past 3 hours, I have learned that I have a tumor in my brain. My chances are pretty good. I asked the nurse where Carolyn and my mother were. She gave me a small smile and a nod before coming back in with Carolyn.


Carolyn rushed to my side and started to sob on my shoulder. She kept telling me that I was fine and that she was happy they caught it in time. When I asked her where my mother was she let out another sob and said, Baby, please. Please enough of that. You know your mother died 3 years ago. I dont know why you keep doing this to me. I tried to support you and to understand the stress you must be feeling. I even tried playing along with you, but this is too much baby. Please. Please just stop.


I know my mother died 3 years ago, but that doesnt mean shes gone. I mean. She was there for me when my previous manager died 2 years ago. He was shot in the head. Did I kill him? Of course, I didnt. I dont even own a gun. My mother just wanted to make sure I got the best position possible at my job. She was there when Carolyns ex-fianc was found in the middle of his living room. His face was completely torn off and his limbs were sliced off and thrown all around his room. Did I do it? How could I? I didnt even know where he lived. 


What Im saying is. My mother loved me and she always made sure I was always given the best opportunity. 


For now, I will act like I made a mental breakthrough. I will play the part of the man that was under so much stress that he imagined his mother still being alive. I will spill tears and let out sobs as I tell the doctors, nurses, and Carolyn that I have finally made peace, but most of all.


I will wait for my [mothers return.] (https://www.facebook.com/subject8631NoSleep/) 





 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-06 14:44:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Everything this.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-05 07:58:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Oh yeahhhhh! I'm right. 

^^^high ^^^five </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-05 07:57:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Oh. You must be referring to my twin. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-05 07:56:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You are literally the most confusing person.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-05 04:37:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Probably, but a good way to fix that is by making a facebook author page with the link to the book on your page! Plus, it's a lot better for the readers to feel more comfortable buying the book lol </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-05 02:20:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm only commenting on here because for some reason there is a lot of comments on here and it just seems like the cool thing to do.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-05 02:13:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Again. No idea what you are trying to say lol </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-04 16:26:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> check my account. you will see the last part there </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-04 16:02:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I have a hard core feeling you did not read this story or you don't really know English.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-04 11:00:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> thank you so much!!! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-04 11:00:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> thank you!!!! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-04 03:25:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I can't remove comments:) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-04 03:16:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'll figure it out. I know I'm not the worst guy here, but the sad thing is. I'm not the best person here either. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-04 01:39:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I have no idea what you are trying to say </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-04 01:38:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Haha well thank you very much :c </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-04 01:37:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Haha well the reason why i told you to change the title was because the one you have now actually breaks the clickbait title rule as well as the summarizing the plot with the title rule. And what do you mean by fix up the srory? Haha </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-04 01:28:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Plus add some meat to that story lol it is very short and quick. Maybe about 300 to 400 more  words lol </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-04 01:27:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I Have Been Getting Voicemails I Never Wanted To Hear </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-04 01:24:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Nope </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-04 01:24:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Wrong sub and you really gotta change that title brobeans.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-04 01:18:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Oh don't bow down. I'm far too short and not talented enough for such noble gesture </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-04 01:06:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Oh is it as fake as the overwatch porn you watch?:) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> New Story! </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-03 17:23:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> This is Far Worse Than Basic High School Drama </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-03 17:22:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> **Jeff Mendoza:**

**May 2nd, 2017:**

*Class 3*

*2nd Year Student*

***LOG 1***

Today was the first day of my 2nd year of studying at Prodigal Child Higher Education. I don't know if you have heard of my school, but my parents were all for it when my guidance counselor suggested it to them after I was expelled out of my high school for bringing a gun to school. Now, I'm not some crazy school shooter. I just brought it to scare my bully, Jeremy, so that he could stop bothering me. What I didn't know was that I didn't zip up my bag all of the way so on the way to my locker the gun dropped out of my bag. I didnt have any time or wanted to risk picking it up. I left it on the ground and rushed into my first-period class. 

It didn't take long for a couple of cops to come into the class with my principal and escort me out. 

As soon as I got into the principals office the cops started to badger me with questions. *What were you doing with the gun? Are you mad? Is there someone that you needed to shoot?*

I shook my head after their questions and calmly said, If you check the gun you will see that there were no bullets in it. It was just to scare a guy that kept bugging me. He said he wanted to fight me after school. I was just gonna show him the gun before the fight so that he would back out of the fight. 

My principal asked me to step out of the room and sit on the bench by his door. I walked out of the door and sat on the bench. I tried listening in on what they were saying, but they were speaking in whispers. Curiosity got the better of me and I slowly started to get up from the bench to lean in closer to the door when I heard my fathers voice come from down the hall. Jeff. What in the hell were you thinking? Why the fuck would you bring a gun to school? Are you fucking stupid boy? You wait till we get home. I swear you will wish you never knew what a gun was. My mom was walking next to him completely silent. She had the look of absolute anger and disappointment etched across her face. 

The whispering from the room stopped and I heard footsteps approach the door. One of the cops opened the door and nodded his head while saying, Morning Mister and Misses Mendoza, could you come in and have a word with us? The cop then looked at me and pointed into the room. I got up and followed my parents back into the office.

Long story short. We are a small town. They arent sending me to jail, but I am expelled from the school for the remainder of the year. I was expelled from the only high school within a 65-mile distance, but my amazing guidance counselor stopped us on the way out of school to give my parents a brochure and told them that it was a boarding school for troubled children like me. They gave her a look of concern until she said with a smile, Its free. 

Three days later I boarded a bus that was completely empty besides the driver and two other passengers my age. A girl and a boy. We didnt talk to each other for the entire 3-hour bus ride. The bus stopped in the middle of the field. When we got out I saw a plane in the distance. As we walked up to the plane I noticed that it was completely white. It was a huge plane or a small plane. When we walked in, I saw that there were about 36 seats on the plane. We were the only passengers on the plane as well.                                                

I was asleep for most of the plane ride. So I really dont know how long the plane ride was, but I woke up as we landed. I wanted to look out the window, but for some odd reason, I was nervous. I didnt really want to know where I was. I mean, when I asked my parents where I was going they would just ignore me and start talking about something else. 

As the plane started to come to a stop, I finally managed to muster up the courage to look out the window and saw that we were sitting in front of a giant purple brick building. An old weathered down sign hung loosely off of the front gate.

**Prodigal Child Higher Education**

The first couple of months inside of the school was pretty much like every other school, but I fucking loved it. Almost zero rules about what we could do after classes were over. Im not going to describe what went on for the first 11 months. Its basically whatever you would think happens when you group up 200 teenagers and let them do anything they want to do. Not the Lord of the Flies shit. More like the teenage version 50 Shades of Gray minus the shitty dialogue and the so-called dominatrix. 

Everything was perfect until the last month.

Shit has turned completely fucked up. I dont mean the regular teenage drama. Im talking about waking up and walking out of your dorm room and seeing the guy in the next dorm leaning against the wall next to my door. I tried to ask him if he was okay, but he fell over on the ground. His back was completely gashed open. There were twelve knives stuck into his back. I looked down and saw several other bodies lying on the ground. I closed the door and stayed on my bed.

I got back on the bed and lied there for as long as I could. I didnt want to get out. I was far too scared. Screaming came from the first floor every couple of minutes. I looked out the window about 45 minutes ago. There were bodies everywhere. Blood and body parts were strewn across the bottom floor. 

Im writing my first log now. Every website works here, but I feel like this is the best place to reach out. We dont have phones here, and if we do Im far too scared to leave my room. Please. Help me if you know any way to escape out [of this nightmare.] (https://www.facebook.com/subject8631NoSleep/) 







 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-03 16:05:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Ohhhh thank you:) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-03 15:10:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Wait that's what I'm missing?!?!?! WHAT THE FUCK. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-03 04:09:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Nope. That is unavoidable my friend. Like warm blood, far too many teeth, really big creepy smiles, and for some fucking reason McDonalds </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Gotta Love Grandparents </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-02 16:11:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> My Grandfather's Journal Saved My Life </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-02 16:10:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> For a 86 year old man my grandfather was extremely active and showed absolutely zero signs of slowing down. Even after breaking his hip bone just 2 years ago, he has recovered extremely quickly and walked around the neighborhood 3 times about a month after his surgery. 

My grandfather has always meant the world to me. He was always the man that tried to make me become the best person possible. If he caught me lying he wouldn't hit me. He would grab two 1 gallon jugs of water and made me hold it for an hour. On the other hand, if I ever did something praiseworthy he would use the little bit of money he had left to spoil me. My parents would also punish and reward me, but anything my grandfather did for me was far more memorable. Plus, my parents were always far too busy with their church. 

That is why when I started to struggle after college I reached out to my grandfather. By the next morning, he found me a room in the apartment he was living in. He paid 3 months up front for me and just asked me to go walking with him every morning at 7 am. I gratefully accepted his offer and promised to get a job so that I could pay him back as well as help him. With a laugh, he said, "First fix yourself. Then help others. You will succeed at whatever you do. Just figure out what you really want to dedicate your life to."

Three days after I moved into my one room apartment, I found a job at a place I truly loved working at. It may not sound like much, but ever since I was young I have always loved the thought of being a salesman. So when the manager at the local electronic's store offered me a job I took it without a second thought. That was two months ago, and I was doing great. I was 2nd place in sales the first month and then 1st the next month. The base pay was pretty low, but my monthly commission check was more than enough to pay back my grandfather and both of our rent and utility bills. 

Life was finally perfect for me. 

Every morning I would wake up at 6 am, take a shower, get dressed, eat a quick breakfast, and meet my grandfather on the first floor for our daily walk. Honestly, that was probably my favorite part of the day. We would walk to the local park and walk a couple of laps around the park. After about an hour of walking, we would go back to his apartment and drink a cup of coffee while I talked about my latest sales and he would bring out one of his 48 journals and read out a page. I know it sounds cliche, but every single day, he would read something that would end up helping me out that day. Usually, it would just help me with something minor like getting a huge sale or avoiding a bad purchase on my end, but two days ago it saved my life.

Two days ago, he told me about how he walked through a watermelon patch. He stopped in the middle of the field to tie his shoelaces, but while he was tying his shoe lace an angry farmer tackled him onto the ground. My grandfather started shouting at him and asking him what the hell he was doing, but the farmer kept accusing him of trying to steal his watermelon. It took him over 2 hours to finally convince the farmer he just stopped in the middle of the field to tie his shoelaces.

The moral was to never put yourself into sketchy ass situations. 

That day a couple of my coworkers helped the manager force an older woman buy a 4k OLED tv for 7k dollars. I was about to join in with the coworkers but the story my grandfather told me stopped me. I stood back and watched as the manager walked out from the back storage with a proud grin that matched equally with the oversized tv. Right after he completed the sale, I walked up to him and told him that I was feeling sick. Still excited from the sale, he just told me to go home and to come back the next day. 

I drove back home and saw my grandfather waiting for me in the parking lot. I got out and started to tell him about the sale the manager just made, but he just waved me off and said, "Don't tell me. I know. Go to your apartment and rest. Tomorrow is a new day." I gave him a small nod and walked up to the fourth floor and into my apartment. 

For the next three hours, I sat on my couch and watched tv. I was watching the news and waited for any type of new story about my store but before it was reported on the news I received a text from my manager.

*"Help. The old lady is back. Called 911 but you're closer. Her son is here. He has a gun"*

I know I should have gone there to help them, but I'm also not dumb. That's how motherfuckers die in movies. They try to be a hero and end up getting shot before anyone else does. Ends up looking like the biggest ass out of the rest of the characters. I know everything doesn't turn out like movies, but I don't have a gun or the heart to save the day. I ignored the message and kept staring at the screen.

One hour later, my store came up on the tv screen. The headline read, **"3 Found Dead From Store Shooting."**

Photos of my manager and the two salesmen that helped him make the sale came up on the screen. I shut the tv off and went to bed. While I was lying on my bed a million thoughts flew through my mind. Will I still have my job? Why does everything my grandfather warn me about end up coming true? What am I supposed to do now? Could I have saved their lives? 

After hours of interrogating myself, I fell into a restless sleep. 

Yesterday morning I woke up at 6 am. I went through my normal morning routine and walked downstairs to the first floor. My grandfather wasn't there. I knocked on his door. It was completely silent inside for a couple of seconds, but finally, I heard the sound of soft footsteps approaching the front door. When the door opened, I looked up at the man that pretty much took care of me as I grew into the man I am now. He was completely pale and looked far more sick than anyone I have ever seen in my life. Thick blue veins were visible from his near translucent face. With an obvious struggle, he said, "Come in. Take the journals. Use them. They will help you become the best person you could possibly become, but don't help others with them. That is when your life will start to leave you. That is the deal. Above all, don't pass them off to anyone else. That is when you completely give up on your life."

I saw something move behind him. Even in the dark room, I managed to see what looked like a completely naked man slowly walk behind him.  As he got right behind my grandfather I caught a good glimpse of him. He was completely pale, but words were written all over its body. Its face was completely normal except for the mouth. The mouth was unnaturally small with on single tooth coming out from the top of its mouth. Before I could warn my grandfather, it sunk its tooth into his neck and slowly started to suck. Within seconds, all that was left was my grandfather's skin. 

It has been about 24 hours since my grandfather gave up his life to give me the best life possible. Even after 24 hours, I cannot process what the fuck happened. I want to cry, but I refuse to accept the fact that my grandfather is dead. No. I haven't called the cops. What the fuck do you want me to tell them? That some journal spirit sucked the inside of my grandfather? Fuck that. Instead, I have been reading the journals nonstop. Trying to find some sort of way to bring my grandfather back, but I have yet to find the answer.

If any of you guys know what kind of spirit I am dealing with please let me know. Especially if you know if there is a way to bring a person back. I'm not ready to be on my own yet. I refuse to believe that my grandfather is gone forever. So please. Please. Help me. Please help me bring [my grandfather back.] (https://www.facebook.com/subject8631NoSleep/?ref=aymt_homepage_panel) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-01 15:16:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I like it being two words :) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-01 03:40:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Oh you guys are so lovely :) thank you for the back up:) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> New story </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-30 17:41:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Baby Wipes Are Recalled For a Reason </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-30 17:40:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So do you guys remember the whole I Found Glass Pieces in My Huggies Diaper phase? Basically, a lot of parents complained on all platforms of social media about how they could see glass pieces on the baby wipes they used on their babies. It ended up being a false alarm. Just chemicals they use in their baby wipes to clean the baby shit better. 

My name is Marshall and I was one of the guys that thought all of the parents freaking out were stupid as fuck. I mean. They really were. Who the fuck would accidentally put glass in millions of baby wipes? 

That is why when I found boxes of recalled baby wipes sitting in the middle of the local church I grabbed up two boxes before I walked the 2-mile distance home. 

You see, I live in a one bedroom apartment with 4 other people. John and Richard were my two friends from college. We all dropped out the first year of college. 

Zach was a guy I went to a bunch of parties with. He was around 35 years old but he never complained about how late we stayed up or how loud we were. Shit, I mean he was usually the one causing the most noises and stayed up the latest. 

Brian was a friend of Richard. I was a little skeptical of him at first, but after I realized how much of a great guy he really was I ended up becoming more close to him than anyone in the house. He was 22 years old and was always trying to find ways to better all of our lives. He would go out and walk around the city until he could come back home with a huge stack of job applications for all of us. 

The rent was 400 but we barely made enough to pay the rent as well as buy everything we needed for the month. 

We were close friends, but the last couple of days were the absolute worst. Fuck, I mean we couldnt even buy toilet paper, but that is what happens when all of made most of our money from odd jobs and begging on the street. We didnt all go out on the same day to beg for money. We took turns. The original deal was that while a group would beg for money the others would go around town and look for jobs. Brian was the only one that fulfilled both jobs.


That is why I lugged two boxes of foreign looking baby wipes two days ago. 

When I walked through the door I saw my four roommates sitting in the living room. I threw the boxes in the middle of the living room and started tossing them packs of baby wipes. Everyone blankly stared at the item in their hands except for Brian, he looked up at me and said, Dude. Thank you. I have gotten tired of having to take an ass shower every time I take a shit. I laughed and walked to my couch in the living room.

We all watched a couple of tv shows until around 1 in the morning. During that time we all used the baby wipes for our bathroom trips. 

Yesterday morning I woke up to probably the itchiest ass hole ever. I ran into the restroom and um. Well. I looked at my ass hole and saw that there were tiny bumps surrounding the hole. I tried pressing on a couple of the bumps but it just made it even itchier. 

Im not stupid, I knew the bumps came from the baby wipes. So for the next day, I didnt use the baby wipes. I warned the others, but none of the others had any kind of discomfort from the baby wipes. Well not until around 3 pm.

Zach ran out of the room with what seemed like a bloated sausage in his hand. It took me a minute to realize that it was his dick. Fuck. Before he could even tell us how much it hurt I knew. There were two huge bumps on each side of his deformed limb. He started screaming at me, What the fuck dude. What the fuck is going on? You. Dude. Youre fucking twisted. Youre fucking evil. You piece of sh- In the middle of his screaming one of the bumps exploded. 

Thin tissues hung loosely around the gap of what seemed like where the semen and urine traveled through to exit out of the body. Blood started to pour out of exposed flesh. He tried to grab it and stop the bleeding but the blood continued to come out of the gaps of his hands and spill down his fingers. I heard a soft pop come from inside of his hands and Zach let out a silent scream before passing out. I called the ambulance and paramedics rushed into our apartment about ten minutes after I made the call. When they placed him on the gurney his arms hung limply off the side of it and the tip of his dick barely hung off of his body by two small strands of tissue barely hanging on. 

Brian was with me when they took Zach away on the ambulance. He asked me, Yo. What the hell is going on? What the fuck happened to Zach?

After a couple of seconds, I responded back in almost a whisper, Please. Please. Man. Just. Shit. Please tell me that you didnt use the baby wipes.

Brian put his hand on my shoulder and said, Yeah man. I used it once last night, but this morning I found a couple of small bumps on my butt. I figured I should stop using them after that.

I let out a small sigh of relief and said, Yeah. There is something really wrong with these baby wipes. I found small bumps around my fucking ass hole. It sounds dumb, but shit dude, I knew that I shouldnt use it. I tried to tell the others to stop using them but they didnt listen.

Brian went into the room after our talk and I didnt see him for the rest of the day. 

Around 9 pm, John and Richard came home from their day out on the streets. Richard sat on the couch and started watching tv. John looked at me for a second before asking, Where is Zach? I told them about how Zach was now in the hospital. I told them about how his dick was fucked up from the baby wipes. I begged them to not use them. They looked at me while I told them everything. After I was done speaking it was quiet for minutes. Richard finally spoke up. With a voice slightly above a whisper, he said, So yeah. We will stop using those baby wipes. Fuck it. I made enough money today to get us a pack of toilet paper. What is Brian doing now? I shook my head and gave them a shrug before I got comfortable on my couch and fell asleep. 

I woke up this morning with the worst pain coming from my bum. I ran into the restroom and saw that there was now only one large bump poking out of my ass hole. With a deep breath, I poked at the bump. The bump was light pink with white dots floating around. I poked at it several times until the bump popped.

I knew that there would be a lot of muscle missing from that section, but I wasnt prepared for what I was about to see. Tiny clear worm-like creatures were latched onto my flesh. They were burrowing themselves inside of my flesh. I tried to grab them out but all I managed to do was tear more of my flesh out.

With strips of ass muscle hanging from my hands, I passed out. 

When I woke up it was around 8 in the morning. I was feeling really lightheaded but I managed to get to my couch and call 911. I dont know what happened to my roommates but when the paramedics walked through my front door I passed out again. 

I woke back up at the hospital. Im afraid to look at what happened to me, but I still feel something within me. Little fucking shits swimming inside of me. Fuck. Im writing to you guys. When baby wipes get recalled. Dont trust that shit. Theyre recalled for a reason. 

Like I said. There are thousands of unknown parasites eating my flesh and dwelling inside of my body. I dont know what happened to the others. 

Please let me know if you used baby wipes called Cleaner Than a Newborn. If you somehow survived this shit please let me know. I need all of the [help I can get.] (https://www.facebook.com/subject8631NoSleep/notifications/)
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-30 15:54:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> HAHAHHAHAHAHAHAHHAHAHAHAHHAA


 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-30 03:56:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Do it do it do it! ^do ^it ^^do ^^it ^^^do ^^^it </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-29 08:13:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Ohhh i liked "snuff" :c </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-29 01:52:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Haha it really is a good story!!! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-28 15:13:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Because we are totally obligated to completely force ourselves to write stuff that EVERYONE LOVES AND JERKS IT OFF TO. 

Always appreciate your comments on here!  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-28 15:12:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So yeah. Point proven. 

That story was removed and he deleted the removed post because it literally serves zero purposes to have your story up there. He can repost it now because it follows the new rules.

Maybe double check your points before throwing fingers at someone.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-28 10:22:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So um.... Usually they get reposted because the story was removed before lol and they had to fix the story and get the mods approval to repost it. Honeatly, the repost almost always does worse. Report it if you feel like it is wrong. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-27 10:07:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Here i am all happy and junk for hitting 5 months :c

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-27 06:12:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The next part is on my account page </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-27 02:45:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Wait i dont understand haha </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-27 01:46:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Haha thank you XD </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-26 22:09:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Oh my god i was mentioned  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-26 09:59:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> But if you need time to recover from something you have written then it might not have been time to write it out. Whenever i feel a little uncomfortable about any story i write i do one of two things.

1. Wait.

2. Drink alcohol.

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-25 19:35:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yepppp cannottttt write about that either actually </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-25 11:12:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yesssssss! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-25 09:17:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Btw. You're not the only one lmfao just ask my poor abused inbox. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-25 09:17:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Honestly, that is one of the few things I will never write about. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-25 09:11:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> No offense taken:) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-25 03:41:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If I'm on your team I'm gonna spray asian love juice all over my keyboard. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-25 03:38:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Pretty much everything i write has zero monsters in it. Probably because i am terrible at creating monsters. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-24 23:34:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Oh congrats on the marriage sir!

I'm in! I'm in!! Im in!!! 

Let's fuck shit up.

^^and ^then ^fix ^it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-23 03:11:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> pretty sure  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> My first attempt at a comedic horror. I'm not funny but damn it I really wanted to try XD </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-22 15:54:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The Serial Killer is Probably a Virgin </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-22 15:52:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So being a twenty-nine-year-old virgin is hard enough, but the fact that Im probably living with a serial killer has made things far more difficult for me. My name is Richard and I work as a security guard at a really creepy looking mental hospital. (No this is not where the scary shit takes place. Stop with the eye rolling or the super humid deep breaths youre taking to fog up your poor phone screens.) I live in a 4 bedroom house with my three high school buddies, James, Will, and Timothy. Yes, we are a household full of basic ass names. Dont judge us.

What makes us unique is that we are all pretty much the same type of person. Rejects since high school, socially awkward, and never went on a single date. I guess Will is kind of our hero. He had sex with a prostitute when he first graduated high school. I mean, we all kind of looked up to him until we found out that the woman came with an extra body part he never really expected. I still had a sliver of respect for him. He went through with it and was still pretty proud of the whole experience. Whenever any of us tried to make fun of him he would always respond back with, A butthole is a butthole. Dont matter.

Even though we had our faults and I never had a decent wingman for when we decided to go out to the club or the bar, I was completely happy. My parents kicked me out of my house when I decided to not go to college or the military. Three days after my graduation I saw my stuff sitting on the outside of my house. I tried knocking on the door and calling them but they ignored me. I grabbed my stuff and Will was the first one to offer me a place to stay in. 

Like I said, I was perfectly happy with everything. 

Yesterday, it all changed for me. I came back home after work and sat on the couch. I turned on the tv and started watching a show about pawn shop workers with really shitty attitudes. In the middle of the show, James walked in and sat down next to me. He tapped on my shoulder and when I looked over he said, So. Yeah. Check this shit out. He pulled out his phone and showed me a news article. It was about a guy we went to high school with. His name was Jerry and he was found in his apartment with half of his face melted off. His right hand was chopped off and shoved into his half burnt mouth. His genitals were mutilated, and he was still alive for three hours after he arrived at the hospital. The worst part of it all was that we saw him maybe three days before. He was bragging about how he finally managed to get a girl back to his place. He bragged about using his hands to please her as well as his mouth and well, his penis. 

After I finished reading the article I looked over at James and asked him if they had any clue on who did it. He just shrugged his shoulders and said, Shit if I know man. Some sick fuck. I didnt say anything back after that. He got up and walked into his room after sitting with me for a couple more minutes. 

Timothy came home around 8 in the evening. He didnt really have anything to say. He just gave me a nod and walked down the hall to his bedroom. Will came home around 11 pm with a woman. He introduced me to her. Her name was Grace. She was a coworker of his at Walmart. She was going to hang out with him for the night. I wanted to talk to the other two about the death of Jerry, but it just didnt seem like the right time. That night I struggled to fall asleep. The thoughts of Jerry along with the sounds of lovemaking coming from the room next to mine made sleep impossible. As the sun started to rise, the sound stopped, and I was finally able to fall asleep. 

When I woke up this morning I saw Timothy running as fast as he could to the front door. As I started to get off of my bed I saw cops walking past my doors. 

I walked out of my room and saw that they were walking into Wills room. Curious and concerned, I followed them into his room. Will was lying in his bed, but his face was deathly pale. As soon as the officers pulled the cover off of Will I saw that he was beyond saving. His body was on the opposite side of the bed. It was sewed to the face of Grace. His head was sewed to the body of Graces and cut into the stomach of the body Wills head was attached to said, College or Military.

The cops talked to all of us. After a couple of hours of all of us answering question after question, they left the same way they walked in. Confused and clueless as to what created this gory double homicide. 

Of course, I really hope it isnt any of my roommates, but I have my eyes on my two remaining roommates as well as the people that we have grown close to outside of our circle. 

I know most of you guys are going to tell me to move out or get a gun, but I really dont have any place I can go to. I dont have any sort of rental history so I cant get a place without an outrageous deposit that I do not have. I cant use a gun when I dont know who to use it on. Please let me know if you have any idea. I know no one is really an expert on this matter, but I feel like this is my best shot at getting any kind of answer. 

A lot of you guys may think that its my parents, but its not possible.

My parents died in a car crash [3 years ago.] (https://www.facebook.com/subject8631NoSleep/)
 
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-22 00:48:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> U/recordatus 6 minutes lol </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-21 10:01:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> oh man. I will wait on the update. Seriously. Thank you for sharing :D </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-21 09:55:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> One of my favorite series going on right now. Thank you very much for the update op </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-21 06:20:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> oh me too haha </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-21 06:19:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> hahhaha XD </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-21 06:04:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> is that a bad thing? :c </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-21 05:55:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> it's already up XD check my reddit account lol </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-21 05:38:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm good lol </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-21 05:25:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> 4 plus 3 is 7.

Okay. Now. 1.49 times 3 is 4.47.

Now add 7 to the 4.47 and what do you get?:)

11.47.

After 9.25 percent tax what is it?

12.53

Why doesnt it add up? Change to spare and within 13 dollars. This is such a small part of the story for people to fuss about and it is really getting quite annoying. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-21 04:02:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If they do not have the minimum comment karma it will not show up. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-21 04:00:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> -holds out 2 expired tickets to a 1980's cubs game </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-21 03:56:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> you are about the most attractive pumpkin i have seen </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-21 03:04:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> she's been doing it for a looooooot longer than a few months. but thank you for picking apart my series :) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-21 01:53:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> HEYYYY SPOILERS MANE  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-21 01:46:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [This is me trying to be like Glenn] (https://scontent-icn1-1.xx.fbcdn.net/v/t1.0-9/300196_304191869708477_1885883870_n.jpg?oh=391adffd1ad3dd2fd6a9234fce9eb23d oe=5987A837) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-21 01:39:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> *furiously pming kneeod* </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-21 01:37:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Drink soju and write. :) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-21 01:35:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Didn't say men;) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-21 01:08:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's better to be as emotionally detached as possible. That is why i didnt want to see her shoot up. That is why i couldnt help but stare at her on the bed after she died. I needed to win and if I tried talking to her it would just make me become more emotionally attached to her. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Final part of the series </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-20 16:47:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> I Will Either Face a Gruesome Death or Make Half a Million - Final </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-20 16:44:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [Part 1] (https://www.reddit.com/r/nosleep/comments/66373g/i_will_either_face_a_gruesome_death_or_make_half/)

[Part 2] (https://www.reddit.com/r/nosleep/comments/66ally/i_will_either_face_a_gruesome_death_or_make_half/)

Elijah woke me up this morning. When I opened my eyes he said, Your chances of survival increased. He pointed over to the right and I looked over and saw Allison lying on the bed. She was sprawled out on her bed, but she was completely pale. A needle and an empty bag were in her clutched right hand. Elise was already sitting up on her bed staring at Allisons lifeless body. She looked up and stared at me before shrugging her shoulders and walking towards the kitchen. Her arm was in a makeshift sling Elijah made for her, but other than her arm she seemed to be her normal self.

Elijah gave me a light tap on my shoulder and said, Come on. Time for breakfast. Eat up. We are starting the next challenge right as soon as you guys finish. I gave him a nod and walked into the kitchen. There were only two chairs at the table. I took a seat and slowly ate my eggs and bacon. 

In the middle of the meal, Elise cleared her throat. I looked up and she said, Well might as well learn more about each other before the contest ends.

I wasnt really interested in learning about her, but I nodded my head and said, Sure. Why not. I mean. It wont really change anything, but at least our memory somewhat moves on if we lose.

I dont know how much this conversation really means to everybody, but for me, it changed everything.

Elise: Im an artist. Well. I like to think I am but no one really appreciates my art. Not even my father. He threw me out of the house when I refused to go to college. So I lived out on the streets for the past year. I tried selling my paintings out on the streets but no one really appreciates art created by a bum. Its always been like that. Singers that could have topped the billboard charts die every day. The next Edgar Allen Poe dies on the streets with powder on their nose and dreams still captured in their still heart, but what do they get? Just judgment their whole lives and a sense of absolute loneliness.

Me: Yeah. Shit. I really wish I had something to live for like you. My family is fucked up. My mother and father kicked me out of my house when I refused to kill my grandfather. They wanted his money, but unfortunately for them, I loved my grandfather far more than empty promises. I dont really have a dream. I dont have anything that I am amazing at, but I want to get my revenge. I want to end their pathetic lives.

Elise: Wanna make a deal?

Me: What kind of deal?

Elise: If I win, I will make sure I end your parents lives. If you win, go to my house. The house I received when I killed my father. He was the guy I stabbed in the video. Just so that something I created can stand proudly on display in the house I forever sought acceptance in. Deal?

Me: Yeah. Deal. Um. Well. Good luck.

Elise: You too. Can I ask you an odd question?

Me: Sure.

Elise: Was I prettier than Allison?

Me: Um.

Elise: Never mind. My dad always told me that Allison was the prettier and smarter one. Turns out he was wrong about her. She definitely wasnt smarter. I was just hoping he chose the wrong daughter to favor.

Me: Wait. What?

She was silent after that for the rest of the meal.

Right after we finished our meal Elijah walked up to us and said, Follow me. He walked out the front door and we followed him. While we were walking, I couldnt help myself. I lightly rubbed Elises arm and she looked back with a small smile before grabbing my hand and held onto it as we walked towards the back of the house. 

Once we got to the back Elijah took out his phone and started up the camera. With a huge grin, he started speaking, Now our last challenge. Allison had an. Hm. An accident. We have our two final contestants left. Let me tell you. This has gotten quite emotional. Thirty minutes ago I overheard them telling each other their little sob stories. He sarcastically wiped a fake tear from his eye and continued. So. The last challenge. He whistled and snapped his fingers. His two helpers came out carrying a large bag and dropped it in front of Elijah. He winked at his helpers before continuing. Okay. So Allisons dead body is in this bag. The challenge is to eat as much of her body as you can. The one that loses will be held down by my two wonderful assistants. It is up to the winner how they will die. If the winner cannot take the life of the other person they will also admit defeat.

I heard a gasp from Elise as Elijah opened up the bag and revealed Allisons dead body. Elijah moved the bag out of the way and pointed the camera towards her body and said, Alright guys. Dig in!

I didnt hesitate for a single second. 

I knelt beside the corpse and started to bite down on her thighs. With each bite, I felt her meat tearing at the force of my teeth. The meat ripped off and landed on my tongue and I started to chew as fast as I could and before I knew it, a decent sized chunk was taken out of her thigh. Elise was screaming at me to quit ruining the corpse of her sister, but I ignored her and continued to stuff my mouth with as much meat as I could tear off of Allison. 

I started to feel sick to my stomach so I sat back. Elise was taking little bites off of Allison in between sobs, but I was unaffected. 
After my stomach settled I started to bite into her other thigh. It only took me two more bites before I saw Elise start running away as fast as she could. 

Elijahs helpers caught up to her before she managed to even get around the first corner. They dragged her in front of me and I stood up. Elise looked up at me with pleading eyes, but with a smile, I kicked her in the side of the head. I was this close to the money I wasnt going to quit now. She started to plead for her life but I ignored her as I knelt down next to her head and started to punch her head as hard as I could. 

A gun landed next to my leg and I picked the gun up. Elise looked up as the punches stopped. When she saw the gun she said, Just make it quick. Remember our deal. Please. Just make it qui

I shot her left foot. She started to scream and sob but I ignored it. I shot her in the other foot and she tried to break free out of their grip but she couldnt. I gave a little laugh as I shot her three more times on her back. 

She looked at me after sobbing and asked, Why?

Before I took my last shot I said, You made one big mistake. Allison. She was my sister. She was the one that my family favored over me. You thought you could make a lie that big and get away with it? Dont worry. I wont forget our deal, but know that you told the wrong lie.

I closed my eyes after I placed the end of the barrel on the back of her head. 

Before I pulled the trigger, I heard her beg me to forgive her. To let her live, but I have come too far to give it all up. With a scream, I pulled the trigger and I heard Elijah say, Its over. Jared. Its done. I dropped the gun and stood up. He gave me a small smile before the world went black.

I woke up on the same spot I woke up before the competition. I sat up and felt around my pockets. I found a card in my pocket. There was nothing on it except a black strip on the top of one side of the card. On the other side #6930 was written on the bottom right corner of it.

I checked it at the ATM. 6930 was the password for the account. I checked the balance and saw that I was 500 grand richer. 

I went to the local Walmart and bought the cheapest laptop they had. After that, I went to the cheapest hotel and rented out a room for 2 months. 

I keep thinking about Elise. How she struggled on the ground as I kicked and punched her as hard as I could, how she begged me before I shot her in the back of the head, but most of all, how she looked when she found out Allison was my sister.

Then I think about how she would have looked at me if she saw me standing by Allisons bed heating up the rest of the tar on the spoon then filling up the needle and releasing the drug inside of the vein prominently sticking out of her arm three times. 

Like I said. I needed to win. I have a mission to accomplish.

My sister was always favored by my parents, but it seems like they picked the wrong child [to favor.] (https://www.facebook.com/subject8631NoSleep/) 
   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-20 15:49:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> omgggg </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-20 10:27:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Wooooooosh </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-20 05:00:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> well i'm a fan of yours now! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-20 02:07:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You have not only insulted the story, but you have also reported it with a sarcastic complaint. I haven't banned anyone yet, but I am happy to announce that you are gone. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-20 02:00:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I love it and I love Smash Mouth. Well Done! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-20 02:00:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> XD </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-20 01:21:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> A lot of those authors dont care about upvotes. They just want to get their work out there. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-20 00:53:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Is there any way to reduce unnecessary complaints on the OOC? No. 

People do what they want. At least the authors are giving up hours of their time a day to entertain others. 

While the complainers try to bring down writers. 

Are you helping nosleep by complaining about something that is actually a huge part of NoSleep? No.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-20 00:05:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> 6 days ago then automaticaly 10 months ago.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-20 00:03:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What does that even mean? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-19 17:31:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I know. I was trying to make myself laugh by making a dumb joke. You gotta understand. I'm really stressed right now. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-19 17:29:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hello. I replied  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
