<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject7165</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-10 16:57:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> No, Lorne Michaels did not produce **The Blues Brothers** (1980).

That is a verifiable fact.  And think about it, where the heck would a young Lorne Michaels had the muscle and/or funding to jump on a major Universal Studios project in 1979?  

Anyway you might find this interesting: http://vhsrewind.com/vintage-cable-box-the-blues-brothers-1980/ </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-10 16:44:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yes but the OP was about Lorne Michaels as producer not whether the subject matter had been performed on SNL (that topic itself was addressed in my OP, however.) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-10 16:43:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Particularly Rick Moranis's character. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-10 16:40:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Lorne Michaels wasn't anywhere near **The Blues Brothers** (1980) and that definitely was an SNL movie. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-10 16:38:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You have a very good point regarding the tone and atmosphere. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-10 16:36:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Cool, hope you enjoy it.  I just found a copy at my local public library and probably will be walking over there to check it out this arternoon myself. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Do you consider Ghostbusters (2016) to be an SNL movie? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-10 16:30:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Do you consider Ghostbusters (2016) to be an SNL movie?

It was rather clever, since the original 1984 Ghostbusters featured a few SNL alumni, but the 2016 remake has many more:

Kristen Wiig, Melissa McCarthy, Leslie Jones, Kate McKinnon, Bill Murray, Dan Akroyd, Cecily Strong.

Of course this film isn't a feature version of an SNL skit but do you consider the 2016 **Ghostbusters** as an SNL film anyway, due to the cast?

Thank you. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-10 16:11:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> No problem.  I'm a Miami native as well.  I believe this new book was released in September 2016. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-10 16:09:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yes. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Is Carl Hiaasen's latest book, Razor, any good? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-10 15:49:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Miami Herald columnist Carl Hiaasen has been writing a novel about every three years since 1985.  I've read all of them except for Nature Girl (2006) and the latest work and agree with the general consensus that the quality of the books has dropped markedly since 2000.

Have any of you read the latest volume?  I myself haven't heard a thing about it "on the street" or word of mouth.

Thanks. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-09 22:46:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You do realize the legislature completely PWNT the executive on the recent budget agreement, right? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-09 22:44:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Indeed.  This is where the "the GOP needs to keep TRUMP (why Trump only?) in power no matter what" crowd falters innit. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-09 22:32:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Another "all opinions are sound no matter how unmoored from context or reality" person!  Oh goody! 

Or better yet "all opinions are sound no matter how unmoored from context or reality as long as they echo my own personal prejudices."

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-09 22:21:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Well it was bipartisan in that Sasse was staying on topic.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-09 22:21:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Agreed. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-09 22:20:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yes, I think we (republicans, fascists, conservatives, liberals, moderates, socialists) can all agree on that.

On a related note, what's up with all the swearing on this subreddit? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-09 22:18:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Intellectualism?

ROFL.

Get over yourself, you pretentious, longwinded "all opinions are sound no matter how unmoored from context or reality" jackanape.

Earlier I asked of you, "[c]an you even function in daily life?"  By now it's clear we have an answer to that query.  A resounding NO. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-09 22:17:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Do you?  If not, what makes you feel that way?  Is it because you cringe at the very thought that Trump supporters *exist*? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-09 22:15:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's sad they will do anything to keep him in power no matter what he does/says. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-09 22:12:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  I'm open to hearing about how you substantiate how independent opinion equates to an unreasonable inference

Because it's both hyperbolic and hysterical.  Both things that obviously appeal to you.

Got any other longwinded peabrained questions? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-09 22:09:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Oh, ok, thanks!  My bad. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-09 22:07:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Too much *coffee* . . . </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-09 22:04:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  Goddamn I love Amy. I hope she makes a Presidential bid.

Amy Winehouse?  I think she's dead, brah. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-09 22:00:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The statement wasn't even a reasonable inference from the OP.  It is you who are attempting to mislead -- not to mention being hysterically hypersensitive.  Can you even function in daily life? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-09 21:54:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> She's hot, brah! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> If Republicans dont stand up to Trump on Russia, theyre helping him undermine our democracy </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-09 21:53:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-09 21:50:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  It's sad they will do anything to keep him in power no matter what he does/says.

In no way did the OP state that. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-09 21:40:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So what do you think of this anyway?  Do the women who star in such clips actually *enjoy* what they are doing?  Or do you think it's just a performance for remuneration? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Cinthya Beating the Spanked Male Slave, Porn 09: xHamster </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-09 21:40:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-09 21:34:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That is really awesome!  I'm really happy, glad you liked it!! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-09 21:08:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Tell that to the negative nelly above. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
