<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject9284</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-10 01:13:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The IRS aka Democratic Hit Squad vs Republican Business Owners needs to go </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-10 00:11:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> SORRY IM YELLING!  WE'RE ALL JUST VERY EXCITED RIGHT NOW!

Carry On </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> TREY GOWDY - PLEASE MAKE THIS MAN THE NEXT FBI DIRECTOR! TREY M*FCKN GOWDY! </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-10 00:09:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-09 23:43:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Why is this still important today?

Because WaPo and the MSN is trying to push the narrative that Weiner's laptop, was overstated and that Comey is the fall guy for said over statement.

You can read Devlin Barrett's hit piece here:

https://www.washingtonpost.com/world/national-security/comey-misstated-key-clinton-email-evidence-at-hearing-say-people-close-to-investigation/2017/05/09/074c1c7e-34bd-11e7-b373-418f6849a004_story.html

(Sorry for the long annoying link, thanks WaPo!)

Notice the source 'says people close to investigation'.

Sooooo what would Comey have done with those other 13 devices?  Is it really Comey's fault that unethical Hitleray lost the election?  

Or was it that the American people had more respect for leaders who hand over their devices when subpoena'd because you have nothing to hide to begin with?  

Or maybe we were fed up w leaders who wipe private email servers and then claim no comprehension of the difference between classified information and non-classified information?

Maybe selling 19% of the US's Uranium reserves TO RUSSIA in exchange for $250,000,000 donation to YOUR FOUNDATION is a reason to vote for Trump instead, hmmm?

What would your devices e-footprint have said about those 'deals'?  

Stop blaming Comey.  As MJ once said 'start w the man in the mirror'. Hillary lost because of Hillary.

Keep positive Mr Comey!  And please help keep us safe from threats to the US, both foreign and domestic :-)


 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Hillary blames FBI Director James Comey for losing the election to Trump and the MSN pushes Comey's 'overstatement' of Weiner's Laptop containing forwarded classified information (it does) but let's not forget she DESTROYED - WITH A HAMMER - her own iPads, iPhones and Blackberry WHILE UNDER SUBPOENA </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-09 23:31:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-09 20:30:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I take this hand plus bodyguard.  When I hit level 3 it's pretty fun to lock down a hallway w the help of an ally or two </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-09 20:28:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Like in SW Lego </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-09 16:40:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Who was that asshole?  He ever hear of a sack tap? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-09 16:36:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If I were a legal student at this school I'd suddenly claim to have no documents  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-09 07:53:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If you're level 10, chances are it's magical.  Go with that? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-09 07:16:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> He was just about to be drafted  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-09 04:50:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Facebook is a demon.  Go outside and play instead </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-09 04:47:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Wait it wasn't an Honors AP Physics student? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-09 04:44:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> She's the Jackie of out time! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-09 04:43:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Turkey was once such a great Roman place.  RIP world </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-09 04:40:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I guarantee you Obama asked for the unmasking but Susan Rice will NEVER testify because she will end up in a weightlifting accident the morning of her trial, courtesy of the Alt-Left </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-09 04:38:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> And look!  It's Nancy Pelosi and Jesse Jackson sharing the stage with this criminal!   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-09 04:34:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That's taking things a bit too far, even for shitposting </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-09 04:32:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You know that's Mike Flynn sitting next to Putin, right? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-09 04:17:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Obviously Mike Flynn was unmasked.  That's household knowledge.

James Clapper, Barrack Obama's Director of Intelligence, admitted to unmasking today in the Senate Hearing.  As the Dir he has no reason to unmask anyone, unless it was for political leverage.

https://youtu.be/1VeX1KzbUzQ




 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> 68 Year Old Woman Slammed to the Ground   Violently thrown in a pool. Filmed by partygoers who were laughing at the attack. Police still searching for suspects. No help from 'local community leaders' </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-09 04:08:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-09 03:59:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> TWITTER IS OWNED BY Saudi Arabia!    </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-09 03:49:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The look on Trump's face at 56 - 60 as he looks off camera at someone and smirks as if to say 'can you believe this guy?' </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-09 01:24:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Obama would invite him to the White House and show off his school project clock . . . . Oh damn!  He did that already.  Fucking cuck. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-09 00:05:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Sadly, this fucker made babies.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-09 00:02:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Covering out planet w parking lots can't help though either </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-08 23:58:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yea, but my architectural point is that based on its current build the only want to add '20k' seats it to go up. 

And even then you're really far.  Also the concrete weight load might not be sufficient, or elevators need a complete overhaul to handle emergency exits etc.  

It's extremely difficult to 'just add 20,000 seats'.  The shitters might even overflow if the sewers can't handle the extra load. 

Yes, pun intended. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-08 23:55:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Exactly.  Maybe they had something happen the day before, or live far away and can only get to half the games etc etc </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-08 23:12:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> High Speed Internet is not an 'inalienable right' nor a 'truth we hold to be self evident'.

It's a product that takes trillions to make happen, and it shouldn't be cucked into giving it's owners labor away for free  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-08 23:09:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Because they aren't reeeeeeeeealy AntiFa.  They are in it for the LOL's and some money from G6 Man Soros.

Once they realized Because Consequences notice how their crowds are smaller and smaller  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-08 23:06:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I think Don Lemon is the most racists person I know </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-08 23:04:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If she wants to lose a job based on her beliefs, that's fine by me.  I think she's stupid, but I respect her right to make a stupid decision.  Because in America, if you want to go full retard, you can go full retard.  Just don't expect me to pay for your cell phone, rent, internet, car, car insurance, health care, health care insurance, govment cheese etc </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-08 22:46:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's there.  You have to remove the %5D from the end.

Copy and paste exact link </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-08 22:28:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> CIA or Spez?  Btw did you post a video yesterday showing immediate downvotes by posts that ht T_D? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-08 21:23:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Let's be clear about this-

The Hillary / Obama team is the group that ILLEGALLY unmasked non-relevant people for the sake of hoping to discredit them, who later on Obama thought might be part of Trump's team.

It goes like this:

Person A is Russian, and the Deep State is tapping every line of communication they have going on, 24 7.

Person A talks to 1,000's of people in a year.  Sometimes just to say 'here is idea A I have to sell you product xyz' that goes nowhere.

Some of those 1,000's of people were possible Trump team members.  The Deep State blacklines those 1,000's of people who are not relevant.

What Obama ordered his team to do was un-blackline and un-redact ONLY the potential Trump team members SOLEY to paint them in 'looks who's talking to Russia!' fabrication.  Oh and just so we we all crystal fucking clear- unmasking non-relevant people is HIGHLY ILLEGAL.  

Obama and his team should be in deep shit for this.

He didn't WARN about Flynn, he gave the order to illegally unmask him. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-08 21:09:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I love how ShariaBlue is downvoting your thread and our comments.  Fuck SpezCuckBots </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-08 20:43:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Twitter has gone full retard </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-08 20:35:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Gets invited to speak on Steven Cobert and Rachel MadCow about how his culture was inappropriately insulted and his feelings are hurt.  Poor murdering Muslims terrorist rapefugee </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-08 20:33:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Let's be clear about this-

The Hillary / Obama team is the group that ILLEGALLY unmasked non-relevant people for the sake of hoping to discredit them, who later on Obama thought might be part of Trump's team.

It goes like this:

Person A is Russian, and the Deep State is tapping every line of communication they have going on, 24 7.

Person A talks to 1,000's of people in a year.  Sometimes just to say 'here is idea A I have to sell you product xyz' that goes nowhere.

Some of those 1,000's of people were possible Trump team members.  The Deep State blacklines those 1,000's of people who are not relevant.

What Obama ordered his team to do was un-blackline and un-redact ONLY the potential Trump team members SOLEY to paint them in 'looks who's talking to Russia!' fabrication.  Oh and just so we we all crystal fucking clear- unmasking non-relevant people is HIGHLY ILLEGAL.  

Obama and his team should be in deep shit for this. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-08 20:29:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Let's be clear about this-

The Hillary / Obama team is the group that ILLEGALLY unmasked non-relevant people for the sake of hoping to discredit them, who later on Obama thought might be part of Trump's team.

It goes like this:

Person A is Russian, and the Deep State is tapping every line of communication they have going on, 24 7.

Person A talks to 1,000's of people in a year.  Sometimes just to say 'here is idea A I have to sell you product xyz' that goes nowhere.

Some of those 1,000's of people were possible Trump team members.  The Deep State blacklines those 1,000's of people who are not relevant.

What Obama ordered his team to do was un-blackline and un-redact ONLY the potential Trump team members SOLEY to paint them in 'looks who's talking to Russia!' fabrication.  Oh and just so we we all crystal fucking clear- unmasking non-relevant people is HIGHLY ILLEGAL.  

Obama and his team should be in deep shit for this. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-08 16:22:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Lambeau is built up to be an amazing experience, but part of its charm is that you're close to the field.  Adding 20k more would, at this point, require only building up, up and up </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-08 07:09:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> A red pill I delivered earlier - reposting here 

Health Care, Cell Phones, Food, Shelter, High Speed Internet, these things aren't a 'right' that The State should be providing free and clear to every person.  They don't just 'exist' to be handed out in perfectly equal portions.  Things have to be created by labor, effort and foresight.   All this is best produced with passion and relevant self determination.  None of which manifests in societies that value Need first over Freedom and Individual Passions to pursue your own life goals.

You want health care?  You want car insurance?  You want cell phones and high speed internet?  Go create something of value (like a job) and trade that value for what other people create (like medical services) on even footing. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-08 06:54:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I saw a post that said proof of Reddit downvote bots but it was deleted before I could even UpVote it.

Tried to find vid on YouTube and that was deleted too! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-08 06:45:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> JFK today would be called like Marine Le Pen 'Far Right' or 'Alt Right'.

He was likely murdered by The Deep State </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-08 06:39:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Almost all purely socialist countries can't really afford anything.  Their currencies are out of control.  In communist Venezuela you need to bring shoeboxes of cash to buy bread.  This happened in Europe in the past.

I agree.  Out HC system is messed up.  It needs serious overhaul, but change like that should come from a market disrupter like Alphabet and FB upset the advertising industry.  Like Netflix, Hulu and HBO On Demand upset the Cable Industry.  Like Pixar and Dreamworks SKG (Spielberg, Katzenberg, Geffen) upset Disney Animation.  None of the great innovations in non-war have come from The State.  

Healthcare should be no different.  Healthcare should be let loose, to innovate, not to be gripped tighter by the all powerful Federal Government. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-08 06:08:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That's because we rely on insurers to set costs AND people in the US will sue for like no reason.  Malpractice is a HUGE determining factor in HC Cost.
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-08 06:04:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Use it all you want.  Spread it like wildfire. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-08 02:56:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Health Care, Cell Phones, Food, Shelter, High Speed Internet, these things aren't a 'right' that The State should be providing free and clear to every person.  They don't just 'exist' to be handed out in perfectly equal portions.  Things have to be created by labor, effort and foresight.   All this is best produced with passion and relevant self determination.  None of which manifests in societies that value Need first over Freedom and Individual Passions to pursue your own life goals.

You want health care?  You want car insurance?  You want cell phones and high speed internet?  Go create something of value (like a job) and trade that value for what other people create (like medical services) on even footing. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-08 02:50:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Username Checks Out!  

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-08 02:49:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> After a valiant ten minute struggle! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-08 02:46:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Because driving a truck down a Bastile Day celebration and running over innocent people is . . . supposed to be accepted? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-08 02:39:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I guess yeah, which is pretty much what a LOT of T_D is too.  The MSN labels us and Marine Le Pen as Alt-Right or Far-Right as an attempt to discredit our logical way of thinking.  While labeling Far-Left Socialists like Macaroni as 'Moderates' in the hopes of brainwashing independents into voting for their crazy State 1st People 2nd ideas. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-08 02:10:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Maybe.  The problem is once France straight up becomes Syria w 100M refugees flooding in like locusts, they won't likely need to execute terror attacks.  Breed out French and game over.  

RIP a once great culture.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-08 02:03:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hollywood should just make Hollywood and stay out of politics.  

Politicians should just manage laws, and stay out of culture. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-07 20:31:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> To be honest though, an explosion like that, so close, would kill  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-07 20:28:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Wow.   So I'm guessing the 'Defeat' code had already loaded, and the Victory Code loaded and ran as well.  Since the Defeat code was loaded and ready to launch there wasn't a check for 'if this then don't run' one more time </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-07 20:24:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I am rooting for him to fail because he want to import Syria into France and allow truck drivers to annihilate people on Bastile Day.  I am against the spread of ISIS and sleeper cells under the guise of refugees.  This is Macron.  So yes, I absolutely want him to fail. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Annnnnd what about the missing ballots? Torn up ballots? Double Macron ballots? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-07 20:21:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-07 20:11:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thank you yes!  I wasn't trying to fact check whether it truly was or wasn't the 'first' detective / mystery novel.

Really it was to highlight some worthy books and see if others had some similar recommendations. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-07 16:28:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> More like a novel w a narrator since if memory serves me even after his death he continues to tell the story </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-07 16:24:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You also have to be an early spawner because there is an alliance token somewhere when the match starts, for Walker assault at least  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> "Islamic Terrorism is just part of every day life you know? Get used to it" says Macron. Fuck Off says France! BTFO influencing our elections Obummer. Vive La France? Then don't vote for stupid! </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-07 09:57:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-07 09:52:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Let em defect.  Build the wall! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-07 09:49:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Because they (The FBI) finally got the go-ahead to do so.

This is why I'm glad Hillary didn't win.  All else equal, she was complicit w her husband and staffs indiscretions.  And that to me is accomplice.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-07 09:45:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> And physiotherapy, education, and child / young adult mentoring too so we don't have to worry about home or national defense to begin with! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-07 09:42:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Ooooh, one more I wanted to share was 'The Meaning of Night' by Michael Cox.  It was his debut novel and at the time sold for a record 500,000 (for a debut novel).

Sadly the author died 3 years later but scrambled out this 600 page masterpiece.

I fully intend to buy the follow up novel as well. Hopefully it's as gripping and imaginative.

Thanks for the recommendation!   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-07 09:20:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> He was the guy from Milwaukee right? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-07 09:18:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Objectives are key!  Hero Token spawns are semi-randomized so that no player can lock down or camp it </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-07 09:17:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I LOVE vehicle tokens, but only when my team is actually DOING objectives.  Because ruling the sky, is pointless when you got no YWings </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-07 09:01:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I am fascinated by 'Mystery Novels' set in the grand 1800's where wit and intellect ruled over tools of science and technology.  

A great read of this is Wilkie Collin's 'The Moonstone' and the incomplete but fantastic 'The Mystery of Edwin Drood' by Charles Dickens.  Sadly Dickens passed away before finishing the murder mystery but it was his attempt at dipping his mighty pen into the field as well.

Any recommendations for a solid Victorian Mystery Novel that's fun, suspenseful and on par w Dickens, Collins or the like? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The First Mystery Novel (with a 'detective' as the main character) </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-07 08:28:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-07 08:24:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Bleak House - Dickens Masterpiece.  It's on par w Wuthering Heights and Jane Eyre, but personally I liked Bleak House even more than David Copperfield, which is also great.

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-07 08:21:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's a great read.  One of the best Roman historical novels ever scribed </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-07 08:20:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yes it's the same Claudius.  He had a speech impediment but was a genius in both leadership and writing.  He built, I believe, the most aqueducts of any Roman emperor, even more than Hadrian.  

{spoiler} 

But even I, Claudius, could not appease the insanity that was Rome (Washington DC) level of corruption and died I think to his wife's (and cousin maybe too) murderous charm </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-07 08:13:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That's it!  Yes the Lake Cook Road sign was what confused me.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-07 06:34:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I bet you he wins by a landslide as much as I want an actual landslide to take him down, this media blackout is abhorrent!  This is why FREE SPEECH is a huge part of MAGA / MFGA </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> This is a scene from Tom Cruise's Risky Business (still a classic) but I'm trying to figure out what exit this is his parents take outside Chicago! Any Chicagoian's recognize it? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-07 05:50:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-07 04:13:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Wow that's awesome!  I kind of like it when games have massive glitches like that.  I remember a few DotA, LoL or Wow glitches where jumping = flying or a certain spell would cause massive glitch in the matrix.  It lightens the mood and reminds us all to have fun first! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-07 04:10:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That's probably my problem.  I'm guessing I unlock after firing and assume it's 'fire and forget' but from now on I'll treat it like 'laser guided missile'.

Thanks for the tip!  Appreciate your help! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Macron, the far left globalist pro-terrorist 'it's just part of life' offshore banking meth using crazy socialist must be stopped! </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-06 18:40:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Pepe loves Marine Le Pen! Vive la France! Vote Marine Le Pen! </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-06 18:24:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-06 18:10:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Have you seen Macrons teeth? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-06 18:08:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Didn't this guy die?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-06 17:58:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> ABC, CBS, NBC will all die in 20 years, dinosaurs of Fakeness </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-06 17:53:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hahahahahah!  Nice find </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-06 17:52:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Flying in BF is two ships flying in a circle until one breaks away only to be shot by the one that didn't flinch first </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-06 17:50:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah I think so!   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-06 17:48:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Oh yeah.  I hear the Beeeeeeeeeeep, then fire.  They go straight.  I think it's server lag.  Don't have the issue w guns though </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-06 17:42:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Marine wants to Make France Great Again

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-06 17:41:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> In God We Trust </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-06 17:40:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This should be the #1 goal.

All posts lead to Le Pen
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-06 17:39:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Ok so this is saying Macrons team faked the docs and the rebuttal docs? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-06 17:33:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Only Marine Le Pen can save France </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-06 17:24:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Do you take The Emperor and sit on top of the ship ?  

Or can you win w any hero? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-06 17:20:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Highest kill is 2 so I assume sarcasm or you might have thought points were kills lol? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-06 17:17:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The EE4 got a nerf too.  Jump pack and bacta are the same though  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-06 17:12:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Wow you got 31 of 31 diorama?  I stopped trying to get 10 Hero Hunt wins </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-06 17:08:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Dang!!! Nicely done.  I got too frustrated when I had to keep remaking my decks to fit the challenge.

If say there were three or four decks instead of two maybe I'd have stuck w it.  

Gratz you though! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-06 17:07:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yes this.  If you pick a mode, of a DLC, you could be waiting for a while.

I wish the Walker Assault from DLC was added to the Walker Assault rotation in the WA mode too. Even if people don't have the DLC then at least it mixed up the players some, or have an option to queue w all modes </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-06 17:04:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm not sure how you didn't take more damage.  I get blocking works, but if they aim at your feet, etc 

Gratz Vader though!! Beast mode. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-06 17:00:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Re watch the scene in The Force Awakens where Rey and Fin escape Jaku in The Mil Falcon.  They scrape lots of sand, bounce off things, and slam down hard quite a few times!!!! 

Yet we touch leafy shrubbery and it's the end for that ship flying 700 mph </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-06 16:58:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> My missiles almost always miss, even if I have 'lock on tone'.  They just fly straight as if no ship is present.

Totally agree w spawn camping, it's lame. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Only Marine Le Pen can save France! Vote Marine Le Pen this Sunday! Vive la France! </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-06 16:55:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-06 16:49:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Of everything they overcame together, the one thing they couldn't beat was childbirth.  Everything society threw at them, handled.  Making a baby on their own, disaster.  What I didn't understand is WHY Hemingway chose to kill her off.  The story was about the war, however fucked up war can be, everyone did their best as individuals.  Still having friends, falling in love, etc etc.  then she dies, for like no reason.  I wondered if Hemingway was recently scorned when writing it and wanted to kill love in his story to reflect the pain in his own heart.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-06 16:44:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The last paragraph of the Gatsby is amazing 

So we beat on, like boats against the current, borne back ceaselessly into the past

But leading up to (spoiler!!) Gatzbys death it seemed that every character changed 180.  And of course I didn't want Daisey to stay with Tom!  Fuck him he's a lying cheating asshole!  She should have left him.  

I know it's thematically fits.  Gatsbys name is derived from gun, etc etc. but Buchannon has him murdered by pushing his lover's husband towards Gatsby and then doing nothing afterwards.  But again, just wanted the good guy to win

Edit : me fail English?  That's unpossible! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-06 04:27:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The Great Gatsby
For Whom the Bell Tolls
Farewell to Arms (I think at the end of this one I actually said out-loud 'Fuck You Hemingway' and closed the book. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-06 04:20:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> 2 . Self Confidence  -  Breaking the Chain of Low Self Esteem, by Dr. Marilyn Sorensen Ph.D.

It's actually more of a work book with introspective analysis and thought provoking reflection.  You are in the right place and hopefully others have great recommendations on your other items too! 

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-06 01:12:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Guess I'm used to reading time left to right not right to left as in on yours.  All good though.  Thanks! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-05 23:55:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> How'd you make the pattern? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-05 23:54:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I can almost here them saying 
'here I pass it to you'
'no I'm good' 
'ok me too' </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-05 23:50:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Love the brigading by ShriaBlue paid schills and bot whores (allowed by CucksPez even though strictly against Reddit Policy).  Have an UpVote! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-05 23:47:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Wow that's awesome!  Gatsby is about the only book I've read many times.  Ha!  I guess your devotion to it fits the OP List then.  Have you read The Magus as well?  Or The King Must Die? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-05 20:48:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I didn't know Scientology was a religion.  I thought it was a huge wealth transfer company </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> MFW tying to think up MACRON LIES quick to cover up offshore holdings FALSIFIED UNDER OATH to the French people. Viva Le Pen! </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-05 19:40:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-05 19:04:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If he HAD used the condom he wouldn't have kids, and therefore he wouldn't be annoyed.  Yes I assumed his gender. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-05 19:03:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Nice WW2 joke! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-05 17:44:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So why give them more power?  Why not less? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-05 17:43:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I felt it was too contrived.  Aside from the stellar ancient history lessons, it didn't feel more gripping than your typical thriller / slasher novel.  (No offense) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-05 16:41:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> 6 mana for 6 damage and a 5/5 hasted creature.  Need a lot of RNG to make it happen but it's a nice combo! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-05 16:37:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Look I agree that the US Insurance Industry is completely fucked up.

The fact that we even have to have it is messed up.

Here's how insurance works: they calculate the 'odds' of something happening, then give you worse odds.  It's like a casino for life events, where no matter what, you lose. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-05 16:30:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If only that website was readable in mobile app </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-05 16:28:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So military costs should be really low too?

And taxes?  Super low?

Nothing the US Gov't has ever touched ends up being cheap because of cronyism.  The Gov't is made up of people and those people award contracts and those contracts are almost always to their buddy.  

This is why communism doesn't work.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-05 15:49:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Single Payer is where there is only one company (The US Gov't) and all insurance firms are banned? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-05 15:41:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I wish many snipers would go play other games </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
