<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject751</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Did the Amazon book store description just spoil A Scanner Darkly for me? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-08 13:11:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I had heard some good things about A Scanner Darkly and had no idea exactly what it was about, just that it was thought provoking. So I went to Amazon and read the description, as I do with all books, and it states in the third sentence that [Potential Spoiler](#s "Bob and Fred are the same person").

I feel kind of unenthused to read this now that I feel a major plot point, that seems to have a lot to do with themes of the book, has been spoiled for me.

So, is this as crucial a "twist" as I am assuming? Is this revealed fairly early and is not a crucial reveal moment? I want to enjoy this book but I'm not sure I can force myself to read through it knowing this. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-02 14:54:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Maybe, but that doesn't really change the fact that he incited people to do something. Obviously this wasn't what he wanted, i doubt he would want to endanger people, but he invited the risk; I think that makes it reasonable for Twitch to take action against someone who would do that. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-02 14:36:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The way I heard, as some one who hasn't really been following this, is that he gave away his gate number and egged on the watchers to "get him" or something like that. I.e. inciting this to happen. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-19 23:28:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Here's my ticket!
Fingers crossed! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> I have so many questions, but I guess they boil down to when did Japan lose its collective mind? Did '45 do something to their air? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-05 09:26:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-02 18:06:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> As someone who hasn't played ranked: why shouldn't I be using mobafire? I find the guides are generally useful when I need a quick idea of how to play a champ. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-26 17:54:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Do you think the stammers were shooting.... vertically?

Oh god, I just got chill thinking about it </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> When you know all the people on the track are jaywalkers </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-31 21:17:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-23 05:22:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> For some reason the first thing my brain went to was pokemon, e.g. stun spore, sleep powder from strange fungus on his arms, or if you want to play up the "aged adventurer" he could have some fungi a la shriekers or purple fungus from the dnd monster manual.

Maybe vine whip or razor leaf.

Maybe some form of regeneration? Like photosynthesis but more magical

And maybe he can swing it a certain way to cause a strange noise that summons nearby woodland creatures. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-15 11:53:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So this is what happened to Hannah Montana? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-11 02:36:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I feel like they might be trying to lead into a point later where Steven, like with centi, fights against "what has to be done," and it will make him question how many gems "have" to be shattered. I think it really foreshadows how the crystal gems can still be just as dogmatic as the homeworld gems. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-09 09:42:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I think the best remedy is something that can get the jump on them.

e.g. blink dogs, ankhegs, bullets, shadows.... any thing that they have little chance of seeing coming or are very fast. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
