<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject8335</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-08 16:04:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hey, a lot can change in 4 days! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-08 07:31:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Haha true. I'd label it more a "sigh of relief" than a "victory" but sometimes you take what you can get I guess </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-07 14:04:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> From this article, I'm not sure if Trump's aides are American villains or vaguely temperate forces preventing even more evil/chaos </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-06 08:11:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Certainly you may be a US citizen, but a person's mindset and opinions on things like healthcare, for the vast majority of people, are highly informed by the culture and environment where they grew up. If you ask someone in Italy or France if they consider healthcare a right, almost *everyone* will agree that it is, just as if you ask folks who grew up in a place like Laos or Chad, they will almost be confused by the question as they are not taught that it (or many other things) are considered "rights." 

I'm not sure of course, and have no idea how long you've lived in the US, but I suspect people who grew up in Armenia, like other parts of West Asia, would have similar viewpoints as you, just as most people who grew up in Canada, where I'm from originally, generally think that the debate as to if healthcare is or is not a right is patently redundant. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-06 06:59:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> According to your comment history you're Armenian so maybe it's safe to say your opinion doesn't really reflect current American sentiment. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-04 15:51:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Agree. If she showed even an ounce of compassion for Offred, perhaps, but thus far she is not only complicit but unnecessarily cruel. It will be interesting to see where this is taken; she is shown to be manipulative and exploitive in the book plot and though it is certainly possible the show will eventually portray her in a different light and redeem her somehow, for now, it looks like she's truly not meant to inspire sympathy. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-04 15:39:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You're not alone - a lot of fans were underwhelmed and disappointed with S6. Though the series could have ended fairly neatly and logically with S5 (or S4 for that matter), I would go so far as to say S6 was better than S3, 4, or 5 as seasons in themselves. I found it creative and, for lack of a better word, just more mature, with honest story arcs for the main characters dealt with both compassionately and sharply. I wasn't a fan of the finale exactly, but the season as a whole I really loved. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-04 09:22:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> command r what what </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-04 09:20:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> How dare everyone be alive and well after all those hours of tension </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-04 02:47:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Guys, *relax*!!! This is not the same coat. Sharon is wearing the classic "London-via-Dublin" style of this jacket, with somewhat randomised stripe patterns. Nikki's version, known in fashion circles as the "Fully Actualised Mid-West Ex-Con Girl" version, boasts more contrasting stripes and is made of faux fur in order to avoid the chi-disrupting use of animal products.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-04 02:35:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> These look delicious, but I'm at a point in my life where I only want to enjoy eating octopus made in specifically Chinese styles. If only there were an app for that :( </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-03 15:25:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Extremely important point. Literal readings of many Old and New Testament passages are more misogynistic, racist, and oppressive than anything found in the Koran or any other major religious text. To pretend that, culturally speaking, a country like the USA is light years away from such implementing these ideals is dangerous and naive.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-03 11:27:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Very disturbing comment history. Guarantee he's not a doctor. And yeah, he made some comment about how he could never "accept" trans people, has multiple comments serving as Trump apologism, said "Men are definitely the underprivileged sex in the first world and only idiots can't see that lol", calls people "retards" routinely, etc. etc.  Much liberal </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-03 04:04:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Fair enough. The intent of the sub when it was created about 6 years ago had been to discuss the interpretation and practise of vipassana in the tradition of Goenka-ji. It's really been the past year I guess that other practises and traditions under the "vipassana" moniker have been discussed here too with some frequency. I was definitely a bit concern troll-y here, but if the sub continues to morph into something different than its original intent, well, I guess that's up to the mods and community to either stop, allow, or encourage. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-02 10:26:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Speaking as someone who adores this show and the previous 2 seasons, the end was a bit cheesy. If they wanted to show the dead it could have been done more authentically, like the last seconds of their "real" lives. Teo would have been interesting to see especially. I wasn't as annoyed as with Taylor's big epiphany face or Richard Cabral's mid-sentence cut though in the previous finales. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-02 10:16:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hi Philip :) This sub is for vipassana specifically as taught by S. N. Goenka. You said you x-posted to r/thaiforest, but you may want to try posting to r/meditation as this really isn't the right sub. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-02 02:32:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I hope so. But they apparently made the choice to cut out her mother's character so I don't know what to believe! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-30 15:44:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Fwiw ME Winstead revealed that Hawley told her her character was straight up in love with Ray and she should play it that way accordingly. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-30 15:36:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I think so, though I'm wondering if they'll play it out that he's not fully conscious of it. He's just *wayyy* too emotionally invested in Emmit's shit. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-30 15:34:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I think many of us lady-watchers made the connection before the reveal.The period-mention earlier was Chekhov's tampon. Plus she had pulled her pants down, which was another huge hint once one were to wonder "Is that lipstick?" </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-30 05:57:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It was genuinely painful to watch the majority of the audience's stone-faced non-reactions. Many of them were clearly uncomfortable, though they seemed to warm up after he got away from the more explicitly darker stuff. Regardless, this was some moderately bold material and he did great. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-30 05:52:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Cecily Strong was the first millenial host. But yeah, he killed.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-30 05:09:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I wouldn't be surprised if they don't go into her past at all. It would be a bit of a shame if they didn't somehow reveal that she'd played some type of role as an advocate for "traditional", anti-feminist values, and played some part in having Gilead come about, as this was a major aspect of her book!character. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-30 05:03:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I think a lot of the success of her performance in this role has to do with how the type of writing and the character are just better suited to her abilities than Gilmore Girls could be. It takes a talented actress to be able to hold her own next to Elisabeth Moss, but Alexis nailed it. I love The Handmaid's Tale.

On a very superficial note, I got a huge kick out of hearing her say "fuck" and "shit" compared to Rory's constant "Oh Jeez!"s </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-29 16:59:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Unless you want to hurt his feelings on multiple levels, probably don't. Your classmate does not want to hear he has dead-ringer hair for a woman who literally made headlines in 1995 because of her notoriously bad hair(cut).  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-29 16:51:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The beds weren't harder at the centers I did my 2nd and 3rd courses at. AFAIK centers generally have more comfortable arrangements for old students. 

I actually struggled *less* with both the schedule and diet the 2nd time around - I think because my body and mind were like *Oh, yeah, I remember this* so there was no shock to the system really. And the tea-only at 5 wasn't a problem.

Like someone else suggested, you will want to re-start your practise before the course begins, but I guess that's just in a few days! Also, many find their 2nd course is *not* like the 1st in any number of ways. You will struggle with different things, and elements that felt "easier" or more difficult the first time round may be diametrically different this time. It's best to let go of any expectations. 

In any case, have a good course :)

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-29 16:38:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If you really don't know, they're probably fairly equal in terms of what may be "best" for you. Most people have a helpful hunch and naturally gravitate towards what's most suitable for them, based on their past experiences with either small, medium, or large children :)  Personally, I thought I wanted to teach high school, did for a short time and then got a job at a middle school, which I, to my surprise, *hated.* I went back to high school and never looked back, but this year was made to teach a Gr 8 class for the first time in 8 years. And I love it.

Listen to your gut, but be open to trying different things, and keep your  mind open - you will evolve, and your teaching preferences and talents may too. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-29 16:19:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It is horrifically sad. Shockingly (or not?) same-sex relationships are either severely restricted or illegal in dozens of other countries, including most of Africa, the vast majority of the Middle East, and also most West and South Asia. Several countries also impose the death penalty on same-sex intercourse. 

Every horror in this book and series is real and happening, just in a different (and sometimes not-so-different) form. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-29 16:09:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The jolt was a smart choice to be sure. I guess I mainly took exception with it coming *back* after Offred realising Ofglen's been replaced, after her "fuck." It seemed something less catchy and fun would have been more fitting for the credits. Maybe something with a quick beat, but dark. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-29 16:04:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I interpreted it as a good ol' fashioned "fuck you" from Offred. She wanted it, but was showing she wasn't some subservient slave graciously accepting a tiny scrap of a treat. I think it was the "good girl" comment about her that clinched her decision to spit it out and leave the rest in sight. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-29 16:00:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I *really* was into the idea of seeing more of Alexis Bledel in that role. She was completely killing it, and Ofglen (Senior)'s role didn't feel complete. Hope she comes back. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-29 15:59:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I felt like "Dont' You" was way *too* fun, especially the 2nd part as the credits rolled. That was a somber af moment/reveal, and after Offred's "fuck" something darker, if cheekily dark, would have felt more fitting for me.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-29 15:52:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I have no clue but I clicked on this thinking from your title it would be about the usage of "Don't You" by Simple Minds! (which has roused highly ambivalent feelings in me) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-27 14:29:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I wouldn't say he's "unintimidating" to Trump at all. Trudeau's no intellectual genius, nor is he an aggressive bully, but his poise under pressure and gentle but firm and logical way of explaining his and Canada's positions would make Trump feel very threatened in another, more subtle, and more important way.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-27 14:19:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Maybe we should have a spoiler tag option. For those of us who have read the book, it will be *very* painful not to compare! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-27 14:17:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah, I think some of the more dramatic elements they'll throw in pretty quick to hook the viewers. It makes for better "tv" where in the book, Atwood could build a lot slower. Nick got pretty suss pretty quickly too, and there was a lot of character development with Moira. They're almost definitely angling Offred as more rebellious than she was portrayed in the book as well. Love it so far!!! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-25 15:30:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> so in character </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-25 15:27:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Reminded me of [this shot](http://imgur.com/a/i4arZ) of Jesse and Jane.  (Hopefully not foreshadowing that Kim will die of a drug overdose.) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-25 12:53:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Just a shadow of its former self. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-25 12:50:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If it's a question where the asker seems to have good intentions (i.e., not just trying to get into some type of debate), I usually say that I believe that Jesus was an incarnation of God, but certainly not the only one. Sometimes I elaborate on my belief that God reveals Himself to different cultures/people in the form that will allow them to most easily connect or that they can best "understand." </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-25 10:05:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I just looked it up and apparently everyone was under the impression that he was the North Korean ambassador's son.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-25 09:03:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Apparently it was all very hush-hush and neither his classmates nor teachers knew, and were under the impression that he was just some over-privileged  student from South Korea (like several others at the school). </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Globe editorial: Donald Trumps first 100 days, summed up in one interview </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-25 06:10:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-24 15:38:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You don't need to choose any one path "for the rest of [your] life" just now. You're, what, early 20s? Try some different things that attract you, but stay focussed on the search for truth I would suggest, not chasing after "spiritual experiences" or "awakenings" as ends in themselves. 

It seems you may have had a habit of jumping from one spiritual tradition to another - like following Christianity intensely for 12 days, then quitting, in spite of an awakening experience. If you're expecting quick enlightenment like from being hyperaware of everything (not sure what that means tbh), it will almost definitely not happen.

The *overwhelming* majority of 13-year-olds who try vipassana will find it too difficult unless approached in the right frame of mind and with the right intention. That you couldn't sit still for 2 minutes is not unusual, but is also a sign that you would benefit immensely from a regular practise. A regular mindfulness practise will absolutely beneficial. If you're up for something a little deeper and more intense, I would look into doing a proper 10-day vipassana course if you are so inclined. Check out www.dhamma.org for more details/info.

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-24 12:26:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Were you in China (or nearly any East Asian country) they would say the reverse. I am living in China and have several friends with mixed race children, who hear *constantly* from people how "white" their children look - comments on their skin tone, how "big" their eyes are, even their body types! North Americans, believe it or not, tend to be *more* subtle.

In any case, you can gently correct people, by saying something like "We find she has features from both of us" or "Actually, we find she looks more similar to me/my mother/her grandmother/whomever." You can be more direct, as well, saying "To be honest, it hurts a little to hear that as we think she is a beautiful mix of both of our features."

Explicitly racist comments, like derogatory comments about her eyes like you mentioned, are well dealt with by gently saying you or your family find that word or phrase offensive. You may choose to briefly explain why if you're comfortable. 

*Most* of these comments, like how she looks Chinese, come from a place of simple ignorance rather than bigotry, and a kind simple explanation can help them understand how their words can offend. It's up to you, though, and if you feel more comfortable letting it go or nodding and smiling curtly then going about your business, that's definitely your prerogative. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-24 06:17:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The fact **35%** think he is doing a "good" or "great" job is truly unbelievable. Sweet jesus </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-24 02:24:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> A moron might do this in, say, Palm Springs. Where these houses are, by the Santa Monica pier, summer temps generally range from 65-70 degrees.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-23 16:55:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That is interestingly specific. Why that particular prescription? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-23 16:17:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Probably, yes (unless like another.poster said it was a hot vinyasa kind of thing). For a short period, I used to do 12 sessions per week, with 1-2 hours of class per session. If you can encorporate some home practise during the week that would be much better - otherwise you may feel quite stiff come saturday AM and set your progress back during the week, each week. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-23 03:01:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> There's more to it than a binary war on drugs / legalisation for all drugs. Some countries, like Sweden, have hard drugs categorised as "illegal" but do not have anything like a "war on drugs" where that devotes vast resources to things like prosecution and incarceration, focussing more on education and rehabilitation. As a result the hard drug use and trafficking is, by European standards, relatively low and frees up incredible funds for other, more useful gov't spending. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-22 16:14:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I believe this is a general title that's tossed around a lot for her and bannon, whereas Jared Kushner and Stephen Miller have the official "senior advisor to the president" titles </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-22 16:06:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Haha true! Better than Trump as father-in-law though. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Senior Trump adviser Kellyanne Conway can't understand why Democrats won't help to destroy Obamacare </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-22 14:09:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Origins of "Hobbit" Species Discovered </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-22 13:02:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-21 16:23:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> While this appropriately neckbeardy, I'm mostly confused as to if this sad vehicle is on the ground? Is it on a flatbed truck?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-21 14:26:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> the ~~leaks are~~ story is real but the news is fake </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-21 14:18:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I guess it depends on your definition of "famous". He and Hamilton are **FAMOUSSSS** now. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-21 14:10:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hey Atmabodha - This sub is for vipassana specifically as taught by S.N.Goenka. You may want to try posting to r/meditation or r/buddhism. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-21 13:33:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That occurred to me but I dismissed it because it just seemed so awful. It does makes sense though. Heartbreaking. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What is up with Gabrielle's injuries in E06? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-21 12:22:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> There's Clair's mentioning how she "did it to herself" but it's weird that we didn't actually see that before the shot of her running her hand under water. Also, with Nicky having kind of smacked her earlier, and the weirdness of Clair's phrasing, I'm wondering if maybe it had been from a type of altercation with Nicky somehow? That seems odd, but so does it being self-harm. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-20 14:01:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I very occasionally will read the last 10 pages or so of a novel before reading. I'd done this after hearing a really radio show where the guest was advocating this as a technique. The idea behind it was that with many novels, the reader spends an enormous amount of energy wondering and speculating about "how it's going to end" when they would enjoy the book more, and ultimately get more out of it, if they already knew the general ending in advance. The few times I've done this, I have found it gives a richness to the narrative and also creates a different kind of intrigue, as it is the most intense form of dramatic irony. It alters the reading experience, though not always in a bad way. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-20 12:03:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Sensitive flowers? Maybe. I may be an overly sensitive flower because my great-aunt and -uncle were killed at Treblinka. Anyone who propagates that Jews "had it coming" like in that quote above is morally vile. And those who think being repulsed by such ideology is being an "overly sensitive flower" are probably not far off either. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-20 04:20:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thanks! I watched *Killin Them Softly* last night. It was great. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-20 04:19:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Ew. That's horrific. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-19 12:06:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Roald Dahl? like what? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-19 12:05:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Aww... Poor River Yamuna. I was there a couple of months ago and thought it was lovely. That smog tho </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-19 10:57:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What old shows would you recommend? I haven't seen any old Chappelle really. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-17 02:53:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Ew. Nothin' says funny like killing and raping children. Beyond tasteless. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-16 15:23:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I thought I was the only one! I find it to be the most revolting and weird feeling. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-16 14:09:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> On the absolute contrary, this show has mostly *been* about failure, struggle, and starting over, for basically all the characters. Hannah has had intermittent successes and failures and admittedly caught a great break with this teaching position but looking at the others:

* Shoshanna had a massive struggle finding the "right" job for her before she got the job in Japan - from which she was laid off only a few months later. She also seemed to have nothing solid for a while before her "current" job.

* Marnie was unsuccessful at interviews and ended up with piecemeal temporary work (hostess, barista, Soo Jin's assistant) until focussing on her career as a definitely struggling musician who couldn't even make rent.

* Jessa has never had stable work that lasted more than a couple of months.

* Elijah, as a character, had the raw talent for the gig he got, but he seems to have been on the brink of poverty for years after graduating.

* Ray worked for Hermie for what could easily have been 15+ years before Hermie died.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-14 05:26:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I loved this article, and this writer's perspective. 

So many of the criticisms of this show that I've heard revolve around the idea of *Girls* being some massive statement piece about what life is exactly like for intelligent, fairly creative 20-something white women in the modern urban western world. This is the story of a few unique characters on unique journeys. It's not so easily categorised, and nor are its characters or the themes it illustrates. I am going to miss it immensely. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-12 02:43:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Would it make her head explode to hear Drake is a bi-racial Jewish Canadian? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-10 13:39:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm 35. The book was definitely meant for teen-aged readers in terms of the writing and characterisation (Asher has been open about that too). The series I find kind of a mixed bag. I don't think the show was *intended* for teens - it's way too graphic, too harsh, too dark for them to be the core demographic - but it also has a tone that's not fully "adult" either. There's an immaturity to the script, that makes it seem sometimes like it's meant for anyone, sometimes for mature audiences, sometimes for high schoolers. Maybe because Hannah's voice is so authentically teen-y, and it's though the script and even dialogue was written by a teenager, not an adult, in many ways.

That said, I will recommend it to most of the adults I know who, well, like good TV. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-10 07:27:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> No comma splice, no. The actual issue here is your verb tenses. You should say:

* However, as my medical experience grows, I could suggest simple advice and encourage them [if you're reflecting on what could happen in the future]; or

* However, as my medical experience grew, I could have suggested simple advice and encouraged them [if you're reflecting on what happened in the past]
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
