<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject388</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-02 21:31:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Ha-ha what a great post, almost as great as it was last week thanks for bringing it back OP you reposting piece of shit </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-31 07:32:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I can't stop listening to the original Australian cast of Mary Poppins and I don't know why </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> I have no idea why anyone ever gets out of bed. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-31 07:27:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-04 11:41:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah I just wish the lizard was here tho. I used to have dogs but she took them when she left. If it's a lady lizard Imma call her Penelope and if its a dude lizard Imma call him Reginald </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Update: my (soon to be ex) wife wanted me to reverse my vasectomy to cover up her infidelity. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-04 11:02:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm gonna be honest here, I'm not doing well.

My lawyers have told me I have about a 100% chance of keeping the house - it's been in my family for  generations, and our (my) family name is wrought into the gate. Apparently these facts matter. God bless Texas.

I get too drunk too often now. I lost the love of my life. Things don't seem worth it.

Anyway, yeah, I've started divorce proceedings (luckily there's no custody to worry about - if I had done this a few months from now, things would be very different).

I love her, and I hate her for what she's turned me into. Luckily, my boss (remember Dan from the last post? Dan's the best.) has given me some extra PTO so I can deal with all this. If I had to work right now, I don't know what I would do.

In related news, she's keeping the literal bastard,

I dunno if any of this makes sense I've been drinking. Also I bought a tegu lizard online which should get here soon.

Tl;dd; fuck her, I've got a house and soon a lizard and no kids.

Update: that bot that deletes shit because of flair can go fuck itself in the asshole

Update 2: For fuck's sake, stop PMing me about redpill. I'm sad not pathetic. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-11-21 07:11:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This has to be satire. Right? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-11-12 04:09:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Bethesda games never let you join *every* faction. Like in Skyrim, you can't be both a Stormcloak and in the Imperial Army. Or a Vampire Lord and part of the Dawnguard. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-11-11 20:30:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I mean, *you* could do that if you wanted </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
