<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject9880</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> A touch of love. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-08 21:41:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> She was so beautiful. My love, my life. 
Laying in front of me, peaceful and still. 
I touched her bare skin gently with my finger tips, she stirred only slightly. A small gasp escaping from her lips, red and full under the light of the moon.

It was a warm night here, my lover was wearing nothing and I only a shirt. There was a slight breeze blowing across us, through the trees and kissing our skin. I could almost trace its path, just by watching the goosebumps rise across the pale skin of my partner. 
Our naked forms were sprawled across the soft grass between trees, we had both needed a rest from tonight's activities. I wasn't worried about our privacy, my land was large and secluded far from prying eyes.

I felt rested, and although still wrapped in a haze of sweat and adrenaline, I wanted more. I was beginning to feel the familiar electricity of excitement inside of me, and I couldn't help but gaze downwards and admire the prone form of my companion. Her breathing was calm and her eyes closed, no doubt dreaming about some other peaceful place. 

I traced small circles across her stomach with my fingers, watching the shadows dance across her belly. I loved watching her breathe, her ample chest rising and falling with each small panting breath. Her stomach quivering in turn, she was starting to stir and awaken to my touch more fully.

I was eager to rush, but I knew that I mustn't. I licked my lips, and moved my hands across her hips. I loved every curve on this woman, truly I was lucky to catch such a prize. Other women had passed through my life so quickly, fleeting and brief. The woman before me had already outlasted all of the others, she was a true fighter. 

I pulled myself into an awkward kneeling position and adjusted my shirt. My love was still slowly coming too, so I placed my hands back onto her body. With one hand on each side of her waist, I pulled her closer to me, bending her knees upwards so that I was kneeling between her toned legs. Her arms remained stretched out above her head, she looked so peaceful. 

The view I had was incredible, and I could tell that she was just as ready for round two as I was. 

I leaned forward, over her body, And planted a kiss firmly onto her lips. A small sigh escaped from her mouth and I couldn't hold back. I propped myself above my lover on one arm, and used my free hand to caress her firm breasts. Hearing her moans was exciting me more and more, each breath felt like a whisper right into my soul. Urging me forward, pushing me on.

My hand travelled lower and lower, tracing invisible pathways downwards. Until I reached it, the warm and inviting source of my arousal. I could feel the warmth, and I was more than eager to explore further. 

I lightly traced my fingers around the edges, i tapped and I tickled feeling the wetness of her body. My fingers were coated in her already. My lovers eyes were open now, half lidded and blue like balls of glass.

I heard a small whisper, I paused to listen again. 

"Please"

A please? I knew she wanted me, and this. I paused, and then decided to give her what she desperately needed. I plunged a finger deep inside of her, causing her to violently shudder and then I quickly added one more. I was staring right into her eyes as they flew open, I saw the pain on her face as she started to scream.

The thin slit across her stomach was my own handiwork, just big enough for my delicate hands. I removed my fingers from the warm and wet wound, and lifted my fingers to my mouth. 

I dripped the taste of hot iron across my tongue, and laughed as my lover tried to struggle free of her bonds. I removed my blood stained shirt and wiped drops of blood from my breasts. Her eyes weren't quite so glassy now, which means she still has some fight left.

It was time to tie up my hair and call for my husband. We were both ready for him, although only one of us beautiful ladies would be able to walk away from tonights experience.

"Shall we have some real fun now my love?".  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-29 08:48:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You got lost somewhere that would have kept you. But no name guided you home, you're lucky and he protected you :) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-29 08:39:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That's a sizeable investment to just shoot.. unless they have lots of daniels already in progress. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-18 00:09:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I think I need to reread this series, I cannot work out how it fits together. At all. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-12 05:01:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'd worry about the survivor... might be pissed at being left for dead!  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-06 08:46:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Amazing. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-04 09:04:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Or he could have just kicked them out of the school, but whatever works I guess xD </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-03 10:53:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Well, it wasn't your fault op. But I can understand why you feel bad. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-03 02:41:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The thought of my family dying is pretty fucking scary. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-02 09:42:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hat was he studying for ten years then? What was in the syringe? Or was he just boing bonkers?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-02 09:27:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Amazing amazing amazing, I loved this tale, although I'm so sorry that you went through it op.
Your writing is absolutely outstanding, I was hooked.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-02 09:06:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This is the thing that scares me the most, a random act of horror. If you were in some 'haunted' location and scary shit happens it's something you could see coming.
But a random disappearance from your home? Damn. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-21 08:55:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Umm. You are aware that a dog is not a human, right? There is zero need to be jealous of a dog you fruit loop. I mean, all that's going to happen is you losing your boyfriend because of your irrational behaviour.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-21 08:48:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Why was your wife always in the kitchen? Why was she always so tired to look at? Why did you fall asleep immediately every day? Why did she say run? 

How did she cook omelettes for breakfast if the stove was broken? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-21 08:45:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> But what if your wife doesn't support your choice? Or she believes what the news says? Don't lose your family!  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-17 10:41:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm looking for mr right... but honestly, the idea of meting someone and having a knife pulled on me is kind of a turn off. It's really not the best foundation for a relationship. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-13 10:21:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I don't understand, what debt did he have to pay?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-09 21:25:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm not sure that I understand? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-07 01:09:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I would love to adopt mittens, I enjoy looking after older kitties. I'll keep the talking a great secret!  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-04 09:41:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I adore the idea of this. Some kind of creature that can sniff out evil, or guilt maybe and deal a twisted justice. 
It sucks that they have destroyed your life as well though :( </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-24 20:19:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It kinda sounds like Timmy or his dad(someone in his family) is doing this. No idea why they would want to target you though? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-15 07:05:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Maybe she should have given you a heads up first. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-14 08:45:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I would never let you have internet ever again. Oh man.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-14 08:36:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Basically though, I up voted for the rhyming title alone. It's so pleasing to say. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-13 21:19:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I missed that line somehow, had to reread for the sever years part. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-13 03:20:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Umm, a more pressing question... is someone gonna nuke Hawaii? That would be bad.
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-12 06:04:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I want to visit the library. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-12 05:53:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What is the title in relation too? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-12 05:31:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> He had lots of foster families, are you the only ones he sent these gifts too? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-12 05:22:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm guessing it's just because he is a malicious entity, he doesn't really care about the deals.. just the torment.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-08 11:56:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Keep the penny, it's good luck. 
Angels don't have to be fallen to visit humans, and even if they are fallen that doesn't mean that they want to harm anyone. You've been given a advice, nothing more. He didn't grant you any special favours, just cheered you up.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-08 11:43:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yup, bury that talisman with him. I'd also get one for yourself, because honestly it seems like you're about to suffer the same fate.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-06 09:13:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I get that, but what actually happened? What does it mean?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-05 09:08:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Im not sure that I follow. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-05 09:02:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Uhh, you were a last minute voter but you're also voting early? Which was it? 
Also, if this cult is serious, they shouldn't be using facebook to organise their  Meetings etc. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-01 23:39:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If the parents knew that this could happen, and the rest of the street, it was super irresponsible to trust a lone child with this. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-01 12:25:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You literally had a bowl full of snickers? As in, snickers chocolate bars? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-01 12:07:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I really hope that there is more to this! I'm loving it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-01 08:24:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Well, honestly that narrative was missing. I guessed that it was coming to spice things up, but there was nothing extra in the story to truly hint at it.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-01 08:22:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Speaking as one myself, and for the good of the whole.. It makes more sense than asking for the healthy. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-31 04:44:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Well, it's not the worst trade off. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-28 22:56:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So, its tied to the Garnet.. but you don't have the garnet anymore? Plus, why did it kill the extra people in your neighbourhood? Will it still kill violet?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-28 13:38:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I thought this was going to twist, and be about racism or homophobia... But nope. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-28 00:45:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> My son just got turned into a bass. Better not really even mention how that made either of us feel, or what happened with them after we legged it. Lol. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-14 22:14:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Well, you're a dick and you do deserve it. But your writing is superb. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-13 23:41:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> At least you now know that he is real, just under a different name. I hope that your new husband believes and understands you when you tell him that Darren is never welcome near you!  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-13 08:31:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It sounds like the cage is helping to create those creatures. A posse should just swarm the woods and try to kill or capture them, before too many get made. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-11 11:12:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I don't really understand what happened? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-11 06:46:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Everything is real on nosleep. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-11 06:42:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I can't imagine how hard it must be to deal with hallucinations, having to doubt your own mind like that. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-11 06:37:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Amazing, the twist was actually really good and unexpected. Bravo. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-11 06:27:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Isn't this a symptom of OCD or something? I remember vaguely seeing it on TV once, the one that I saw was opposite though. The guy was always so scared of bodies/body parts being inside bags that he couldn't ever open them. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-07 09:57:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The "shutters should hold them out"... that's oddly specific?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-07 09:54:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I don't know how you make mayo, but the meat and cheese is from the hitler cows.. so he thinks it doesn't count as eating real animal products. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-07 09:41:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So we're families really leaving for new towns, or where they being soapified?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-07 09:33:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> How can it be hypnosis, if the person is aware and able to shout warnings? These text messages just turn people into robots, or something.... the writing is really cliche.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-28 00:11:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I hope that you said thank you for not being late!  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-27 09:03:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Are we sure that the hiker isn't the fellow in the water? That was my first thought to be honest. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-27 08:46:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Well, that was really something else. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-27 00:55:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah, I agree with the other comments to be honest. Leaving like that was the worst reaction, assuming that the switch was real... You wouldn't have been blamed for her murder I don't think.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-17 06:24:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What on earth did they do on that holiday?! Well, at least it saved their marriage. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-15 23:46:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Sounds like intrusive thoughts, but I don't know if you can get them while asleep. It's a sign of a variety of mental health issues, such as schizophrenia and it seems to be linked with high stress levels in your life. Might be worth seeing a doctor to talk about these things.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-10 05:06:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-10 05:04:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Games are meant to be fun. So far the only outcomes of this are bad for the player, and it sets you up to lose. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-19 22:16:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> No, glasses. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-19 22:16:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Why did he take him home in the first place then?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-19 22:08:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> True, when you put it like that ... I do feel stupid for asking.

But up until the reveal I was just a bit confused, like, even if it was caller ID the young girl wouldn't be the bill payer.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-18 10:16:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> How did you know olivias name?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-14 10:49:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Wait, the mum summonsed you but you got stuck in the doll? Did the mum kill her daughter? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-14 10:25:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Come on guys, you know what they mean lol. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-14 10:20:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> you have to wait 24 hours between posts op.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-14 10:19:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Maybe something moved in to the barn, after you'd been living at the house for a few years. Some creatures or entities aren't bound to one specific place. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
