<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject3700</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-10 14:10:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What is wrong with being gay?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-10 14:09:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Lindsey Graham or John McCain only has to say impeachment, they still have heft in the GOP, and both have more popularity than Trump.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-10 02:55:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Those fuckers will never take Oregon.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-10 01:44:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> We need to be prepared for Trump to send a tweet to his followers to rise up and take control of critical infrastructure.  

We are wading through the Rubicon right now.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-10 01:42:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Maybe it is time for individual states to have their own foreign policies.  The Rust Belt will sell itself into slavery to Russia and the West Coast can open up free and fair trade in Southeast Asia because we are adults.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-10 01:38:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Vegan cheese is good substitute for the function and mouthfeel of pencil erasers.  Arugula is good in a spring salad a few times a year.    </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-10 01:31:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Trump has fucking staged a coup.  

The Jr. Hawaii Senator says we are in a [full blown constitutional crisis](https://twitter.com/brianschatz/status/862083890646835200).  

Trump has no legitimate claim to power now.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-10 01:29:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Apple slices, walnut, and pork pizza = good, come at me.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Sen. Brian Schatz on Twitter: "We are in a full-fledged constitutional crisis." </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-10 01:27:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-09 23:04:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Maybe some Trump voters I know would finally watch Trump speak and realize what an idiot he is.  

There is a subset of Republican voters who voted for Trump and refuse to watch any video of him, yet they still blindly support him.     </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-09 22:58:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Trump must be keeping Steven Bannon around so he can point at him behind his back and say at least he is not Steven Bannon when moderates are in the room.  

Only about 50% of Bannon's horribleness is getting into policy.    </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> We Have Seen Times This Dark BeforeHeres How We Fought Back </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-09 22:52:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> New Film, 'Go For Broke,' Explores Formation of U.S. Military's Most Decorated Unit </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-09 22:22:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> How Trump's EPA cuts could gut Oregon environmental programs </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-09 22:01:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-09 21:47:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> GOT.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-09 21:38:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Pineapple on pizza with salty meats is great though.  Sweet toppings are underrated.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-09 21:35:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Just like Trump and Roger Stone did.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Kevin Spacey on 'House of Cards' in Trump's America </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-09 21:34:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> No Longer Driving a Cab, a Syrian Writer in America Focusses on His Fiction </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-09 21:00:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-09 20:58:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Clear some room on your pull-out couch for Oma and Opa, and learn how to change diapers.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> GOP Senators Signal Theyre On Board With Big Medicaid Cuts </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-09 20:39:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Customize Your Cannabis Experience With Terpenes - Wherever You Are </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-09 15:30:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> In North Carolina, Pigs Dont Fly but Their Feces Do </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-09 15:17:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-09 14:28:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hahaha, if Google think they can displace their own Android OS they are delusional.  This would be like trying to compete with Windows 95 with Netware 3.1.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-09 14:26:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> FFS, date people outside of Downtown and SE.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-09 14:25:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So true because so many.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-08 23:08:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> DemocracyNow.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-08 23:07:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Centrists can't even win an election.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-08 20:35:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> No, of course not but currently TWC2 has enough people in enough time zones that they can run platoons 20-24 hours a day.  No outfit on NC or TR is doing anything close to that nowadays.  

It was not too long ago that NC and TR both had the same thing going with major public platoons and population was much more balanced during primetime.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-08 11:41:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm not in TWC2 I don't even have a VS toon. 

People bitching about public platoons can either lead them or stop whining, it is getting old.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-08 11:13:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> No, TR and NC having too many small private outfits is the problem.

Man up and lead public platoons.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-08 09:03:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Didn't France behead the Vichy government?   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-08 09:02:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=uq-gYOrU8bA </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-08 08:13:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> TR and NC need more pub platoon leaders.  That is the problem.  TWC2 has two platoons going 8 hours a day.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-08 08:08:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Why are Clinton supporters so Unamerican?   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-07 22:12:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Meanwhile, by 2018, the whole West Coast will likely have tuition-free community college.   

The country can't be like this.  We need federal leadership to move forward.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-07 21:46:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Americans are Americans, it is not like they are a different species.  They will respond to honest economic populism but that means raising taxes to pre-Reagan levels.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-07 21:42:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> 30-40% of rural America is still liberal.  If the Democrats want to win those seats back, they need to look back to when they last had them.

The New Deal era Democrats had rural and city America.  Maybe it is time to spend some dough on bringing up the living standards of rural folks again.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-07 14:05:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It was too late.  Pennsylvania was already Trump country when Clinton finally noticed it.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-07 14:04:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> They would participate in them and do in open primary states.  In closed primary states 40-50% of voters are not allowed.  

The reason is that the Democrats and Republicans are de facto the only parties in the US who have political power.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-07 13:44:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Clinton supporters like Clinton deflect all blame for their actions.  Shameful.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-07 13:43:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thanks for chancing all of our civil rights on trying to elect a crooked grandma.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-07 13:41:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Only takes one minor nuclear conflict turning major.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-07 13:38:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Only 50-60% of Americans are registered Democrats or Republicans, depending upon the states.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-07 12:52:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Because Clinton wanted a popular vote win she spent nearly 200 million in solid blue states instead of visiting the rust belt.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-07 12:52:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Clinton still isn't for single payer, Jill Stein has been for 20+ years. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-07 12:50:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You mean the same primary process that chose Kerry and Gore?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-07 12:49:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> No one is arguing for a pure single payer system.  The only nation that has tried that was Taiwan, and they stopped.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-07 12:19:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  We have apple picking jobs up here in Oregon where you can make 100-160 a day and there ain't many white folk in those fields.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> How Mountaintop Mining Affects Life and Landscape in West Virginia </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-07 10:56:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-07 10:49:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah look at Clinton she couldn't even win the White Women's vote.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-07 10:48:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> No, we are that tribal.  98% of human evolution took place before cities.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-07 10:42:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Why should voters pay for primaries they can't vote for?  If Democrats want to have closed primaries they can pay for them themselves.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-07 10:33:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Putin has direct control of the go ahead for any foreign interference campaigns or he is a puppet.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-06 20:44:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The Democratic party never should have supported a center right candidate in that district in the first place.  There was no reason.  

The DNC enabled Lieberman because he got a lot of donor cash, and then he sold them out.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-06 20:42:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Because centrists are fucking cowards.  Remember the Centrists helped form the Vichy government with the Fascists. Pelosi and Clinton would do the same.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-06 20:06:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It is what the fascists did in Vichy France.  They used to send teenage gangs to do their dirty work too.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-06 19:35:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Rural America once united behind FDR for the New Deal, and help hold supermajorities in the House and Senate for nearly a decade.  Honest economic populism is the only sure way forward I see for the Democratic Party.  We need a New New Deal.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-06 19:13:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So long as the cowardly centrists stay the fuck out of the way this time.  Looking at you Lieberman.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-06 19:12:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Part of the problem that Democrats have with getting donations for these candidates is that Democratic Donor class is concentrated in three cities, LA, DC, and NYC.  So the vast majority of fundraising occurs here, not in the heartland, and not in the interior west.  

Meanwhile Republicans are fundraising like gangbusters in those regions.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-06 18:15:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You are vichy.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-06 17:27:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Can you imagine the world if everyone lived to be 250?  

Imagine if the Baby Boomers are still in control in 100 years.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-06 16:43:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The altright is a 5th column that must be struck from America.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-06 16:13:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The US government should've arrested and wiped out the remaining Mormons after the [Mountain Meadows Massacre](https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Mountain_Meadows_massacre).  Mormonism is a plague on the Western US.  Everywhere they go they espouse hatred of other Americans like LGBT folk and Atheists.  Mormons are some of the most Unamerican people in the United States.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-06 16:01:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I am starting to think either we go down the road to regional governments like a North American, European, African, Asian unions in our lifetimes or we face another major world war.  

No reason we can't have Mexico and Canada in the same union in 50 years.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-06 15:57:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> They wanted to ban pre-existing conditions, all of them, at the national level.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Emergency Doctors Are Breaking Tradition to Oppose the AHCA Compromise. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-06 15:39:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-06 15:36:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Sanders is a Senator, Clinton is an unliked grandma.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> 'Out with fascists': egg thrown at Marine Le Pen </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-06 11:39:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-06 11:06:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hillary Clinton was hot garbage, she couldn't even clinch the white women's vote.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-06 09:43:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Georgia was the test run over a decade ago.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-06 09:42:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This is why sites like 4chan should have been nuked from orbit earlier in their existence.  

It is utter manchildren were are dealing with.  

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-06 09:35:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Cradle to grave education.

We should be engaging our seniors with courses.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-06 03:23:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=kwckonqbeos </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-06 03:10:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [Do you believe in the Union?](https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=ZL-5uyp44WA)  

[Bonus](https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=-eEMit4pljs#t=44.789104). </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-05 23:50:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> We should start dressing in Union soldier uniforms.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-05 23:46:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Not for long.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-05 23:46:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Look at the TD posting of this story, they are fucking delusional.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-05 23:45:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Can Pence lactate from those manboobs?   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-05 22:56:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Reapportionment must occur or polarization will continue, it last happened in 1929 but they didn't touch the Senate, they talked about it but chickened out.  

We can't keep passing the buck to future generations on foundational problems in our constitution.  That is the sort of thing that leads to civil war.  Civil wars still happen.  

Fixing Citizen's United is a band-aid.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-05 21:52:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The Apportionment rules have provisions for the Senate, they can be changed.  

Without that foundational change Trumps will keep happening.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-05 21:00:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Eventually California will have 100 million people and Wyoming still will have less than 1 million.  

You honestly think that each of those states deserves two senators?   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-05 20:30:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Two senators from each state no matter the population means the rural states will always be overrepresented in the Senate, always.  

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-05 20:20:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You watch too many movies.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-05 20:20:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Those rural Senators aren't there because city voters voted for them. 

I am not sure you know how the Senate works.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-05 17:41:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Of course not, that is why we have more than two political parties to choose from.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-05 17:34:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If you have health insurance.  What about those who don't?   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-05 17:33:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> 60% of medical spending in the US is already through medicare/medicaid.  It is only a 40% gap.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-05 17:31:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I know, instead of making a liveable wage an issue that gets broad support let's go balls to the wall on trans bathrooms in 2018.

Hire me DNC.     </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-05 17:14:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It is the entire MO of third-wayism.  

Look at Blair and B. Clinton.  B. Clinton passed more of Newt Gingrich's Contract with America than the Democratic party platform.  Why would I vote for that?   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-05 17:04:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Centrists have pet issues but they waffle on too many others. 

Obama and Clinton both were latecomers to too many LGBT rights.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-05 16:50:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Of course not, we all believe in some sort of mixed market economy but we need a liveable wage.  Something Obama never campaigned on.  

Centrism/Third-Wayism is identity politicking paired with analytics to determine policy.  It is voodoo politics.  I am not talking about being an honest moderate.  I'm talking about not taking a position on something until the polls tell you to do so and sometimes wedging on both sides of the issue with no clear policies at all.  That isn't smart to me, that is cowardly.  
   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-05 16:44:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So in 100 years you think the US will still not have a baseline single payer healthcare system?   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-05 16:43:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Let's break it down.  

Corporatism is siding with capitalists over labor.  

Centrism is waffling on issues so that two groups think you believe two different things. 

I can't support either ideology.    </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-05 16:38:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Bingo.  It is playing lip service.  It is smart consensus-building politics.  

Non-smart politics is thinking enough women will always vote for abortion rights when some House districts are 70% pro-life.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-05 16:35:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So the US will have this fucked up ACA/AHCA abortion in 100 years?   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-05 16:24:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Of course they have the resources, they are the CIA.  

They don't spend all day plotting on how to take out friendly leaders FFS.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-05 16:23:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Any plan expires, are you implying that the CIA can predict the future?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-05 16:21:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Either the legislative or executive branch should have at least tried.  There are millions of people employed by faith institutions in the United States.  They deserve contraceptive coverage same as you or me. 

That being said, if Democrats go big tent, they have to accept pro-life Politicians again.  All of those were thrown out in the 1990's.  That is the Realpolitik.  The Republicans have openly pro-choice politicians, they are the bigger tent on that issue and it is a 40/60 wedge issue and it is not going away.   
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-05 16:09:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I am sorry but are you implying Obama was hard on the banks after they fucking crashed our economy?   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-05 16:07:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> 100's.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-05 16:07:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Because it would be a waste of resources, shit on the ground changes too quickly.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-05 16:06:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Obama is a corporate centrist, of course he did.     </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-05 16:06:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Pragmatism in governance and pragmatism in voting are two separate things.  

Pragmatism with Obama saw him allow an anti-choice amendment to Obamacare stripping workers at faith institutions of contraceptive care.  

That is not acceptable to me.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-05 16:04:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The CIA plan shit on the fly, that is what they are paid to do.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-05 16:03:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Agreed on that.  We should elect Congress   the President by national popular vote.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-05 15:42:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> No way.  A single leak would doom them.  

They might have a few cooked up ones for some egregious dictators like KJU but they don't have one for the PM of New Zealand.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-05 15:39:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Moderates need to be more pragmatic and back progressives and conservatives.  

FFS, Carter was a Conservative Democrat and I think anyone here would rather have him in the White House than Trump.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-05 15:21:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I think you only need 250k for an entrepreneur visa or whatever it is called, and that can partly be in loans if memory serves.  With that you can do 6 years or whatever for citizenship.  Just open a small store.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-05 15:08:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Both of them were supported by authoritarian followers engaged in cult worship.  The rest of America loathed both of them.

They were the most unpopular candidates ever in the history of the US, and they ran in a race against eachother.  

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-05 14:56:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Because his identity politics called his supporters strong.  

Clinton called her supporters fragile and weak, and said only she could save them from the big bad Trump.  Well, she lied.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-05 14:54:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Sounds like identity politicking, which fails more often than not.  

One or two big populist goals are what win elections.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-05 14:53:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Elections work fine here in Oregon.  

We got free community college, you don't.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-05 14:27:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Nope, she spent over a billion dollars to lose.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-05 14:26:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hillary Clinton talked about them and then lost to a fascist.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-05 14:26:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Blumenauer, Merkley, and Wyden all won in my state.  

Want to know why?  When mail-in voting was initiated it pushed the cowardly centrist democrats out.  Higher voter participation in primaries kills centrists.  

We need national mail-in voting.        </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Czech Scout on her viral fame: it's important to fight against fascism </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-05 14:23:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-05 14:20:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Centrists are the ones losing elections today.  

So are you advocating going left or right?  Hard liberalism was Obama, it was mediocre at best.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-05 14:19:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So?  You don't win elections on fragile identity politics.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
