<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject8314</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [Homemade] Vanilla naked cake with fresh strawberry cream </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-10 05:27:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-15 23:17:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I am also an Akita owner and volunteered with the Akita rescue from which I adopted my dog. I have seen at least two VKH bears go through this rescue and both are living fulfilling lives with caring owners. I don't know specifics as far as cost of care, or what to expect moving forward, but do know these two are doing well. Yes, they are both fully blind, and one has completely lost all his pigment. Head over to /r/akitas, I remember seeing at least one redditor on there with a VKH bear. Best of luck to you both!  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-13 21:14:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> R D. Not research and development, but Rob and Duplicate. Network with other sports teams of a similar size who do rely on sponsorship money and get copies of their MOUs/Sponsorship proposals/etc., to give you a good framework for where to start. Contact teams through social media in geographical areas outside your own. I did this for the last nonprofit I worked for when we were delving into sponsorships, and haven't had an ask to a similar organization in a different area go unanswered.

  In my experience, the biggest pitfall we encountered was setting our initial offerings too low, which screwed us out of extra income down the road. Sponsors who we had for several years refused to increase their sponsorship amount, even as our reach in the community grew. 

  In terms of approaching potential sponsors, research as much as you can. Find business owners with an affinity for your sport, start with your club players and ask them to throw out names/contact info of potential contacts and ask them to help you arrange in-person meetings. Look at businesses in the surrounding neighborhoods where you play, such as restaurants who could benefit from your players and fans visiting afterwards for a bite. Find incentives to offer your sponsors that won't cost you anything (such as social media mentions, logo placement on your team's website and the like). Treat each encounter like a business meeting, since sponsorship money often comes out of a businesses' marketing budget. Hope this gives you a good start! Best of luck!  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-02 14:47:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You mean you wouldn't support the theoretical merger of FedEx and UPS to become "FedUp"?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-16 14:45:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Eat essentials. Don't try to fit Keto versions of non-Keto foods like baked goods into your new lifestyle. Use a slow cooker to tenderize cheaper cuts of meat. Frozen veggies are just as good and easy to prep in a pinch.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-09 21:14:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Super Bowl Sunday IFU- went to a party and ate pulled pork, completely forgetting that not everyone uses sugar free BBQ sauce/spice rub. Def. kicked me out of Ketosis, and now a few days later I'm going thru Keto Flu all over again! 

  Pray for me, it wasn't nearly this bad the first time around!  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-05 17:54:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thank goodness for Buffalo Chicken Dip!  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-31 08:39:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> My Dad was a Filipino citizen turned American by way of the US Navy. In his 20s, he was a self-described fuck-up who was forbidden from seeing my mom due to his lack of future job prospects. As an ultimatum, my paternal grand parents made him take the ASBAV. He showed up to the test hung over after a huge bender. He scored top out of 400 and was able to enlist. 

  A few years pass and his ship is due to make port in the Philippines again. He visits my maternal grandparents, and they hardly recognize the polished young professional that he's become. Amazed at his transformation, they practically arrange my parents marriage in a 48 hour window of opportunity. (Don't worry, mom was happy about it!)

  A few months later, my mom is taking her first airplane trip in her life, alone, to meet my dad in the US. She's sitting next to an older white gentleman who is clearly hitting on her. "I'm going to meet my husband!" She says. Thinking that she was some sort of mail-order bride, he tells her "I'll wait until he shows up. If he decides he doesn't like you, I'll take you home with me."

  Even more years pass and my sister and I are born. Mom and Dad save enough money to bring Grandma over. I remember my mom and grandma studying hard, for several days, so they could pass the citizenship test, which they eventually did, making them official Americans. 

  After 16 years in the Navy, my Dad was able to retire, thanks to post-gulf war draw down. He secured a job as an engineer for a then small tech startup called Qualcomm. One of my fondest memories of my Dad was sitting by the computer, working on a technology report for my middle school computer class. He says "here, use this for your report", and shoves a thick technical manual at me. "It's what I'm working on right now." 

  The manual was all about Code Division Multiple Access, or CDMA. This lead to the beginning of 3G cellular service, and the development of the Qualcomm Snapdragon Processor, which also lead to Smart Phones. 

  Every once in a while after his career in the Navy, he would still drive down to 32nd Street Naval Base in San Diego and have a smoke down where the Carriers and Amphibs were docked. He'd tell me "Sometimes work is hard. But at least it's not as hard as the Navy. Be thankful for the Navy, kid." 

  God Bless the US Navy and all immigrants who have served or are currently serving in the US Armed Forces.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-28 23:16:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Heart Rate Monitor- targeted heart rate training has really changed the way I work out. It's good to have that quantitative data to measure whether I actually am working out hard or not. 

  ETA: an actual heart rate monitor that goes in your sternum, not a wearable that goes on your wrist.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-28 22:19:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> MFP: Fartn0ise 

I also have a fairly new Keto-instagram: kissmyketobutt  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Spotting after vigorous workout? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-23 06:19:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Anyone else experience spotting after vigorous workouts since starting Keto?   

Began officially on Jan 2 after a few failed starts. I've been consistent keeping net carbs below 25g/day and have so far enjoyed almost a 14 pound weight loss. Yay!   

Saturday mornings I work out at a gym that focused on targeted heart rate training, with the goal of getting you to spend at least 15 total minutes working in the 85-90% zone over the course of a 55 minute workout. According to my heart rate monitor (which I know already overestimates this metric), I average a 550 cals burned per workout. However, each time I've come home from said workout, I've found some bleeding and experienced some mild cramping which carries in to the following day's evening, plus all the usual PMS symptoms, especially the general blah feeling.  I do 3-4 less intense workouts during the week which don't give me this problem. Just wondering if anyone else experiences something similar! Hoping this isn't a permanent thing. TIA!!!  ETA: no history of PCOS. I'm on Mirena IUD. 


 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-21 15:29:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> NSV- talked myself out of cheating with chocolate by telling myself "You don't need to cheat. You're cheating every day with bacon, cheese and HWC! BTW, didn't your Keto-ass just eat steak for breakfast too?!" Damn, I love this diet!  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-21 00:26:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Awesome! Great job!  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
