<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject1628</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-09 14:07:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thanks for all the replies, they make me feel better haha. I'm the same, give it 100 pages. That's fair. Plenty of stuff to read out there, why waste time on something you are forcing yourself to get through? Best wishes to all.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Do you ever feel bad about not finishing a book? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-09 03:28:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> By this I mean you dislike it so much you just cannot continue. I do feel bad when I do this. I just read about 100 pages of a 450-page book about Simon Wesenthal and just want to forget about it and move on to something else. It feels like a waste of time but man this thing was painfully boring. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-09 02:54:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Could be a liquid, depending on severity. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-09 00:10:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Haha thanks. Purely by accident I assure you, have never watched the show but hear it's worth a look.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-09 00:04:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Here's what I went with folks. Thanks to all for the input. I'll post in the sub when it goes live. I appreciate all of the replies. 

https://imgur.com/gallery/rOfuC </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-08 23:57:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thanks, you raise some good points. Yes I am the author and a stutterer and it does evoke what I feel. I ended up going with a similar pic but a male. Nothing against the female pic or females in general. I'm a male and males do stutter way more so it just fit better.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-08 03:38:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thanks. Any ideas as to what to do? Maybe add some sand, change to a bigger pot to better allow drainage and just keep them in indirect sunlight for a few days?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-08 03:21:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Most are yes. I thought about this as well.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-07 21:11:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thanks </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-07 21:11:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> With that picture? Some ppl are saying it doesn't really fit.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-07 19:47:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thanks very much. I have never watched that show but hear it's great. It's a pen name, my real first name but mothers maiden name.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-07 18:47:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thanks. I agree.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-07 18:16:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I agree. I think some things are difficult to portray. To me Stuttering can appear to be a disconnect between thoughts and words but how do you illustrate this with a picture? Maybe I'm better off going with the 2nd one. Thanks so much for your input, it really does help.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-07 18:03:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Great advice, thanks so much. Would you go with the 2nd or would one with a picture like the one you said be better do you think?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Had someone design my book cover, she did one with a picture and one without. Your advice is appreciated. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-07 17:26:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-07 05:52:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Fuckin hate when people say actual fuck. As opposed to what, a hypothetical fuck? A fake fuck?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-06 19:34:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Sorry not a terrarium that's not what I meant. Until it warms up outside I just have them under a light in an aquarium tank. The pots sit in a saucer. They seem to drain OK but the pots just seem soggy.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Pots not draining enough after watering </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-06 18:53:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hello, have 2 hurricane palm seeds in 4" pots, 1/2   1/2 potting mix and perlite in a terrarium under 2 60w LEDs. Last time I watered them was probably 3 days ago and they still seem very wet. I can't put them outside yet because it is a bit too chilly. Any ideas? Should I move to a mix with some sand and peet and hope they drain faster? Bigger pot? How often should I be watering? Thanks in advance. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-05 14:41:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Some academic journals are readily available online. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-05 02:18:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah I imagine. Hope justice is served.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-05 00:53:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Certainly not saying it didn't happen, but she went to the hospital after midnight. So....did she return to her seat, watch the rest of the game and then report it?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-04 23:19:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thanks.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Do I need a bibliography for my non-fiction e-book if all my sources are hyperlinked? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-04 21:52:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Any response would be appreciated. Thanks. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
