<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject82</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> One-Third Of New Drugs Had Safety Problems After FDA Approval </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-09 20:28:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Oldest Evidence of Life on Earth Possibly Found in Australian Rocks </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-09 20:18:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-08 21:27:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I *have* heard that jet fuel melts steel, even steel beams. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Happy Birthday to one of the greatest games, Wolfenstein 3D </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-05 17:55:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Skateboard legend Tony Hawk films rats causing car fire </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-03 15:52:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-01 23:04:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's the formula for a mineral called "cummingtonite".  He'll make your bedrock.

Edit: if you get with me, you'll be cummingtonite. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Border Patrol finds 67 pounds of pot in casket after stopping hearse near Tombstone </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-01 20:15:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Nerd joke at the local brewery </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-01 19:35:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Congress just cleared the way for internet providers to sell your web browsing history </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-29 00:39:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Congress just cleared the way for internet providers to sell your web browsing history </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-29 00:39:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Comet Pizza gunman pleads guilty to federal and local charges </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-24 19:23:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-14 18:57:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> He was born in 1879 and would be in his early 40's by this point so it is understandable he would be showing some age.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-14 16:48:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm not sure about grandchildren but Albert and his first wife, Mileva Mari, had a daughter who was either adopted or died at a young age, but her real fate is unknown. They also had two sons. The eldest son, [Hans Albert Einstein](https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Hans_Albert_Einstein), went on to be a professor of Hydraulic Engineering at the University of California, Berkeley. Their second son, Eduard, was diagnosed with schizophrenia at 20 and eventually he was permanently committed to an asylum. 

Albert and Mileva divorced after she learned he had a romantic attraction to his first and second cousin Elsa, who he eventually married. So if they had kids, they probably wouldn't have been the brightest. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Albert Einstein, 1920's. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-14 16:04:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-11 23:46:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Those pancakes are going to be done long before the sausage is.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-10 17:22:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Oh don't worry, there is.
 Of course, this being Russia  where alcoholism has been called a "national disaster"  no holiday would be complete without plenty of alcohol. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> TIL of Maslenitsa, a week long Eastern Slavic holiday that consists of organized fist fights, dancing bears, effigy burning, and pancakes. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-10 16:43:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
