<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject8764</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Kansas City mom humiliated, shamed after forced to pee in cup on United flight, she says </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-09 23:29:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> 94-year-old Royals fan leaves hospice care to honor Yordano Ventura </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-24 01:54:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Missouri Rep: CCW license owners can borrow gun from office to carry around in State Capitol </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-12 21:50:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Missouri Rep: CCW license owners can borrow gun from office to carry around in State Capitol </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-12 21:42:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Missouri Rep: CCW license owners can borrow gun from office to carry around in State Capitol </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-12 21:42:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> "No whites, BLM" graffiti found on Kansas City home </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-23 00:28:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Armed Missouri man shot by police after dog complaint, neighbor says police went too far </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-01 02:41:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Kansas State's Bill Snyder writes letter of support for crash victim </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-30 23:12:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Former Power Rangers actress involved in police standoff in Kansas City </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-16 23:54:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Man helping neighbor without power threatened by utility; refuses to unplug extension cord </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-24 05:20:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Wyandotte County man serving life for murder says he's innocent, gunman agrees </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-23 05:58:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Man serving life for murder says he's innocent, gunman agrees </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-23 05:56:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Illegal immigrant, accused of killing 5, wants change of venue for county with more Hispanics. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-10 03:22:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> University of Kansas communications professor who used racial slur in class fired </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-24 18:31:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Over a dozen wrecks so far this month on I-35 at 75th Street </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-25 08:44:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Over a dozen wrecks this month on I-35 and 75th in Overland Park. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-25 08:43:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Kansas City man creates expert Planet Comicon costumes </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-14 01:20:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Support pours in for Kansas City area family forced to destroy their front yard vegetable garden </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-07 13:07:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Support pours in for Sugar Creek family forced to destroy their front yard vegetable garden </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-07 12:50:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Support pours in for Sugar Creek family forced to destroy their front yard vegetable garden </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-07 12:49:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Support pours in for Kansas City area family forced to destroy their front yard vegetable garden </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-07 00:53:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> New city ordinance forces family to destroy their vegetable garden </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-01 03:43:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> BIG GOVERNMENT: New city ordinance forces family to destroy their vegetable garden </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-01 03:38:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> New city ordinance forces family to destroy their vegetable garden </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-01 03:25:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> New city ordinance forces family to destroy their vegetable garden </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-01 03:14:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> New city ordinance forces Sugar Creek, Mo., family to destroy their vegetable garden </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-01 03:13:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Kansas City Election Board sends disabled man, wife wrong ballots twice </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-15 01:25:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Kansas City Election Board sends disabled man, wife wrong ballots twice </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-15 01:24:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Kansas City man says Parkville police mistook turban for hat </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-12 15:32:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Collection agency horror story: Kansas City man threatened with arrest for $67 fine he said he's already paid. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-12 02:58:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Collecting agency brings nightmare: Arrest warrant issued over Kansas City man's $67 fine he said he already paid </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-12 02:51:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Kansas City hospital testing weight loss "balloon pill" </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-19 19:36:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Police arrest homeless man for living in tiny house donated to him by samaritans </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-19 18:46:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Would-be robber pulls knife on hotel guest, then guest pulls a gun </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-01 16:25:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Homeowner credits pit bull for saving his life during attempted robbery in Kansas City </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-11-21 21:56:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Royals fans camp out overnight before parade </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-11-03 12:57:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> MLB tells 'Straight Outta Kauffman' designer to cease and desist </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-10-27 00:49:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Olive Garden apologizes to Kansas City police officer after he was allegedly asked to leave for carrying gun </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-10-12 06:26:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> First ever transgender lingerie line to open in Kansas City </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-09-27 20:01:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Veterans fear smoking ban could force Kansas City-area VFW post to close </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-09-07 02:55:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Veterans fear Kearney, Missouri smoking ban could force local VFW post to close </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-09-07 02:54:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Kansas City, Kansas soccer program feels impact of district budget cuts. Team has only handful of soccer balls. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-08-05 14:47:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Missouri man still waiting for freedom after governor commuted his life sentence for pot. State spends $120 million annually on keeping drug offenders in prison. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-08-02 16:57:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Missouri man still waiting for freedom after governor commuted his life sentence for pot. Missouri spends over $120 million annually on keeping drug offenders in prison. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-08-02 16:53:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> "I mean, it might sound bad, but I was in a way hoping this was the outcome." Brother relieved over Richard Matt's death. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-27 19:18:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-29 21:50:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Doc Rivers is an average coach who lucked into Danny Ainge trading for one of the best five power forwards ever and one of the greatest shooters ever. None of Rivers' teams won a first round series until Garnett showed up in Boston. And while his rosters in Orlando and Boston weren't great, he still had Tracy McGrady and Orlando never won a series with him. 

Is he a good leader? Absolutely and I think he did a nice job with the Sterling stuff last year. 

But he doesn't deserve to be mentioned among the best coaches in the league.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-07 19:26:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I agree with this. It amazes me how reporters and the average basketball fan will nuke Calipari and Kentucky for ruining college basketball, while giving guys like K, Self, Roy and (back then) Ben Howland a free pass. 

And for what it's worth, I have absolutely no problem with coaches getting one and dones. It's a bad rule that can be exploited for wins. I'd do it. I just wish there was a consistent opinion about it on the guys who do it.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-07 06:06:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Duke deserved it with their play down the stretch, but it seems like it's becoming a common occurrence for great college basketball games to be marred by officiating. Just awful.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-31 02:16:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Marshall might not be the ideal fit there. He's one of my favorite coaches, but he strikes me as a guy who wants to be the top dog at his school. He won't be that at Texas or Alabama. Some media in the Midwest also think he's a bit weird personality wise, but I don't understand that. Coaches naturally are wired differently.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-31 01:19:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This didn't have to be a season-long arc, but I would have loved to see more of an internal struggle with Dexter in terms of who to follow: Harry or Brian. I think it would have been cool to see those dueling personalities (Angel vs. Devil) last longer than just one episode. Perhaps it could have come after the Season 4 twist. 

I don't know....perhaps make Dexter "The Big Bad" for the finale season if you wanted to go in a completely different direction.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-26 23:17:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Knowing the NCAA, this is what they'll penalize North Carolina for while letting the academic fraud go.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-24 16:02:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> First, I think it's unfair to call him a bad tournament coach simply because of the runs in 2008 and 2012, especially 2012. That team had no business getting to the national title game and it did. It won a lot of close games that year in the tournament and coaching wins in close games. I'd call him an average coach, but not a bad coach. 

I think what's hurt KU's teams under Self over the years are a mix of things: Lack of a consistent conference rival (Texas was great in 2008 and Mizzou's 2012 pushed KU), perhaps coming out too tight in a lot of games and luck. 

With luck, look at the VCU loss. VCU was 12-of-25 from three that day. KU was 2-of-21. You're not going to win too many games when your opponent is 30 points better than you from the three-point line. If KU finishes that game 6-of-21 from three, they win. VCU was playing some of the best basketball I've seen. Is that coaching? Maybe a little bit. 

Bradley and Wichita State were cases of really young KU teams going against experienced teams. Outside of size, Wichita State had almost every advantage coming into that game. KU was one of the youngest teams in the country. The Shockers' core had played in a Final Four, finished a regular season undefeated and went to war with a Kentucky team that nearly won the title. 

The Northern Iowa and Bucknell loses were inexcusable. KU was the best team in the country in 2010 and that tournament should have been their's.

I read something on the NBA reddit page about how Popovich takes the pressure off his team by telling them basketball doesn't mean everything. I'd be curious what Self's game-day preparation is like. I do think KU teams have a tendency to come out tight in the tournament. Usually that means the players have the wrong mindset entering the tournament. Maybe that's what Self can work on. 

But overall, I'd take Bill Self over 97 percent of coaches out there. I think KU needs a rival where the game matters more than the standings. Time to schedule Mizzou or Wichita State? I don't know. Maybe hope Texas hires a great coach or Hoiberg stays at Iowa State? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-23 22:18:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yay....yet another SEC school that has a coach better than Mizzou. If only Mississippi State would have hired a "true son" like Mike Alden did.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-17 01:49:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> RECENTLY: I really thought Brian Shaw would work out as a head coach. Not so much. Maybe he still will, but certainly not with the Nuggets. 

NOT SO RECENTLY: I thought the Spurs were done the year Memphis beat them as a #8 seed. Instead, they made three straight WCF, two conference finals and won a title. You can also argue last year's Spurs team was the best in the Popovich era, though the '07 squad has an argument.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-14 21:20:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I guess it was the Auburn win that finally sold the committee on Kentucky.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-12 20:50:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> One of the biggest problems with Alden and basketball coaches is that he's a micro-manager of everything. It scared off some of the better candidates during his last two hirings. 

I wasn't a big fan of Haith and I'm not sure he deserved an extension. 

But if you let Haith leave, you must do better than a Division 2 head coach who built his D2 program through transfers, JUCOs, ect. He's never proven to develop talent from the freshman level. He was Norm's lead assistant during some of the bad years in the mid-to-late 1990's. He absolutely did not deserve the job and the fact some Mizzou fans think he did a good job this year is a good example why Mizzou's never made a Final Four.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-12 20:43:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> With all due respect, what improved over the course of the year that makes it clear Kim Anderson is a better developer of talent? Kim did most of his damage at CMSU through transfers from Division 1 and JUCO programs. 

I want the guy to work out, but I'm not optimistic about Kim.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-12 20:40:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Mike Alden deserves most of the blame for this. The original sin, of course, was hiring Quin Snyder over Bill Self and John Calpari. 

Then, there was his brilliant decision to hire Mike Anderson over Bob Huggins. Now, I love Mike Anderson and I hope he does really well at Arkansas. But it was no secret Huggins was putting together a great recruiting class behind the scenes. If Mizzou hires Huggy, things are better. 

After Mike Anderson goes home, he pulls Frank Haith out of nowhere, when Gregg Marshall and a few others wanted the job. This was before Marshall went to the Final Four, but it was clear he was building something at Wichita State. 

Finally, he hires Kim Anderson, a Division 2 coach who was NEVER even a candidate at a school like Missouri State, UMKC and other area small Division 1 schools in the Midwest. The only reason he was hired was because he was a Tiger alum. Fact. Alden hired Kim Anderson and threw a bone to the older fan base and donors who are bigger Norm Stewart fans than Mizzou fans. Ben Howland, Brad Underwood and Chris Mack would have taken that job, from what someone close to the Board of Trustees told me. Yet, they hired a True Son Division 2 head coach. 

I wish Mizzou would fire Alden before his retirement becomes official. He murdered the basketball program.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-10 21:06:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Considering Bradford is a member of the Cherokee Nation, this might score some points with Stephen A. Smith.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-09 07:21:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This kind of reminds me when the the Bulls blew up the team after winning its sixth title. A little bit different since the Niners didn't win the title during the Harbaugh era, but I think the results will be earily similar.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-04 08:45:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If OU hangs on to a 21-point lead against Iowa State and West Virginia doesn't lose an 18-point lead, OU is playing to break The Streak this weekend. Crazy how that works out.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-03 02:16:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> While I loved Captain America: The Winter Soldier, I wish there would have been more to how Steve adapted to 2010-14. I think there could have been some nice realization that while some things changed for the worse in Steve's eyes (less patriotism, less connection between individuals), things also improved for the better - less racism, more accepting population to differences. 

I know it may have added more time to the movie, but I think it would have been great to show him struggling with the time change, rather than just putting it off as a funny line with the checklist early in the movie.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-03 00:08:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> God, the Colts are a perfect fit here.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-26 21:04:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Came in here to say this. Better yet, I'd love for them to beat Notre Dame in that game considering that's Jed's school. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-26 07:35:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Eh, I think the football game will be pretty boring myself judging by the last two decades.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-25 20:53:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I don't buy that Tattoo gate was orchestrated, but I do think there was communication between the Meyer and Ohio State camps during that scandal. Between Meyer's wishy-washy ending in Florida when he retired twice and the timing of how it all went down, I wouldn't be surprised if there was a wink and a nod type of deal between the two. It's amazing how those heart problems and migraines went away. Also, in terms of Ohio State having an interim head coach the year between Tressel and Meyer, I could see Meyer wanting to take a year off to let the NCAA settle with Ohio State. 

And for what it's worth, I don't blame Ohio State at all if something like this happened. Urban Meyer is one of the two best coaches of the past 20 years and if you get a chance to land him, do it.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-25 19:24:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Season 2 by a hair over Season 1. I think both of those seasons are the only ones where it felt like every episode mattered, though I admit I would have loved to see Dexter having to make the choice of killing Doakes or not. 

Lithgow was outstanding in Season 4 and the ending was the most shocking TV moment I've seen, but there were some flaws to that season that are often overlooked because of how good of a villain Trinity was.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-23 08:12:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Last week's loss must have knocked Kansas out of the Top 5.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-23 08:06:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Kim "no hats while eating" Anderson approves.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-23 01:53:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah, we have no room to talk smack when it comes to basketball. Also not included in that is an 8 point loss to UMKC. 

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-17 21:31:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You might replicate this type of beatdown to Missouri very soon. Nolen's teams were fun to watch....it was one of the reasons why I was excited about Mike Anderson's hiring at Mizzou.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-16 18:03:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> After a bad story about Mike Singletary came out, he accused someone on his staff of "being a rat." According to a Bay Area sports talk host, Harbaugh suspected there was a rat on his staff. (https://twitter.com/JohnMiddlekauff/status/566383965280280576)

One coach served on both staffs. He's the same one that was hired as the head coach. Gee, I wonder how he got the job.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-16 01:59:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Good read and a scenario that's not often mentioned with "what if" stories. Dr. J and Kareem would have been fun to watch for sure. 

The one "what if" scenario I think about is if Orlando kept Chris Webber instead of trading him for Penny. Not sure if they overtake MJ's Bulls, but Shaq+Webber would have been very interesting.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-13 05:39:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Mizzou's football team has a really good chance of having more wins than the basketball team this season. 

I guess that makes us a football school, so I can't answer this.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-11 18:13:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> A lot of great coaching talent has left the world in the past week. RIP Tark the Shark.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-10 22:44:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Where do I start? 

First, our coach is calling out his players because of the bad manners they are displaying. He's punishing kids for wearing hats while eating. He called out two players by name for showing bad "posture" during a post-game interview session and one of his priorities is how they enunciate words. 

Missouri basketball: First in manners, last in the SEC. 

Sadly, a lot of our fan base is eating this up because they are bigger fans of Norm Stewart than they are Missouri basketball. Some Mizzou fans would be perfectly fine running out five white kids from rural Missourah each night, as long as they "hustled" all the time. 

Missouri fans have accepted sucking for a long time. The deification of Norm Stewart/Kim Anderson are great examples. Norm would be the sixth best coach in the history of Kansas Jayhawks basketball. He'd be a footnote there. 
  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-08 12:49:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> How any prominent loss from an SEC team means it's overrated, never mind the fact the conference still brings in the most top recruits and produces the most NFL talent most years. The amount of times fans brought up Oklahoma beating Alabama and Indiana beating Mizzou was absurd. The Mizzou loss was terrible, but it was not a reflection of the conference's 13 other teams. 

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-08 11:04:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Anyone wearing a Cleveland Browns jersey.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-08 11:02:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The development of young talent and the fact the Raiders beat the Chiefs and 49ers, two of the team's biggest rivals. The Chiefs victory began their downward spiral that prevented them from getting in the playoffs. The 49ers win was one of the final nails of the Harbaugh Era in San Francisco.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-08 10:54:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> * Philip Rivers
* Antonio Gates
* Jamaal Charles
* Derrick Johnson
* Aqib Talib </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-08 10:41:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I like the City of Lawrence. That's about it.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-08 10:37:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Kansas begins with a close win over South Dakota State. The next week, they are hammered by Memphis. 

It's now basketball season.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-08 10:32:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Seeing this Tweet and the Mark Pantoni tweet makes me the biggest Michigan State fan who lives in Kansas. Go Sparty! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-08 00:04:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> ELEPHANT #1: The prospect of the Raiders overspending and signing bad contracts with players. Having $50-60 million in cap-room is good if you know what to do with it. However, it's also an invitation to giving away money for guys who may not be in their prime any more. As much as Marshawn Lynch in a Raiders jersey appeals to me, the fact that's nearly 30 also scares me. A team like the Raiders has to pay a little bit more for a quality free agent due to how bad they have been lately. But hopefully they do not break the bank. 

ELEPHANT #2: The fact Jim Harbaugh and other quality head coaching candidates rejected the Raiders. If the rumored contract offer for Harbaugh is true. he left a ton of money on the table. The Raiders have not had a quality head coach since Jon Gruden.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-07 22:34:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So, are Iowa State fans the only Big 12 fans that do not storm the court after beating KU? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-07 22:34:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Bill Self is playing the long-con here. Good move! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-06 20:50:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What kind of a world do I live in where the Raiders are making pretty good moves? Love this.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
