<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject6906</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-10 06:29:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The value of human life is not well understood by brainwashed drunk frat bros.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-10 04:05:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> HA HAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAA! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Former Rutgers football star, Khaseem Greene, indicted for role in Elizabeth shooting </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-10 04:01:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-09 17:55:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Your scenario sounds a lot like that Dropkick Murphy's song, just sayin. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-08 23:43:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> How bout Lil Kim's "My Neck, My back." </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-07 19:12:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You might be the first person in history to admit he shoots blanks. Bravo! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-07 04:58:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Don't use them for sex...just use them as water balloons. Win/Win. You won't get anyone pregnant and you'll still have fun in the process. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-07 04:27:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Many graduates who land jobs, work in the Tri-State Area; which have higher starting salaries due to locality/cost of living. The numbers are skewed. Numbers can be sliced and diced so many ways..... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-06 22:58:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's not a scam at all. The schools are accredited and seen as reputable places for education by employers, and other institutions. 

An educated society has value, but the price individuals affix to a college education is truly subjective. Some feel that the blue collar route is the better path, while others feel attending college is of utmost importance. 

As citizens, we should not be manipulated by the narrative that college education is close to mandatory. Unfortunately, since most employers require college degrees for a large amount of roles...it puts many people in a tough situation.  There are people without college degrees, who are far more intelligent than some college students. However, the proliferation of the inherent value of education causes people to attend college, (NOT because they want to, but because they are pressured to).  

Blue collar workers are needed. If college isn't interesting, then a trade school should be a viable option. It's just a different form of education, a more hands-on type. 

The for-profit schools are really messed up because they seek to exploit people that are sold on this narrative. However, they (students of Strayer, UPO, etc.) are unaware of the reputation and accreditation of those schools in the eyes of employers. 

Institutions know the narrative is important to their existence. College Tuition/Fees will continue to rise as long as college admins, officials and coaches are making money to pad their lavish lifestyles. If colleges didn't operate like businesses, they would not make any money.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-06 22:39:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Don't worry. Most people who have active friend circles will be at more of a loss than you. After all, they peaked in college and will see real life as just obligations. 

Instead, you'll graduate and move onto new things; a fresh start. You'll have chances to branch out outside of the Rutgers Bubble and make connections. If social anxiety is getting you down, seek help now, so you can enjoy life the way you would like to.  

Remember, it's going to be mother's day on Sunday. Most people will be sitting with a few friends or by themselves. Many students will be with their families pre and post graduation (Sunday). 

Be proud.  Half the people taking pics together will eventually get busy with life and lose touch with each other...(especially if those friendly connections were formed through drinking/partying/shananigans etc.)

Behind all the picture taking is a repressed fear of the real world for some, especially if he or she is swamped with student loan debt. Re-frame your situation if possible and look at all the positives to your college experience. There are many people who may or may not have done as well as you. 

Also, you do have friends, you just have to reach out to them and show interest. People won't know if you value their company unless you verbally tell them.  

I wish you well! 
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-06 04:05:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> University Coaches are grossly overpaid due to a systematic failure. The "Institutions" of Higher Education have become drunk off of athletic departments - serving as the main brand promoter for their school. 

By definition, college is an institution....but if it wasn't a business, why would college's invest so much money in branding and other lavish accommodations? (Because they want more students to come to their school instead of other schools. Each student is a walking $. 

The entire "College" Narrative is something that is proliferated through the masses of our society. WHY? Because you'll be at the mercy of the (1%) for a significant portion of your life (time range for paying off debt is a case by case basis.) The people in control have control of you, to an extent. 

Think about it. If college wasn't a business or a racket, why would schools try to squeeze every last penny out of you before graduation?

Universities get paid for dispersing x number of gov loans to students...of course the school is going to provide you with some form of "financial aid." 

Also, I'm not out of touch. I understand both sides of the argument and why college keeps getting more expensive. It's a systematic failure that exploits students and it's not going to stop. The gov, admins and other college officials are making far too much money to make changes to benefit students financially.  

* Greed 
* Ignorance
* Mass Manipulation  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-06 03:42:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Looks like the Dancing Bear was late to the co-ed porno shoot. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-05 16:34:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Great Point! 

Institutions know that student loans are easily obtained. Therefore, they continue to raise tuition/fees in small percentages each year...thinking, ehhh they won't mind if it's just a little bit more. College is College and most are pressured to go to college in search of a better life.  

SOLUTION: 

* Minimize the bloated salaries of state workers at Rutgers

* cut the overlap in jobs (bureaucracy)   minimize the administration

* Students should find another way to go to college and NOT sign their lives away in loans

* Students can take-up part time jobs while in school

* "Following your passion" in Art History, Music, or any other major with minimal potential for employment is not practical.

* College is a Business. Treat it like one. As a student, bust your ass in class. There are financial aid awards/scholarships for continuing students.

* Commute to Rutgers for Freshmen/Soph, if possible. Don't waste your money on shitty food and housing. You won't be eligible for the nice on-campus anyway.

* Be smart with your money and the decisions that you make. 

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-05 16:16:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I wouldn't drink that. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-05 16:15:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> He was in one of my classes. Good kid. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-04 04:44:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Grab your pitch forks! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-04 04:40:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You are NOT any safer on-campus.... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-02 04:29:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Good point. Never heard of Poets and Quants before.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-01 03:58:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> How much is Rutgers paying you to be a Shill on Reddit?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-30 03:47:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Ja Rule is going to put in on ya </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-30 02:48:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> laughable consequences... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-29 21:04:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Winter time is fine b/c everyone is indoors. Just wait till the summer.... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-29 21:03:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Go to Florida. You have not experienced lightning storms until you've traveled there. The bolts spread out through out the sky...like shatter proof class cracking. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-29 06:56:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Nah, don't deal with that frat. They will only protect themselves. Just go to the police.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-29 06:46:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> "HAHAHA it's funny cause he's fat!" </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
