<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject4297</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-10 02:13:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You can find them for less than $.10 everywhere. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-09 08:36:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This is such a trainwreck thread xD </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-09 05:45:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This paints a very clear picture of a 70's bush gangbang. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-09 05:39:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Man drifter... Your kind of an ass. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-08 22:20:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I really like what you wrote here... But the only reason that MTG shorting doesn't exist is because people choose not to do it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-08 22:11:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That was the first time I made/tried it. It's a good blank canvas. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-08 20:37:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Sorry nott the msrp I meant current market value. As far as I can tell it sells for $200 min right now. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-08 17:40:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Oh jeez I didn't know that. That sucks. Thanks for the advice! I'll try to sell it sealed. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [Homemade] Vanilla flan with pink peppercorns, mixed berry compote, caramel, and spiced whipped cream. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-08 15:57:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Does anyone know of a cube that I can massentry buy through TCG or SCG thats both fun and under $60? I know similar posts have been made before... but to little avail. Thanks! </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-08 15:29:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-08 15:10:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Trackmania turbo </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-08 15:05:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Battleblock theatre </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-08 14:53:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Well my thought process right now is to keep it sealed until I can sell the mox. I'm very new to speculation but I've been looking at the cards and I think they could ride collectively. I think reserve list cards are going to go up over time just because they are collectible. Also, the only reason sol ring is worth anything in that print is because it's sexy af. As commander gets more popular I feel people will want it more. Also the whole set and packaging is just stunning and in low supply so I figured there's no harm in waiting it out. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> How do you guys feel about buying sealed From The Vault sets? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-08 14:14:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I recently got in to MTG finance and found a FTV relics for $100 under msrp. Considering Mox Diamond makes up for almost all of the money I spent on it, I decided I would keep it sealed and try to sit on it. How do y'all feel about similar buys/strategys? (friendly discussion) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-07 06:19:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> 6 sellers left on TCG... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-06 21:54:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Does anyone see mox diamond going up? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-04 02:24:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Ah well I actually have only drafted it once so I have little experience. Drafted it once and it was amazing. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-03 19:37:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Not an answer... But they are fucking fun to draft. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-03 19:36:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Ashnods coupon can get you a good return on sodas. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-03 18:33:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I disagree. I don't know the quote you were referring and I'm expressing that when I or certain communties/people that I know use the term feminazi, it is not referring to a feminist. I am a feminist. A tumblr blogger who rants about how men should be abused is not a feminist. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-30 00:35:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Simic. Your kinda an ass. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-29 07:14:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Ebay, and no but the seller has good ratings and eBay money back  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-29 01:42:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> My secret Santa experience was terrible. Got a no show. Never doing that again. Spent a lot of time and money on the other guy and was so excited for my gift. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-26 19:53:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I just bought my first real nice card, a revised badlands in NM-SP condition. It was only $60. Should I flip it quick or sit on it? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-26 05:58:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Just bought one for $12 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-21 15:33:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If you are currently looking for clients please msg me on discord at Fox#2227 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-21 04:13:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm just worried I'll sell it and it will spike 100% again </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-20 20:39:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Oh they must have updated the post since I last checked. It definetly didn't say that before. My B. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-20 18:30:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> They only have MTGO listed for release </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-20 17:52:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's MTGO only I believe </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-20 15:56:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I bought a Unlimited Mana Vault some years ago for $10. After quiting for a few years and returning during Kaladesh I see it has risen to around $90. I dont know whether to sell or sit on it. Im pretty short on money so this little investment is nice. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-20 07:14:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I added you -Fox#2227 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-20 07:11:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I have a kitten mittens shirt that I got for like $2 online and its made out of some weird ass jersey material. People comment on both aspects. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-18 20:38:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Could add me on discord at Fox#2227. I have some questions :) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-18 17:13:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> How far along is this project? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-11 02:30:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thanks. Gl to you. I suggest doing some serious schedule management, put everyone on a polar schedule.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-10 21:45:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Tell that to Rudy from alpha investments  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-10 21:24:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's not going to work. To cramped and the food is to far away. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-09 08:22:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm new to magic. Why is siege rhino a big deal. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-05 21:06:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Great guy I highly suggest hiring him. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [HuntNetwork] looking for a skilled and experienced plugin developer. This is a PAID position. Payment on completion of every plugin plus profit percentage options. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-04 17:36:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Please contact me at Fox#2227 on discord if you are interested. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [HuntNetwork] Looking for a skilled, experienced person to build HuntNetworks mini game server from the scratch. Everything is paid for, and you will take large percentage of profits. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-30 16:11:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Please contact me at Fox#2227 on discord for more information. Please do not contact if you have little/no experience or are under the age of 16. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-29 15:50:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm not all that experienced by I believe the logo should be a bit bigger. Try them out :3 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-29 07:44:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Please contact me at Fox#2227 on discord. I think I can help. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-28 19:14:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I would be interested in sponsoring you. Please message me here or on discord at Fox#2227 so we can talk. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [Homemade] Hazzlenut, Burrata, Pear, Thyme Hazzlenut Butter Maple Chive Caramel Glass, Burnt Onion Maple. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-25 21:26:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [Homemade] As a 16 year old culinary student, this is the dish im proudest of. Burrata with thyme butter roasted hazzlenut, burnt onion maple, hazzlenut butter chive maple caramel glass, pear, lemon. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-25 07:07:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-24 15:00:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> When I show a card to a bystander it's always a land. When I say "go team foxy" it means I'm going to lose. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> HuntFactions [PvP]{Factions}{Crates}{1.11.2} </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-24 03:29:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> About HF: HuntFactions, founded by spiffyFox, is a new and ambitious factions server, with a small yet dedicated player base.  While creating Hunt, we aimed to bring back the clean, simple, and bloody factions experience that has become so hard to find. The team is devoted to introducing and developing new, clean, and balanced features over time. For example, we plan on adding a custom end map, spleef with rewards, and custom items soon! HF Is an extremely new server, so as expected, we have a small player base. Most people who play on the server are also active on discord. Its a really great group! We yearned for a refined factions experience, a flashback to factions servers of a few years ago. We built it.
We are currently developing our Hub Expansion. This will include prison, skyblock, OP factions, survival, modified survival, and more!
Players who join during our current beta will be given a [Supporter] rank, with access to special permanent features.
We are looking forward to new faces! Please post comments/concerns/questions below.
Server Information: Plugins and Features of Note: * Factions (ECON Enabled) * Crates * Crazy Auctions * Voting * Donor Ranks * Parkour * Competitive * PvP Arena * PvP Log * Expendable Obsidian * Vast Spawn Shop * Fun and Dedicated Playerbase * Discord
Server Address/IP: HuntFactions.mc-srv.com
Server Locale: East Coast (USA)
Game Play Type: Classic Competitive Factions Experience
Version: 1.11.2
Website: [Here](http://huntnetwork.buycraft.net/)
Discord: Here
Rules- * No Racism * No Hacking * No Abuse * No Spamming * No Advertising </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-22 17:40:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Feel free to catch some hackers on huntfactions.mc-srv.com </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Anyone know of a available epicworldgenerator leak? Anyone interested In creating a world file for me for a few $$? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-17 16:39:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-17 16:33:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yea I need to run retropi for this. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-17 13:20:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Can you exlain how? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-17 12:21:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Well I want to make a small retropi console, and then have some sort of LED marque on the breadboard. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> I'm new terrible with pi... Is there a way to have retropi and be able to control a breadboard? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-17 04:56:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-15 16:07:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You are the worst kind of person, and based on your reddit stats and such, A LOT of people agree. Go fuck yourself. Your server is shit. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
