<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject8367</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Nano-sized structures released by infected cells help spread HIV, new study finds. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-10 16:02:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-10 15:25:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Don't get me wrong, I'll happily read a tattered paperback, but a well-designed book is a pleasure unto itself.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The Unsung Delight of a Well-Designed Endpaper </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-10 15:25:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Origins of Male Domination May Lie in Food </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-10 14:59:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-10 14:28:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  It took a median of 4.2 years after the drugs were approved for these safety concerns to come to light, the study found, and issues were more common among psychiatric drugs, biologic drugs, drugs that were granted "accelerated approval" and drugs that were approved near the regulatory deadline for approval.

Damn. I was assuming the issues came to light just after approval, when they were used for the first time outside clinical trials. 4 years is a long time to not know about safety issues.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-10 14:25:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This is so cool. Can't wait for a future in which everybody has their own personal probiotic cocktail that gets tweaked at your annual physical.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-10 14:10:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'd read the hell out of a study on two-parent households that had a variety of gender groupings.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-20 20:35:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> http://science.sciencemag.org/content/356/6335/307 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> In a new discovery, naked mole-rats can metabolize fructose like plants, allowing them to survive for over 5 hours deprived of oxygen. The finding has implications for heart attack and stroke treatments. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-20 20:34:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Umbilical Cord Compound Boosts Brain Power in Mice </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-20 18:34:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-20 18:09:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This is the key idea: "They should just realize that closing the information gap isnt the goal. And instead, they need to learn how to communicate science strategically." </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-20 18:07:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yes! I knew I saved this card for a reason :)  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Google's Plan to Build Ad-Blocking Into Chrome Could Be a Very Good Thing </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-20 18:06:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Scientists, Stop Thinking Explaining Science Will Fix Things. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-20 17:55:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-20 16:37:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Feel like I've been hearing a lot about newly discovered potentially habitable Earth-like planets lately. Anyone know why? Better detection methods? A more intentional effort to look for them?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-20 16:33:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Here's the study in Science: http://advances.sciencemag.org/content/3/4/e1600582

The crazy thing about this to me is that even the guy working off of models that predicted this trash would be there is "surprised" by how much it is.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> A major ocean current is carrying plastic debris into the Arctic, where it's trapped by landmasses like Greenland and the polar ice cap. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-20 16:31:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-20 16:08:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah, there are so many cool studies about novel sources of new antibiotics (like say [Komodo dragon blood](https://www.nytimes.com/2017/04/17/health/komodo-dragon-blood-antibiotics.html?_r=0)!). But probably the biggest bang for your buck solutions are in less sexy stuff like this (no offense to OP or the scientists who did the research)  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-13 16:41:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Congrats! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [Article] A Dinosaur Cousins Crocodile Ankles Surprise Paleontologists </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-13 16:34:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-13 15:58:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I was at the start and then I bought a few packs. Is the f2p tag gone at a certain limit or is it just 1 pack bought and it's over? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> NASA's ocean worlds announcement: watch the live stream at 2PM ET </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-13 15:53:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-13 15:45:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Was gonna craft that quest but realized it was just a curve deck and decided against it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Burger King thought it had a great idea. Instead, it ended up with a Whopper of a problem - ad designed to trigger Google's voice-activated Home smart speaker </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-13 15:43:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-30 12:54:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Study is available here: http://dx.doi.org/10.1038/s41536-017-0012-5  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Eye grafted onto tails of blind tadpoles allows them to see, and learn from visual information. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-30 12:50:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-28 17:57:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Amazing thank you! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-28 14:26:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I completely agree. You have an idea for an effect and consider it of legend quality one set and the next you go nah it's rare. Just goes to show how good Sylvanas was </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Facebook launches stories to complete its all-out assault on Snapchat </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-28 14:24:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
