<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject6703</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-10 04:46:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Its a light read and goes pretty quick. The first few stories are probably the worst and seem like they're all the same, but (imo) they get better as you go on and piece certain things together. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-10 04:41:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I like to think this is a joke.

I mean I do think it is and people are taking you seriously, but I've been wrong about these things before. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-10 04:41:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hey man, don't talk shit about Wordsworth Classics. They have the best covers. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Who here has read James Franco's Palo Alto? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-10 04:37:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Might have been the quickest I've ever read a book other than Of Mice and Men. I really liked it but I can't figure out why, and I can't find much discussion about it. For example, I think its really interesting that the second part of the book introduces a bunch of new characters out of nowhere, and then focuses mainly on them. And how "I Could Kill Somebody" never tells you who the narrator is, or how the situation ends.

Anyone wanna discuss it with me? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-09 23:43:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Went in last night for the first time in a while and asked a guy about it. He gave me some weird answer about how certain companies give special prices to the online store, and some other stuff that didn't really make sense. It seemed like he gets asked that a lot and just has to make shit up. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-08 22:31:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I wonder if my my mom would be able to get it from a distributor, since she owns a bar. Then again I'm thinking there's a distributor like Diamond, except for alcohol. I don't know how that works.

Anyway thanks for the info! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-08 07:22:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Can confirm, I've been at my job longer than probably half of my co workers and I've only been there 6 months. The company treats us like shit, doesn't pay on time, doesn't pay right, and otherwise cheats the workers.

Good thing I'm done this month. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-07 23:19:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> ? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-06 18:52:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That's really sad. I love Boy's Club. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-05 22:19:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I've been meaning to ask this for a while now, so, thanks!

I do it for characters who I think we're perfectly casted (like Batman and Joker, Cyborg, Iron Man, Rocket Raccoon, etc). Other times, I have to make up my own (Dennis Quade is Hal Jordan, Donald Glover is Miles Morales, Jake Gyllenhall/Brad Pitt/stereotypical New Yorker/myself as the different personalities of Moon Knight, Bruce Campbell is any pulp or over the top character).

I'm having a hard time "casting" Hellboy (Ron Pearlman never did it for me), Dr. Doom (I always heard Christopher Lee, but Doom should have an Eastern European accent), Robotman (I'm thinking some Old Hollywood actor like James Dean, with his racing background), and Kitty.

Oddly enough, aside from MK, I hear myself when I read Negative Man and Reader. Not because I have a good voice for it, because I don't, but it just happens. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-05 21:50:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I like the color version because the art style makes it hard to tell which character is which sometimes, and color helps with that. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-05 21:30:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Kind of ridiculous that the gaming industry has gotten to the point where DLC is announced before the game is even out and everyone's fine with it.

And I was gonna guess Subz would be in this one since Scorpion was in the first and that's just how they do things, but I second guessed myself because Freeze and Captain Cold are already in the game. Guess I was wrong. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-05 21:19:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Slightly off topic but where do these restless covers come from? Like who has access to the original art to post it? Or is there some sort of Photoshop trickery at work here? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-05 19:07:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I think just honest.

Having to deal with fanboys all the time would suck, especially if it's fanboys for a series you're not even that proud of.

Whereas most famous people seem really fake about loving their fans, Harrison Ford just seems like he's tired of it, which is a nice change of pace from the "I'm so humble" approach that many take just to sell the product and look good. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-05 10:34:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That movie makes Mortal Kombat fatalities look like hugs from grandma. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-05 08:23:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I used to watch Nerdwriter videos, until I started watching Every Frame a Painting, KaptainKristian, and Ryan Hollinger.

Now Nerdwriter doesn't seem worth the time. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-05 07:10:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  go on a rampage

Didn't he only shoot like one or two people? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-05 07:08:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Dude Mark Hamill does a great fucking Harrison Ford impression. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-05 01:30:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I read on a wiki or something that Reed is confirmed to be on the spectrum, but that could have been wiki fuckery. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-05 01:19:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I think Alan Moore actually dismissed that, but I could be wrong. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-04 07:29:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> $ </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-04 00:51:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm a guy so probably not. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Are the library editions worth it? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-03 22:46:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> New to Hellboy but I've been wanting to get into the series for a long time. I've read Seed of Destruction and a couple of one shots, but those were a long time ago.

Anyway now I'm hooked, and ready for more. I've been thinking about just getting the trades because, for the main series, that's like $100. But if I went for the hardcovers (which I love the look of, and I buy probably 1/3 of my comics in that format), it would be *way* more expensive. Are there any cool bonuses that come with the library editions, or do the just look good on a shelf? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-03 20:56:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Oh my God that dog is so cute I want to pet him </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-03 20:33:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'll be getting whatever free books look good because my regular store has a limit of five, but I live close to Things From Another World, whose limit is 10. They're also giving out swag bags and I intend to get there early to get one.

I'll probably get trades for a few Image books I've been wanting to read (Head Lopper, Seven to Eternity, etc) because my LCS is having a 25% off everything sale.

A bit later in the day I'll hopefully be getting Steve Leiber to sign my copy of The Fix #1, and Joshua Williamson to sign The Flash #21 at a different TFAW location. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-03 20:17:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If I had one guess as to who didn't write that letter, it would be Frank Miller. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-03 20:15:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Danger Five comic adaptation when? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-03 10:22:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Please explain </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-02 10:48:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah it was really fucked up that someone spray painted some ATMs that belonged to a group of really rich people who were stealing from the lower and middle class. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-02 04:03:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That would be much appreciated, thanks! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-02 03:32:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I dig it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-02 03:08:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hey did you end up finding anything out? I checked the website and didn't see much, but I haven't called or anything.
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-02 00:05:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> **HELL YEEEEEEEEEAAAAAAAH!** </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-01 23:59:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Fuck you. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-01 22:52:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Don't be a dick, man. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Is Mansions of Madness being reprinted? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-01 05:19:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I went to a LGS the other day and was talking to an employee, and lamented never being able o try MoM. He said I am in luck because they're making more copies of the second edition, and took my name and phone number to call me when it comes out.

I haven't seen anyone mention it and didn't see anything about it after a quick Google search. Any info about that? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-01 01:03:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Nice, super excited for this now. Not expecting that to happen, but its really cool he would do that. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-01 00:17:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> How much does he charge for commissions? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-30 23:42:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  We talked for the entire time about the industry, Hawkeye, Superior Foes, The Fix, what Nick Spencer is actually like in real life, 9/11

Quite the jump there. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-30 23:41:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm gonna try to get Leiber to sign my copy of The Fix#1 on FCBD and hearing this makes me super excited. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-30 23:39:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Found this a few weeks ago for $4.

I probably would have bought it for 10 times that. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-30 23:10:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Moving back to Salem at the end of May. It's not that bad, I promise.

Actually it's horrible please don't let what happened to Portland happen in Salem I have no where else to go </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-30 22:41:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah all anarchists are violent and chaotic. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-30 22:13:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So Much Less sounds like the "deep" album that no one liked by the shitty 90s boy band Really That.

The song sounds more like it would be by The Descendants or the Dead Milkmen. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-30 05:42:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Or just don't use paypal. I made an account and never completed all of the registration (didn't feel like putting my SSN into an essentially unregulated busimess). A few weeks ago, I got a collections letter for a PayPal credit card that had spent $~3000. It wasn't connected to the PayPal account I had made but never completed registration for, but was in my name.

Weeks later I'm still trying to get it off my record. PayPal customer service was no help. I'm fairly young with essentially no credit history so if I don't get this figured out, I'm fucked. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-28 21:04:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Fuck. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-28 00:07:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah I'm the same way, I'd rather earn it but if I have it, it might as well go towards some warehouses. Thanks for the info! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [Discussion] Recommended preliminary reading for Watchmen, for someone who hasn't read many comics? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-28 00:06:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> After some prodding, I got my girlfriend to read Saga and Descender and she really liked both. She expressed a little interest in Watchmen so I want her to read that, but I feel like it's important to have a bit of comic history knowledge to fully appreciate Watchmen.

I figure a couple Golden Age and Silver Age superhero stories will give her enough contex on cape comics at the time. What would you recommend for this? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-27 23:58:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> For some reason I had it in my mind that he had several X-Men series running concurrently. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-27 23:57:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This is sick </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-27 23:57:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I thought those were OOP and super expensive like hHickman's FF but they're all $100. Thanks! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-27 22:19:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I've been wanting to do this, but I can't find a guide for the order, which is something I'm a big fan of. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-27 21:36:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Messing with the timeline again... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-27 21:31:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  getting rid of modded money

Is this something you have to do? My cousin and I played a couple of days ago and something happened where we teleported to the airport and got several hundred thousand dollars each.

We were scared because we don't want to get banned+reset, but I didn't know what to do. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-27 11:03:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Bloody Disgusting, coming at you with real journalism! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-27 11:01:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> While I agree that taking out the color doesn't make it black and white, there are definitely film noir elements in the movie. A few shots as well as plot points give it a bit of a neo noir feeling.

That said, I think this is kinda dumb. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-27 10:48:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I don't know where you're getting that it was partially a horror movie, but I don't think thats even slightly true.

And if you're watching that movie for the characters, you're not watching that movie right. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-26 23:12:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Well shit now I have to buy it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-26 08:42:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm not even kidding when I say I would buy Fuck Shit Holocaust in a heartbeat, just to have it on a shelf. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-26 04:51:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What's in the Iron Giant set? I've been thinking about snagging one but I can't find what it comes with. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-25 18:59:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Tom king vision omnibus

I would be completely open to that if the omnibus part wasn't at the end. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-25 08:48:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Did you just have a mad discount or what? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-25 03:16:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I never knew that about it starting as a UT mod.

So in a way, Reactive Drop is kind of like a mod of a remake of a mod for a game. Weird. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-25 01:23:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Like the Hills Have Eyes? That would be so fuckin sweet. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-25 00:54:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yo I'm not a comic snob but Stan Lee gets all the credit for a bunch of stuff he only partially contributed to, takes credit for stuff he didn't have a hand in at all, and may have intentionally portrayed women in comics poorly (I mean he did, but as to whether or not he wrote specific elements for the sole purpose of making women lame).
I don't hate him and I'm grateful for what he's done for the medium, but I can understand why people would dislike him. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-24 17:57:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I...I like handjobs... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-24 05:49:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm broke and can't afford 4G, so I'm still that idiot that gets lost every day. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-24 05:43:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Listen to the ones that say featuring Alina. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-24 00:13:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I have a job!

Rent, food, low impulse control, and gas are expensive tho </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-23 23:38:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm 19 and I wish my checking account looked like that. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-23 01:54:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Except that didn't happen. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-21 09:04:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What about people like me who eat it because its healthy but don't really taste it at all? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-21 08:58:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> While I agree, I'd also like to say that the whole thing about soldiers being abused by everyone when they came home is vastly exaggerated. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-21 08:55:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I live in Portland and I know of three video stores. I also know that that's just in SW and there are probably a lot more.

I love going. $2.50 for a huge selection and five nights? Plus its a regular copy of the movie so there's special features and stuff, unlike redbox and digital renting? Fuck yeah, you know I'm going to a video store at least once a week. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-21 08:51:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> And even then, he doesn't become the hulking, undead monster a lot of people think of him as until the sixth movie, which is pretty crazy. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-21 08:43:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Of course I missed it. Well thanks anyway! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Anyone got the hook-up on the Gorillaz show pre sale code? 94/7 won't send it to me. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-21 05:41:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I've been signed up on the 94/7 mailing list for forever but for some reason, they're not sending me the link for the pre sale tickets. I feel like they're gonna sell out immediately tomorrow. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-20 07:25:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I know the word is being overused right now but this post is so effin wholesome. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-20 04:24:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I started reading and figured I misread the top and that this is a joke. 

I giggled, and went back up to see how I misread it.

Turns out, I didn't.

What the fuck </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-20 01:00:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Case in point: GTA V. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-20 00:41:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The only one I'm pulling is Green Arrow and I love reading that shit. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-20 00:37:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I've only read half of the first issue but it's already one of my favorite current comics. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-20 00:36:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Same writer/artist. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-20 00:30:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  ok </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-20 00:19:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Probably not. Maul gets fucking cut in half in TPM and Attack of he Clones had way more violence (drawn out war scene, tusken raider massacre, Sam's slow death, etc), and both of those are still PG. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-20 00:14:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  ok </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-20 00:13:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Sure, but not because of the ending. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-20 00:12:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> How could I forget </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-20 00:00:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm so upset I was never able to play the game in its prime. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-19 23:17:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> While I agree that HP Lovecraft's treatment of minorities and women was terrible, I also agree that it seems like that was normal at the time (as someone else said). I've also read stuff about him being a pretty nice guy (like him always playing with the neighborhood kids as an older teenager).

Then again he's one of my favorite writers so I might be a bit biased. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-19 04:22:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Okay? I'm saying on the whole, the movies had a PG rating, and specifically, those two, even though they came out after the introduction of a PG-13 rating. Regardless, this a really dumb argument because the movies wouldn't have been PG-13 anyway, unless, like a lot of movies, they were altered specifically to get that rating. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-19 04:12:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Episodes I and II didn't. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-19 02:45:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Not even a little bit. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-19 02:45:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I don't understand this answer. A color being involved in a movie has never been something I've heard a movie praised for. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-19 02:44:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  Chainsaw would still naturally move away

 implying someone's head wouldn't

lol </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-19 01:42:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This is a series about space wizards. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-19 01:40:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> There's always a relevant Mallrats quote. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-19 01:40:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I meant why is that a selling point. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-19 00:43:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What do you do with these? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-19 00:29:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What's the big deal about the green lightsaber? I watched the movies as a little kid so most stuff like that goes over my head when I watch it now, since I've always known it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-19 00:28:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The "ending was too happy" complaint is so weird to me. Like I've never seen Star Wars as this super gritty series. Sure, there are dark moments, but at the end of the day, the movies are PG. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-19 00:13:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> As an aspiring bank robber (not really but I'd be lying if I said that's not one of my top fantasies), Waingro is the worst because of this. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-18 19:43:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Wait this link doesn't lead to Click hole. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-18 19:36:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm usually the first to point out something unintentionally dirty, but I don't actually see anything wrong with this. Like nothing points to this being sexual or incestuous. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-18 06:23:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I would do unspeakable things for a first printing of that baby. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-17 23:37:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I've never worked in or owned a comic shop, but there are two things I can suggest in regards to pull lists.

Like someone else said, a discount for pulling more books is awesome. I get so many more books than I normally would because it gets me a nice 20% discount.

Anorher thing that I haven't seen anyone say is offer a discount for charging people's cards when the comics are put in the box. So Tommy might only come in once every two weeks for his comics. That can hurt owners by having to wait to get paid. So instead, give people ~5% off as an incentive to let you take their card info, and charge the remotely on Wednesdays. It's a win win. My shop does that and it makes me feel good knowing I'm not hurting the shop just because I can only afford to make it in once every two weeks or so, usually. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-17 23:14:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Got a couple new games for my group, and we tried them out on Saturday. We're pretty new to board games (aside from the classic ones, we've pretty much only played Dead of Winter and Betrayal at House on the Hill), so it was interesting to play three wildly different games.

The Voting Game was kind of fun. It's not much of a game, though, as much as it was a catalyst to start discussion and storytelling. Or maybe we played it wrong.

The Oregon Trail was...interesting. it was $10 at Target so I figured I'd try it. By that point in the night there were only three of us playing, and we got about halfway before we were all dead. Seemed like there's not much skill or strategy involved, which is kind of a turn off. I'll have to try it again.

The last game of the night was Love Letter. It was a hard sell, but after I used the guard and guessed that my friend had the princess as the first turn of a round, we started having a blast. So much metagaming. At $10, probably the second best game I've played in terms of band for your buck. First is Betrayal because it was like $25 and I've already played that for like 10 hours. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-17 20:00:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What you don't wanna spend $500 on one book? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-17 19:57:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The fucking Doom comic.

Not Doctor Doom, but the one shot based on the game.

It's the most insane comic I've ever read, and I only got to read it because there was a digital scan that someone voiced over and put on YouTube.

I have no idea where I would even find it.

Edit: a physical copy, I mean. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-17 19:47:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Ah, thanks for the info. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-17 19:47:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Touch  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-17 05:29:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Is there any way to tell them apart, other than the name? I've always wondered how all the old horror anthologies were different, because they all seem pretty similar. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-17 05:20:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> They downvoted because people are dicks and this might oppose what they think.

The top comment says it would be him basically because his stuff makes the most money. How much merchandise do you think Luke sells compared to Darth Vader? Yoda? Chewie?

If you think about impact, legacy, importance in the universe, similarity to the most archetypical hero, etc, it's definitely Superman. The DC universe seems like, in a way, it kind of revolves around Superman. For example, look at Red Son. He lands in a different part of the world, and the entire world is completely different. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
