<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject3122</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-10 04:53:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Do you have a source for this? I wonder what's up.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-10 00:03:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Sounds about right. We have these sorts of issues by both subarea and gender. Tricky stuff! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-09 17:13:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> As a solid Democrat, I feel like Salon is my tinfoil hat-wearing Uncle. This article is nonsense...stop making us look bad, Salon!! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Use of Bayesian Decision Analysis in Patient-Centered Randomized Clinical Trials in Oncology - A one-size-fits-all approach to Type 1 error controls fails to minimize expected patient harm in clinical trials for cancer drugs. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-08 21:37:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-08 00:56:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Are they sufficiently secure in their gerrymandering efforts that they aren't worried about losing power? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-07 23:05:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> How hard would it be to create an app that could crowdsource that information? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-04 00:12:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That sounds like a project that will require the careful combination multiple data sets. Income inequality data can be obtained from a variety of sources. Emanuel Saez has data for his various papers on income inequality available at his research website. There must also be other groups that have similar data and statistics. The rest of the data, and the appropriate design for the analysis, are a mystery to me.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-03 18:30:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I don't understand why we have to get abusive police officers on video before this type of action is taken. It seems like the officers (the few bad apples) most likely to engage in this type of severe bad behavior already have some history of complaints and aggressiveness. Why isn't that viewed as a red flag that leads to greater scrutiny and monitoring of the officer? That's how it would work with any other employee...smoke would at least lead to a suspicion of fire. 

Citizen journalism shouldn't be the only way to keep the police honest! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-03 06:39:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I pick Kakuryu, Takayasu, and Yoshikaze. 

Edit: Changed my pick from Terunofuji to Kakuryu on May 3rd at 1:03 AM.
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> This pooch is waiting at the drive-thru! </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-29 17:01:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> I guess he couldn't wait for his parents to make dinner... </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-29 16:44:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What are the most important battles in history? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-21 07:36:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Former Sumotori Musashimaru and Akebono Hospitalized in Japan </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-19 07:13:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-19 06:40:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I can't tell if you are a faculty member or a post-doc,something which I think is important to consider here. If you're making a lateral move, it's possible your current department might look askance at your passing off hosting duties to someone else. You should do it anyway, but they might be irritated.

In any other conceivable case where you'd be making a move up (e.g. Contingent faculty to full time, clinical faculty to tenure track, post-doc to faculty member), you should expect and get the full support of your current department to go and take the interview. Don't even think twice about telling them the situation.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-19 06:32:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Fraud aside, that's not a bad writing effort for a 7-year old. I say he gets a drawn-out lecture telling him how he isn't as clever as he thinks and a night of video games for the writing. Some punishment, some reward.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Nurse Practitioner Refusing to Accept a Private Practice Patient </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-15 03:46:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-14 14:53:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> In his mind, the two situations are probably not connected at all. He's turning her down was a good thing (In his fantasy land) because she needed "improvement" and it led her to lose weight. OP turning him down cannot lead to improvement because kids can't be unborn. 

The delusion is powerful in this fellow, OP. He thinks he should get first crack at the physically hotter, but personality-wise the same, you based on your prior interest. Explore your expanded set of options and avoid men prone to tantrums.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-11 06:33:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I reach out to my colleagues to both commiserate and ask for their insights. I generally do exactly what you've done here - lay out the situation, their behavior, and my response. One or two of those conversations is usually enough to reassure me or, by contrast, to help me conclude what I've done wrong and plan for better future responses.

The read I get from your post is that you did the best you could under the circumstances. Your response sounds firm but fair. I bet further information about things they said would get you some combination of sympathy and "toppers."  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-10 00:35:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Jesus...talk about a hit job! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-03 18:58:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Man...I need to learn me some Japanese. I bet that's a very interesting video.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-03 18:11:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I think it's important to give the author credit where it's due. The author appears to have done an acceptable job of accounting for the sorts of health policy and socioeconomic factors you'd expect to be alternative explanations for the observed correlation. While I'd like the author to better explain their regression methodology to provide greater confidence in their results (they say time-series but don't explain which type of time series adjustments they make), they have done a strong job of developing the general model framework. Using leads and lags in their analysis establishes support for temporal precedence, one of the conditions required to support causation. More importantly, the paper includes several sensitivity/robustness checks which lend support to the result being more than just correlation. 

I'm not saying that paper provides 100% assurance that the relationship is causal. Writing off the results as being mere correlation, however, inappropriately (IMHO) discounts the robustness of the results.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-30 01:40:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Poor Kisenosato...looks like he's being subjected to water boarding. :-/ </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-28 07:40:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Nobody's more surprised than me that it all worked out. :-D </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-27 00:20:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This sounds a bit like how I'd expect my drunk uncle to tell the story on it's 15th telling. All that's missing is the viscous bloodhound chasing him to the ring and the Phoenix flying overhead when they approached for the tachiai. Oh...you also missed the very obvious "Terunophooey."

Mind if I swipe it for when I tell my friends at work tomorrow? :-D </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-26 13:04:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Fantastic end to the basho...simply fantastic! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-26 00:41:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Good for you! You deserve to have a partner who values and cherishes you. I'm sure you'll bounce back from this and move on to something better.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-25 21:27:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That's an interesting reply you got there! Someone translate untermensch (sub-human) from the original Nazi sources to use on you as an insult. Sounds like you struck a nerve! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-25 10:02:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I wouldn't put it past Kisenosato to show up tomorrow and keep on fighting, despite the fact that he is clearly in no shape to fight based on what we just saw. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-25 09:47:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm watching a live stream online and just logged in to say that Terunofuji is a scum bag. That henka was one of the most unsportsmanlike acts I've ever seen in my entire life. Against a man fighting for his career, that henka is simply indefensible. Disgusting! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-24 19:02:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I think you're right. I'm trying to find updates on the sumo forum, but some of it's in Japanese which I can't read. I wish him well, whatever it is.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-24 17:18:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> http://www.japantimes.co.jp/sports/2017/03/24/sumo/basho-reports/title-chase-heats-kisenosato-suffers-first-loss/#.WNVGUTz3aEc

Doesn't seem like It's a dislocation. I really hope he is well enough to finish this tournament up. He's been looking so good!  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-22 18:26:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Do you have any concerns about the appropriateness of this algorithm for sumo? For example, statistics in individual sports are (potentially) more skewed by injuries and specific match-up parameters (on-the-belt vs. pusher/thruster rikishi). Could a larger sample help this? What are your thoughts? Interesting analysis either way.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-22 18:15:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I have the ability to deliver bad news in ways that leave people feeling good.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-21 20:31:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That's great to know. Being relatively new to watching sumo, it's good to learn how the current era differs from historical trends. Thanks for your response! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-21 15:07:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Takayasu is looking fantastic! Is there any possibility that a 14-win performance gets him the promotion to Ozeki, or will he have to have a third winning tournament to get him there regardless of his performance this time? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-21 04:26:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I hear so many people crap on Kakuryu but have never actually gone to look at his record.

...that's some weak sauce for a Yokozuna. Several 9-6 and 10-5 showings since he was installed. How is he even hanging on? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-20 14:21:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I can't find the video for any of these sets on YouTube. Anybody have a link? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-20 06:02:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I think you misread something in the initial comment.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-19 22:55:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I know this isn't quite what you intended, but some of my research is in the area of behavioral economics. It causes me to view the behavior of people close to me in very different ways than I am used to. I've grown closer to my family in recent years as I have gained some understanding of the "economic" dynamics of our family. Of course, I've also had to learn to keep quiet about my observations because people don't enjoy being scrutinized like study participants during Thanksgiving dinner.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-19 22:15:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The pig clearly committed suicide. If he'd had a gun, he wouldn't have had to inconvenience anybody. Let's make guns easier to get! Nothing to see here... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-19 21:53:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Grape? Try strawberry jam, man...perfection! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-19 21:46:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> In accounting, they call that "spreading their fixed costs over as many units as possible." They paid for the rights to screen it, so they win when they play the movies as often as possible. I'd say we win too...but we all own our own copies already. :-/ </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-18 17:43:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That would require someone to go belt to belt with him. That isn't a great strategy for the smaller rikishi given how large he is and how much leverage it would take to just topple him over. He would also take the risk that a smaller, more nimble rikishi would simply sidestep his attempt to fall on them because of their relative spryness. When people go belt to belt with Orora, you usually see him simply use his physical bulk  to push them toward the bales and out of the ring. 

Here are some examples of his losses. Notice that they seem to focus on working him off balance, a considerable issue for larger sumo (smallish legs plus a big top makes for a shaky foundation). 

https://youtu.be/s1Bmqa7lLdE

https://youtu.be/k6qYpNWy0ZA

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-18 17:08:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So is depreciation on robots.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-18 02:58:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Rounded slice "tips" are for communists! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-17 20:21:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Propaganda takes time and careful construction...don't rush her! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-17 18:45:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Depends on the field and your job experience. I've seen some small, lower tier schools hire lawyers to teach things like accounting or finance in place of PhDs. But those lawyers tend to also have some expertise in the area (e.g. Estate planning). A master's doesn't give you the benefit of having a terminal degree to sell, however, so that will make things more difficult.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-17 16:30:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Vowel sounds are what actually travel through the air most clearly when speaking, so that's a practical reason to speed through the consonants...to get more sound going that reaches the rafters.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-15 23:42:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm starting to think Kotoshogiku will make it back to the ranks of the Ozeki. He looked great today! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-15 17:18:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It seems really important to you to get me to take back, or revise, my belief that he leaked his own return. I won't do that. 

I clearly did not see him put the returns in the reporter's box, nor did I hear him order anyone else to do so. I rely upon his well-documented pattern of behavior with respect to leaking things, his quick response to the leak (as opposed to his generally ignoring such things), the fact that 2005 was a unique year for him (Melania going up for citizenship and all), and the timing of the release in the middle of a bad news cycle related to health care. Of course, this evidence is circumstantial and will not convince you. I find it compelling, however, and will continue to do so. 

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-15 17:06:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You can believe what you want about what I meant. If being offended is so important to you, you'll find a way to get there without my help. 

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-15 16:57:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Being a regular contributor doesn't preclude the act of brigading. Nevertheless, I was talking more about the CNN bot when I made that comment rather than your post.  

As for the rest of your post, I won't dignify it with a response. 

Edit: See what I mean? And they are only posting material that is anti-CNN, which can be construed as pro-President.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-15 16:12:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I don't agree with your conclusion, but you're correct that nobody has provided evidence of the source of this document.

Edit: Of course, your frequent trips to Trump's subreddit suggest you might have some other reason for being rather belligerent in response to my initial comment. Perhaps I won't worry so much about what you think...

Edit 2: Are we at the point that /r/accounting is being brigaded by the President's supporters? I don't know what to make of this.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-15 15:56:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Even with the client copy stamped on the signature line and his history of leaking things selectively? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-15 11:25:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> A banana cactuar?!? Hahahahaha!! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-15 11:13:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I think saying she embarrassed herself on national TV is unfair. She used the occasion to point ask the right questions about his taxes. She also pointed out the variety of important information that we could learn from the full return (i.e. Income sources). The tax expert she had on even pointed out he might have leaked them himself. It's still not a very informative reveal, but I don't think it amounts to an embarrassment. 

Edit: Thanks for the gold, anonymous Redditor! I appreciate it.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-12 19:27:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Sex trafficking...I'm sure there is a lot that could be done to identify trafficking patterns.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-12 19:15:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I was cheering in my chair all by myself at home...I never do that. He's going back to Ozeki! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-12 19:14:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I am thinking Kisenosato makes it back-to-back wins with a 13-2 record. Also, Aoiyama (my favorite) is going to move up again with a solid, if unspectacular, 8-7.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-11 08:52:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What if you treated it as 10 samples of 100 instead of 1 sample of 1000 for each message? Then you'd have appropriate means (of the proportion) you can use for an ANOVA.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-10 22:23:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That's fair. Perhaps skepticism is a better  term.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-10 21:57:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This is an unpopular thing to say, but I think it needs to be said. Questions about the integrity of scientists in China (in particular, rather than just Asia more generally) spill over to evaluation of the graduate candidates they train. The resume embellishment issues are not limited to Asian candidates, but that will also lead to greater scrutiny for your package. 

Do you have any sense of the quality (i.e. ranking, editorial board composition, etc.) of the journals where you've published those papers OP? Can you provide clear evidence of your experience with engineering (i.e. Patents, highlighting specific project contributions, etc.)?

I second what has been said about aiming your sights lower in terms of graduate program ranking. Your GPA is too low to be considered as a viable candidate by many programs. Try expanding your pool of school, perform well while there, and then perhaps consider using that as a springboard to a better school for further graduate study. It's an expensive plan, but it might be the most viable given your circumstance. 

Edited: Added suggestions and deleted "academic" from "academic integrity." </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-10 21:22:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Congratulations! I hope it's everything you want it to be for as long as you decide you want to stay! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-10 21:16:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Nope...these are fine, but OP is clearly 47% better than any of them. I laughed so loud someone poked their head into my office to check on me! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-08 23:53:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I get your meaning and wasn't trying to be obtuse in my response. The issue, to me, is that society is much slower moving than even an industry. It's certainly slower moving than companies. It's not clear that society can adapt fast enough given how polarized things are these days. Still you raise a fair point...we at least have multiple years of notice if current estimates are accurate. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-08 20:58:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I don't think slow is the right word to use here. In fact, I think relatively fast might be the better way to describe the change. Some estimates suggest that 15-20 years is a range in which millions of people could be facing automation-related displacement. That's rather fast in terms of societal development.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-08 16:32:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That's because their hypermasculine daddies didn't know how to show emotion, leaving a generation of traumatized parents. Giving your child a trophy is reassurance that your own father loved you! /s </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-08 16:28:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I didn't say they weren't. I'm simply saying that I only now know them because they were highlighted in the title. 

I'm not defending reposting. Just saying I got some benefit thus time. 

Edit: I also saw a different video when I watched this match initially, so that's perhaps why I didn't know the names.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-08 16:20:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I didn't know the names of the rikishi before, so at least this repost has some added value.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-08 09:00:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I figured you were making a very subtle political commentary on our dear Leader's similarity in appearance to the depicted root vegetable and his propensity for poor spelling and grammar. I gave it 10/10 for subtlety. So subtle you didn't even know it was happening.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-08 08:35:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I've always loved Kingpin because of a quirky ending like that.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-05 02:56:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah...that's the missing piece of the story. I wouldn't want to be enmeshed with people like that either. I'm sure you'll find other ways to get by, but it certainly sounds like making friends isn't "on the cards," so to speak. Best wishes to you! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
