<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject7891</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-11 19:58:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Because it was me. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-11 16:13:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That guy on the right looks awesome... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-11 22:52:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hot Fuzz is also set in those parts. But in both cases the accent is watered down (apart from the unintelligible farmer with the Arsenal).
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-11 10:02:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That's certainly not what I learnt at college. England has a huge variety of accents, all tied intimately into very pronounced social class structures. What you are probably thinking of as "the English Accent" is called Received Pronunciation or RP and originates in the Home Counties around London. For most of the 19th and 20th centuries, and to an extent now, this was the prestige accent associated with the rich and powerful wealthy enough not to actually have to live in London but who tend to cluster near it for access to Whitehall, the City, and the Royal Court. It's where one can have a stately home with 10,000 acres but still be in Lord's in time for port and cigars.

But the English settlers who first colonised North America didn't come from London or the Home Counties; they came from the area around England's major merchant port of the time, Bristol (called the West Country). The West Country accents still have pronounced terminal /r/s and long flat vowels today, like most North American accents.

So there hasn't actually been that much of a phonemic shift at all. It's just that the settlers never spoke with what you think of as "the English accent".

And as for "the influence of Irish immigrants to New York" - well, just remember that Dublin is a hell of a lot closer to Bristol than it is to New York... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-20 11:24:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Buddhism is about practice, not beliefs. Practice has effects. To an extent, "belief" or "faith" as they are defined in Abrahamic religions have no place in Buddhism. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-10-27 20:37:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Well, if you're allowing "pair" you should also allow "trio", "quartet", "quintet", "sextet", "heptet", and "octet" too. There are probably members of that set for 9 and 10, as well, but I can't think what. Oh, and a group of 1 is a "monad". </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-10-14 03:19:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Did You Know?: Until the late 18th Century, "cunt" was the accepted anatomical term in English and "vagina" was considered obscene and derogatory. I guess the translator for this sign is, like, *really* old-fashioned.

Source: This fascinating book. https://www.goodreads.com/book/show/6783738-womanwords </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-10-02 00:43:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You could use PayPal... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-08-24 00:53:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Good theory, but the measure you should be looking at is not physical size, but number of regional (or class) accents. Britain has a ridiculous number of different accents, many of which are very distinct (eg. Edinburgh compared with Cockney). We also have very strong associations between accent and social class, much like I understand there is a distinct "redneck" accent. The difference is that in Britain, *EVERY* accent carries its associations and their attendant rivalries and prejudices. Hence the saying that "every time an Englishman opens his mouth, he makes another Englishman hate him." Because of this social function, I suppose British people are conditioned into being more aware of accent.

FWIW, Gwynnie Paltrow did a convincing accent even before she moved over here. Robert Downey Jr is just laughable. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-08-17 01:29:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I think people would probably stop downvoting you if the photo, the subject matter, or the joke had anything to do with islands whatsoever, or if you had capitalised "Isle" to make your alleged joke make even the barest sense. Just admit you selected the wrong homophone, and take the corrections with grace. We all do it from time to time. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-08-16 17:24:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Upvote for using "trepidatiously" - one more thing to be proud of, op. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-08-13 04:38:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Okay, now I feel bad. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-14 20:29:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah, but I'm not saying I have a different assessment from the majority of people, I'm saying I have the same assessment DESPITE having different experience. So your argument that the fact that the majority of people give the same assessment suggests that the majority of people have the same experience is false. If you follow me. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-14 20:17:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I probably find aesthetically pleasing the same colour combinations that you do, but I'm red-green colourblind. That to me suggests that your reasoning is flawed: my qualia ("the experience of perceiving") with colours are significantly different from yours because my sensing equipment is different from yours, but we both (very likely) think that the same specific colour combinations are appealing. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-14 20:11:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Then they can kiss my heavily-armed proletarian ass. Boycott the Cryptarchs! #occupythetower </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-15 04:56:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I thoroughly recommend Headblade. Their shaving lotion and moisturiser (branded "Head Slick" and "Head Lube") are also really good. With the razor clipped around your finger, the motion is the same as running your palm over your scalp. Really easy and safe. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-06 16:59:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The *economic* rather than political opposite of communism is not democracy but capitalism. "Capital" is the concentration of wealth. Capitalism without regulation ("free-market") largely serves to concentrate wealth in a relatively small section of society. It's a natural function of the system. You can try to mitigate that by regulation, or you can try to remove capital from the equation by making sure that the means of production (which generate wealth) are commonly owned by everyone. That's communism. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-20 08:58:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> 35mm frames may be "squarish" but different aspect ratios are not caused by changing the shape of the film or by cropping out parts of the frame; they're achieved by filming and projecting through anamorphic lenses which "stretch" the image. You may have experienced a film being projected with the "wrong aspect ratio" which means that the projectionist has selected the wrong lens for the projector. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-11 22:37:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> More likely OP is either a troll or a psychopath. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-11 22:23:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Also, I think the quote marks are in the wrong place:

Blurred Lines "by" Robin Thicke </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-18 20:29:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> In the image it's "lighted" not "lightened". "Lighted" is a perfectly acceptable past-tense participle of the verb "to light". It is more usual to see it as an adjective, but it is actually interchangeable with "lit" in both British and American English.

http://www.dailywritingtips.com/shone-vs-shined-lit-vs-lighted/ </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-07 21:29:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Walt dies happy? I think you and I watched different shows.... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-26 10:38:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Presumably because the extra syllable in "accidentally" is just too much effort. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-14 02:49:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Bumblebees don't generally live alone. In most species, the queen nests underground and will generate a colony of up to a few hundred daughter bees and drones. The queen hibernates over winter while the rest of the colony dies. She'll start a new colony when she wakes up.

Honeybees are fascinating, but so little is known about bumblebees (because their nests are so hard to find) that they're fascinating AND mysterious.

I thoroughly recommend this book on bumblebees - "A Sting in the Tale" by Dave Goulson

http://books.google.co.uk/books/about/A_Sting_in_the_Tale.html?id=MeKKfNsaWEEC redir_esc=y

Also, if you're interested in honeybees, "Clan Apis" by Jay Hosler is a really good graphic novel by a bee scientist.

http://modernfarmer.com/2013/05/this-is-the-best-comic-book-about-bees-youll-ever-read/ </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-10 13:03:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> And that's why you keep your spare sticks in a holster on your floor tom. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-05 14:12:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Did You Know?: they had to replace all the seats on the rented bikes after the shoot.

Source: Roger Taylor said so on a Queen documentary I saw a while ago. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-12-28 20:14:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yes, but the damage starts at 300/302. You do lose the perks and have to unlock them again. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-12-26 10:08:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I think you'd probably enjoy Man Plus by Frederik Pohl.

http://en.m.wikipedia.org/wiki/Man_Plus </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-12-18 23:06:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Came here to say this. Double thumbs-up for Ubik - I'm pretty sure Charlie Brooker would acknowledge it's influence on the Winter Special. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-12-17 09:10:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If you had continued to watch, you would have found out that that character is a sex offender and torturer. It's not like he's being held up as an example. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-11-30 16:28:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Oh my god, YES. I play on headphones and every time there's a high-stakes gameplay challenge that would require teamwork, the music swells and I can't hear my team-mates. At least not until they start shouting at me for not doing what they were telling me to do, but by then I already look like an idiot.

Destiny: "Hordes of bad guys coming? Big boss around? Wouldn't it be a shame if I suddenly took away your ability to communicate with the rest of your fire team? Especially so you can hear that track that sounds like it was lifted directly from Saving Private Ryan. At ear-splitting volume. Again. Muahahahahahaaaaa!"

Bungie, stop me looking like an idiot through no fault of my own. You know it's the least you can do. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-11-30 08:53:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That's really ingenious and very well explained. Thanks, </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-11-28 13:18:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The Volkswagen Beetle (and the start of VW) was Hitler's project to show how the Nazis were benefitting ordinary German citizens. I think the modern company would rather just stay away from anything that might bring that to mind.

http://www.bytwerk.com/gpa/vw.htm </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-11-28 12:34:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Because investing in education is expensive, and it takes years or decades before the benefits are felt in the wider economy. If you were in charge, why would you spend that money when you might not be in power in five years? Why not spend it instead on short-term vote-winning things like wars? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
