<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject7806</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-10 11:30:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Not really, but they probably do exist somewhere. You know, with the entire "anonimity" thing of this sub, it can get fairly easy to hide a nationality. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-10 04:26:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Aye, sir </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-10 03:05:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Oh, well, thank you. There are actually many more than one could expect, in fact, and I don't know if that's good or not. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-10 01:09:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Oooh I know where you took the inspiration for that one from!

... which means I need to stop reading so much TRP bullshit, Jesus on a bycicle Christ. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-10 01:06:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Or an Australian going "OI, YA CUNT" :^D </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-10 00:57:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm in love with the comments on this thread, thanks a lot y'all :^D </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Childhood Memories, Part I: How I Killed My Sister When I Was Two </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-10 00:31:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I am sure you sleep well at night after reading the stories you find here. Everyday, with every new story upvoted, you already know everything is fictional, but acts out as a believer because of the rules of the sub.

Well, I wish I could do the same. My story here will not be fictional, or in any way "dilluted" out of respect for any of the characters present here. For a fact, I can say that I'll lack some depth on certain parts of the narrative for lack of memory, not out of fear; you see, these events happened up until I was 9, and some of them lack enough to be confusing. But what can I say? When you're young and want to forget certain traumatic events, you slowly start to forget them until they fade away at some point.

I guess I should present myself and my past first. I don't see the need of using my real name, so let's just say it's Alex. I was born on a small hospital somewhere on the East of So Paulo, and that's it. The day I was born, my older sister had to go from house to house close to where we lived to ask for baby clothing, as my family had little to no money to even buy one - and the money we had was either spent on what food we could get... or my father spent it on alcohol.

My father always wanted a son. For his lack of luck (or some form of karma, probably, though I am not one of believing it), on his four attempts of having a male child, every single one was born a girl. 

The first was a disappointment. She was born when the family still held a good amount of money; for the next five years, she lived an exceptional life, being homeschooled from an early age and being teached piano classes every Wednesday. My father, although disappointed, did not mind his first child being a girl. For security reasons, just call her Lucy.

The second came two years later, and made him feel angry. She was also a girl (which I'll call Cleo), and a stronger one, but he did not care. When she was born, he blamed my mother for not giving him his "well deserved son".

That was when money started to grow scarce, and the stronger beatings began. Before, he'd do so only on a few moments and away from his daughter; after his second child was born, he did not care at all, and simply did it, also using it as a way of impregnating his children's mind with fear.

Then, one year later, his third child was born, and she made him feel scared. Scared because she never felt fear. Scared, because she knew everything that would happen later on with details, including her own death. Scared, because she had a strong presence in front of him. Let's call her Elizabeth; she predicted that she was going to die when she was four years old.

Then, two years later, I was born. My family was in such state of poverty that they almost never had butter, and food was mostly composed of pure bread with a cup of coffee for each. In fact, when I was four months old, my mother did not breastfeed me anymore; at that age, I was already being fed with cow milk mixed with coffee by my own sisters, as my mother never had the time to feed me, overworking herself with cleaning other people's houses and washing and ironing clothes for the neighbours. She didn't manage the money of the house, though: my father did. That's why we were always lacking food.

My father was not very present on my childhood. Actually, the only person who ever dealt with him on a closer level was Lucy, but as the elder child, she was the favourite one of the bunch: mom liked her more than the other three, and Lucy had to deal with less fear than her sisters. When she was the only child, my father treated her like a little princess; at that age, she was not aware of what happened between her parents, nor the things her father did when he was outside home. He was a drunkard, addicted to both alcohol and gambling, and when he was with his "friends" on the bar, he'd smoke. Plus, he cheated on my mother, both with other women he deemed more attractive and with prostitutes.

But mom never told her. Lucy just learned about that later, when she was 12. The only bad thing she knew he did was the beating.

Cleo... was pretty left out. She had the surname of my father, and considering how both my mom and father's families were "rivals", treating the other side as despicable, she never got to be treated properly inside my mom's family. See, grandma would often call her a bastard simply because of the surname difference. On the other hand, dad's family received her well, a lot better than it ever did with any other child of his. 

Along with the poor treatment she received from her relatives, she was often blamed for the lack of money that came along after she was born: as my parents had to move out from hundreds of houses lots and lots of times, each because my father would not pay the rent properly, he'd put the guilt on her and on grandma.

Cleo also never knew about his wrongdoings, and thus believed him when he said it was her fault. She would find out a lot later as well that it was a lie.

Elizabeth... I can't truly remember a lot from her. What I do remember is that she was both the happiest and the saddest of the bunch; her emotions were a complete paradox, probably because of her future sight. I know, it sounds impossible and even odd, but she truly *did* that. She would always tell us what she saw during these events.

That includes her death. I was the one who caused it.

You see, she was around four years old when she told us that; she never told about these sights to my father, only us, and this one was no exception. But still, she saw her own death, and on the vision, Elizabeth was hit by a car and died instantly.

Back then, we dismissed it. I, for one, also dismissed it, more because I was too young to understand than anything, but also because the thought of having my own sister dying scared and saddened me.
It happened one week later.

I was playing with the neighbour kids on the other side of the street, on the unused sidewalk. I still remember vividly: they had a collection of dolls, and some of them were even expensive (though I can't confirm this one here as I didn't have a lot of toys; everything would be expensive according to the amount of money we had).

One of them decided that I should have one of the dolls; I remember that she knew I only played with her and her sister when it was "dollhouse" because I never had a single one, and thus, on a moment of pity, she decided to give one to me. It was not her favourite, of course, but it was pretty and well groomed. It was a blonde one, with a pink dress on an "Alice in Wonderland"ish style.

I called for Elizabeth so she could come and see the doll I received as a present. Back then, we were close, and as the younger ones, we would be often left out from the plays of the two older ones for reasons we never truly understood; thus, whenever we received something, we'd show it to each other and be happy for these things.

It was no exception.

But the final result was different.

As she was crossing the street, she forgot to see if anyone was coming by. Our street had a long history of crazy drivers inside Volkswagen automobiles, so we always had to check before crossing *lots of times* before we even dared to put a foot outside the sidewalk.

That was also no exception to the rule.

She was hit by a green Volkswagen Carocha in front of me.

The image of her, smiling, crossing the street to see me and suddenly being forcefully dragged by a car at over 110 km/hour and being splatted on the street still feels recent.
The driver called an ambulance, and Elizabeth was taken in a hurry to the hospital. 

She died on the same day.

Everything went by in a blur after that. Mom would often tell me it was not my fault later on, but you know when the person treats you differently after the incident? Well, I felt it on my skin, even if she tried to fake she did not. It was hard not to when you're already the outcast child: you know the neglecting you get. A new one would surely stand out and feel different.

Elizabeth's funeral was pretty empty. Nobody wanted to visit her grave.

Years later, everyone forgot the cemetery her body was.

Considering the entire incident, my family, including aunts, grandma, *everyone*, tried to erase her existence from the family. We would not mention her name; we took every picture we had of her away and burned it; we donated her clothes, and her toys were given to the orphanage. When asked, mom would say she had only three children.

But I did not forget Elizabeth.

Since that day, I never played with that doll. I threw it away and avoided dolls for a long time, not even daring to look at one. My sisters would make a pained expression whenever someone mentioned Elizabeth's name, but in front of me, they would not dare to talk about it. In a way, I believe they thought it would keep me from feeling guilty, from feeling the pressure and weight of what I did.

But it was always there, on the back of my mind. After all, though, I guess they tried to keep me away from committing suicide -- which was something my mother herself would try to do later on.

But that's for another story.
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-09 18:35:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Well, my childhood friend grew to be 2,07 m, and he says that he doesn't get treated that much different other than by a few men.

Those "few men" don't try to fight him because of his height. That's pretty much all, and he's quite grateful around that as he hates fighting. Anything else, nobody gives a shit, so yeah... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-09 17:30:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> OH YEA, IT SURELY WOULD.

THAT ALPHA 'STACHE

THOSE BUCKY TEETH THAT LOOKED AWESOME WHENEVER HE SMILED

THOSE MANLY MOVES

THAT AMUSING MACHO VOICE

WHO WOULDN'T GO GAY FOR FREDDIE, MAN? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-09 01:09:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I know.

Best. Use. To. The. Lyrics. Ever. Thank you very much for making my favourite band since childhood even better, m8. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-09 01:06:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I legit love your Queen meming around this sub.

GOD SAVE OUR PRECIOUS FREDDIE </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-09 01:05:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> normie who gets sex everyday

lmao

lmao

'Ay ya cunt

I'm more incel than you by that logic, ya bloody bastard, lmao </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-09 00:43:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Can you grow tired and get out of this sub already pls </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-08 23:38:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Nah, TBP is not connected to inceldom at all. It's not a proper philosophy, but more of a "contingent of people who are not part of MRA, TRP or MGTOW" and dislike these. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-08 22:55:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Let's not forget be able to be a good househusband and capable of giving up his STEM diploma to be home 24/7 taking care of the kids and being ready to be sechsed all da tiem whenever his wife wants to. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-08 22:19:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> TRUTH

Troof* </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-08 18:41:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> "Merde"

LMAO

Also, 'ey man, weren't you part of the group who said women were incapable of leading? Why are you so butthurt of a man winning? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-08 17:56:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Why don't you leave this sub already if you're so much more smarter than us and we're apparently all just a bunch of arsehattering bullies? Even if we try to explain you'll just dismiss it or distort it to fit your view of "bluepillers are twats".

Go mither another sub already. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-08 05:05:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Is it me or TRPers are seemingly closer and closer to being like the fellas from my school when I was 12 or something?

I mean, *aren't they supposed to be grown alpha men?* </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-07 18:59:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Lolwut

I had a one month break on July and another month break on January and that was it. July breaks often got shortened to 1-2 weeks, though. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-07 08:10:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> people who made fun of the socially awkward kid

I was that kid being poked fun at everyday, sir.

Still don't blame all the men for it or try to self pity my way around using it. I felt bad to the point of depression back then? Yea, I did. Still didn't blame any guy for what a bunch of arseholes did. As I mentioned lots of times on this sub already, assholes are on every demographic; putting the blame on the entire group is pathetic. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-07 08:00:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> r/im14andthisisdeep material right 'ere </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-07 07:24:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> BEM BOLADO, BEM BOLADO </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-07 07:18:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You know it's just this sir, right? I mean, I deal with two blokes on a daily basis at my work plus the ones that come as clients and all of them talk to me normally.

It's just this dude in question who acts like that. See the answer I gave above to more details.

EDIT: oh, and also, I never ended up in a long talk with him. He was pretty much like that from day 1 I started working there. The man's pretty much like that with me for literally no reason at all, and never tried to have a proper talk with me other than the one above. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-07 07:16:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> But don't make entire self pitying posts, though. Commenting is one thing, doing entire posts on a sub that's got nothing to do is something completely different. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-07 05:04:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> In non-freedom height, my father is around 165 cm tall and hey, I am here, am I not?

^^^or ^^^I'm ^^^just ^^^a ^^^general ^^^illusion ^^^and ^^^didn't ^^^notice? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-07 04:37:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Wew, how many "schools out" a year these blokes have? Mine were only two, ffs </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-07 03:37:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yep. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-07 02:52:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thanks for answering for me here. I was too busy dozing off in front of my computer and waking up only now.

Also, this guy should probably go back to the post I mentioned the two fellas I fell in love with. Once again, the first was short and chubby.

And the guy I find amazing on a platonic level? Yeah, his face is attractive to me, but that's because I "met" his personality first. Was he just a pretty face, I wouldn't even remember his existence by now. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-06 23:04:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Not much. Mostly unknown fictional works around the internet (no, not fancfiction, this is 2beta4alphame), r/nosleep, a few news and... well, Dom Casmurro again.

All hail Capitu. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-06 23:00:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm just waiting 'til I fall asleep, honestly. Not been playing any games recently because of lack of time, and the time I *do* have is spent either here or by reading something. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-06 22:58:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Deleting their posts, maybe not.

But not giving attention, yeah. A few ones can be "saved", but still, in any case just keep distance until proven of not being a troll. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-06 22:56:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I am trying to relax a bit after doing a test here

90 fuckin' questions and I had to wake up early on a bloody saturday to do it.

Also need to do researches to build an entire essay from 0. It's mithering.

Edit: today is saturday, goddammit. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-06 22:53:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I mean, wouldn't spending one week building a park on Roller Coaster Tycoon 2 be more productive or whatever? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-06 22:50:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> "Attraction"

Except if you mean "instant attraction", ie you find someone hot but not necessarily want to have a long term relationship, I can disprove that.

First, once again, my fuckin' family is full of short men on long term relationships.

But my cousin who's tall and with a "strong jaw"? Still single because he's a twat. I didn't meet anyone who could stand his personality for too long. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Wtf? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-06 22:45:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So, yeah, this is not aimed at trying to hit them in any way, but...

What are incels doing on this sub? I mean, I've seen lots of them appearing out of nowhere here and arguing about how because they are ugly they have no one or summat, and well, they also don't change their views around the "women are not completely human" thought. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-06 22:40:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Sarcasm



You

EDIT: oh, and also: facial structure and height got nothing to do with attraction. Most men who are married for a long time in my family and have great connections with their wives are short (as in 1,50-1,65 m short). And not exactly well built, too, nor with strong jaws. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-06 06:57:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Well, sir, English is also not my native language and I punctuate my phrases.

Still, keep going. No need to wait until another life comes up, mate. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
