<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject6120</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-10 03:23:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That's fucking depressing. The level of corruption exhibited by this administration is breathtaking. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-10 03:19:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Is this going to slow down the investigations? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-10 03:18:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Fuck I have to upvote you. But I think you're dead-on with this assessment.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-09 08:25:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That was good. Funny. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-09 04:07:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That was horrible of Yates. Beating up on the feeble minded :-D </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-09 01:51:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Petty as it is, this is the more likely scenario. I think Trump's aim is to rollback and shit on everything  Obama did to get back at him for the bitch-slapping that Obama handed out at that White House Correspondents Dinner. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-09 01:48:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That gives me a boner. Keep talking, I'll keep stroking. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-08 18:46:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yep. Can't let up until the Nationalist/Populist/Fascist mindset is stompedbout or deemed a joke. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-08 18:37:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Our team is looking for a couple of SE's by the way. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-08 17:24:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Mattis would be awesome.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-08 17:09:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That seems like it would be a good feature... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-08 17:08:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It could happen. But until then some might find it useful. :-) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-08 17:07:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's okay bud. Now you know you have a treat waiting for you in either book or movie form. :-) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-08 03:07:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Those points were very hard to get. 

Not the sexiest way to win a fight that got so much anticipation built up before it happened. But he won. 

Pacquiao's job was to make it a definitive win since he was the contender. Which he failed to do. Unfair... but that's what he had to play with. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> If you're looking for something to read - checkout: 100 Million Books - discover a new book every time you open a new tab. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-08 00:40:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-07 21:56:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Same thing with Pacquiao. Not a Mayweather fan either but got say it: he outboxed Pacquiao. 

Pacquiao's attacks were brutal and overwhelming but Mayweather defended and fought smart. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-07 20:19:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm okay with Obama finishing Cheeto Benito's remaining term... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-07 19:37:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I only saw the movie  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-07 19:23:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I watched a couple of episodes. I think it's meant for Trump. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-07 19:08:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Political maneuvering is the only thing the GOP knows now. 

Obama castigated an audience of Republican Congressmen about this back when they were trying to fix the crash, pointing out that their side of the house was more concerned of positioning versus actually looking for a solution. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-06 07:19:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I suspect we'll see him hanging out with Trump soon. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-05 21:18:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Trump's too. This is his response to the thrashing that Obama gave him at the White House Correspondence Dinner... basically tear down every thing that Obama worked on. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-05 18:30:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> "Rational" being the keyword here. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-05 18:29:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Choosing between Hillary and Trump is like choosing between getting a bad haircut (Hillary) and getting you dick cut-off, having same slathered in shit and shoved in your mouth (Trump)

Why would anyone choose Trump over anything is beyond me.

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-05 05:02:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Ah fuck - leave it as is. Those scratches mean you now own those books. It's like scars. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-05 05:00:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> But buy it anyway. I got the hardcovers as a gift, wanna use it everyday but won't... I'll get the softcovers for use one of these days. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-04 18:49:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> People should be marching in the streets now. If there's ever a time for an Occupy Wall Street level amount of participation, it would be now. To ensure it does not pass, and the Republicans don't try to repeal it again. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-04 18:42:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What the fuck are you talking about?! They didn't. You're likely going to get screwed if they repeal ACA -   it's a special kind of stupid to side with something that will cause you harm. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-04 18:38:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> But they also are compelled by their board of directors to make money. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-04 17:22:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Right on. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-04 06:42:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Fuck, and POTUS will have to go. This would be embarrassing... can't we substitute Obama? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-03 22:33:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Unfortunately you're right. The kind of dumb that won't believe what's in front of their eyes fact dumb. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-03 17:14:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hard to argue with someone so fucking dumb that they don't even know they are dumb. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-03 07:48:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> They're both good. And on the same side, hitting the same target. Support them both. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-03 04:52:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That's kind of a dumb statement - especially given all the facts, public analyses, and informed opinion available at your fingertips. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-02 17:34:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> How many times can they try to kill Obamacare? Is there a limit? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-02 06:21:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Right on bro

No sense being delicate about facts and well informed opinion especially given what's at stake. Dumb is dumb and corrupt is corrupt. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-02 03:37:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Ditto. She got that psycho/frazy aura that is a good indicator of a sex freak, anything goes kinda chick. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-02 03:25:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What's the brand/model of your display? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-02 03:10:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I don't it's reason that made it happen. But a win is a win. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-02 02:37:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I wish I could upvote you several times for this :/) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-02 02:33:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I wonder how they'll twist it if it goes against their predictions...

At this point my revulsion of T_D has been overcome by morbid fascination. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-01 21:39:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Vote for the less sucky one to ensure you don't get the worse choice. Because no matter what, one of these choices will be made for you -- I know it sucks, but that's what you have to work with for now.
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-01 17:44:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That was in 1825. That was a long time ago.
Some say it was just yesterday. But I think it was. Do you like chocolate cake? I love chocolate cake, believe me, I know. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-01 17:19:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Found a Trumpette! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-01 06:22:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Seeing really some good responses here. Thanks OP for this question. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-01 06:20:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Anything covered by Gaiman. His take on the Matrix, Cinderella, and Snow White are all great. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-01 04:31:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> No one's allowed to be this hot in the 1950's </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-01 04:13:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Definitely. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-01 04:00:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Oh shit! I got downvotes?! That's funny! Probably explains why some people voted Trump... they need cues/clues on the actual meaning of things... :-p </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-01 03:56:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> More the merrier. :-) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-01 01:49:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Had one when I was 5. That was a long time ago, my mother says we were inseparable... but I really can't remember anymore. I need a house first, with a yard -  we live in SF, having a dog here means they stay cooped up the whole day during weekdays... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-01 01:43:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yep that he did. That's how I noticed the safety check. :-) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-01 01:23:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> 1 more year and she's practically a hag. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-01 01:12:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I think it's actually that. The dog even nudged the cat towards the spot that it checked. 

I want/need a dog so much - they seem like the nicest companions (pet wise) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-01 00:05:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Husband and boy-lets you mean? :-) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-30 23:07:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I would actually like all newly elected Congressmen and Senators be required to spend 6 months of their lives living on minimum wage so they understand the problems of the majority of their constituents before they start serving. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-30 23:04:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Why would a Cardinal need to live in a 12 room apartment? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-30 22:47:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The dog checked first if the cat might get hurt if it's head get shoved in the snow... really cool. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-30 22:33:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> There's not much in the article. Basically Trump pointed out KYU is smart but that the problem with NK should've been taken care of before (by Obama, Bush, or Clinton) --- and that's about it. Pretty empty except for that weird fucking statement by our Dear President providing a hint of legitimacy to NK's Dear Ruler. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-30 18:21:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Bruce Willis tapped Fabienne? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-30 17:45:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That Hitler though, he knows how to hold a rally... right? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-30 07:44:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This whole thing is like a lab experiment to understand how dictatorships come about. What mindset is required, etc. for someone to take on the role.

We know right now, intelligence/smarts is not a factor...

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-29 22:47:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Are grants like RSU's? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-29 19:09:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> He's just talking faster here. Vocabulary is slightly larger, but it's still the same speech patterns. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-29 03:15:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> There's a false equivalence here. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-28 11:27:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Because that's his biggest accomplishment. Dubious as it is. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-27 23:59:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Minimum amount of work is what I'm looking for. Just slightly above 50 Shades of Gray literary (almost threw up) quality should be enough. :-D </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-27 19:03:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I mean a little less dry than that :-) use the porn video as a frame for what is described, e. g.:

He sits on her face and yells "lick my ass!"

She is taken aback, was not expecting the sudden change in tone of their sexual encounter, but starts licking... both afraid and excited.

She feels her hips being lifted, even as puts on more weight on her face. Forcing her tongue into his asshole.

She feels a finger being inserted in her moist cunt, then another, and another - three fingers! - but before she could get over this amazement, he starts to insert another...

--

It's terrible, but better than Stephanie Meyer's prose... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-27 18:28:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I wonder if just putting up a porn video and describing it in text would work as Literotica...  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-27 18:11:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Abortion would be legal everywhere. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-27 05:09:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Oh cool, performance art. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-27 03:26:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Why "Chaos Actual"? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-27 03:19:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You're being sarcastic right? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-27 01:38:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's so easy for anyone to look good and smart now after all the fuckups. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-26 08:16:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> LOL. UA's just not getting a break these days. 
And yeah, Simon dying is sad, but also funny in context. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-25 18:46:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> She's good at this though. Saying a lot of things that gives the appearance of sharing a well thought out answer but ultimately saying nothing. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-25 04:13:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Prez Cheeto needs a rating boost. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-24 18:56:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The research and staff used for content can be expensive though. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-23 07:46:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Any and all of the above theories is possible. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-23 07:33:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Put the god damn lotion in the basket!!!! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-22 19:00:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> RemindMe! 2 days Donation for /r/millionairemakers </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-22 04:21:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Unless Putin's assassins gets to her first. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-22 02:59:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Those tapes are just cherry on top now.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-21 21:51:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Belated Happy 420 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-21 06:45:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That response was awesomely dry. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-21 04:04:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Talk about outsiders in the WhiteHouse huh?

Trump might as well take a big dump on that desk and be done with it. Comey needs to get a move on...

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-20 08:25:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Don't remember when it dawned on me that being a medical doctor does not necessarily mean someone smart. Scary thought. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-20 02:22:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I don't think Ryan is involved, but he's also not doing anything to help. Which would be his best move, with very minimal downside. But we could dream... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-20 02:20:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Which is now the least important issue but might have been the seed planted a long time ago. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-19 19:55:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That's what I thought about those golf trips. Expensive, but that's at least 2 - 2.5 days where Trump is not playing POTUS at least. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-19 03:13:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Pancake tits though. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-18 01:38:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Didn't he just bomb Erdmagerds airport because of the beautiful babies that were gassed? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-17 07:29:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You gotta be trashy to do that. Only Trump and most Republicans can pull it off. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-16 07:17:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Ditto. There's probably going to be a minor sacrificial lamb who gets a year max. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-16 05:55:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Your a master. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-16 00:41:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Day after day after day. We get news of some form of corruption or another from Trump  Co., and yet he's still sitting as POTUS - sullying the office and everything it stands for. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-15 04:35:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Shady as fuck. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-15 04:34:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> :'-( </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-14 05:11:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> There ain't no chicks with dicks, only dudes with tits. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-13 19:47:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Trying every which way to boost his approval ratings. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-12 04:46:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's like issuing a revert on a commit because it fixed the bug. Fuck!!! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-12 02:02:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> How the fuck did we ever get here. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-08 21:06:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's theater with Russia. The strikes were harmless (relatively) and Russia and Syria had advanced notice that they were able to move personnel and most equipments before the strike. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-05 07:50:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Obama's way too classy for that. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-05 07:49:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Obama tried to be bipartisan early on. Several times. The Republicans simply said no to everything (even when it contradicts their earlier position) - so no, it'll never happen, not in a long time. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
