<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject5484</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> America's new post-Comey reality </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-10 13:09:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-10 12:58:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> *Could* be a cover-up?

No, *criminal* obstruction of justice. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-10 02:54:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The special prosecutor investigation that's about to kick off? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-10 02:53:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> My guess is that, if called to testify, he's going to wave the letter around and say it says all he has to say.

Nothing fills the little boy with fear like being made to sit on the penalty chair. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-10 02:49:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> At least you didn't have a lawyer send a letter to Congress. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-10 02:41:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> No, but why are we finding out about THAT in May, in the midst of an investigation of HIM? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-10 02:39:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This paves the way for the special prosecutor. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-10 02:38:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> TP

Hehe </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-10 02:26:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Trump made no mention of Comeys role in the Clinton investigation. But the president did assert that Comey informed him on three separate occasions that I am not under investigation.

I'm just waiting for him to try to shut down the investigation. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-10 02:05:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Listen, there was no Obama in the 80s.

Uncle Ronnie tripled the national debt.  It went from billions to trillions, and for all the praise he gets from soft heads, his chapter and legacy remains open until we successfully unfuck ourselves.

Not that I expect an apologist to understand that. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-09 21:54:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's called house training.

And if my dog keeps bringing it up, more shit is gonna go down. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-09 21:44:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> But how many shed kits would I have to buy to build the world's largest shed?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-09 21:40:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Aka management </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-09 21:38:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I really like the cover by Avalanches. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-09 21:36:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah, and the pile of poo in the middle of the rug has nothing to do with me being mad.

Bitches.  Literally. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-09 21:25:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If birds could start fires, we'd be seriously fucked. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-09 21:18:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> No, Danimal, let's leave it at this:

You're more upset about the content of the poll than anything else, which tells me you're a Trump supporter.  Maybe not the howl-at-the-moon type, maybe a conservative Democrat.  Whatever.  The whole concept of "let's help Trump pass his tax cuts for the rich" is very telling.  Cut entitlements or raise import taxes?  So contempt for the poor and xenophobia.  And, your very limited sense of what a poll is tells you it's only right where we must include climate deniers and young Earthers.  I hate to break it to you, but it's not the 20th century anymore.

There are all matter of polls with various goals, rates of sampling, and question types.  I'm not here to teach you about all of that. But look Dan!  If you scroll all the way down to the bottom of the actual report, there's a link to "contact us".  let me link the report again so that this is not lost on you:

http://www.igmchicago.org/surveys/tax-reforms

You can contact the Booth School of Business personally and tell them what's wrong with their poll and polling practices.  One bit of advice: make sure you spell "poll' correctly, or they may mistake your economic brilliance for something else. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-09 21:06:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The 1% are not terribly keen about giving their money up.  They also have it stashed and protected.  They also tend to donate a lot to political campaigns (for both parties) so that Congress doesn't go after them. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-09 21:02:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah, so he tripled the debt but it's pointless.

Numbers game.

He blew ridiculous amounts of money on missiles that we ended up dismantling.  In hindsight, this suddenly became his brilliant secret plan to take down the Soviet Union.  It's a lovely narrative except people leave out how much the defense industry kicked money back to the GOP and how, despite the fairy tale of Reagonomics, that money is still outstanding in our ledgers, left for other people to pay off who weren't even alive for "the good times". </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Trump says allegations of collusion with Russia 'total hoax' </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-09 18:06:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-09 15:27:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> And maybe you should write a letter to the Booth School of Business and take them to task with your deep insights about "poles".

In fact, why don't you get on it right now and stop repeating the same platitudes? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-09 11:28:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>   Literally, I live in a district shaped like a crescent moon fucked a swan with a broken neck.

I've been wanting to get a tattoo like that. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-09 11:23:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'd add several more points.

1)  If this graph is supposed to show us that they do pay their fair share, then why should congress give them tax cuts?

2)  This is all based on personal income tax, but the corporate tax rate is 15%.  So, 15% is the share of the profits Comcast and Verizon pay to the government while they throttle your internet speeds and all of those other nice things that corporations do for the people.

3)  Look at other countries, especially the G20.  Are our tax rates low or high.  What about for the rich?  The answer is low and low.

http://www.taxpolicycenter.org/briefing-book/how-do-us-taxes-compare-internationally

4)  Should the rich pay less taxes?  Maybe we could rank along with these countries:

http://www.insidermonkey.com/blog/10-countries-with-the-lowest-tax-rates-for-the-rich-379880/10/

5)  The uber-rich in our country are doing more than fine:

http://foreignpolicy.com/2011/09/20/does-the-u-s-tax-its-billionaires-less-than-other-rich-countries/

Not to mention that this top 1% is most likely to take their earnings and sit on them as wealth rather than put these funds back out into circulation.  It does little good for the country if the money simply disappears into coffers at the top.

6)  America has a long reputation for whining about taxes and tax cuts.  This continues to this day while the debt balloons to scary, catastrophic levels.  No one should be getting tax cuts.  And I already know: BUT BUT we need the tax cuts to get the economy going.  That BS has been claimed for fucking years, and where has the debt gone?  The economy is what it is, and that's cyclical.  Leave the economy out of it.  Taxes need to cover the federal budget.  They don't.  We don't need to be giving anyone tax cuts.  Do not believe the people who try to make it more complicated than that.

Now, do we need to raise taxes?  Sorry, but yes.  That's the adult answer. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-09 09:26:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Oh yay!  Numbers games!

Ronnie tripled the debt.  That's 300%.

Obama raised it around 26% very early in his term to avoid default.

And yeah, I can see the brilliant methodology behind the discovery that expenses are a drag on the economy.  That is a truly startling finding.  Then, I know, we can have Expense Free Days to show people how life would be without expenses.  Woohoo! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-09 09:15:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> And you can right your big pile of nonsense on an internet forum.

Before you go talking about brains, go read about what the Booth Initiative on Global Markets is:

https://research.chicagobooth.edu/igm/

And to help your brain, you do have to click on the tabs there to gain access to things like About Us.

Then, you can read the actual study, which you have not but was published by the IGM.

If you had even a modicum of interest in investigating credentials before assuming that the credentials are bad, you could have done so, professor.

Let's not look at the article I linked.  Let's look at the real study, Genius...oh I mean Danimal:

http://www.igmchicago.org/surveys/tax-reforms

Oh, and make sure your brain uses the scroll wheel to go all of the way down and read the whole thing, Mr Credentials.

The structure is crap based on you reading a newspaper article.  Got it.  Congratulations.  I'll be writing my recommendation to the Nobel committee this evening. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-09 09:03:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Simple answer: It's about balancing the national budget.  Every year, the US government spends more money than it makes.

Extended answer:  The US government behaves very much the same way as someone with bad credit card habits.  They like to shop: the various government agencies need funding, programs ranging from research to financial aid need funding, and then things start to get juicy.  The government hires contractors for everything from defense to construction to cleaning up oil spills.  This money goes out to private companies and corporations who, in turn, make campaign donations to congressmen.  Unnecessary and/or wasteful spending done so for the sake of campaign contributions is known as "pork barrel spending".  Our congressional pork barrel is large and bipartisan.

That's my explanation of spending.  On the other side, we have income.  The government gets its money from taxing people.  Not just people, but businesses, merchandise, activities, etc...  There are all kinds of taxes on all kinds of things.  But all of those taxes do not add up to pay off our spending bill.  

This leaves congress with only a few options:

a)  They can raise taxes.  This has been known to anger the populace and get politicians voted out, especially in the land of Republicans.

b) They can cut spending.  This is typically the move where we have to ditch social programs because they don't pay back to campaigns like the pork barrel spending does.

c)  They can borrow.  Borrowing would be best described as taxing future Americans.  Someone's going to have to pay for this.  Just not now, and hopefully not us.  It's ugly, but it doesn't have that same immediate pain response that imposing new taxes does.

So, who benefits?  By far politicians.  Then come their political donors.  China has bought a lot of our debt, gambling on us being able to pay it back and enjoying the fees not unlike the credit card companies.

Why do we let them get away with it?  It's not as easy to address as other issues, because the solution is not a single issue.  Calls to kill the debt get answered with "OK, which programs to defund?  Oh, nvm, I'll decide which programs!"  For the last few decades, social welfare programs and defense spending are the perpetual yo-yo, but  that's never close to enough to put a dent in the debt, which continues to grow.

If we default, the results will be catastrophic in a way that makes 2008 look like a little oopsy. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-09 08:31:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah, well there's also the Affordable Care Act, known as Obamacare.  

How did he create that if he was President?  Answer:  It's the signature piece of legislation passed under his leadership.

Raising the debt ceiling obviously was not his signature piece of legislation, but the increase was passed under his leadership and with his support.

https://www.thoughtco.com/presidents-who-raised-the-debt-ceiling-3321770

I voted for Obama twice, and I hate the national debt.  That said, your niggling attempts to fully resolve Obama of responsibility are Trumpish. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-08 23:49:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah well, it's smothering to have laws, too, but understand why we have them, and they don't just come into existence for the purpose of cramping people's lifestyles.

Now, if you're serious and want to be taken seriously when talking free markets, give us a country whose model you think the US should emulate.

That would go a lot farther than fanciful claims about the magic of pure competition and whatnot typically espoused by priests of Mises and Ron Paul.

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-08 23:28:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Oh yeah, the theft argument.

Well, rather than living with warped English, there's always the option to go live in a country without income tax...

Is there such a a thing?  Yup, you have three choices:

a) Petrodollar countries

b) Offshore banking countries

c) Monaco

http://www.telegraph.co.uk/expat/money/countries-that-dont-have-income-tax-in-pictures/

I'd recommend Monaco, but your sweat might not go very far. 

For a country to function on a large scale, income tax is both normal and necessary. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-08 23:18:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yes, and so did a whole legion of T_D types who responded to your post. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-08 23:15:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> *But you know it's true that all these people accept it as truth.*

That's what you see through your skewed, oh-really-I'm-a-centrist-and-not-a-conservative goggles.

But it's a non-starter as an argument, and the same goes for the rest, with a special prize for saying the Dossier has been found inaccurate because of a spelling error.

Now, watch this:

What I said in my previous post stands.

Done. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-08 23:05:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Booth School of Business has been regularly polling economists for years.  They typically ask around 40 economists.  Moreover, Booth has graduated over ten Nobel Laureates in Economics, so I'm sure they're hurt that you think they did your Trump unfairly, but I think they'll get over it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-08 22:54:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Uh oh.  It's the guy who wants to unchain the 800-pound gorillas.  Run! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-08 22:52:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Already happened more than once, but here you go:

http://www.igmchicago.org/surveys/tax-reforms </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-08 22:51:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yes, but again to be fair, Obama supported it.  Moreover, to say this never happened when Obama signed off on it is...Trumpish?

I guess you don't, but I'd call having veto power is a choice in the matter.  It's a huge choice in the matter fundamental to our Constitution. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-08 22:47:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> He did that while, at the same time, going on a massive defense spending spree that launched the national debt into the stratosphere.  A debt we have yet to pay off.  So yeah, the 80s were this awesome feel good moment about the economy but short-sighted and at the expense of future generations.

Moreover, the Tax foundation:

Ideology

The Tax Foundation describes itself as an "independent tax policy research organization".[29] They are cited in the media as a nonpartisan or bipartisan organization, and are also described as business-friendly or conservative.

Being bipartisan is swell, but functioning as an organization that is essentially anti-tax doesn't make this study unbiased. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-08 19:34:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> O.O </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-08 19:26:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> OK...I agree.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-08 19:22:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Are you talking to me?  If so, it seems you've changed your name.

If we're talking about what I think we're talking about, I think you're saying in a very roundabout fashion that this article says nothing different than the 2012 article.  Right? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-08 19:17:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You are free to keep explaining.  It boils down to you not liking the headline because you imply that people didn't know what the headline was about.  I have yet to see anyone talking about anything but the right topic so far, though.  Have you?

And I'm not trying to argue tax plans.  I simply asked what your opinion of the tax plan was.  See, as much as you'd like to make this thread about Reddit, the WaPo, and why they should be following your rules, the purpose of this thread is to discuss the tax plan.

Any plans on your behalf to discuss the tax plan?

Considering you've already had multiple invitations to do so, the answer is no.  No? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Sally Yates Testimony to Congress: How to watch live online </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-08 19:01:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-08 18:55:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What did you think the headline was referring to?

I know. You haven't said anything about the tax plan.  So what do you think about the tax plan?

Talk to people what way?  Am I being unfair to you?   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-08 18:49:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Sorry for that formatting Sally? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-08 18:48:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> #GOT-ME-IMPEACHED SALLY

#MADE-AMERICA-GREAT-AGAIN SALLY </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-08 18:45:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm Gene's neighbor, and I endorse this version of events. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-08 18:40:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Well, yes.  They were going to use Iraq's oil to pay for it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-08 18:25:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Most of the headline is numbers, the other bit says a number and that those economists changed their minds.  Is there any element of that which is incorrect?

In any event, it seems you like the President's tax cut plan.  What do you like about it? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-08 18:00:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Do you mean traveling as constantly being on the road or traveling as living abroad?

I can't speak much for the first.

As for the second:

This may come as a surprise, but many many many jobs can be done in the living abroad format.

Teaching English is the most common one, and you can make some very decent money if you are a qualified teacher and work for international schools.

Chef is probably the second most common.  I know less about that, but chefs do get around.  Wonky hours, but good chefs fetch good salaries.

Cruise ship anything probably doesn't pay as well as you'd like in exchange for living in cramped quarters and serving finicky people.

Large hotel chains offer opportunities.

The gas and oil industries need people willing to work in far-flung places.

But, for example, say you're an engineer.  There are engineering projects all over the place and, if you work for a firm that serves thos places, you can go there.  Better yet, people with houses and families often do not want to be sent abroad, so you get extra pay for being willing to do so.

Engineering is just one example of the above.

State Department.

Airlines.

The merchant marine pays fabulous if you really wanna travel your ass off and stick with it as a career from a young age.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-08 17:43:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> r/culinary would be the place to ask </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-08 17:36:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What time does this go down? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-08 17:35:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So, you're saying your 2012 article corroborates this current article? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-08 17:27:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You are making a strawman by saying people accept it as fact.

It's in a report.  Has any part of the report been shown to be incorrect?

There is no rule against upvoting speculation, and you are knowingly making a strawman by implying that what should and does get upvoted is factual.

I'm not sure why you should have a tantrum simply because you're skeptical.

If there is a pee pee tape, could it be used by Putin for blackmail?

I personally have no reason to be skeptical.  That doesn't mean I say or think they are proven.  I don't see anyone here saying they are.  What I see is you attacking people for accepting them as true when no one has said so.  It seems you don't want anyone talking about pee pee tapes unless there's proof.

My response:

Too bad.

Pee pee tapes!  Pee pee tapes! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-08 17:12:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Here you go:

http://www.igmchicago.org/surveys/tax-reforms </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-08 17:09:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Someone posted it earlier.  I'll go see if I can find it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-08 17:08:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So, let's pin this down.  You're saying the current poll referenced in the OP article is in line with your poll from 2012, right?

You do not think the proposed tax cuts will pay for themselves.  Correct? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-08 16:59:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> OK, I'm mildly interested in indulging you, so:

What's sensational about these numbers?

I don't know what your definition of sarcastic is.  Mine is "stating the opposite of the truth for humorous effect".  I see nothing opposite of the truth here.  What's your definition of sarcasm?

Low-quality is an opinion, but go on.  How would you rewrite this headline in a high-quality fashion?

How is it misleading?  What context would you add to correct this?

You are declaring a rule on Reddit void.  Do you make the rules?

And sorry, I haven't downvoted you at all.  In fact, I'm interested in hearing your answers. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-08 16:46:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Not the exact wording, but will Trump's proposed tax cuts pay for themselves, as he claims? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-08 16:36:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Oh this is ripe.

Yet in a survey of leading economists conducted by the University of Chicagos Booth School of Business, 92 percent agreed that the stimulus succeeded in reducing the jobless rate.

You're using a 2012 report not about Trump's tax cut but based on a poll of economists by the Booth School of Business to rubbish a 2017 Booth School of Business survey of economists about Trump's tax cut.

Try harder. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-08 16:22:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hi there,

A WaPo article about economists analyzing Trump's propose tax cut doesn't fit r/politics?

Whether it gets deleted or not, can you explain why?   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-08 15:05:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This is all a very old and tired trope that, for reasons I don't why, Republicans have had far more success with.

They label liberals "tax and spend", spreading fear among the populace that Democrats will raise taxes. 

But there is a lesser known equal and opposite: "cut and borrow".  "Cut and borrow" defines Republican policy since (and including) Reagan.  The deficit is this abstract thing lurking above us all that the populace cares less about than higher taxes because the deficit has yet to come knocking in a meaningful way at the average American's door.

Before going on, let's try to be fair here.  Democrats often do raise taxes.  One reason is that they are trying to recover funds lost from previous Republican tax cuts.  The other, perhaps more important reason is that they believe in the social net and that we save more money by taking care of the poor and giving them better opportunities to better themselves than simply leaving poverty to fester and paying to house criminals in prisons (among other things).

Likewise, Republicans do raise taxes.  HW Bush did so after promising not to and was ravaged by conservatives.

Obama also raised the debt ceiling to avoid default post-2008.

Now, back to the program:  The latest Republican wrinkle is to claim that their cuts and spending will pay for themselves.  They did this under W by claiming the Iraq invasion would pay for itself.  Now, Donnie is going to cut taxes and have them pay for themselves.  Fool me once...Fool me twice...um, you can't fool me.

During his campaign, Mister T wailed on and on about our national debt.  He was the one to fix it.  Even if you indulge the infantile prospect that these tax cuts will pay for themselves, cutting taxes is not going to do anything to help the national debt, and these cut will raise the national debt when they end up not paying for themselves.

Old news.  New lip service. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-08 14:38:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> a) No one here made up the pee pee tapes

b) There is a reason to believe the pee pee tapes exist

c) Who says anyone here is skeptical or not?  Are you saying we can't talk about pee pee tapes until we see the pee pee?

d)  'You guys' believe Trump when he lies in public and on record.  It seems some people really believe the shit he makes up without any skepticism at all.

e)  Pee pee tapes!  Pee pee tapes! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-08 14:22:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> To be fair, wasn't she the very first person to be fired?  

Could it not be that this was the Donald thinking that he was now in the DC version of The Apprentice and that he would just fire everybody until he got his way? 

I suppose he might have also thought he was going to fire his way out of the Russia scandal at that early point, but... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Implant warp bug </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-08 14:12:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This has now happened to me multiple times:

While waiting in the queue to enter a full continent, I flip through the various tabs like store, character, etc...  If I'm looking at implants and the "Warp to [Amerish or whatever]?" prompt comes up, I can't click on it because it's in a layer below the implants.  Everything else is also greyed out, so I can't switch to another tab or even log out.  I've tried esc, clicking on other programs and returning, but the only solution I have is to kill the whole game and relog.

Has anyone else encountered this?  Is it old, or a new thing due to the new implant system?  Any other workaround that didn't occur to me?  Does this suffice as a bug report?

Thanks. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> 35 of 37 economists said Trump was wrong. The other two misread the question. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-08 13:36:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-07 11:48:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> In the prison system, he'll go to some special lock-up, sleep on satin sheets, and at best his punishment will be playing tennis instead of golf. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-07 11:42:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> For example? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-07 10:18:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Wow, Berkely or somewhere coastal is one thing, but this is in Pence's back yard.  That speaks volumes for sentiment among the young towards this administration.

As for liberal bias:

a) as long as conservatives define themselves by rejecting science and promoting bigotry, then yes, it's hard for a university not to be seen as liberal by comparison.  Moreover, it's a bullshit middle ground fallacy to say that universities need to add more science deniers and bigots to their faculties in order to make universities 'fair and balanced'.

b) Remember the Oklahoma frat boys singing about lynching?  Universities are far from uniform in how liberal they are, and some campus populations are really anything but liberal. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-07 08:21:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> But polls are not perfect.  They do not record spite. They do not measure bitterness, deception, and selfishness.

TLDR: A bitter, spiteful, deceptive, and selfish U of Maryland journalism major uses Le Pen as an excuse to blame Sanders supporters for Clinton's loss.

I voted for Clinton (Well, tried to, tyvm electoral college), but if you supported Sanders and didn't vote for Clinton, then that's your prerogative.  The old Democrat strategy of pandering to the right is in peril.  That's a good thing.

20/20 hindsight tells me that we needed to elect Trump just to exorcise this demon from our system, just like Kerry's loss gave W full responsibility to own his war and the shitshow that accompanied it.  If Kerry had won, Democrats would be blamed for somehow screwing up the GOP's perfect plan for Iraq.  If Trump had lost, he might be gaining supporters right now talking trash at rallies about how he was the right choice to 'fix' America.  It seems quite right that he'd rather be doing that right now instead of demonstrating how unfit he is to govern.

And I do believe those emails did demonstrate that the DNC was throwing the match in favor of Clinton, so it's a bit hasty for Mr Thirst Turtle to summarily announce that Clinton didn't cheat in the primaries. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-07 07:26:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Oohhhhh....let me translate:  the pee pee tape must be coming to the surface soon. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-07 07:23:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Or he could just shut his cock holster and stay the weekend in the friggin' White House.

But let's face it: he's afraid it's wiretapped, and every weekend he says incriminating things that might add to the list of reasons he should be spending his entire weeks at the Sing Singminster or Leavenworth A Lago. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-07 07:11:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I think his rallies have a solid (if not more bigoted) parallel with infomercials.

Did you know 95% of Trump voters owner a Shark vacuum, a Nutribullet, and at least one bacon bowl? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-07 04:09:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's actually both:

https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=5lYe-0CLXrs

https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=HI0x0KYChq4

Not that that makes your TIL accurate... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-06 18:49:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This is a reference to the Venona Project, now being spun into a massive untruth that, because some of the people McCarthy accused actually were spies, it somehow vindicates him from the various lists, smear campaigns, and disproportional hysteria he was responsible for and deservedly censured for.

And it's really kind of sick to make it into a joke about people being hung in Salem. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-06 18:37:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That's not the only motivation.  People do produce art for art's sake, and art produced purely for monetary reasons is often not up to snuff. 

But if you want to think of it that way... it explains why the GOP has Tobey Keith, Kid Rock, Ted Nugent, and Scott Baio as supporters while the vast vast majority of performing artists are liberal.

It's also why we have horrible sequels, spin-offs, and reboots. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-06 17:44:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Um, this was at a presentation promoting Chinese investment in a new Kushner project in New Jersey, people there were told to get the visa before the rules change, at least two reporters were kicked out, and organizers tried to corral attendees to avoid them being interviewed on the way out.

And, if you read the article, they, um, talk about the golden visa you're educating us about. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-06 17:30:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> OMFG!  We need to stop the whole Russia collusion investigation right now and get to the bottom of this. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> TIL Jules Verne originally envisioned Captain Nemo as a Polish noble on a mission of vengeance against the Russians who killed his family in the January Uprising. His editor eventually persuaded Verne to change this so as not to hurt book sales in Russia. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-06 17:27:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-06 10:12:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> And if Kroc had chosen a mouse as his mascot while Disney made cartoons about a creepy clown, none of us would even know these two people existed. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-06 10:09:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> To save you the click: that's a pic of Justin Trudeau, who is not the first head of state to have a tattoo. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-06 10:05:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Didn't they also test the nude bomb there? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-06 10:04:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> "Miguel" better finish his tweeting before ICE come knocking.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-06 09:59:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That's what you get for dressing all ironic and drinking Pabst. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-06 09:57:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> And somehow it still got elected. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-06 09:54:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I've tried to trace this back, and my theory is that this specific vocal style started with NOFX and, as the article alludes, it's inspired by Joe Strummer.  I hear the Clash version of "Police and Thieves" when I hear that vocal style. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-06 09:33:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Countries not even in the G20 manage to pay for these systems.  It's more affordable if you don't have a predatory insurance industry on one side, a predatory pharmaceutical industry on the other side, and predatory hospital practices somewhere in-between.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-06 09:22:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I actually thought the timing of this was in anticipation of reps breaking ranks and a general nosedive in public support once the grand jury announcements come out. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-06 08:45:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The primary "tradition" of Iowa and NH first and other places permanently last needs to change to a rotation. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-04 07:43:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If you can't keep it constitutional, who really cares what you care about? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-04 07:41:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  It just permits discrimination

Unconstitutional.  Done.

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-04 07:35:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Good point.  How about this then:  We could enslave the black people and force them to be foster parents.  No more foster children at all.  Done. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> 5 Takeaways From James Comey's Hearing </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-04 07:30:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-04 02:40:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah, and I'm totally open to a bill that prevents black people from applying for certain jobs if it creates more jobs.

That's not just bigotry.  It's unconstitutional. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-04 02:32:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Considering many saw the campaign as between two horrible choices and her having serious negative charisma at this point, I think she needs to retire.  She will never win another presidential primary, so she needs to call it a day. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-04 02:27:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah, because reducing the number of potential adoptive families leads to more adoptions, and governors discriminating against people based on their orientation is OK if you're a Trump supporter. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-04 02:18:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The Phantom Menace.

Seriously, every fan who was around for the original trilogy had 17 fucking years to talk about what the new movie would be like.  People had all matter of ideas and theories, but few expected Sarlacc's armpit.

Let me translate for 2017:  Imagine you had to wait 17 years for the last Season of Game of Thrones, and then when it finally came out it was a mishmash of tropes from earlier seasons that didn't really go anywhere. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-04 02:14:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Raspberry Pi </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-04 02:07:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Nobody has mentioned the seasons.

With VE day being in May, the US would've had 5 months to overrun the entire Soviet Union before they joined Napoleon and the Nazis, perishing in their not-fit-for-Soviet-winters winter gear.

And, on a simple, sane note, this was time when American involvement in wars lasted 4 or so years.  The country was happy to have won but also seriously war-weary.  People were not going to just hop on a bandwagon to go on another campaign that, rather than 5 months, realistically could have lasted years without end. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-04 01:56:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Kind of like ass-kisser?

Is ass-kissing gay foreplay?

Is it butt-phobic to call someone an ass-kisser?

Or, don't we all get it that it means you're being subservient and submissive?

And as if that rodeo of bigots in any way shape or form cares about LGBTQ issues. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> FBI chief Comey says he has no regrets about his preelection letter on Hillary Clinton's emails </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-04 01:41:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-03 20:26:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Write a song about it:

https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=KGAQJI-BBs0

Cover a song about it:

https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=kS5oa5IPSX0 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-03 20:05:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> https://www.govtrack.us/congress/members/ </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-03 11:59:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The Apportionment Acts of 1911 and 1929

https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Apportionment_Act_of_1911

https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Reapportionment_Act_of_1929

The House of Representatives was meant to grow with the population, and the frozen size of the House consolidates power while promoting corruption.

It's a bipartisan issue.

Don't listen to me.  Read and decide for yourself.  If you agree that these need to be gone, spread the word.

Please. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-03 11:44:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yup, that's why he suddenly wants to talk about Jackson and the Civil War. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-03 11:41:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Wasn't he "angered" to hear about Flynn's contact with Russia?

That's acting the part for a lie.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Trump Gets a Win He Wasn't Counting On: He Saved the Filibuster </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-03 11:37:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-03 04:02:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Mr Ego is already tired of his office and would rather not be in office.  He'd rather be sitting with Bannon plotting how to stir up the closest thing possible to a civil war.

The man cannot function without lying.  He himself knows that and will resign before he has to testify under oath.  At that point, he will be all about how DC is a massive conspiracy against him and how he is going to continue to fight it from Trump Tower.

Then again, depending on the charges, he may still be arrested and get to be sworn in and testify, but I believe at that point it would be a conventional trial in a conventional court with no cameras and whatnot. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-02 18:32:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> By being my own unit and not feeling that I had to belong.  If I meet people or find a situation where I belong, that's nice, but I move around a lot.  In the next location, if I don't find a group or situation that clicks, then I'm still comfortable being me and doing my thing.  In either case, I know life will go on and that no situation is the only situation always and forever.  It's all temporary, so if the current scenario isn't doing it for me, I start planning how I'm going to move on to a new one.

I think there's a strong parallel here with people and falling in love.  It's good to have a special someone, but if you try to hard to get into a relationship, you'll probably end up in a bad relationship.  It's better to accept being alone and make a more careful choice than to dwell on or feel guilty about being alone and rush to not be alone.

I guess I try to be patient and not force things.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-02 18:12:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Understood.  That does make for a far greater challenge.  Still, I wish you the strength to persevere and and move on when you graduate.

Again, best of luck. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-02 13:31:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Why was there a Civil War? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-02 13:25:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Just wait 50 years. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-02 13:19:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Interesting indeed.  If one were in his position though, wouldn't you just open a new, not the WH Press Secretary account, and do it in a low-profile way?

He's supposedly worth $25 million.  Is he hurrying to bury his money in cryptocurrency so that he can...dunno, something?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-02 13:13:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Andorra won't feel left out when Ted Nugent is appointed their ambassador. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-02 07:13:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Bad joke.  NVM </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-02 03:10:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> LOL, Obamacare is a failure because of a website.

I miss Bill...not really...not at all.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-02 03:00:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Is there a tape of this? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-02 02:44:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Me?  

NO WAIT I DIDN'T MEAN M-kaboom. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-02 02:34:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Trump:  Perfect.  Are you on a mattress?  What are you wearing? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-02 02:31:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That's because he only has a thing for Putin.

Then there's that thing with the mattress.

Same same, but different. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-02 02:27:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What has civilization come to? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-02 02:23:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If we can kill the first amendment, there will be no more failure and/or catastrophe.  Just winning. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-02 02:11:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Well, good luck with moving.  Start planning where and how to move now and manage your money carefully so that you can make that move long term.

Use your plan to move as motivation to take your studies seriously.

Also, remember there are things like the Peace Corps and Teach for America that might help you get out of there in ways other than simply moving.  A lot of people aren't so interested in Peace Corps or Teach for America because they don't pay, but they do pay to move you somewhere else so that you don't have to risk your own money, and both look great on job resumes.

Anyway, good luck! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
