<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject5518</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> When did you know that you wanted to become a teacher? Have you found that it's a fulfilling career? Are there any specific characteristics or traits that you believe a person needs to posses in order to enjoy/succeed at educating children? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-02 19:33:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'd love to read your responses. I'm in college, currently debating on whether or not to major in education. It's something I've always wanted to do, but I'd love to hear others opinions and insight to have a better understanding of what this career path may entail. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What is a book that can help me discover my life's purpose? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-10 02:37:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Mt. Sequoyah // Fayetteville, Arkansas </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-03 06:04:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-31 07:29:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's a mental disorder that requires diagnosis by a medical professional in order to be treated with prescription medication. Yes, you can feel depressed, so it is a feeling. But it is also so much more than that. For many people it is something they battle on a daily basis. Calling it a feeling is really not doing it justice to the people who suffer from it. It's an unfortunate reality for millions of people, and it requires tremendous strength just to simply live day to day. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-31 06:04:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Care to explain why you believe that you can't be diagnosed with depression? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-30 23:17:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Amazing view! Love it! Thank you so much! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-30 23:17:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Great photo! I love it. Thank you so much! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-30 23:17:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Awesome! Thank you! Much love to you in Cali! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-30 23:16:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Love this! Beautiful photo. Thank you so much! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-30 23:16:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It worked! I love the photo! Thank you so much  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
