<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject5401</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-09 17:21:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> this is like when white people claim 1/85th native american to get land for casinos </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-09 06:12:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> lol common white supremacist tactic....get shut down run around like a bitch haha stop embarassing yourself child </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-09 01:06:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Glad it's a multi platform glitch and not a switch defect  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-08 20:48:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> same here...glad im not alone </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-08 17:50:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>   I haven't played a DNZ fighter

havent played on of those before </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Little girl refuses donald trumps hug sayingyour a disgrace to the world </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-08 16:52:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-08 15:33:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> THIS!!!!! he just needs to git gud....combat is the best part....love having a long duel with a lizalfos....the durability punishes mindless spams and if youve played dark souls like i have this is not an issue at all </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-08 13:34:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Lol you say something idiotic... Get hit with facts... And run away like a coward lmao </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-08 06:25:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> yes he is you fuckin retard just google the name nathan damigo youl see all his alt right videos where hes spewing his white supremacists views....follow your own advice and GTFO...https://www.youtube.com/channel/UC5AWJ25SWOANhxfbwl55RJQ heres his page for your stupid ass </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-07 17:06:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  Yes, and antifas' views are influenced

were not talkin about them tho....and this is not a video of an antifa member punching someone is it?  not saying that antifa is better of course but briging them up seems like a delfection imo </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-06 21:34:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> you have no idea..... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-06 21:33:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> never got to play Skyward sword but would love too if i got a good port....to be honest if they remade Oot or MM with the BOTW effect im totally game...just want more open world zeldas </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-06 21:17:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> that means on the neons the discoloration will be VERY noticable </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-06 21:16:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  Link between worlds. Nuff said.

its an indirect sequal not a remake, i would prefer a port of windwaker or skyward sword before Oot and mm theyve gotten enough attention for the time being </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-06 20:57:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> switches get bitches </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-06 20:56:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> naw man...they should give a link to the past the BOTW effect thats the next remake they need....Oot and MM have been remade already </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-06 20:45:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> dam in cases like that id keep a small bottle of alcohol im my bad and some wipes for after usage...im wiered like that i dont like smudges or nothing on my gadgets...are they the neon ones? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-06 20:38:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> dam that sucks...im gonna inspect my friends hands before they use mine haha </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-06 20:31:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> mine also came with a vert tiny scratch in the lower left region only noticable when the console is off and you LOOK for it fortunately </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-06 20:30:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> i always wash my hands before i touch my joycons and i play with a fan blowing on me because my hands sweat to keep them as pristine as possible </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-06 20:28:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> they are supposed to have a little wobble incase you drop them for shock absorption </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-06 20:01:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  it just seems like an even bigger reason to avoid combat than the base game.

the combat is the best part of this game, you just need to git gud good weapons are EVERYWHERE your getting about 40% of the games potential </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-06 17:31:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> i dont even think its a coil....looks like a penny that has a hole drilled in it....you can see metal shavings on the edges </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-06 16:59:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> wow...i wonder how this guys guts are holding up </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-06 16:18:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> sharks dont care how nice your tits are </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-06 15:57:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> wonder why theres no picture of the offender </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-06 15:35:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> are they actual nazis? maybe but there views and quotes are influenced heavily by hitler and nazi-ism and the only difference? hair as far as im concerned they are nazis with hair lets call them what they are, hell go listen to spencers Hail Trump speech </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-06 01:58:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> not at all...i used hittler since damingo is a member of alt right wich are nazis with hair </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-05 23:21:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> comparing the two is like comparing adolf hittler and a crazy person swinging a bat while they are both bad which one is worse?????? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-05 22:29:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> the man who punched her is white supremacist nathan damigo very vile and disgusting man </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-05 18:39:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> i know certain breeds like pugs suffer from breathing and weezing because they are not a natural breed. There are also several other man made breeds that suffer medical conditions Siberian Huskies seem to be predisposed to a variety of autoimmune disorders, many of which affect the skin. oh and when i said mixed i did not mean a mutt lol refering to dogs bred specifcally to look a certain way </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-05 18:29:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> shit looks goofy as fuck </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-05 17:25:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> wow...so getting it for some mixed races that are BORN with pre existing conditions because there a mix are SOL??? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-05 17:24:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> thats what the back protectors are for bro </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-05 15:56:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  pet insurance

wtf???that exists?? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-05 14:00:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> not worth the risk....and probably voided the waranty </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> White teacher fired for dragging black child through hallway </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-05 03:27:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-04 23:43:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> make his own account? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-04 23:07:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> no...please no....the voice actors are what make rick and morty </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-04 22:28:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> looks like hes about to drop the hottest mixtape of the year </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-04 21:38:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> who has an autistic spectrum disorder and belived to be the cause

notice when its a white bomber they always have a mental disorder? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-04 19:08:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yep that's the one I bought... Don't want any other style of cases... 
Fits perfectly in my jacket pocket, the long ones look silly and I hear they mash the shoulder buttons  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-04 19:00:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> i hope the backpack wasnt in your car overnight??if so kinda your fault too </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-04 18:58:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> not a fan of the long cases....wish they made a smaller version that holds everything detached </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-03 21:57:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> this is unstirred paint????thought it was an anotomical picazzo style heart </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-03 17:24:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> i shut down mine all the time...so this will only happen if i shut it down with low power right? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-03 17:11:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> me!!! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-03 15:39:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> your right...but its better than previous cases </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-03 15:32:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> wait....justice was served??? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-02 23:13:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> because of the title...show me a similar title with a white victim </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-02 23:12:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  Toss it on the dock and leave it alone: Might wear out the battery

even if you turn it off? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> switch gets warm while docked </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-02 18:29:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-02 17:24:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> the right one? got the classic left joycon issues...playing about 12 ft away from the dock and the left one starts getting wonky the right is alwasy on point moving close to about 7 feet from the dock solves the issue tho </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-02 16:51:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> complexion for the protection </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-02 16:46:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> why on earth are you being downvoted? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-02 16:43:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> i have yet to use mine because of the horror stories...they have been banished to a drawer never to see the light of day again </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-02 16:39:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> switch is barely two months old....why do people speculate so early? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-02 15:44:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> the shit that flies out these peoples mouth to defend whites.... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-02 15:31:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> or he threw up the peace sign during a facebook pic wearing a purple shirt he would have been associated with the grape street crypts </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-02 15:30:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> thats white supremacy....they dont care how vile or disgusting the crime is as long as a black person is killed they cheer </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-02 15:28:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> here comes the splainin..... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-02 15:14:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> how long is kamiko? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-02 15:06:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> release date?!?!?! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-02 15:01:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  super boring to never need any other weapons.

this your first zelda? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-02 14:55:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> dont even have to click the title and i already know hes black </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-02 14:50:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> lol i love this </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-02 13:42:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> i wonder who will try to defend this racist fuck this time </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Switch in the wild penonome panam </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-01 23:40:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-29 04:53:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I third this question </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-29 04:45:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> wow just bought mine today and didnt even think to check...thankfully everything was there </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-28 16:26:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> waiting for the first case of racial profiling from a robot </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-27 20:42:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> its gonna be a one on one fight depending on which side you choose thats who you play as and the book of love will be playing in the background...it will be beautiful </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-27 20:39:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> even if he was? when the cops approched him he wasnt pointing it at anyone when they blasted him...besides why shoot someone whose pointing at gun at people? what if he discharges and kills someone hes supposedly pointing at? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-27 20:31:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> it always matters when its a cop </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-27 20:26:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  Requiring evidence for racism is not ignorant.

The fact you even said this when the racism is so blatant proves your willfull ignorance...

 That's actually not true - at least not for this year. So far, 134 white people have been shot by the police. Nine of them were unarmed. 79 black people have been shot so far this year. Six of them were unarmed. That's 6.7% of unarmed white people shot; 7.6% of unarmed black people shot. That's less than a percentage point difference. It's hardly cause for cries of racism.

i said shot and KILLED bro...show me those stats, none of these whites are getting killed white supremacists protect there own kind and show me a white unarmed 12 year child that was shot please...at least not this year? look at your logic that makes the last decade ok?

 BLM exists because, apparently, the black community identifies themselves by black first and an individual second. 

proving your ignorance yet again...BLM started after the murder of trayvon martin absolutely NOTHING to do with black first individual second...only white supremacists have that mind set, BLM campaigns against violence and perceived systemic racism toward black people nothing to do with your ignorant comment

The white supremacists community, apparently, identifies themselves as WHITE first every other color second. FTFY


In other words, if a white person is shot by a cop, who cares? He probably did something he shouldn't have been doing.

said no one ever.....


 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-27 18:37:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> he lifted his shirt....passed the point of reaching his waist...cops came out of the car whist his shirt was lifted </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-27 18:32:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  Citation needed.

your willfully ignorant...you made that clear

 I actually don't know that. Plenty of white people are shot by cops every year. In fact, MORE white people are shot by cops than black people

yes you do know that now your just playing stupid even your momma will tell you that...in fact, MORE unarmed black people are shot AND killed by cops...why do you think BLM exists? is there a WLM group doing protests for these white people getting shot?it must be real low key </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-27 17:55:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> gonna address the elephant in the room....was the  73 year old man black? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-27 17:51:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  This was all within a few seconds. You do realize that, right?

how many times did i say he was blasted within seconds? regardless the fact that tamir was black is why they reacted they way they did...if he was a white 12 year old the scenerio would have been COMPLETELY different and you know it....and once more the cop got out of the car whilst he had his shirt lifted...passed the point of pulling out...you have to reach for your waist when you go into your pocket to get things like you know your ID? keys? felando castiel reached for his wallet and got executed in front of his wife and child, he could of gone to scratch his ass and he still would have been blasted...tamir rice was the wrong color in the wrong place...plain and simple
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-27 17:09:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> rats lookin up like.....yea???? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-27 16:23:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  He 100% reached for his waistband.

to lift up his  shirt....not even near his waistband anymore when they shot him...which means they saw him go for his waist, lift the shirt, then they shot him...it says clearly the officer exits the vehicle while he has his shirt up...no where near his waist anymore when the cop comes out...anyone defending this is a blatant white supremacist....and you dont pull up to someone that close when you suspect them of having a gun....gtfo </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-27 16:06:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> the officers were called in about a gun and that it looks fake.....he never reached for his waistband he was blasted in seconds </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-27 15:49:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> gun was in his waistband...he never pointed it at the officers...watch the video and get your facts straight....get your facts straight can we at least start there?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-27 15:45:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> anyone defending this is a blatant white supremacist </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-27 15:44:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  a possible gunman

pelletgunchild FTFY </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-27 15:40:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> these are not cops, these are race soldiers they join law enforcement for the sole purpose of maintaining  white supremacy....tamir rice was the wrong color in the wrong place....thats all </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-26 23:34:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> i also call BS </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-26 16:44:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> it makes no sense for the next gen MH not to be on th next gen console...switch and MH are a match made in heaven </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> MH5 for switch can someone confirm? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-26 16:40:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-26 05:41:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What if its Wally? That would traumatize me............ </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> utorrent seeding by itself out of the blue </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-26 01:01:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> utorrent is seeding completed torrents and downloading movies from my completed list automatically since yesterday...woke up to find my hard drive almost full and 14 movies seeding and movies already downloaded REdownloading by them selves!!!!!i stop the seeding and they just start right back up....very frustrating  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-25 23:37:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> exactly...its ingrained in my muscle memory when ever i get up from sitting wallet, keys, phone....even when im home and have shorts with no pockets i will pat them and feel despair for like a second when i dont feel anything lol </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-25 22:57:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> been waiting for that rotation haha </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-25 22:33:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> am i the only one that finds that hippos mouth funny as hell? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-25 22:27:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> unless it was a VERY close friend or family memeber...would not be stopping or rolling down the windows for  no one, hell i wouldnt even answer the phone till all of that is deposited </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-25 20:46:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> how boaring </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-25 19:30:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> watching the 2016 anime made me read the manga from start to finish...dont have any issues with the animation...people just need to stop being whiney pansies...when i discovered there were missing arcs i EAGERLY picked up the manga and have even convinced many of my friends to watch the series who are now reading the manga...i think the anime does an excellent job peaking peoples interest to make them read the manga and discover whats been cut out like it did for me and many of my co workers...speak for yourself  bro </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-25 19:24:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> THIS!!!!im just glad theres an anime adaptation that continues period </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-25 19:23:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> i did not mind the animation to begin with...i think the CGi works very well for the big sword fights...slan vs guts and grenbald vs guts will be amazing </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The 3 musketeers </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-25 18:50:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-25 18:33:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> i slap my pockets even when i get up from the toilet....better to be safe than sorry imo </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-25 18:33:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> hell yea! much better idea especially if you sold everything you own for it </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-25 18:32:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> exactly...once she said pidegon would of kept driving </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-25 18:31:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> lol yes pat thanks!! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-25 18:31:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> not at all </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
