<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject8128</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-04 21:21:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> He loves life. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-04 17:53:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's not a photocopy, just a shitty photo. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-04 12:35:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> My buddy took one like that, it's pretty good. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-04 10:30:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It sounds like they're probably better off without your "help" anyway.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-04 08:11:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thx bruh </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-03 22:24:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> People can be worse than fairy tale monsters. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-03 21:19:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> All this is irrelevant because you look at breasts on the internet. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Paranoia on the subway [OC] </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-03 20:20:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> ITAP of a guy who really likes the theme from Titanic. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-03 19:52:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-27 08:05:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's just that even though more lefty types voted, you're all consolidated in a few places. If you want to really change things then leave California  and move to the midwest!  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-27 08:00:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'd say it's law in *some* cities. I was in law enforcement years ago and we called ICE for illegals. I'd have to ask but I'm pretty sure it's standard practice for all of my buddies that are still cops.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-26 21:28:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What are the percentages? 

Just looked, 81% of Russians are ethnic Russians.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-26 20:21:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Okay. That legitimately sounds like what he said. So some dudes asked me if I know the devil in the middle of the night  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-26 20:18:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Oh god, stop!   lol </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-26 20:13:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That's a little creepy if he was asking me if I knew about sacrilege.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-26 15:38:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Stuttgart, so regional dialect is a distinct possibility. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-26 13:59:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I was taking pictures of a festival at night from outside the festival and he seemed to be walking to the festival with a friend. It's possible that I heard it wrong .  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Help translating something </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-26 13:31:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The other night some guys said something to me and I couldn't figure out part of it. The part I couldn't figure out sounded like "tea-fell" and it was used in this sentence: "Kennen sie *tea-fel*. Thanks! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-26 09:54:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Also, parking in the US is much better than the place in Europe I've been to. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-26 09:48:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The amount of people taking you seriously is amazing.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-25 10:41:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm usually uncomfortable with people talking to me closer than arms length unless I know them but I've never freaked out about it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-24 12:45:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Coffee </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-24 10:03:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I believe the high suicide rate is actually among veterans. There's been controversy in recent years with their medical care.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-24 09:58:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> They get pretty good coverage, not necessarily the best care. Officers are paid pretty well and enlisted get pretty good benefits like money for college. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-21 10:58:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You're just a baby boy, you don't know any better. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-20 21:07:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That's tastefully done. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-20 20:04:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The fly geyser. 

Edit - nevermind, seems to be closed to the public.

White Sands, NM or Marble Canyon, AZ. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-19 16:35:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> National defense is one aspect but not the only aspect. You're just ignoring the parts you disagree with and throwing in things that you think are witty. Sedgewick, Mason, Monroe, Patrick Henry and many others are quoted talking about the defense from tyranny.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-19 16:19:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That's weird considering the controversy when moving from the extremely limited central government under the Articles of Confederation to a stronger federal government. I don't really agree with you. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-19 15:12:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I think the National Guard are excluded considering that they rely heavily on the federal government for funding and that the President has the authority to put them under federal control. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-19 14:59:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> My interpretation is that they wanted everyone armed so that a militia could be formed when/if it was needed.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-19 12:42:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That's interesting, thanks. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-19 11:46:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hitler actually used the word "degenerate" and not a German word? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-19 09:01:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Just want to point out that it says that a well regulated militia is necessary for the security of a free state but nothing about it being necessary to be in a militia to have the right to own fire arms. The Supreme Court also agrees with that interpretation.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-18 08:00:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> They don't do that everywhere, at least not at the hospital I used to work at in Kentucky (not sure of the local police procedures). They would just have a person sit outside your room in the ER and walk with you up to the psych unit if you were admitted. Now if you became violent that's a different story.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
