<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject9504</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-10 15:50:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What image/kernel are you running? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Cat-God Panorama created by Google Photos. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-10 14:57:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-09 23:59:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> "showing it off"....yeah, I'd lose that if I were you.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-09 19:32:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> One of the guys I went to the academy with was 20...turned 21 a couple of weeks into the academy.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-09 16:05:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This isnt going to be popular, I know this in advance. I am not a Trump fan, but I am open-minded and reasonable. When I first started hearing the term "fake news" thrown around I thought it was just a Trump distraction tactic, but then I started paying attention when I read the news and began noting (just for me) if 1) it was newsworthy, and 2) if so, has it been spun and if not, has it been spun. Thats when I decided that "fake news" is a very real thing. This tweet is probably news, but the article and the accusation that its a threat, fake news.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-09 15:26:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> One spring morning in the early eighties a red-breasted baby bird appeared on my grandfathers back porch. After sufficient time had passed when it was apparent there would be no momma-bird rescue, my grandfather took it in. He fed it worms scavenged from his large yard after a rain and little strips of bologna and watched it grow into an adult bird. I dont think it ever had a name, other than "Bird". Bird always stayed with my grandfather, on his shoulder, or riding in the top of the fishing hat he always wore. Eventually, my grandfather built a small window, complete with a platform for Bird to land on, in the back room of his house so that Bird could come and go. And thats what Bird did. All summer long. Until one day he didnt.  My grandfather must have anticipated this, the only pet I ever knew him to have not returning home one day, but we never spoke of it. Within weeks, maybe a month, Bird was seemingly forgotten, the small window in the back room the only reminder of his ever having been there. Surprisingly, when spring returned the next year another red-breasted baby bird appeared on my grandfathers back porch, and the cycle repeated itself. This happened once more after that. Looking back it was a beautiful thing. Through my eyes my grandfather was the toughest man alive, a WWII veteran who worked as a lineman and electrician after the war.  He once came in contact with high-voltage while working atop a utility pole. The shock knocked him unconscious, causing him to fall from the pole breaking his back. Hitting the ground knocked him back to consciousness. He was told he would never work again, but returned to climbing poles two months later. Probably my biggest memory of my grandfather, captured in an old photograph I have, is him lying in bed, shirtless, with bird standing proudly on his chest. Immediately after the photograph was taken Bird cocked his head to the side, eyed my grandfathers nipple, and bit it. I always laugh when I think of that.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-08 17:19:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> upvoted. Also..Super Troopers... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-08 12:41:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I cant believe I just upvoted this.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-05 17:16:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> True story. I once had a girlfriend who said "no I dont like bananas. They make me gag." So I said, "Maybe you're eating them the wrong way." I thought that was hilarious! I ended up married to her for almost five miserable years.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-05 16:27:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Be polite, be professional, but have a plan to kill everybody you meet. -James Mattis </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-05 16:23:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Great article. Well written. Interesting.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-05 12:27:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I wonder if Lil John puts up much of a fight when he attempts this...or if he calms him by saying "shhhhhhh, let it happen. Let it happen." Works about ten percent of the time when trying to convince my wife to express my penis gland.... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-05 03:02:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> We've done it for years and never had any issues with it. In my opinion its the most trouble-free of all of the solutions. It forces the patron to use headphones and...well, it just works.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-04 20:52:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> We have always disconnected the speakers on all public machines. Patrons may buy headphones from the front desk for $2 or may bring their own. 

EDIT: just re-read your post. The speaker can almost always be unplugged from the board with no problems at all. I have never run into a machine that this wasnt the case. Open the case. Locate the speaker. Follow the wires. Unplug from board. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-04 15:01:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> ..and the dad managed to keep his cool throughout this entire ridiculous encounter. Some incompetent dipshit who should never be allowed to interact with the public, much less have authority tells him he and his wife are going to jail and his kids are going to foster care. THAT is a huge thing.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-04 14:56:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Delta, right up there with United....and Comcast </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Cock of the walk...(SFW) </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-04 02:00:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-04 01:55:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> As someone in IT who constantly gets asked "can you update our website", I read this as Word Press Freedom Day. I came here for free plugins. Disappointed.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-03 22:52:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> CATS HAVE NO SOULS </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-03 21:11:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> ba...ba....duk </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> ..thats not your reflection </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-03 17:52:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> When you realize thats not your reflection... </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-03 17:44:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> When you realize thats not your reflection... </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-03 13:52:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Soulmates (album). Rescue dog and stray kitty. Best friends. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-03 02:11:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Happy Dogo </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-03 01:46:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-02 13:45:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Saltwater fortune cookie... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-01 14:48:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This guy fucks. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-01 03:50:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Slammin Salmon is GREAT. It's right up there with Super Troopers. 

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-28 16:33:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> He doesnt realize that he has a double feed or a misfeed of some sort.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-28 16:33:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> He doesnt realize that he has a double feed or a misfeed of some sort.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-27 19:41:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Wow! Great job, lady!  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-26 16:49:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Definitely need to be more specific. No idea what you mean here. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-26 13:28:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I didn't even want to upvote this, but I also couldn't stop myself from upvoting it.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-26 12:29:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I came here to leave this exact comment, but you beat me to it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-26 12:28:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> pimps </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-26 12:20:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You mentioned (in an earlier thread I think) that you have read some books about history and about the Egyptians and where we came from. Could you recommend some of these please? Thanks. Also, love the ink. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-26 12:15:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You mentioned (in an earlier thread I think) that you have read some books about history and about the Egyptians and where we came from. Could you recommend some of these please. Thanks. Also, love the ink.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-25 23:47:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Downloading now. Thanks for the work! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-25 23:33:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thanks for the info. The shape and the curve really look great. Be sure to post a finished pic...or maybe an album of the entire project. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-25 23:22:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I know nothing about metal-working, but wouldnt a file be too brittle to make a good blade? Just curious. Is there a way, by heating and submersing in water, to re-temper or un-temper or something? Again, not speaking negative about your work. It looks great to me. Just curious.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-24 18:10:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> looking through their site its interesting to note that each tier of service has its own "coverage" link that takes you to a different cellular providers coverage map. The cheapest plan links to Sprint. The next up links to Tmobile. Next to ATT. And their most expensive links to Verizon.  This isnt a bad thing, I dont suppose, just interesting.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-23 04:26:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> uggggg..sorry to hear that, man. I hope it gets worked out soon. Its not unreasonable to expect something to work that you're paying for. Good luck to you!   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-23 00:58:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This is a horrible tragedy.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-23 00:51:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This was great! The delivery and timing were great also. Very funny! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-23 00:37:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> A little off topic, but OMG YOU ARE EXACTLY RIGHT!!  The worst has to be Sprint. I have been a Sprint customer for almost 12 years and have avoided making changes to my account for that reason alone! Isnt that ridiculous of me!! Because the account is so old I am still paying for "free nights and weekends" and "nights and weekends starting at 6pm" for four lines! These cannot be removed from my account through their web interface. It requires a phone call, but anytime I call Sprint I end up speaking to someone in a call center in India (I assume). Sometimes their accents are so thick that I have no idea what they're saying, and I find myself straining to use simple words and phrases to ensure accurate communication. It actually causes me anxiety when I have to call them. Sorry for the rant. I hope you love your Project Fi phone! I love mine! Good luck to you!   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-23 00:14:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Just in case you dont read my main comment I am posting here also. Have you noticed that the Specialists seem to be over-the-top polite and cheerful, and that this seems to take priority over actually solving your problems? I have called them many times, and this "niceness contest" that they all seem to be preoccupied with makes me doubt their competence.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-23 00:12:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I have had nothing but great experiences with their Specialists, and I have had to call many times. A recurring theme I have picked up on is the Specialists seem to be having a see-who-can-be-the-nicest contest, and this seems to take priority over actually solving problems. It does NOT inspire confidence at all.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-23 00:05:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Dow Chemical will, undoubtedly, have their way. Ignore the studies. Handout a White House office to a lobbyist. Yay!   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-22 17:37:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Fluxion is way more feature-packed than Linset. I got my start on Linset, and had a lot of success with it, but then stumbled upon Fluxion..and I love it for getting into wireless networks. The only problem I had, in the beginning (with both Fluxion and Linset), was getting close enough to a target to take over their network. If I was in an apartment and shared a wall with a target it was no trouble, but sitting in my car outside of a targets office building was a challenge. What I am saying is that both Linset and Fluxion are great tools, but they have their limitations. One way to be more efficient might be to capture the handshake and try cracking it somewhere WHILE you are simultaneously running a Fluxion attack. That would certainly increase your chances and be a more efficient use of time and resources in my opinion. Good luck! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> NSFW Once I saw it I couldnt unsee it. My dogs rear looks like...maybe a Simpsons character..or something </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-22 17:05:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-22 16:12:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> LoL, yeah, it's lonely here in the....uh...embassy.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Perfect timing...and lucky I didnt lose a finger.. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-22 05:42:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-21 20:58:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I thought so, too...creeeeeepy... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> My dog does NOT fuck around with she sleeps. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-21 19:16:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-21 18:58:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> lol..you are exactly right! Thanks for the response!  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-21 18:55:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> There used to be a way to make Windows Firewall log all connection attempts to a text file. You could enable that an keep an eye on it for a while. It may turn-up some info eventually.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-21 18:52:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I dont know if this still works or not, but if ssh is enabled on a jailbroken ipad and if the default password hasnt been changed.. theoretically you could ssh into an iphone or ipad.. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-21 18:46:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If you are looking to get the password to someones wireless I have had great success with Linset and Fluxion. I recommend these all the time because they have worked for me. Sure, you can capture the handshake and wait to crack it...or you can use the above and just let the target handover his password. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-21 18:35:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> YES! EVERY. DAY. My newest one is a year old...and she'll spot me glaring at her from a distance wondering what shes chewing on. She always turns her back to me and chews faster. Sometimes I make it to her in time. Sometimes I dont.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-21 18:29:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> As far as I know It is not possible to find someones IP address using only their home address or coordinates. There are other methods that might work with a little luck. Make a webpage and give the link to your target. Once the target visits the webpage from his home location you can retrieve their ip address from logs/code on your site.  Also, if the person sends you an email from his home then his ip address will be included in the email headers (although this isnt the case with gmail). There are more, but thats a start. Good luck. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-21 16:58:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Good comment, lol.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-21 14:37:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> For me that means I'll download it and then stare at my phone for the next week wondering if flashing it is going to break everything I love about it. Eventually I will download it again (because I will forget where I put it) and flash it while biting my nails and wondering how I am going to communicate with the world without my phone.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-21 14:05:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Its March. My bad. Sorry about that. I just checked. https://www.androidfilehost.com/?w=files flid=34545 sort_by=date sort_dir=DESC </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> There is just no way either of these guys are comfortable. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-21 12:58:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-21 12:46:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This. For sure. Reddit may be blocked my mistake, but the library should disable the filter for any adult without question. Library IT/sysadmin for ten years. We used out own homemade filter and would remotely disable it for any adult who asked - and we never questioned why.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-21 02:27:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I hear ya. Mine is more responsive than ever. The camera still lags most of the time. Especially in low light, but I can live with that. Good luck! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-20 21:05:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> EXACT same thing happened to me last week. I had the Dec ver of PureNexus (no idea why). It started working as soon as I upgraded to April. Also, I noticed that current PureNexus release was significantly larger than the previous releases. This is just something I noticed and was not a problem. I posted over in XDA and got a little help. Good luck.

Edit: dirty flash worked for me. Didnt lose anything. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-18 17:00:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I am ashamed to say that...I was waiting for him to smell his finger once he saw the mans ass. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-17 23:36:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I think the dependencies are pretty common ones and installation is straightforward if they arent included in the install. It should run on ubuntu.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-17 19:37:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Youtube is a GREAT resource.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-17 19:33:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I learned with linset running on wifislax on an old eeepc. It worked great, but wifislax is mostly in Spanish.  I'm glad I learned on it, but I think I like fluxion better. Fluxion is updated more regularly and has more options. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-17 16:34:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> My N6 is the best phone I have ever owned. When it got old and slow I flashed PureNexus. Then when I got tired of it again I flashed the Franco kernel. Now I feel like I have a brand new phone. Its great! I am always watching my local craigslist for N6's that are reasonably priced.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-17 16:30:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I always try linset or fluxion either first or while I wait for the handshake to crack. Sometimes I try them several times per day at different times. In my experience about 75% of the time I have tricked the user into giving-up the password this way. 

Edit: this is not a direct answer to your question, but assumes that you are looking to get into a wireless network.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-17 16:20:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That was awesome! Watching that video really put me in a good mood. I dont know why. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-17 03:17:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Wow....rabbit hole. Looks like I'll be neglecting my dogs, girlfriend, my son, work, etc for the foreseeable future. Thanks.

Seriously though. Thanks. Great stuff.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-14 18:16:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I had the same problem, except I had the Dec security update. I tried all kernel builds (r60-64) and still no audio. I also tried dirty and clean flashing. No audio. In the end I restored to my backup. I am still looking into using the franco kernel. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-10 20:27:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> True story: a friend of mine has had a similar model for years. He likes to use it WHILE HE IS HAVING A BOWEL MOVEMENT. The result is brown shit-splashes dried all around the seat...top and bottom of the seat...shit EVERYWHERE. He acts totally unaware. What the fuck? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-10 13:32:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I could actually see this scene. Thanks for posting.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-10 13:21:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yep, they do not and will not give a shit about him. Whats "concerning" is the money they're anticipating losing since this has blown up.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-10 13:18:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I dont follow airline news, but it seems they're always bitching about losing money. THIS is REALLY going to cost them.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-10 12:32:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I would hate to be the United employee who took his seat. That crowd was very sympathetic to the removed passenger.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-08 17:03:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thank you.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-08 16:21:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I see what you did there.. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-08 00:25:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This reminds me of the Ted Danson blackface incident.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-05 15:25:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> same... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-05 02:59:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I was home alone a few days ago. It had been a long while since I last looked through that joke folder. So I decided to take a look. I laughed so hard that my stomach muscles hurt. Later on, I ran a few of them by my wife. We both had a great laugh.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-05 01:41:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> No..convenience I guess. Its just quick (for me) to send a text to my email address. I started doing it years ago. Its really worked out.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-04 02:19:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> In my everyday life in conversation or sometimes alone, I will think of something hilarious (hilarious to me), and I will email it to myself.  When I go back and read those emails, which all go into a special folder in gmail, some are hits and some are misses. Some are killers (to me) and some I cant even remember why I thought they were funny. But I have them all in my email...and going thought them is always a blast.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The Accident No One Talked About </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-02 08:37:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-01 17:04:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> ...fucking awesome! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-01 17:04:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> ...to be... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-01 17:03:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This is going.... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-01 12:55:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> In Russia....phone finds you. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-31 21:48:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Also posted over on hackernews. Checkout the comments over there https://news.ycombinator.com/item?id=14001903

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-31 19:21:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> after hearing from a Verizon spokesperson EFF has withdrawn this post as of 1320hrs while they investigate further. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-31 19:21:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> after hearing from a Verizon spokesperson EFF has withdrawn this post as of 1320hrs while they investigate further. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-30 19:43:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I've had similar experiences for many years.  Very scary. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-29 18:26:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thanks for the info, but shaming these greedy dipshits does absolutely no good...because they're completely SHAMELESS. COMPLETELY SHAMELESS...and dipshits. They seldom do whats right for their voters unless it somehow aligns with whatever lines their pockets.  But still..thanks for the info.. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-29 13:26:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> My apps did not auto-install during initial setup as I had expected them to do, and I havent manually installed them all yet. Actually, I have only managed to install a few of the "most-used" apps. So I assume that I may have trouble down-the-road with root. Thanks for the heads-up.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-29 03:08:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I installed the purenexus rom on my N6 today. I was running marshmallow, and was tired of the lag when switching apps, sending texts, opening the camera, and taking photos. I installed purenexus 7.1.1 and am delighted with the speed of my phone now. My only complaint is the camera is still a bit slow. Otherwise, I am very happy.



 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-27 23:50:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I think it was stocked recently.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-26 16:02:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Donald Pup goes right for the pussy. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-26 16:01:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Donald Pup goes right for the pussy.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-24 02:00:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> worked...thanks man.
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-23 20:17:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Definitely....definitely asking for a friend. I totally forgot to mention that.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-23 15:14:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thanks for the heads-up. Is there anyway at all to access TPB right now? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Pretty fly for a horsefly. Repost. Not photoshopped. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-23 14:02:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-22 18:05:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Have an upvote </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-21 00:00:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Actually, No.  It was like a precise strike. She ripped the mask from my face without touching me at all. But she has nipped me a few times in the past: http://m.imgur.com/8siKgJH.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-20 23:55:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This article states "To hear the head of the FBI in essence call the president a liar or wide-eyed conspiratorialist is bracing, if not humiliating..." But that never occurred. At least it didn't occur literally. To twist Comey's actual words , the words he spoke, into that statement seems a bit, well, "fake news-ish" to me. According to the article Comey stated, "I have no information that supports those tweets." He didn't say, "Yeah, no that's bullshit. Trumps a liar." Comey didn't say that. He didn't really say anything like that at all. What he basically said is, "I personally am not aware of any such activity by the Obama administration." To say that this is devastating for Trump isn't even news at all. I'm not even a Trump fan and I feel like this not really news. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Dogs reaction to scare.. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-20 22:53:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
