<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject6932</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-10 08:19:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Chromosomes are not the sole determine factor of one's sex. They are in fact the factor least often checked. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-10 08:05:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> She did not openly begin transition until after her arrest, though apparently there were signs before. I'll have to find that link.

Edit: [NYT](http://www.nytimes.com/2013/08/23/us/bradley-manning-says-he-is-female.html) article from 2013. They detail some of the early signs partway through the article. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-10 06:23:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I can see MSNBC but why Ellen? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-10 06:20:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Tagged as "Fuckin' called it." </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-10 06:13:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Well given reports coming out of the DOJ that they were instructed to come up with reasons to fire Comey, it seems a little one-sided to provide one quote from Sessions, who was supposed to have recused himself from the Russia investigation completely. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-10 05:59:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Appears to be weird lighting too. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-10 05:29:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah but it used to up until it wasn't anymore, so obviously it still is, duh. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-10 05:25:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I bet that /u/thickner is okay with the thick. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-10 05:22:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Then why are subpoenas being issued today? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-10 05:04:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Oh, I checked. It does seem bizarre but for two reasons I wouldn't call them a shill for sure:

1. That kind of accusation can get you banned here.

2. Some people just love to spam everywhere and scream at every little thing.

3. Edit: And they respond. Not saying that an account can't be shared between a person and a bot, but it isn't some set and forget script. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-10 04:57:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Probably not a bot. It's entirely possible they're just a partisan hack of the most paranoid kind. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-10 04:52:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Buckle up buckaroos! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-10 04:52:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Might have something to do with subpoenas being issued today. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-10 04:50:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Aaaaand subpoenas have been issued.

The FBI probably just wants to make sure that people know they're not being investigated. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-10 04:48:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Technically calling out any shills is a bannable offense (though you get warnings). </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-10 04:12:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Huh. Neat. 

Sidenote, I'm an idiot and was wondering why there was no sound.

Edit: I suppose it's somewhat telling that there isn't a sign for "rhyme". </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Is rhyming a thing in sign language? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-10 03:21:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I ask because [this video](https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=KoVDZJqTmRo) came up in an /r/videos thread and it got me wondering. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-10 03:19:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Because driving is not something that humans evolved to do. Sitting down on a comfy chair in an air-conditioned box doesn't really trigger our danger response. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-10 03:12:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Because it would be super obvious who did it and there is no hiding from the long dick of the law when you try to play the IRS. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-10 03:10:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Higher framerates look weird when the camera moves, and changing framerates between static and moving shots would be super distracting. Basically when you move, your eyes don't move smoothly; they jerk from point to point and that blurs your vision. If you don't get that blurring effect when the camera moves, it looks really bad. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-10 02:54:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Okay are you going to do anything but spam this everywhere? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-10 02:54:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That's bureaucracy though. Things take time to happen.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-10 02:22:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So the gays are openly in a tiff with the Jews then. That doesn't really make any sense either. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-10 02:15:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> And Sessions just says he agrees with Trump's decision. The whole thing is just a circle of twattery.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-10 01:55:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You've posted this exact same comment over 20 times in about 15 minutes. Care to expand upon it? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-10 01:51:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Really? Someone under investigation for serious crimes fires the director of one of his own investigative agencies and you think that nothing fishy could possibly be happening? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> ACLU Comment on Trump Firing of FBI Director Comey </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-10 01:18:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Chelsea Manning, Legal Team Statements on Her Upcoming Release From Military Prison </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-10 01:17:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-10 00:23:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Well that's not suspicious at all. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-10 00:19:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> b </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-10 00:19:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> a </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> a test </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-10 00:19:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> what I'm going to do is test a thing </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-09 23:48:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> - Chris Mosier

- U.S. Duathlon National Championship

- I don't know why you care. I guess because you were curious enough to comment on it, but that shows that you do care and doesn't explain why. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-09 23:45:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Well you see, they're gay, and that's icky, because they're gay...

They don't have any real reason for it, they're usually just homophobic. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-09 23:42:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The United story just made it popular to dig up dirt on shitty airlines and because every airline is kinda shitty it's not that hard to do. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-09 23:37:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Ah. Must have fixed it then. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-09 23:25:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Spicey, that's a really bad reason to ignore your Atty General. You've just admitted that you're incapable of trusting anyone who doesn't fall in line with you. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-09 23:20:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Well, psych is science. It's just messy. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-09 23:13:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You realize that medicine is science, right?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-09 23:03:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I bet he's just signing the popular stuff so people remember him more fondly than they otherwise would when he leaves office. But maybe that's just me being cynical. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-09 23:01:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Wow, I'm surprised to see this from Branstad. Seems amazingly out of character for him. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Chris Mosier takes 2nd place at National Championship in North Carolina </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-09 22:59:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-09 22:29:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yes, NiMH. I just remembered they weren't LiIon. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-09 22:21:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Must be a Korean Retriever.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-09 21:13:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> There is work for millennials, but for some reason they won't do it!

(Because they're on reddit.) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-09 20:54:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah, but with ~~NiCad~~ NiMH batteries?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-09 20:49:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Obama's coming for our guns any day now! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-09 20:49:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's not for a flat tire, it's for a tire that's come off the rim. Not the same thing. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-09 20:38:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Oh for fuck's sake. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-09 20:33:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If the attacker had been heard to make racist remarks, it would have been in there. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-09 20:33:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Because the attacker made racist remarks, which means that racism likely played a part. Also this is an Indian paper; the fact that this guy is Sikh matters to them. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-09 19:52:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You keep saying things that aren't true to make it look like the two EOs are the same. They aren't. Scope and intent matter in our legal system. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-09 19:37:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> His top two donors are from North Carolina and DC. He's full of shit. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-09 19:36:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> "I want to speak to your manager!" </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-09 19:28:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I have a folder called 'Weird Tentacle Hentai' on my external drive that I use when I need to transfer files back and forth. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-09 19:26:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Ah, the trick is to have a folder called "Porn" and then an actual porn folder buried deep in a file system somewhere else. 

I don't know if it still works because I've been out of the Apple ecosystem for some time now, but on my old Macbook you could actually hide them in the properties of an application. It was perfect, because nobody would bat an eye at a large .app file. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-09 19:15:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> And just to be clear, they only got through a few questions.

[KCRG](http://www.kcrg.com/content/news/Blum-walks-out-of-exclusive-interview-with-TV9-421676713.html) has posted the whole interview, which for some reason he insisted he be surrounded by children. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-09 19:08:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Someone else explained it. If you put in an address for something that already existed, it 404s. If you put in an address for something that never existed, it goes to the healthcare plan. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-09 18:54:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The scope is entirely different. The Obama EO was in reaction to something that happened, and was not a ban as such; it merely required additional verification with another database, something that slowed many applications for about six months that were already near completion. That's not the same as a blanket ban on seven countries. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-09 17:01:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> He passed a CIA check to receive clearance, but not at the same level as before. And indeed not at a high enough level for his job. Obama didn't do that.

And you should care because putting Flynn in could be an impeachable offense. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-09 16:56:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Intent matters. The intent was do discriminate based on religion, which is not allowed. But even setting that aside, the EO would discriminate based on national origin, which is also not allowed.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-09 16:42:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You're not doing a very good job of it if that's what you were trying to do. You're not poking holes so much as just muddling facts. Obama fired Flynn and stripped his clearance because of his foreign ties, warned Trump about the guy, and Trump brought him on anyway. 

It's hardly pointless that a known national security risk was put in charge of national security, because both Trump and Pence lied when they said they didn't know.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-09 16:37:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's a D+1 district historically so probably. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-09 16:31:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That's not true. North Carolina's voter ID law got struck down because of its intent to disenfranchise black voters. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-09 16:30:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You're the one that brought it up. And that's not what you said. You were acting as though Flynn never had his clearance stripped in the first place, as though you believe Spicer and are trying to pin this on Obama. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-09 08:41:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'd say "I bet they feel stupid now" but they have no capacity for self-reflection. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-09 08:38:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> "Am wishings the stronges healthies!" </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-09 08:30:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Because Trump hired him back on. I'm sure Obama *could* have stepped in and personally stopped Flynn's clearance from being reinstated, but he knew how that would play out. Flynn received clearance after a CIA background check, but as it turns out not even the same clearance he had before. 

Also, and I don't mean to be rude, but are you reading your own source? First off most of it is quoting Sean Spicer, which is not a good guarantee of it being true. Second, it mentions how Flynn left in 2014, losing his clearance, and how he regained it in 2016. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-09 08:03:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm ever so slightly less famous than /u/edgar-is-my-real-dad!

Edit: Also wow this thing works. You definitely see a difference. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-09 08:01:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What are you on about? It was stripped in 2014 by the Obama admin. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-09 06:29:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Flynn's clearance was ended in 2014 when Obama fired him. It was reinstated in December 2016 when Trump rehired him. It was then ended again in February 2017 after his Russia connections came to light and Trump fired him again. 

What you seem to be missing is that *Flynn's clearance was revoked under Obama* and only granted again because Trump hired the guy back on. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-09 06:26:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What's for Hollywood elites? Reddit?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-09 04:43:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> ? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-09 04:41:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Seriously, I'm glad they're curbing the glamorization of things like this. I'm really glad they banned child pageants. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-09 04:36:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I wouldn't say something becomes more diverse when you remove one of the big elements of it. Just smaller. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-09 04:35:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> For real; they'd love nothing more than for Westerners to declare a holy war because it would be their whole recruitment process streamlined. Religion is one hell of a drug, especially if you're poor and uneducated and have to worry about death raining down from above more than once or twice a week. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-09 04:32:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Oh shit fuckin gotem. "Neither are you", man that was beautiful, straight from the hip. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-09 04:31:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Well in fairness Macron isn't president *yet*. You gotta at least give the guy a full day of being in office before you can say he hasn't solved literally every problem. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-09 04:28:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Sean Spicer said

Well there's part of your problem. But even he says "reissued" about Flynn's clearance, because it was originally taken away. Yes, he had clearance through his career, but that ended in 2014 and was only revived recently (and then ended again). </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-09 04:26:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It sounds fine in English. 

In English: "I wish you strong health." (Probably would say "good health" instead of "strong health".)

In English, with Russian accent: "I wish you strong health." It's sinister somehow, and I'm not sure if it's the accent or the guy saying it that does that more. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-09 04:24:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That actually makes a good bit of sense. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-09 04:22:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That's how some people consume things. I know I've picked apart conspiracy theories even if I believe that there's some truth to them, because that's the kind of asshole I am. I do the same thing with movies; even if I like it I pick them apart. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-09 04:21:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The documents that show that seem to be faked, and some quite badly.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-09 04:20:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> For real, I can acknowledge that the guy is a banking insider and I think some of his policies are going to benefit big businesses more than the little guy, but that's centrism. He's a business conservative, not a Jesus conservative, and fortunately in France you can have a party that isn't both of those. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-09 04:15:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Stripey flags, same colors, lots of smoking, who can tell them apart really? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-09 04:13:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If someone wanted to marginalize /r/conspiracy, would it not be in their interest to only upvote the most ridiculous and poorly argued posts to the top, rather than a well-written one, regardless of the narrative that post pushed?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-09 04:11:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hi, I'm an even older account. [Care to look now?](https://np.reddit.com/r/conspiracy/comments/69llr1/spirit_cooking_in_the_macron_emails/)

If you don't want to click, I can explain it: It's a scan of a Korean family tree of sorts, with one name circled and *chef spirituel* written next to it. The title of the post is "Spirit Cooking in the Macron Emails". </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-09 04:05:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> After being stripped of it in 2014. It was at the behest of Trump that he was brought back, and apparently the CIA didn't even grant him the highest clearances as Trump claims (that so far is from anonymous sources, but it doesn't change the first part of my claim). </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-09 04:02:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm guessing Dr. Tempest Prow. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-09 03:57:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Well that's just not true. Men and women do have subtly different brains, but there's nothing to support the claim that men are smarter than women or vice versa[.](https://archive.is/BAcBF) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-09 03:52:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Welp, I'm dead now. That's incredible.

Edit: Archives just in case.

[Main](https://archive.is/WtciD)

[Image](https://archive.is/bnbwH)

What a moron. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-09 03:50:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Very close. Just one letter shy. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-09 03:47:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah. And then, crucially, he took it away and fired the guy. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-09 03:46:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's almost as if there was some (dare I say it?) conspiracy behind those emails and they weren't actually real. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-09 03:43:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> They're playing Counter Strike, not rugby. Even if you ignore the effects of hormone therapy, how would they have any advantage here anyway? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-09 03:37:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> But e-sports? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-09 03:30:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Good point. It's a three hour event if you're with *acquaintances*. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-09 03:25:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Might have just been her cooking, I don't remember exactly. 

[You can watch it to find out if you want.](https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=K7LQN1C3Ung)

Edit: Yeah they say the food is Deep South. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-09 03:24:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The American auto industry has twice nearly been killed by rising fuel prices. The first time they made it through "innovating" (copying the Europeans and Japanese) but the second time it decimated the industry. And it's going to happen all over again. Fuel is cheap now so they've fallen back into the old habits of just building massive cars with massive engines and they're going to feel the pain once that bubble inevitably bursts. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-09 03:21:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Certainly reminds the economists that "assuming rational consumers" is not all that realistic. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-09 02:21:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> God you can really see him working to save it. Obviously he can't but it's such a noble effort. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-09 02:20:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The others have no shame but Q is amazingly shy for a guy that does this kind of show. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-09 01:56:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Well he's a voice actor so... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-09 01:49:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I just realized this means that getting internet through your phone isn't a new thing. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-09 01:43:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> We've come a long way since then. Can you imagine trying to explain Snapchat to these people back then? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-09 01:41:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It isn't always, but some leagues are gender specific. Especially since gaming is such a male-dominated thing there are a couple of leagues for women. 

You see the same thing in a lot of fields that have been historically male-dominated for no real reason. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-09 01:39:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Oh that music. It's so 80s. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-09 01:36:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Man, I was definitely the Shy Beginner before I knew how to play guitar. And I still am, because I can't play guitar for shit. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-09 01:28:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> They probably know. I think you're basically required to have a dash cam there; which is why so many dash cam videos are Russian. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-09 01:19:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Except self identity isn't something one changes on a whim. It's deeply ingrained within us. The reason they didn't have ID is because it's a rather drawn-out process in many places to change all your ID, and for many it just isn't worth it because it's so rarely necessary.

And had they self-identified as tacos, they would not have been allowed because tacos were not allowed to compete. [x](https://archive.fo/5qgkV) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-09 01:14:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Intent matters in our legal system. You could say that Texas' gerrymandering equally affects all people of all races from their state, but it was done with the intent of disenfranchising certain races. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-09 01:11:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Unfortunately, yes.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-09 01:09:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Oh it's not really the Germans' fault. The rules simply didn't consider that trans people don't always have ID that reflects them and now they will. I doubt it was malicious at all. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-09 01:05:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Actually I checked, and the ESL rules don't say anything about having a vagina. This was just an unfortunate case of Germans following rules to ze letter, but ze rules vill be altered to be more inclusive and lenient. [x](https://archive.fo/d9zT7) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-09 01:01:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This is going over predictably in /r/news.
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-09 00:59:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> No, they were definitely told every time they bring the first part up that a later immigration act overrides it, but weirdly they never seemed to come back after that was pointed out. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-09 00:57:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Not as of yet. 4th circuit has heard arguments but they haven't issued a ruling yet. But it's the government appealing so they're on the back foot going into this. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> ACLU Comment on Federal Appeals Court Hearing in Muslim Ban Case </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-09 00:51:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-09 00:49:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> For those not in the know, a few transgender competitors were rejected from a competition for women gamers because they had not formally changed their passports to reflect their gender.

I don't think that the rules were set up to be exclusive; this was just an unfortunate snafu, but it is rather encouraging that the league is taking steps to make sure it doesn't happen again. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-09 00:43:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  *liberal* amount

TRIGGERED </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-09 00:40:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Just did this weekend. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-09 00:39:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Wow, that's a very familiar argument. It's like his supporters have ignored  no person shall receive preference or be discriminated against in issuance of a visa because of race, nationality, or place of birth as well. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-08 23:54:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> He already did. He says this is Obama's fault despite the fact that Obama fired the guy.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-08 23:42:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Dinner is a three hour event if you're with friends. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-08 23:41:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You can also cook macaroni but it's harder to clean. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-08 23:39:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Nah Pratt got swole out of nowhere for GotG and Jurassic World. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-08 23:37:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That's not what that sub is for. The comment is equally dirty with or without context. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-08 23:35:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I've never met someone with truck nuts that was able to eloquently argue an opinion. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-08 23:23:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [Relevant](https://youtu.be/w-d-b68p_sQ?t=45s) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-08 23:20:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Which it seems impossible to unsubscribe from. Seriously, I've lost count of how many times I've tried to get Linkedin to stop sending me shit. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-08 22:57:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Philly? Huh, they said Southern on the Kitchen Nightmares episode. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-08 22:46:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Deep South but living in the UK for ages. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-08 22:44:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Something about this seems so Ricky Gervais to me. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-08 22:41:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I don't know how I feel about this. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-08 22:26:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Well that's objectively not true. I could argue all day, but you'd pull four or five pictures out and claim that your anecdotes beat actual statistics. Adieu. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-08 22:24:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The fact that you still have to hold onto one of the least impressive electoral wins (and massive popular vote loss) instead of any actual policy positions or victories sort of proves the point. You only care about winning and upsetting other people, and actually getting anything useful done is unimportant.

Also: https://i.imgur.com/BjYWn8p.jpg </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-08 22:16:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Those on our side don't try to silence opposing views

Are you not seeing how much of this thread was removed? You can get banned from T_D for any sort of criticism, even if you're a supporter. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-08 22:07:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Wow that's bad. How'd you manage that one? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-08 22:06:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Gee, only about six months after people archived the shit out of it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-08 21:41:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [I would spend enough points to make my dick just large enough to cause discomfort to the woman. And spend the rest of the points in stamina so I could make the sex last as long as possible. Hopefully long enough that she cries. Then I would finish on her face.](https://archive.fo/r8DlL)

 \- HavelSucks

I think it's safe to say this person has some serious problems with sexuality. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-08 21:35:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I can appreciate that this guy is upset that his work has been coopted by assholes online, but that's not going to work. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-08 21:30:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Genes, genitals (internal and external), and then some secondary characteristics that you normally don't see until puberty like hormones, body hair, breasts, body fat... And as we now know, there's some minor differences in brain structure between men and women as well. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-08 21:06:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I have to say, I'm still way more of a fan of the shotgun gauntlets.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-08 21:03:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Sure, but chromosomes aren't the be-all end-all determination of sex like people think. They're only one of many, and in fact are the one least often checked. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-08 20:54:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Technically gender is just what you feel.

Sex has a couple of indicators, including chromosomes, genitals, and a bunch of secondary sexual characteristics all used to make the determination, but those don't always point to the same thing. Usually genitals are how we make the determination because those are clearly obvious from birth unlike everything else. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-08 20:48:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Remember how they were all "we stand with France, our oldest ally, our friend..." right up until the second the results came in. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-08 20:45:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Because it's political. This happens every time a John Oliver video gets posted to videos; people really like it so it hits the top but it's political so it gets removed, and people get all up in arms. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-08 20:35:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> SN95. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-08 20:34:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> No Camaro?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-08 20:16:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'd say those are fighting words, but I respect that you have your opinion, even if it's not the same as mine. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-08 20:11:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm in accounting. I feel like I'm dying inside. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-08 20:04:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [xkcd](https://xkcd.com/767/) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-08 20:04:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You realize that Coombs was an understudy on Mr. Rogers' show, right? They worked together. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-08 19:57:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You take all your clothes off when you think of what to do for Mother's Day? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-08 19:56:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Well that bot pretty much confirms this. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-08 19:55:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> And /r/news.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-08 19:49:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> "I support strong Net Neutrality rules backed by Title II classification."

^ ^ ^ Probably some good magic words. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-08 19:44:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That's honestly probably a bigger part of it than anything else. Obama told him Flynn was a bad idea, so he went with Flynn. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-08 19:42:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> https://www.fcc.gov/ecfs/search/proceedings?q=name:((17-108))

Try that link. Yours seems to have some extra stuff. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-08 19:38:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> John McCain, shortly thereafter: I am very disappointed that I and my entire party voted in favor of removing human rights. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-08 19:00:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The people who think "We must secure the existence of our people and a future for white children" has no baggage attached. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-08 18:28:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It was just that first line before. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-08 18:27:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Oh, there are definitely immigrants with French citizenship, but I was taking "refugees" to mean "Syrian refugees", which is a far more recent thing. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-08 17:41:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Vous avez le gagn. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-08 17:33:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So the mods were kicked...

Out of the loop. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-08 17:24:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Unlikely. You have to be a citizen to vote and I doubt that many, if any, refugees have that yet. It's a long process under good conditions. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-08 17:09:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'd really hope they go with six for safety-critical stuff like brakes. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-08 07:03:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That is likely part of it. Sort of how autism hasn't actually had some massive jump; we're just better at diagnosing it now. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-08 06:54:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah. It's basically SWATting at a lower level, because you know they're going to play it safe and check first before they do a proper investigation. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-08 06:52:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Oh I jaywalk like an absolute gangster. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-08 06:48:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I can't even feel bad for these people anymore. I feel bad for the kids, I feel bad for the husband here, but the wife and friends? How many damn times do we learn that Republicans seem to not care about the pain they cause until it hits them directly? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-08 06:42:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah, but Obama mentioned Macron so it's clearly Obama abusing his position (of former president?) and we can't let anything Trump says ever be used against him. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-08 06:40:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hey let's just block about 80 and not even pretend it's for anything other than partisan reasons because apparently that has no consequences. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-08 06:36:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Plus it doesn't say that money actually has to be used for pre-existing conditions. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-08 06:34:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The Brits actually broke Lorenz. Enigma had already been broken by Polish intelligence, but when they were overrun they passed the job on to the English. Turing was in charge of designing the machines that would automate the process, and it was Tommy Flowers that built the first electronic computer to crack the Lorenz cypher, which was only possible after years of listening in and waiting for someone in German command to resend a message without changing the key. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-08 06:27:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The bee thing is still a problem. Just because Doctor Who forgot about that plotline doesn't mean we can. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-08 06:23:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> aaaaaand POST! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-08 06:13:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The runoff was. And more people didn't vote than voted for her. Which wouldn't be news in the US but it's not all that common in France with the higher turnouts. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-08 05:12:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm kind of surprised nobody has sampled auctioneers in a more serious track before. You could definitely make it work. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-08 05:04:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Seamless. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-08 05:01:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Everyone except for old people and government agencies pretty much have, unless they have some bill that only accepts payment by check. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-08 04:59:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Surprisingly decent economy despite that. Really weird, nobody understands how that's happened. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-08 04:58:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah but it's different somehow. At least there's the facade of rational discourse in even the most biased subs, but T_D is a different animal entirely. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-08 04:10:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Wait so the gays are secretly waging war against the Jews? 

Is there a newsletter somewhere that keeps track of all this nonsense you're coming up with? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-08 03:03:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Her supporters sure as fuck did though. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-08 03:00:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> More people abstained from voting than voted for her. She came in third in a two person race. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-08 02:59:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's crazy how quickly they went from "we stand united with France no matter what because they're our oldest allies" to "the French are all cucks and they deserve the brutal death that's coming to them all". </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-08 00:24:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  If you got it

Well... Let's go with "mostly got it". </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-08 00:13:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's so sooooth. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-08 00:08:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> And he'd know about not being fit for presidency. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-07 23:48:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Probably someone else that doesn't like the kid reported him to the school. Given how quickly the school overturned this it seems like they didn't know the extent of the "problem" until they had a look and went "oh, that's stupid". </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-07 23:45:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> They overturned this immediately. Likely someone that doesn't like the kid said he was making threats and the school had to react to that just to be sure before they could take a proper look. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-07 23:01:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [me_irl](https://i.imgur.com/C5DEG1q.gifv) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-07 22:47:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Email has been around for 30 years. How there are people in a business environment that don't know the most basic functionality is just beyond me. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-07 22:29:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Not sure what you're on about; the wash from the main motor clearly kicks up some right at touchdown on the [Apollo 12 landing](https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=4U32lnvAWtc).  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-07 22:09:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I don't believe that Wikileaks has a neutral release policy. They could have evidence of Le Pen eating the brains of orphans, but I don't think they'd tell anyone. Just look at the way they behaved during the US election, dripping little bits just often enough to dominate the news cycle, attacking the Clintons rather than just releasing information. They have an agenda, and it's not transparency anymore. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-07 22:01:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Well, when you start with the premise of fixing a restaurant run by people who can't run a restaurant it's not surprising that there's a high failure rate. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-07 22:00:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Nah, that's fine. You can have a burger pretty much except for really rare; you're not going to ruin it by getting it well-done like a steak. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-07 21:58:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> She did not know a thing about food. That's pretty common with that show; a chef that knows what they're doing is handcuffed by an owner that tries to micromanage the menu. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-07 21:57:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  1. I am simply beyond humour 

 2. I am German

Well I wasn't going to say it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-07 21:54:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I was just making a joke about free travel. No reason to use nonparticipation links when you're free to participate anywhere in the union, right?

And then in my head I shot some finger guns and went "ayyyy". </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-07 21:51:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What if we link to subreddits within the EU?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-07 21:50:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Why would they have rescanned documents that they had supposedly sent to journalists weeks ago? Wouldn't the files have been created then, and not just before it was dumped on 4chan? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
