<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject2561</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-10 14:51:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Chase does sometimes invite people with less than $250k to join CPC with the expectation that you have that amount elsewhere and will bring it to Chase.

That being said, as a grad student I have nowhere close to that amount so I have never received such a banner </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-10 14:39:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> A pre-existing condition of the bill </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-10 14:39:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Key numbers on support for/against the bill:

 "There is a notable enthusiasm gap: 29 percent strongly oppose the bill, but only 13 percent strongly support it. Moreover, we saw the number of Republican voters who strongly support the bill drop from 36 percent last week to 27 percent this week." </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Poll: Support for GOP health bill declines </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-10 14:37:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-10 14:35:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Wanted to pass along a DP: Used the Delta companion certificate today and was able to pay with a non-Delta amex. However, I still have the Delta Plat card active. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-09 22:09:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Nope </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-09 20:59:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> No not those 3 million voters, but the millions of citizens who didn't cast a vote. The estimated voter turnout last November was [just over 55%](http://www.electproject.org/2016g). France's election this week had a low turnout for that country, but they still got 65%. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-09 20:51:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah he said he still supports the bill, but that both sides shouldn't use it for fear-mongering or all-or-nothing fight.

 He said lawmakers should try to have an intelligent debate on it and find out how we can cover people without undermining the health care system. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Rep. Peter King: Obamacare repeal not something to celebrate </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-09 20:47:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-09 20:45:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [Apparently it is possible](https://www.reddit.com/r/churning/comments/66255a/daily_discussion_thread_april_18_2017/dgfax7w/) to do something along those lines... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-09 20:24:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Amex Everyday if you don't have it already. Great to keep for long term MR point storage and the offers via referral have a $1k min spend </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-09 20:22:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I got charged the convenience fee when I used the concierge to buy tickets for Kendrick Lamar. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-09 19:15:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Unfortunately I think you're out of luck (I was in a similar situation with the BCE). Amex's language prevents you from getting a bonus if you've ever had the card before. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-09 18:50:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Try the [benefits site](https://www.usbankaltitude.com/#/login) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-09 18:48:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Absolutely, and with special elections too. I'm hoping with all the recent PR that there is a good turnout for the upcoming election in the Georgia 6th district. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-09 18:47:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Out of curiosity, which card did you receive this on? Our department actually does a lot of printing at FedEx (posters for conferences, mostly). </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-09 18:42:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  People have a tendency to blame politicians when things don't work, but as I always tell people, you get the politicians you deserve. If you don't vote and don't participate and don't pay attention, you get policies that don't reflect your interests </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Obama urges crowd to stay active in elections or 'you get the politicians you deserve' </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-09 18:42:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-09 18:11:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> There is definitely some posturing happening. Still, I think it's good to have it on the record that the entire party is willing to work with the Republicans </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-09 17:45:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's a referral from the SPG Business card.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-09 17:43:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> All 48 Dem Senators signed this letter to Sen. Mitch McConnell stating that they're willing to work together on improving healthcare if the GOP removes "repeal" as an option. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Senate Democrats to GOP: Yank repeal effort, and well talk health care </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-09 17:42:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-09 17:35:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If you have no specific redemption in mind at the moment, I'd recommend opening up an Amex Everyday card. It can store your MR points for a future redemption. Since it has no annual fee, it's a good card to maintain long term.

There is a 15K signup bonus [via referral](https://rankt.com/r/churning/referrals/amex_everyday/) or 25K if you can find it via incognito. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-09 04:26:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Depending on the dates you're flying, you can find round trips between those cities for 60K Delta Skymiles. The current offers on the Delta Plats are for 50K + $100 credit, so that could get you close.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-09 04:19:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That's the business card referral </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-09 04:18:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What's the prefix before americanexpress.com? If it's not www, change it to www and see if the link still works </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-09 00:54:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Agreed for this upcoming year that would make sense to get the green card. I'd still look into the Everyday at some point since it has no annual fee at all.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-09 00:49:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You can write up a short 1-2 page lease and send that. There are plenty of templates online you can use. At minimum it should include the address of the property, your and your "landlord's" name, and the amount you pay per month. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-09 00:46:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Oh! No unfortunately it doesn't correspond to geographical distance. I think the lowest domestic tier for shorthaul flights is 5000 each way, but for something cross country you're generally looking at 12,500 miles each way.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-09 00:45:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I recommend getting the Amex Everyday card. It has no annual fee and stores your MR points, so it's a good card to keep long term, giving you more flexibility when waiting for good offers. It also has a bonus of 15K MR via referral or 25K MR if you can find it via incognito.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-09 00:27:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If you have a Delta Amex, then there are two ways you can use Skymiles. 

1. As miles. You can find award travel on Delta's site and pay based on the tier of travel. This can be very valuable for Delta One flights. 

2. As a 1cpp "cash" redemption. With the Amex, you are allowed to exchange Skymiles in blocks of 5,000 for $50 off the cash price of a ticket. This is only useful when there is a low cash fare (often domestic economy). </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-09 00:24:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> 15K if you apply via referral, 25K if you can find it using incognito </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-08 21:36:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yep it's been happening the past few days. Just change it to www.americanexpress.com and keep the rest of the link, it should work. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Dems to administration: Stop sabotaging healthcare system </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-08 21:28:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-08 21:26:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I would put your landlord's phone number and email (if you have it). Plastiq will likely (according to several DPs) ask you for a copy of your lease to make sure that it is for rent and that you're not just writing a check to yourself. Make sure the amount that you're putting on the check matches the amount in your lease. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-08 21:22:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> They will usually prorate the fee for the remainder of your cardmember year. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-08 21:21:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's highly dependent on the university and what methods they allow for tuition payment. You might be able to use Gift of College for a student loan, pay directly with a credit card, or use Plastiq if your university accepts payments by check. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-08 21:20:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yep it should keep the same number, but the CID and expiration date may change. While you can safely keep recurring payments using the same number, I suspect it won't count towards minimum spend until you activate the new card upon receipt. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-08 16:15:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The loop was getting 3x only on rent/mortgage payments, not all Plastiq payments </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-08 15:57:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I know this doesn't show up in the search, but here's the link to this week's [What Card Should I Get?](https://www.reddit.com/r/churning/comments/68znju/what_card_should_i_get_weekly_thread_week_of_may/) thread </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Austrian court rules Facebook must delete 'hate postings' </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-08 15:32:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-08 14:56:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You could try using Plastiq to pay rent/mortgage </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-08 13:39:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Somebody made a post last night (which then got deleted) for a 125K offer for the CIP. I'm guessing this is either super targeted or was a mistake? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Euro hits 6-month high, Asian shares firm after French election </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-08 04:46:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-07 23:35:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yep! Got some sketchers </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-07 23:08:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Did this on Thursday for some shoes sold by Amazon, worked without a problem. 

Edit: think I had a different offer then. Still had to do with adding discover card as a 1 click option but didn't have the category restrictions, just had to be on products sold by Amazon.com

http://imgur.com/pHjWgHl </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-07 21:38:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Does the $50 include tax or subtotal only? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-07 20:06:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Libert galit fraternit!! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-06 23:30:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Oh huh, good to know. Sorry for the misinformation then, I was probably thinking of a gift card not a cert.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-06 23:10:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yes I believe so, it's treated kind of like a gift card.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-06 23:00:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If the new flight isn't too inconvenient, I'd go ahead and take the $300 instead of miles. While you can get  1cpp for flights with Delta, having cash is definitely much more flexible. The exception, as pointed out below, is if you have a definite award travel redemption in mind. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-06 22:58:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Taking a slightly different approach than what happened in the US prior to last year's election:

 Le Monde, the influential daily newspaper, posted a note explaining to readers that it had obtained the leaked documents but would not be publishing any of them before the vote, saying that they had been released with the clear goal of harming the validity of the ballot. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> As French Elections Nears, So Does a Step Into the Unknown </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-06 22:57:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-05 20:23:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yes that is doable. Make sure to have your landlord/management companys name on the check and be prepared to send a copy of your lease to Plastiq for verification </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-05 20:22:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yep so far that seems to be it, just be sure you have your lease available in case Plastiq wants to verify it. Good luck! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-05 20:20:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Nope you can only convert to the BCE </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-05 20:20:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> While I still have my Delta plat, I used another AmEx card when using the pass </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-05 17:07:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> 100 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-05 16:53:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Day 2. So far so good. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-04 21:58:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I changed mine to www and it so far hasn't gotten removed....will update y'all with what happens! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-04 21:43:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> No, contact Amex about it. It should post within 1-2 business days of meeting minimum spend. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-04 21:42:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> As others have said, if you've only had the gold card for a single year then cancelling it won't hurt your credit history too much. I would instead apply for the Delta Platinum outright. The current offer is 50K skymiles for $1k spend, which while not the highest ever (70K for $3k spend) is better than doing the upgrade. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-04 19:38:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Would it let you edit your existing link instead of deleting/adding a new one? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-04 18:02:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yep! Just make sure you get the right address for your loan provider </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-04 17:34:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Bummer :( Did your new link go to a valid offer? Mine actually goes to an "offer not available" page. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-04 17:10:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> PSA: The Amex BCE and BCP referral links all expired today, so be sure to regenerate them. Unfortunately, it looks like the new referral offer (for now at least) is just $100/$150 back after $1k spend with no bonus category.

edit: as u/DachengZ pointed out, the new referral links will begin with cardappdcq.americanexpress.com, which gets rejected by the ReferralBot. Instead, you can change that prefix to www.americanexpress.com and the link still works, and will be accepted by the bot. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-04 16:53:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> there is some great commentary in response to his tweet along these lines </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-04 16:52:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Here's the [tweet from Bernie](https://twitter.com/BernieSanders/status/860135002662686725) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Sanders: How can you call it 'reform' when millions will lose insurance? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-04 16:52:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-04 16:28:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> DP: I was only charged a $150 renewal fee for my Delta Plat (it should be $195) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-04 04:35:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yep no worries. Just make sure you put their name and loan number when you send the payment memo! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-04 04:28:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> United didn't get Best Customer Service?? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-03 22:46:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Always add compassion when you're flying LUV </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-03 19:54:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> https://accounts.chase.com/banking/prep.do?ID=10141717 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-03 19:50:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Here's a [guide to using Plastiq](https://www.reddit.com/r/churning/comments/66pvq9/a_guide_to_plastiq/) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-03 18:27:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Phrasing. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-03 17:49:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah, or they may not let you purchase them at all with a CC. 

You would have to go the CC -- Visa Gift Card -- MO route. I have never done this so I unfortunately won't be of help. Hopefully someone else will chime in.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-03 17:34:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> 1. Yes
2. I think so, but not 100% sure
3. Yes
4. Yes </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-03 17:23:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> He says that had he concealed that information from Congress it would have been even worse </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-03 17:19:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> 60K is the standard offer for the Platinum card, so it's nothing special. You also cannot change the Blue Cash into the Platinum. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-03 17:18:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> They're just quoting what he said </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-03 17:07:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Lots of people in this community do, they're listed at [rankt.com](https://rankt.com/r/churning/referrals/plastiq/). Best of luck! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> James Comey Says Keeping Quiet on Clinton Emails Would Have Been Catastrophic </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-03 17:04:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-03 17:01:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It might, but Plastiq will warn you if there's a chance of that. If you don't get warned it goes through as a purchase </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-03 16:50:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If they take checks, you can [use Plastiq](https://www.reddit.com/r/churning/comments/66pvq9/a_guide_to_plastiq/) to use your credit card to send a check to them (with a fee). </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-03 16:49:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Not if you train it properly </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-03 16:46:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Saw a generic (i.e. not targeted) code in Paypal for $50 off $300 at hotels.com if you pay with Paypal. Code is **50PAYPAL** </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-03 04:13:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> No, but you can buy Sam's club gift cards then use them at Walmart  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-02 23:22:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If you pay rent or mortgage, [look into Plastiq](https://www.reddit.com/r/churning/comments/66pvq9/a_guide_to_plastiq/) for paying those with the CSP. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-02 23:19:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> r/theydidthemath </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-02 23:16:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Also worth to check if it's on any of your Everyday cards, since then you could get 3.4x (ED) or 5.5x (EDP) MR </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-02 22:35:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> 1. There are no cards you can change to without an annual fee. The cheapest is $95 for the Green card.
2. You need to have one MR earning card open at all times to store your points. If you don't have one, I'd recommend looking into the Amex Everyday card. It is a credit card (not a charge card) but also earns MR points without an annual fee. If you open it first, then your points from your Platinum will be preserved. If you go to Rank.com, there is an offer for 15K points after $1k spend for the Everyday. 
3. There are some data point son Flyer Talk of being able to purchase small airline gift cards with the travel credit. I would recommend looking there.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-02 22:01:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Both offer 10% back on restaurants up to $2000 in spend (so $200 back) within three months of opening.  This part of the offer expires tomorrow and there will probably a new offer on Thursday (it was previously 10% back on Amazon)

The best you can get via incognito is an additional $250 back after $1k spend. Via referrals it is $100 for the BCE and $150 for the BCP. Again this is on top of the restaurant bonus.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-02 20:32:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yah </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-02 19:44:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's possible, you will have to call and ask for expedited shipping.

If you're going to use it to make an online purchase, they *might* give you a temporary number upon approval. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-02 19:36:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Only if they're on the same itinerary as you </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-02 18:22:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> They want to overtake Wikipedia </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-02 18:00:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Bazinga! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-02 17:59:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Only 2nd place :P </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-02 17:51:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I have another of the Chase $300/$200 banking codes, just let me know if you want it.

edit: Expires June 15th

edit 2: and it's gone! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-02 17:48:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> In fact there is! Check out [this FAQ on Plastiq](https://www.reddit.com/r/churning/comments/66pvq9/a_guide_to_plastiq/)! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> 20,000 Chinese writers will create their own Wikipedia competitor </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-02 17:46:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-02 17:38:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You can call customer service and ask them to add it to your account over the phone. They will require verification that you're the owner by asking you the CID from another card on your account.

In terms of shipping, it will usually take about a week. I got mine after 4 business days with no shipping notifications. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-02 17:26:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So if I have an upcoming flight with them at the end of this month... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-02 15:51:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Not as far as I can tell </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Dem to Trump: Our country needs a White House shutdown </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-02 15:42:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-02 15:39:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'd recommend getting the Experian app, which gives you a copy of your report for free (the score is extra). Since many of the big banks pull Experian, it's a great way to keep track of your report. You won't get your score through that, but you can get your FICO score from Experian once a month through Amex or Discover. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-02 15:35:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yep do the in branch application first and then go home and do the online app on the same day. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-02 04:20:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Ah, I see the tower of Barad Ur in the distance </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-02 04:16:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I have the app on my phone and it notified me within minutes of an Amex pull! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-02 03:29:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If you combine the Chase Sapphire Reserve (which gives you 1.5cpp) with the Freedom Unlimited, which earns 1.5 UR per dollar, you could essentially get 2.25% back for travel. That being said, the CFU is a personal card and you'd have to make sure you have a high enough credit limit for your expenses. 

You can also look into the Ink Preferred , which has bonus spending for some business categories </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-01 23:32:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Nevertheless, they profited :( </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Warren: Trump admin is rich guys making each other richer </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-01 23:28:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-01 21:08:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The last time there were historic high offers was back in January with 50K for the Gold and 70K for the Plat. Currently the best is 40K for gold and 50K for plat via referral, though there is a DP below in this thread of someone seeing a 50K gold via incognito </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-01 21:06:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> No need to wait until the statement closes, the miles will post to your Delta account within a couple business days of meeting the spend. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-01 20:22:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I had that earlier in the day but it went through fine when I tried again this afternoon </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-01 19:06:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Cheers! A little bit of self care can go a long way :D

Thanks for the transparency, I appreciate it as a grad student doing data science. In a similar vein to u/1autumn1, I got 2 referrals last month for cards + 2 for Plastiq! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-01 18:42:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You typically have 30 days from when the AF posted, if you're still within that range you should be okay! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-01 18:09:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> r/mildlystimulating, the coffee, that is </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-01 17:41:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I wouldn't recommend it, it could sour your relationship with Amex. The offer itself might be worth it if you've previously had the Plat card and want the second bonus </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-01 17:30:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Got an email for a code for $50 off $350 at hotels.com if anyone wants it

edit: gone! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
