<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject6654</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Our Sasquatch experience in Washington State. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-09 18:49:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> 
Background- We're at an AirBnB in Washington State, not far from Mt Rainier National Park.


Our AirBnB host was outside on her horse pasture feeding her horse. We all went outside to greet her and thank her for accommodating us. She lived across the street, so she offered to show us her other property- with more horses and a few other farm animals. We pass her house and are now in her backyard. Our host, let's call her Michelle, gets us in a circle and whispers, "so, do you guys want to go back home with a story?". Intrigued, we say yes. And we had no idea what we were in for.


She takes us past one of her two barns and we walk into her wooded backyard along a foot trail that she takes her horses on daily. About 100 feet in, she stops us. "Look down", she says. We see what appears to be a foot print, yet wider and longer than that of a humans. It was especially long, so whoever left the print must have slipped in the mud- there were toe imprints as well.


She then begins to tell us that this imprint was made by none other than a Sasquatch.  While huddled around the imprint, she tells us how she got her house and then her second property across the street (our AirBnB). "You might think I'm crazy. But if I knew about their existence, I would have never had moved here. Do you want to see more?"


Of course we (a group of four 20-something year olds) do, so Michelle takes us further down the path. At this point, I was feeling a bit uncertain about what was coming or about to happen. Hair stood up on my arms and I got the chills. I kid you not- seconds later, Michelle says to us "Right about this point here is where you might feel some chills or your hair sticking up. She was spot on here, and I was feeling very uneasy about going forward. Yet, we walk a little bit further down the path.


"They had asked me to bring you guys here, they wanted to say hello.", Michelle told us. "I've never brought any of my guests back here before but it seemed important to show this to you guys."

We had no idea if we were going to see anything, as it was getting darker and darker out. We stop for some more conversation, when Michelle stopped us from talking. "Shh." We didn't hear anything. We're all still quiet, when Michelle asks us something peculiar- "Has any of you recently lost a brother? "Or have any of you ever experienced psychic abilities?" We all say no, it felt a little awkward and we moved on.


We go to the last point in our walk and she was astonished- she had laid some sticks down earlier in the day, and the arrangement of sticks had changed. "They're always mischievous and like to move things around to mess with us", Michelle explained. She also was saying how she left a deceased chicken right at that spot and it was gone- the Sasquatch people must have taken them. She said she often leaves them gifts (usually food) here, and they're gone before she knows it.


At this point, I'm feeling skeptical about all of this. I'm not a believer, but I also didn't have any reason *not* to believe any of this.


We were all quiet. Out of nowhere, we hear a noise far back into the woods. It sounded like an owl's hoot, but very, very far away. Michelle said, "Oh that's just an owl", but then she took it back when we heard the next noise. I can't recreate the noise in person, nor can I recreate it in my head, but I'll do my best do describe it. It sounded like a Monkey's "ooh ooh aah aah" mixed with the laugh of a hyena. Michelle assured us they meant no harm, and that was definitely them talking to us. She yells back in English to greet them, because they can understand our language as well.


We head back to the AirBnB and talk about nothing other than our experience for no less than 2 hours (while drinking, of course). I'm with my best friends and one of them makes it their mission to go back into the woods to search for the Squatch himself. The other one tags along, but I stay back because I didn't really want much to do with it. They leave, and I go grab a joint to smoke out on the deck. It was silent- nothing but me, the cabin, and the beautiful Washington State wilderness.


Then I heard it again. The same owl hoot in the distance, followed by the eerie sounding monkey noises. I was alone and stayed up another hour until my friends returned, and told them I had heard it again. Yet strangely, they didn't.


Before I went to bed, I googled something along the lines of "Washington state creepy laugh animal" and the first result was an article titled, "Bigfoot or animals? Hair raising sounds coming from a swamp on Indian reservation in Oregon". </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-09 18:26:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Sounds exactly like the scream Gus Fring makes before his face gets blown off

edit:  [this](https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=R6CjCEyAJ2s) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-08 21:45:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Might have to look into this.  Thanks! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-08 21:23:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Someone should give this guy gold.  Not me, but someone should. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Transparent dip for clear bra? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-08 19:13:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hi- I'm looking into options for keeping my front bumper safe from rock chips and always thought about a 3M Clear Bra, but what about a transparent plasti-dip job?  Is there a clear plasti-dip available to get the job done nicely, and is this a route you would take?  Or would you just bite the bullet and pay up to $500 for a real clear bra? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-08 14:28:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> old 86 / new 86 wheels? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-03 17:33:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Is that the 706?  We might detour and take that a bit east than back west and back onto the 7. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-03 15:26:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Using Turo this weekend in Seattle!  Lol.  Is it the actual car they use in the show??  Or is it a replica?

If anything it's to promote the show, you can see it's even owned by "Erlich". </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-03 15:07:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> /u/rifleNA </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-03 15:05:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> happy cake day! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-03 15:05:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If our vehicles are so "stupid" then why are you here?  Seems like you're very interested in "stupid vehicles" if you're putting this much negative effort in a post to bash a community essentially.
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-03 13:48:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Can you confirm if 7 is open?  :) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-02 23:37:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Negative.  New Jersey. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> This Turo rental. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-02 19:31:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-02 19:15:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> thank you! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-02 18:49:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Dang that's upsetting.  Is the 706 to Longmire open?  Might drive that out of the way east (and then go back west to the 7) just to see some more views  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-02 18:02:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [This is the route I was hoping to take.](http://imgur.com/XlLfKf0)

Yay/Nay? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-02 17:55:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Transmissions are pretty solid.  In a way they're sorta meant to take a beating (regular use over a long period of time).  The first thing to do is to *not* think you're gonna ruin the tranny/clutch, because with that mindset you'll never learn the correct way to use it.  

As for going from 1st to 2nd...  just let off the clutch slowly and it shouldn't be jerky. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-02 17:43:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's just practice and getting the blips right.  Muscle memory honestly...  I was in the same spot last year when I got my car.  

Watch videos on rev-match downshifting.
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Driving from Seattle to Mt Rainier! Roads? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-02 17:42:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hi All!  I'm visiting your beautiful state this week and will be renting a lodge in Randle, and am driving from Seattle.  I was hoping to take the 410 to 123 to 12 to get to Randle and drive right through the mountain pass to see some awesome sites, but Google Maps is saying that 410/ Mather Memorial Parkway is closed in the winter.  


My question is if the road is open yet at this time of year?  Not sure where WA draws the line between seasons as your winters are probably a bit more intense than mine on the east coast.


If the 410 is still closed, what are some other driving roads to check out with some great views?


Thanks in advance! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-02 16:46:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> East coast, North Jersey.  Hoping to move to/work in a city sometime soon (Looking at Philly and D.C.).  I don't have a background in sales and I'm not really looking to get into that either. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-02 15:55:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Annnnnnnnnnnd this is what understeer is. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-02 15:31:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Are you rev matching when you downshift?  that'll explain why it's jerky if you're just downshifting and releasing the clutch too abruptly. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-02 15:26:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I sometimes cam with my iPhone, but from my experience it's best just to not cheap out and get a real dash cam.  Decent ones go for just $50.

The problem I have using my cell phone as a dash cam is that the lens isn't fish eye or wide.  So you only get a recording of what is right in front of you, not what's on your right or left. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Different career paths? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-02 14:35:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hi all, 


I've been working in Desktop Support for 3 years now and I always thought my career path would go something like Desktop Support - Server admin - Network admin (then possibly management, idk) , but lately I'm not too sure about it.  

My main problem really is dealing with the users.  At first I thought it wasn't too bad but lately it's just the same problems over and over again and I feel like I want to steer my career away from being end-user support as it is honestly taking a toll on my life.

What other options do I have?  I know IT is a very broad career path so there are a lot of options.  For reference, I'm not a programmer, I'm not a DB designer/developer, and I'm not a systems analyst.  I have a BS in Computer Science and Information Systems (with a concentration on the latter).  I have a CompTIA Security+ Cert, but being I'm only 22, I have very limited experience in that field other than the certification.  

Security might be the way I want to go in the future, being that there is such a large need for it.  But what other "roads" can I go down with IT?
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-01 23:17:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> exactly what?  Even with headers and a tune you mighttttt be pushing 200 wheel.  How do you plan to hit higher numbers without FI? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-01 22:05:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> How are you gonna get to 215whp *without* FI?  Stock...  we're pushing like 150-160hp to the wheels. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-01 19:40:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Confusing title cause cammer crosses over solid white line as well </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-01 18:26:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Nope.... probably because I park near a genesis coupe and G37 every day lol </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-01 17:03:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> lol no it doesn't </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-01 05:46:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hey, he lasted 11 days </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-29 22:26:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> STi lip from subaru, yeah.  Comes stock on series blue brz </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-28 22:31:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah I couldn't get that into the kids brain no matter what I said and I didn't care enough to continue arguing with him lmao </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-28 22:28:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> thank you </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-28 22:28:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> coulda shoulda woulda \\_()_/ </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Triggered by an 8 year old... </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-28 22:17:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So I'm pulling into DD today to get coffee, and there's a group of kids outside.  Park my car and get out, to the immediate "HEY HOW FAST DOES YOUR CAR DO 0-60 IN?" and his friend replies with "NOT FAST ENOUGH" before I can come up with a witty comeback to his question...  yeah I died a little on the inside today.


that's all folks </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-28 21:08:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> probably cause you can't chirp the tires anymore haha </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-28 21:07:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I did PSS on stock power and stock wheels (but went up to 225) and OH MY GOD do they make a world of a difference.  The driving experience doubled for me because the car has much more confidence at higher speeds. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-28 21:06:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Driver mod. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-28 21:05:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> RIP clear coat </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-28 21:02:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [get on my level](https://imgur.com/a/HPwA0) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-28 16:26:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's also on the "Top" page of all time on this sub already lol </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-27 20:22:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> eh...  no thanks </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-27 17:37:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Not a question, but I genuinely hope the hardest days are behind you and that you're looking forward to the future.  One of my best friends was diagnosed with grade 3 Anaplastic Astrocytoma December 2015, and after chemo/radiation therapy (and 5 brain surgeries later), the tumor still grew.  It is now grade 4 and they're calling in for hospice services because no treatment is working and he is only getting weaker.

It's a terrible thing that the family and all friends have to go through.  I'm so very sorry that you have to go through this and I'm praying for you and your loved ones.  You got this! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-27 15:33:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I like turtles. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-26 22:11:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [Not Germany but](https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=WEvsqspmnW4) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What kind of elephant is this? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-26 22:02:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-26 20:50:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> lmao same
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-26 20:48:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Happens to the best of us. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-26 02:26:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Haha they came with the house and we've been living here for 15 years now.  Def time to replace the wood, some are falling apart after all that weathering.  Also there are holes dug out in the wood from burrowing chipmunks lol. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-25 14:39:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I thought this was the hood of a WRX with a hood scoop, then I realized you put the cam on the roof lolz </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Sometimes I just can't help but stare out the kitchen window </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-25 14:28:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The only (other) American Idol I have ever remembered. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-25 13:24:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> New company offering job, old company offering raise. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-25 13:10:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-24 17:52:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hmm.  Maybe I'll take the trip to south jersey and take a look haha </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-24 17:36:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Emissions yes, smog no. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-24 17:34:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I feel like black wheels really fit WRB the best.  But that's probably because series.blue came with stock STi wheels lol. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-24 15:12:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I don't see what's wrong here, it looks like it is working fine? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-24 15:11:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> ...why is it parked 1/4 out of the driveway?  the sunshade just makes it seem that it's really going to be parked there like that lol </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-24 15:09:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Good on you.  Best blue too! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-24 15:07:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> maybe ask u/spicyricecake? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-24 13:42:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> honest question, if it landed in a crater, how was it able to drive itself out of there? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-22 22:43:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> As someone who works in IT:  Have you tried turning it off and on again?

But really, maybe disconnect/reconnect the battery and try again </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-22 18:52:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> /u/spicyricecake did the opposite conversion (brz-frs bumper) so it's probably doable? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-22 18:48:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> For some reason I thought you meant $80k and I was very confused for a sec. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The rain brought the dirt from my wheel spokes to my tires </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-22 15:25:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-22 15:12:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Why use an orbital polisher on such a new car? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-22 15:10:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [This one is backwards too](https://youtu.be/01TL9bUWr6I). Super cool, tons of planning  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Why do people in California complain about lack of water when they have the entire Pacific Ocean right there? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-21 22:11:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-21 19:39:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Correct </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-21 19:32:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I never understood this ad.  "Buy this car, your wife will hate you!  But you'll have this nice car." </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-20 23:44:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> didn't even share either. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Duck tries to leave pool but doggo scares it back into the water. Supervisor doggo on the deck oversees employee evaluations. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-20 20:04:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-19 20:23:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> yes </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-19 20:00:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> No, full signal.  I think this might just be a bug in 10.3.1? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-19 19:51:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Interesting, but it was like this for hours (like 4+) yesterday and everything in my mail app seems fine.  

Seemed to stop syncing when I did a hard reset. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-19 19:37:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> click 'formatting help' when typing a comment </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-19 19:36:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Snapchat 17%, GroupMe 15%, Home   Lock Screen 8%, Google Maps 7%, Mail 6%...  None of these services should be syncing like that though? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What is my phone syncing here? I'm not on my home wifi so it's not syncing with iTunes and I don't use iCloud backup. It is syncing like this whether on WiFi or LTE and is draining battery. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-19 18:55:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-19 18:19:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> sorry- red that just turned green </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-19 18:07:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Joisey here as well, can confirm.

One time someone honked at me at a ~~red~~ red light that just turned green, scared me and I stalled. Got out of my car, went to their door, said something along the lines of "Your honk made me stall and now we all have to wait". Prob not the safest thing for me to do but she was pissssssssed.
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-19 16:34:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Well don't go calling moms stupid for not understanding a term intended for younger generations...  don't forget, your mother once taught you how to use a spoon. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-19 15:41:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [neat](http://i2.kym-cdn.com/photos/images/facebook/000/714/256/eb4.jpg) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-19 14:43:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Sounds like my mom when the word "selfie" came about.  She just thought it meant to take a picture.  She would say things like, "take a selfie of the dogs!"  "Take a selfie of the sunset!" </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-19 04:07:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> We got 2 feet of snow here last month lol.  It gets cold, maybe down to 10f at times?  But still, I've never seen that happen before </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-19 03:58:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Ha.  I live in NJ, nothing special here. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-18 18:44:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> the exhaust gets INTO the cabin? um.. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-18 18:35:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Can someone please explain all the smoke coming from the car?  If he's hotboxing that thing he must be FRIED. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> "Cable management" at my new workplace. For unrelated reasons, I'm on the job hunt again. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-18 17:52:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Elephant thinks man is drowning, so he sets out to rescue him (x-post from r/gifs) </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-18 16:34:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-18 15:31:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Not focus...  Just looks like motion blur.  Try to keep it steadier next time! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-18 15:27:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's MY 86.  Not YOURS. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-18 15:25:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  come check out r/ft86!  r/subaru doesn't like showing us any love :/ </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-14 22:59:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Rule #2: Be welcoming and helpful.

Obviously you didn't read the rules yourself lol </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-14 22:58:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thanks!  how long is the train ride would you recon?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-14 22:57:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Rule #2: Be welcoming and helpful.

Obviously you didn't read the rules yourself lol
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-14 22:50:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thanks so much!  How long does it take from the airport to Union Station? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-14 22:48:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Haha we're from NJ.  He's coming from California, I'm meeting him in Denver and we're driving back to NJ. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-14 22:47:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Well yes but I would rather get educated responses from individuals not like yourself.  Just trying to get advice from a human, not a computer.  You don't have to be a dick about it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-14 20:56:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> No temp agency involved.  Temping directly for the company. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-14 20:14:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Generally speaking.  I work OT to keep myself safe, but regardless they'e hours I'm missing out on. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-14 20:06:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Lol I actually do all of the above.  Take short lunches and rack up 2-3 hours OT weekly.  But OT only counts if you are in the building physically working.  Otherwise, they're just additional hours (not time and a half) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-14 19:55:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Desktop support... Can't really work from home unfortunately  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Not a full-time employee, don't get any PTO, office closes early? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-14 19:45:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hoping someone can point me in the right direction here because this is the fourth time this sort of thing has happened to me.

I'm a temp IT employee at the company I work for.  I work 40+ hour weeks, but do not have any benefits/PTO because I'm still a temp.  This Winter was kind of rough on me, because we had 3 snow days and because I'm not "full-time", I don't get paid when I don't work.  

Now, the company is closing this week early (3:00pm let out instead of 5pm this Friday), which is nice because you can spend time with the family etc, but I'm not getting paid for it.  I know we're just talking about a couple of hours here, but this is messing up my already pretty tight budget.  How can I ask for this time back/ask to be paid for this time?  It's not like I deliberately took time off for this, if you get what I mean.  The company is shortening its hours and I feel that it's not fair to hourly employees like myself.

The company is pretty notorious for stringing temps along in hopes that full-time will be offered, but because they never offer it, the turnover rate is ridiculously high (and I'm looking elsewhere for a backup job as well).  

But not getting paid for these hours are pretty annoying, is there anything I can do about it? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-14 19:01:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> now kith </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-14 17:37:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [My Pride and Joy](https://steemitimages.com/0x0/http://i.imgur.com/ui3BS.png) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-13 21:02:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Look into Dr ColorChip.  I have his stuff for my car, it works like magic...  even on WRB. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-12 18:56:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> ayy silicon valley </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-12 18:29:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> all in good fun!  also your color flair isn't WRB (: </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-12 16:53:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [reminds me of my post from last year](https://www.reddit.com/r/ft86/comments/4pnc97/a_turtle_in_its_natural_habitat/?st=j1f3igug sh=23cb1d08)
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-12 16:52:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Congrats!  This is probably me just shit inspecting, but is that front fender bent inwards? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-12 16:16:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I might have defied the laws of physics... because right foot usage is very modest </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-12 14:58:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> "Slowly" because I was looking at average mpg.  The car had the old mpg and was calculating the new average ontop of that...  That'll take a while to raise it back up unless I just cold hard reset the mpg gauge.

I've been testing them out for weeks but this is the only thing that brought me back to the "economy" status of my car.
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-12 14:47:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Usually higher tire pressure means better gas mileage, but my case was the opposite. Make sure your tires are at the right spec!
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-12 14:14:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Positive.  That's the first thing I thought too...  So I drove the last week very modestly (shifting around 3-4krpm) to test it out and I was still getting very low numbers.  The width did change, I went from 215s to 225s and kept my wheels the same.

I'm not going out and telling y'all to lower your tire pressures, but just make sure they're in the appropriate range! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> PSA: Check your tire pressure when you get new tires. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-12 14:05:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I recently got a set of high performance summer tires for my car.  After driving with them for a few weeks, I noticed my average mpg went from about 29 all the way down to 20.  It's important to note that different tires will be more efficient than others, but this isn't what I'm talking about here.


8mpg was too much for me to be losing in an economy car like mine, so I dug a little deeper.  I noticed that OEM tire pressure should be 32, and the tire shop inflated mine to 44psi (44psi is SUV/truck territory, cars should be around 30-35 psi).


I deflated my tires by 12 psi to OEM spec of 32 and my mileage has slowly been coming back.

Usually higher tire pressure means better gas mileage, but my case was the opposite.  Make sure your tires are at the right spec!

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-11 23:49:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Interesting.  So I checked the pressure and all around they put in 44psi.  Dropped that down to 32 on all four and I guess we'll see what happens.  Thanks bruh! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Why didn't Pontiac ever make a Grand PM? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-11 21:21:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-11 18:20:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> September 4th 2017?  That didn't happen yet....

.

.

.

....oh right </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-11 16:55:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Where I'm at now- their HR recruiter reached right out to me (which is very much so preferred).  When I say "Middle Man", I'm talking about a company such as Robert Half. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-11 14:15:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> username checks out </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-11 14:13:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So.. it should be set to 32 then we should be good to go?
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-11 13:55:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Damn, I'm right aroung paramus and am looking for work in the area.  What was the company name just so I can avoid it? I've been dealing with Robert Half too. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-11 04:33:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> lol he's buying an '86 e30...  "dude e30s don't break down and this one is in immaculate condition"...  we'll see </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-11 04:32:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Someone had to finally do it... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-11 02:13:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Def gonna check the pressure.  I think the tire shop left them a bit low.  What is OEM tire pressure/what should my tires be at? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-11 02:11:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The first kid? Nah I see it too </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-10 22:18:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  \_()_/ </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-10 22:18:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Same 225/45/17s but on a 7" wheel...  I should be getting better numbers than you! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-10 21:49:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> hahaha...  I'm actually in NJ </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> These school trends are getting out of hand </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-10 21:48:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-10 21:46:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Interesting conversation we're having here today on the ft86 sub </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Why I hate applying to ANY IT job (rant) </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-10 20:10:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> First of all let me get out of the way that yes, finding a job initially is always difficult. My experience in IT recruiting has always been poor.


What ever happened to just working for a company? Literally every place I'm applying to now is actually me just applying to a consultant company acting as the middle man between me and the company I want to work for. Although this method is beneficial for the consulting company and the hiring company, I cannot express how many headaches it has given me. Maybe there were 3 out of the 50 I applied to yesterday that it was the actual company representing themselves.


The process: You apply. They call you from a 1800 number (or better yet- an "Unknown" number) with no way of you getting back to them. They tell you about the job description but they CAN'T TELL YOU THE NAME OF THE COMPANY because of "confidentiality reasons". What if I'm trying to do some background research on the company? I can't until the middle man submits me for the position so they can tell me the name. Then I can do research only to find out, "Oh, I don't want to work for this company after all".
Then there's the fact that middleman recruiters don't know anything technical- Sure, they can read the job description right off the screen in front of them, but any time you have a question about it, they can't answer it to save their lives- or they'll say to ask them at your interview.


here's a personal example:
The last company I worked for (for only 3 weeks)- the middleman recruiter gave me an incorrect job description. They said I would be working on a Desktop Support/Help Desk team for one of the "Big Four". Ok sweet, a job similar to what I had in the past. Set up computers, maintain them, assist users, etc. They never informed me that my *sole* job requirement would be to work in a call center and answer calls all day like a robot. Some "IT" job for sure. When I called up my recruiter to tell them this isn't what I had in mind/what they said it would be, I basically got a "Yeah if you can stick with it that'd be great". The next day I quit, and spoke with the recruiter once more who was cursing me out over the phone and TBH I couldn't give a shit because of how pissed off I was at the job in itself.


I just hate how impersonal this whole process is. Finding a job is difficult enough, and I know that there are others out there like me that graduate university and are intimidated by finding a job. I wish we could make this, as a whole, much easier.


Ok, rant done. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-10 19:43:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> TBH I don't drive like a lunatic.  Modest driver with a heavy acceleration every now and then.  They're also 10mm wider than stock (225 vs 215) but still.  Basically it's 2/3 as economical as it used to be.  Hopefully they get a bit better as they wear in, I've been told they do. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-10 19:42:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I thought (and hoped) that it was from me driving it harder.  But I've been driving modestly the past week and the numbers stay the same :( </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-10 19:21:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Sadly, yes.  Went from like 28 average to 20.9 average.  Higher rolling resistance tires and the additional grip apparently will do that, these being Max Summer Performance tires.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-10 19:11:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> How light are we talking here? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> ELI5: Why don't we snore while awake? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-10 19:04:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-10 18:40:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Other than losing about average 8mpg (!!!!), they're phenomenal.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-10 18:39:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> idk, I want to change them out but I don't really care enough to haha.  Also lazy </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Let's not forget to show our wheels the same love we show our paint! </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-10 15:55:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> My miso soup formed a star shaped pattern at the top. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-10 15:54:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-10 15:51:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah last summer we drove from the east coast to the midwest for vacation.  This time around my friend is buying a car in California, and I'm flying out to Denver to help him drive it back.  The plan is to go from Saturday afternoon to Sunday evening and take a sick day Monday if need be. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-10 15:00:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> We did the same trip last summer with 3 of us, we each did an 8 hour leg then another 1 hour per driver.  That was ideal but this time its under different circumstances </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Best way to complete a 26 hour non-stop road trip? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-10 14:08:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hey all, my friend and I will be driving a car back from Denver next week to NJ and it will be done in a straight shoot 26-30 hours.  What is the best way to split up the times so we don't get too tired of driving / bored of driving?  I don't want to take 8 hour shifts like I did last road trip.  I'm thinking of splitting it into about 9 3-hour shifts.

What are your thoughts? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-10 00:36:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Where are you from? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-07 22:49:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You can use the 12v plug insert from the glove box to plug into the sound tube.  Welcome! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Don't go 140km/h on the highway if you want to keep your car (x-post from /r/toronto) </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-07 21:01:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-06 19:18:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I didn't throw into the equation that I would experience that.  Don't get me wrong I love the tire it's phenomenal  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-06 19:13:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> ughhh I was so content with my mileage :( </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-06 18:13:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You the man.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-06 16:40:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Need to get to that 750 character minimum! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-06 15:15:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Please supply this large collection of top gear gifs </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> I hope our next president has plumbing experience.... </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-06 15:02:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Because he's going to have to clean up all of Trump's shit. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-06 14:14:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Search this sub on the topic- there is a lot of conversation about it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> TIFU by picking my nose at the doctor's office. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-06 14:10:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This one will be quick... literally just happened.

So I'm at the doctor's office, waiting in an examination room for the doc to come in. He's taking a while, and my nose felt stuffy- so naturally I went digging for gold up there. I'm getting into it and then the doctor knocks on the door rather loudly (maybe even banging on the door?). Anyway, me being so indulged in digging my way to China, this banging scares the shit out of me and my nail digs into the wall of my nostril causing a nose bleed that would not stop for the entire length of the exam. He laughed, I laughed (embarrassingly) and it finally stopped when I got to my car.



TL;DR: Went to the doctors office, picked nose in the exam room, doc knocked on door, scaring me shitless and leaving me with a bloody nose with as much power as the Nile itself.

edit: formatting

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-06 13:52:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Sure but it's useless </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-06 05:05:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'll say... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
