<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject7431</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-10 15:44:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You've helped me understand, cheers! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-10 15:43:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Ahh, this makes sense now! thanks! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-10 15:09:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I thought Flynn WAS the one investigating, no? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-10 15:08:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> To be honest, I've lost track...  
I thought that Trump was being investigated for Russian naughty business. But these subpoenas seem to imply the opposite, that it's not Trump who's in trouble, but the people investigating him. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-10 15:07:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah, I understand the process, but just not who the goodies and the baddies are. I've lost track of who's on who's side now. Are the subpoenas to bring charges against the Administration, or against Flynn and associates? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-10 13:57:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That last one is Kevin Spacey! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-10 12:07:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> "Exclusive" ??? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-10 12:03:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  Flynn associates had been subpoenaed

Can you explain this? I would read it as the courts are investigating wrongdoing by Flynn's associates and have requested them to appear to explain themselves, but that doesn't seem to fit with the narrative.  
EDIT: OK, now I understand that Flynn was in cahoots with Trump, and it's back fired. I thought it was the FBI (and therefor Flynn) who was investigating Trump! Thanks guys! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-10 11:58:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> how does one "earn" a night out? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-10 10:07:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [Richard Ayoade](https://youtu.be/iWoBG8N_2Ok) is the personification of this description!  
"I would like to thank the Academy for codifying this clerical error" </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-10 09:58:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>   the justice department is pursuing criminal charges

Against whom? I'm really lost. Are the subpoenas threatening to the Trump Administration, or to those investigating the Trump Administration?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-09 14:44:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> "It's East?"  
"Yeah"  
"This far?"  
"No, a bit further"  
"Oh, here?"  
"No, that's too far!"  
"What about here.. in the middle?"  
"No, too close, just a bit further, but not as far as the previous place"  
"Here?"  
"And there you shall train with the camels at the top of mountains!" </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-09 10:34:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> True. Being foreign contractors, we were probably afforded some liberties. That said, their expectations were high (but I like that). </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-09 07:52:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Bedouins are from the Middle East, Monks from the Far East (or Europe)  
Where do Bedouin monks come from? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-09 07:28:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You know that you don't have to live where you're born?  
I agree though, spent about 4 months working in Tokyo, would love to move there. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-08 23:44:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  iplayer

Got your TV licence, yeah? ;) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-08 23:37:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I beg to differ. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-08 23:33:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> There's still a demand even if it's gaudy. There are plenty of people in the world without class, and this city isn't without more than it's fair share of tastelessness. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-08 23:25:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  I wouldn't mind having all of my data open for the government to view in cases of investigations and security

What happens when suddenly someone comes in power and doesn't like people who have a certain race/religion/sexuality/opinion... and you happen to be one of them? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-08 23:14:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [Verbatim](https://xkcd.com/16/) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-08 14:36:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> How are you on vaccinating kids? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-08 14:35:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Along with vaccinations </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-08 06:36:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This is correct. Although some are like 1 or 2 king higher. Best bet is to use a sat nav. This will be more accurate and even tell you where the speed traps are. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-08 06:35:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Or use Waze </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-07 09:48:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> As defined [here](https://en.oxforddictionaries.com/definition/suspender) and [here](https://en.m.wikipedia.org/wiki/Suspenders).  
And also as a Brit who wears them. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-07 08:45:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Nope, maybe in American English though. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-07 01:11:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> There are loads of lingerie shops in every mall. Might have to say that you're looking for something for your "wife" ;)  
Edit: and yeah, I'm aware that many men enjoy wearing women's lingerie.  
Edit edit: ok so I was being slightly disingenuous. In my language "suspenders" are women's lingerie. What you are referring to are called "braces" in English. Mea culpa. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-07 01:08:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Cross dressing? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-06 21:00:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> There's a loophole in the law which allows people to possess guns, and even carry them in public!!! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-05 23:22:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You mean... [East Indies](https://youtu.be/dOBhf8f7cXM)? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-05 20:27:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> 'Twas a rhetorical question </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-05 10:45:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> But the acts worship are a requirement of being a Muslim, their omission are attributed to disbelief... as I said, I'm not arguing either way, but it's certainly not as clear cut as you put it.  
However, this is certainly not the forum for such a debate, nor are the likes of me and you qualified to come to any meaningful conclusion. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-05 09:54:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What's the difference between a non-practising-Muslim and a non-Muslim?  
For info, the answer is WAAAY bigger than can be covered here, just more of a shower thought. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-05 09:53:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> For Muslims it's even harder because a lot of the time whilst not fasting is spent at the Masjid. If you're not Muslim but wanted to try the fasting, then you can still exercise after dark.  
That said, fasting itself can be viewed as a form of exercise. It's like going to the gym, you feed pretty knackered whilst doing it, but afterwards, your general health improves. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-04 20:45:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's too long.  
Executive summary? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-04 15:44:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You're username suggests you're British.  Do not, for one moment, compare a UAE 2003 car with a British 2003 car. People in the UAE rarely maintain their cars, or service properly. When they break, they patch it up and shift it along. If you buy a 2003 car, you're probably buying one that's a patchwork of gaffer tape underneath.  
Yes, I'm generalising, but just don't want you to think of a 2003 car back in the "green and pleasant lands" of England and believe you'll get something like that. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-04 15:41:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> TL;DR? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-04 15:38:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Noon's coming tomorrow, as it does every day, just before dhuhr. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-04 15:34:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Because most of the market cares not about the quality, but rather about the name. Once a place has made their name, they will get a torrent of customers who want to eat there just because it's a known place to eat or even a "place to be seen". Their customers don't know or care about good food, so why make the effort? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-04 15:28:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Looking at OPs history, they have posted a fair bit in /r/OnePunchMan ...  
heh </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-04 14:16:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> hear hear </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-04 14:13:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> YeaaaNOPE!  
It is in fact an offence to disobey any member of flight crew with regards to the flight. They are there primarily as a safety, but also happen to serve drinks whilst they're there. That said, it wasn't even a flight attendant who confronted the man. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-04 09:23:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Errr, more like because of cash flow... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-03 17:20:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thanks for translation. Our languages and cultures are remarkably similar [but not the same](https://youtu.be/E837tnxRVS0?t=2m23s) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-03 16:46:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> "... As long as we are in America, or some other war torn country" </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-03 13:09:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  because there's WiFi everywhere

Is data expensive there? There's not a lot of free wifi where I live, that just because it's more hassle to join than it costs just to use your data. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-03 10:36:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [It's all about the colour](https://youtu.be/xOdO_8IiM3o?t=4m56s)  
I have started at the relevant point. But if you've got 9 mins, you won't regret watching all of it! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-03 10:30:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  How unfortunate

Are you serious? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-03 10:30:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That's because dark dashboards don't reflect in the windscreen. Next time you get in your car on a sunny day, put a white piece of paper on your dash board, and see how annoying it is when you're driving because it reflects off the windscreen. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-03 10:26:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'd do it, but the data is a load of bollocks, so it wouldn't benefit you in the slightest. Just move on. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-03 10:05:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> "Aid Donor" </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-03 09:41:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Although I agree with your objection, he was referring to you as a collective (unfortunately there's no plural "you" in English. As a collective, you elected him. (Ignoring the fact that ACTUALLY he lost the popular vote, but one could argue that this system was created by policy writers who were voted in). The problem with a democracy is the argument "well you (collective) voted for this, so you're responsible". </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-03 09:37:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Even "at the discretion of..." </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-03 09:34:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You forgot the fact that it's corporations who then become the policy makers. With policies intended to make the rich, richer, not for the good of society. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-03 09:10:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> ...and stupidly dangerous. If there's a breach causing re-pressurisation, then the carriages turn into supersonic bullets. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-02 21:24:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> By "working on" you mean "wasting time and money on", right?  
Hyper loop is such a bad idea! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-02 13:47:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That's because a Euro is made of metal </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-02 02:17:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-01 16:24:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Helvetica with Jo Malone's kerning (based on the uppercase display, the lower case one has tighter kerning it seems) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-01 16:08:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's not </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-01 16:07:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hahahahaa! I see what you did there!! There's no "p" in Arabic!!!  
/s  
(Seriously, this has been done a thousand times before, not original) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-01 16:04:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  How easy is it to pay fines? Make a complaint about something? Report problems to the police? How soon do they respond? Days? weeks? months?

To pay fines? VERY easy! To make a complaint or contest the fine? Nigh on impossible! How long do they take to respond? When they respond, I'll let you know how many months/years it was. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-30 23:58:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Buying a new puppy is not an "upgrade" you heartless monster! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-30 23:57:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> They're MINERALS! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-30 16:20:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm surprised it's not a full auto, how can you tell it's only a semi? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-30 16:13:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Bravo! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-30 16:12:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Only a quarter hit someone? That seems a very low hit rate? Is that due to bad aim, or just furious shootout with automatics which are more a spray-and-pray, or are they used as warning shots? Genuinely interested, am inclined to think the latter. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-29 09:16:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> By "this behaviour" I meant assaulting someone. Not assaulting an official. Apologies </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-29 09:16:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> By "this behaviour" I meant assaulting someone. Not assaulting an official. Apologies </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-28 18:36:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That's cool. I'll probably check it out, cheers. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-28 18:19:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If *HE* was legless, *then* it'd be low hanging fruit! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-28 18:17:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Haha, good description, well put.  
It's a shame though. I'd be interested in watching (and playing) a gentleman's version of ice hockey. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-28 18:16:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Apologies, I meant a permissible part of the game. Apologies, mea culpa. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-28 18:12:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> see my original comment "except professional fighters when in a match"  
If someone punches someone else, that's assault where I live. Maybe the law is different in your country. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-28 18:09:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Handling the ball with your hands in football (soccer) is also in the rule book. Doesn't make it a permissible. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-28 18:05:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Interesting, thanks.  
Surprising that this works as a more effective deterrent than jail time and a massive fine. I guess they see the legal system not being able to deliver justice to use vigilantism. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-28 18:00:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> /r/nocontext  
I re-read my comment... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-28 17:59:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's the final toss into the bin after the guy leaves which does it for me! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-28 17:51:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah I can see how you could sacrifice a crap player to take out another star player. But this can be in any sport (I agree the nature of ice hokey makes it easier to make it look like an accident over something like curling!). But I fail to see how a fight solves this? The guy can still take out the star player, then have a fight (or just keep his gloves on). How does a fight stop this? (genuine question, I acknowledge I know almost nothing of the sport)  
 Plus it's an accepted tradition, basically.  
  
Fairy nuff! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-28 17:43:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>   clearing the puck out of the zone  
  
No, but it does make progress to scoring a point, or reduce the chance of an opponent scoring points in a legitimate manner.  
Also, without reading the whole rule book, your excerpt alone proves nothing other than how a fight is defined, not whether it is a tactic, or indeed permissible. I'm not familiar with the rules (and haven't read the whole link you sent) so happy to be proved otherwise. You made a better argument than I've heard anyone else make :) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-28 17:33:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  keep people from going after your star players  

In what way? "Going after" as in assaulting? If so, why are they not just charged with assault? or "Going after" in an attack play? Then why do they have to resort to violence to win the game?  
  
 both players have to drop the gloves  
  
I've heard this before and honestly wish they would keep their gloves on. It ruins what looks like an otherwise awesome sport.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-28 17:29:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  eliminating it would make much more dangerous fouls go dramatically up in frequency

I honestly fail to understand this. Does the sport attract violent people who are bad sportsmen unable to adhere to the rules? As for being fast paced, in the professional league then I'm assuming they'd have enough cameras and slow mo replays, and even a ref assigned to watch every single player. This would eliminate any injustice by someone flaunting the rules without their victim having to resort to martial law. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-28 17:11:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hockey? Really? Or do you mean Ice Hockey? I'm not sure about those rules, but is it really part of the game play? As in, do you score points? If not, then it's just tolerated assault so still wrong in my books (and legally).  
Rugby, nope! Being a contact sport and ending up bloody is not the same as intending to harm someone. Most rugby players have great sportsmanship anyway. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-28 16:57:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  yeah the ref is completely off-limits

This behaviour should be off limits to EVERYONE (except professional fighters when in a match) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-28 16:49:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You forgot tax, and tip. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-28 15:00:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Only one time? It's pretty common!  
Some argue that it's unhygienic. But the feet are already clean; as opposed to your hands which you just used to wipe your poop covered butt. It's awkward, sure, but not unhygienic.  
They should clean up any spillage after themselves though. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-28 14:57:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Once you do this, you'll never go back!  
Imagine your dishes... try cleaning them with a dry cloth, clean? Now try with water! No more dingle-berries! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-28 14:52:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That'd be  right? this is more like "Gays" (even that would be more like ) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-28 14:43:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I like your logic. "don't save what's left after spending; spend what's left after saving".  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-28 14:39:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That makes no sense, if it's disposable, then he's already established he's not foraging for scraps... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-28 14:36:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I still don't get the  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-28 12:38:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Had this where I had about 150 worth at the till. Realised I had left my wallet in the car. The guy in front offered to pay for me and I'll pay him back in the car park. I told him I had card only, and she said "oh, no need to pay me back then". I thanked him but obviously declined. It's such a contradictory place, you see the best and worst of people.  
Also, was on long motorbike ride and stopped at a small show. I had no cash and asked if they took card. They said they didn't, but if I needed anything, I could just have it. I was in desperate need of water so just took a small bottle. I was able to go back the next week (same trip) and paid him back. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-28 10:56:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> There is a spectrum of shittiness though. Tokyo for example, rates very low on the shittiness scale.  
That said, I find UAE contradictory. If ever you're stuck in a car, people will help you out. Ever need water? People give bottles for free. Forgot your wallet, people offer to pay for groceries. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-28 10:23:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What about your legs? And why do you need a flip helmet just for glasses? I can't see what advantage it gets you. I use shades in my regular helmet. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-28 10:16:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Maybe onto some vinyl type material. Set it to go just under 80rpm... I think you're onto something here! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-27 23:15:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You missed the point... that exposing breasts and breastfeeding are not synonymous. Someone might have an issue with expose breasts but exclusively breastfeed their own kids. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-27 13:33:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You'll love [this](https://youtu.be/wJsPR1q1ap8) then </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-27 13:30:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> To put the stats in context (which blew *my* mind):  
WW1: 18.5 million deaths / 4 years = 4.6 million per year [Source](https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/World_War_I_casualties)  
WW2: 85 million deaths / 6 years =  14 million per year [Source](https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/World_War_II_casualties)  
Holocaust: 11 million deaths / 4 years = 2.75 million per year [Source](https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/The_Holocaust)  
Alcohol: 3.3 million per year (2012) and still ongoing [Source](http://www.who.int/substance_abuse/facts/alcohol/en/) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-27 10:20:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> They are the ONLY reason I'd be inclined to watch it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-27 10:16:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Your response was equally uninformed.  
"State by state"...? Are you American? Are you aware that the US is only about 4% of the world? Many other countries/cultures seem to cope fine with "overheating" even in 45 degrees (113 F) heat whilst maintaining modesty. How do they do this? I'm not saying they should have to, just asking how they cope.  
That said, I was not arguing for a case, I was merely highlighting a difference between breastfeeding, and breastfeeding-with-breast-exposed to highlight that the issue is not with the breastfeeding, but the exposed breast. I did not infer my opinion nor was I advocating support for or against breastfeeding with, or without, breast exposed. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-27 10:05:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> How do you know what I think or feel about your breasts? My comment mentioned nothing about my personal opinion.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-27 02:03:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Maybe so. But one would be just as silly to not be aware of social convention. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-27 01:23:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> There's a difference between breastfeeding, and breastfeeding-with-breasts-visible-in-public. Displaying breasts is nothing to do with breastfeeding as it can be done whilst still maintaining modesty.  
Exposing breasts in public is not considered acceptable in most places (though I'm sure a lot of the neck beards here will chirp up now). This is what gets people upset, not the act of breastfeeding. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
