<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject3508</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-10 09:55:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You'll have to go look at his testimony May 8. It was near the middle, I think, when the one GOP senator was trying to get pity for the GOP by claiming that bad stuff about the GOP was released when the hackers released DNC e-mails that contained the background opposition work on the GOP.

But you are correct that only old GOP stuff was hacked. Apparently, they didn't get into the current RNC stuff, though they tried.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-10 09:52:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> and firing comey right now is one way to slow that down, especially if the guy replacing him is appointed by the people who might end up on the pointy end of those investigations.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-10 09:51:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> and would do so faster if not for firing comey.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-10 09:45:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Above where? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-10 09:43:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> According to Clapper under oath, that's what happened. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-10 09:42:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> We all know you took no break! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-10 09:22:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Nobody trusted the FBI anymore. 

That is patently false. Lot's of people trusted the FBI and in fact trust in Comey was growing. 

The time line casts huge shadows of doubt over the integrity of it all. 

Do you honestly not understand how this reeks of cover up even if there is no cover up?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-10 09:14:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Who is saying "one month"?

I'd say it will take at least another year. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-10 09:12:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm going to need proof of that. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-10 09:07:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The fact that you "don't get it" speaks volumes. Sure, perhaps Trump really did think from day one that Comey needed to go. But he did not fire him then. Why not? Why now? *THAT* is why this is such a huge story.

I mean, it's this striking inability on the part of the Trump administration to understand optics. 

AND THAT'S NOT EVEN GETTING INTO REPORTS THAT HE SAID JUST RECENTLY "COME UP WITH A REASONS TO FIRE HIM". Because that shows, "Her e-mails" is not the real reason. 

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-10 08:54:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That's what t_d is meming right now. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-10 08:50:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Sounds like Trump's own line of reasonsing. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-09 21:55:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> 2-month old article? From his campaign? We'd like to hear from him as president. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-09 18:18:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> karma </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-09 18:15:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Ah, okay. My bad. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The worlds most valuable resource is no longer oil, but data </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-09 17:40:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-09 15:34:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> /u/zossima bringing you yesterday's news! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-09 15:18:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This one might not have been an actual "bill".  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-09 14:44:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It would make some prime text as part of a Senate filibuster. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-09 14:35:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> such as the power to wear a crop top. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-09 14:34:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> whoosh </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-09 10:44:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You can still choose that. Why is your problem with making people actively make that choice?

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-09 10:43:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Did you just assume his/her/its species? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-09 10:40:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> At 2m, I'm going to guess money was laundered.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-09 10:39:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Judge for yourself


http://art-bin.com/art/omodest.html </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-09 09:55:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Clapper? Say good bye to any kind of privacy at all.

I loved the guy in this hearing, but he has some draconian ideas on how much the federal government should be able to snoop on people. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-09 09:48:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> To be precise, Clapper said that when earlier he had said he saw no evidence of collusion, he was at that time unaware of the FBI investigation (which may have that evidence - my note).

And IIRC, when pressed about if he had since learned anything, he replied that he could not talk about that in a non-classified setting. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-09 09:43:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Remember when Trump could not tell the difference between Rand Paul and Paul Ryan? Well...

[Goldfish are certainly smarter than you think. Some have been observed to perceive and remember well enough to distinguish between people.](http://thegoldfishtank.com/goldfish-info/biology/smart-goldfish/) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-09 07:38:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> To be fair, I suppose that is better for the kid in the long run. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-09 07:07:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I am of the opinion that you are mostly right, BUT that some people in the Trump campaign (I'm thinking Manafort and Page) *definitely* knew they were personally benefitting from helping Russia influence the election. *Someone* (or maybe more than one person) in the Trump campaign was in fact colluding with the Russians all along.

But I think Trump was more "oh, you guys were getting paid by thte Russians to help me win? Well, okay then - I did win! Great!" But that he was probably not making those deals himself.

Like everyone rails on Trumps for "Asking the Russians to hack Clinton's e-mails". I doubt Trump was in face asking that - he was amking a stupid joke. BUT someone probably told him to make that joke. 

For example. Say Manafort needed to prove to the Russians that he could influence Trump. So he jokingly suggests to Trump to make that "joke" on TV. The Russians see that and know it is the signal from Manafort that Manafort is indeed a player here. 

Manafort surely got millions from the Russians and surely gave the Russians valuable informtion on how to release wikileaks for max damage to Clinton, etc. And he surely got paid for the GOP taking Ukraine out of its platform. And I think the intelligence community knows this for sure. 

Trump gets into trouble because - just like Nixon - he now knows these things and is trying to cover it up. And his Achilles heel is that he feels "loyalty" to these people and cannot admit he was wrong about them. His ego will bring him down. 

As for me, of course, I'm just speculating.

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-09 06:49:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Well, if I recall correctly, she demured on that one. She did say that lying to the FBI is a crime. But she did not "in this setting" say whether or not he hd in fact lied to the FBI. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-08 23:45:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Also, correct me if I'm wrong, but Ytes said she did not request anyone to be unmasked herself. However, she did see unmasked names because the agencies forwarding the reports deemed it necessary to understand the bigger picture.

Have I got that right? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-08 23:01:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Amen.

I liked the line whoever said about Trump saying "Well, it could have been anybody!" playing into the russians' hands. 

The next question should have been, "Does not having an independent investigation help play into the Russians' hands?" </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-08 23:00:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I don't. I mean it's fine, but he can do it somewhere besides this hearing?

Yates is correct to say "I don't think I'm going to touch this".
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-08 22:59:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Sorry, Franken right now is not contributing anything useful. Why is he going on about speculation?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-08 22:11:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> He's such a dick. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-08 22:06:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Everyone is thinking that this is mostly all about Flynn talking to the Russian Ambassador. 

Clapper is pointing out (over and over) that 107(?) concerns Foreign targets OVERSEAS. 

This means that apart from Flynn talking to the Russian ambassador, the Intelligence Community picked up conversations (I'm guessing in which US persons were a party or were discussed) *not* from the Russian embassy in the US.

So, my takeaway is that the IC has access to conversations concerning Trump or ( much more likely) his campaign associates which were made overseas (like gained from assets in Russia ) and which were disturbing enough that the someone unmasked the US persons in order to see the context of what the foreign target's intent was. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-08 21:55:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> "Ambassador Kislyak was not overseas on [that date]"

"That is correct"

BOOM!! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-08 20:59:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's good to get this on record under oath, though, I think. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-08 20:47:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I made no claim of "destructive assimilatory warfare.

If you could though, could you comment on any tribes that interacted with the Anishinaabe which no longer exist? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-08 20:46:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Ah, okay, thanks!  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-08 20:40:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> No. He said unmasking should not be used to take advantage of anyone for political aims. He wants to make sure unmasking remains outside of partisan politics. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-08 20:37:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> "To find out all things Russia" </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-08 20:33:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Care to elaborate? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-08 20:32:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What - no pants??? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-08 18:54:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I never called "white culture" "great" and would never do so. 

All of today's cultures displaced previous cultures. Arabs replaced Egyptians, Rome replaced Greece. Anglo-Saxons replaced Picts. Ukrainains pushed out the steppe peoples...

It happened in [Africa](https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Kingdom_of_Mutapa#Expansion)

It happened in Asia. 

And it continues... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-08 18:43:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah, you're right; I really don't get it.

I mean I understand, but this is human history. One group culturally assimilates another, time after time. Be angry, that's fine, if you like. I get angry, too, when my culture is encroached upon by a nearby, more dominant culture. But that's not going to stop time.

Case in point: read the wikipedia entry on this tribe and you will see that they assimilated other tribes in the past. Who is going to call them out on that? 

https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Anishinaabe#Historical_relations_between_the_Anishinaabeg_and_other_indigenous_groups

Other closely related Algonquin groups such as the Zhiishiigwan and Amikwaa were incorporated into the Anishinaabe peoplehood through alliances.

More on the Amikwaa:

The Amikwa were nearly wiped out by disease and wars with the Iroquois and the last of the tribe appear to have merged with the Nipissings or the Ojibwe.

https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Amikwa_people

Back to the main point of my previous comment: I see little to no difference in one person saying "hurr, I can do that, too!" vs "Gee, I'd like to do that, but I'm also going to invest a lot of time "learning about the indigenous peoples' culture and customs with them". The politically correct thing for the tribe to do would have been to reach out to her and assimilte *her*, rather than making a fuss that is only going to turn the dominant culture away from them.

ALSO: Please don't forget to project some anger against young black women who want to do ballet because they are turning their backs on their own culture, betraying their own roots and "giving in to the whites". </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-08 18:31:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I just read that wiki entry and this jumped out at me:

Other closely related Algonquin groups such as the Zhiishiigwan and Amikwaa were incorporated into the Anishinaabe peoplehood through alliances.

So, basically, the Anishinaabe culturally annihilated the Zhiishiigwan and Amikwaa tribes, I guess.

  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-08 18:18:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Why?

What about an African girl who thinks ballet is cool and wants to try it? Should she be shown the door because ballet is white culture and she should steer clear of it?

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-08 17:46:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Othings Obama shoud have warned Trump about:

1) What a terrible idea Single Payer healthcare is.

2) What an abomination Net Neutrality is

3) That in fact, global warming is a hoax and the US deifinitely should pull out of the Paris agreements.

4) That NATO is really pointless and no time or other resources should really be spent on helping Europe stay secure

5) That Ivanka is really, really hot!*

*That last one is just to mess with his mind. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-08 17:35:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> ^ **SOMEONE MAKE THIS A MEME AND SPREAD IT!** </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-08 17:35:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I sense you have a pre-existing condition! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-08 17:16:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> WHEN is this starting? What time do I need to fervishly start F5-ing?

EDIT: Found it! "Yates is scheduled to testify ... alongside James Clapper... before a Senate Judiciary subcommittee at 2:30 p.m." </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-08 12:17:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Crap, i thought i fixed that. :P </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-08 11:27:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> /u/snoodlebooper of course. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-08 11:18:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Do it! Get those plans and comapre them. 

Hey [trumper-friend], I'm thinking you might be right, but I'm having trouble convincing my other friends who think you're wrong. Can you get me copies of those insurance policies your parents had before and what they've got now? I've got to stop the SMS lies! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-08 07:21:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> My god, so much *winning!* </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-07 23:41:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> And by the way, thanks for bringing that 538 data to my attention. I didn't know they had that and broswed it some. Pretty interesting. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-07 23:19:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Amazing. I didn't know the Maverick had it in him to be so *maverick!* </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-07 20:01:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> "Badass. Back Tomorrow" </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-07 20:00:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  if they do make a sequel I'll probably still see it

Something tells me the number crunchers knew this before you wrote it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-07 19:42:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Damn, That Headline Is Hard To Read!! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-07 19:18:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hold it right there - 97% of the time?

You're going to need to offer some proof if you want me to believe he voted against Trump 3% of the time. That's just hard to believe. 

*My* gut tells me it's closer to 0%.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-07 15:43:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You seem to be a really uptight individual. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-07 15:43:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm just glad my name ain't Jake. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-07 15:14:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yes, it is Europe's "United we stand, divided we fall" time. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-07 11:40:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That's a longish video, but worth the watch. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-07 11:29:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> racism </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-07 11:07:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Furiouser and furiouser! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-07 09:17:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Wow, I never even thought of describing globalization as "meld all of the world's cultures together". Sounds like people are arguing about completely different things. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-06 17:59:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> 'cept it doesn't </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-06 17:54:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So find and buy an app that does the same thing, but with no ads. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-06 17:49:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Kimmel should go out and find someone in the exact same position - a baby needing precisely the same care - but that someone a someone making 50,000-80,000 a year and bring thm on the show. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-06 17:17:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Comments like that remind me that heartless bastards do in fact exist and roam the Earth. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-06 12:50:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It was a very good movie.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-06 09:41:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  fucked up in the last debate 

I missed this, can you give me a short, quick "How she fucked up the debate"?

Clearly she did as the polls moved, but I'm not really in the loop here, just casually interested. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> I would really like to watch a historical fictional drama set in Venice. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-06 09:36:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-06 09:03:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The problem is that not all of them do. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-06 08:37:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Good, let them walk down this path oblivious to what lies around the bend until it is too late. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-06 08:35:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm not looking for a solution. i'm honestly wondering why facebook does not simply allow it organically.

it is for security reasons?

maybe Zuckerberg's has personal or religious reasons for not allowing pdfs?

maybe there are licencing issues?

Zuckerberg is under pressure from the images mafia to keep pdfs off "their turf"?

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-06 07:36:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Why does Facebook not allow posting PDF files? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Why does Facebook not allow posting actual, real PDF files? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-05 23:00:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-05 18:55:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> FCC Chief: Net Neutrality Rules Treating Internet As Utility Stifle Growth in Corporate Profits

Hey Mr FCC Chief, FTFY </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-05 09:22:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yup. Scheduled for tonight! Shall I report back on my impressions? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-05 06:58:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The writer's point is to sow confusion and widen the reach of fake news. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-04 20:45:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  and thrown it into the ~~air~~ cesspool.

FTFY
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-04 19:01:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That right there sounds suspiciously like a Trump quote! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-04 18:40:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm sure I'm not the only one who read that in Tywin Lannister's voice. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-04 13:53:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  The globalist movement is very real. The Euro and the open borders movement are a tangible result of it.

And what exactly is wrong with that? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-04 13:42:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I just want to see a political cartoon of Trump standing in front of an arcade game with this on its screen:

https://i.ytimg.com/vi/votpmwC25Ek/hqdefault.jpg </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-04 13:34:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> *Mwa*-ha-ha or Mwa-ha-*ha*? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-04 13:19:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Maybe that's the plan to fight terrorism?

[orator] They hate us for our freedoms!

[crowd] yeah!!!

[orator] How do we stop that?

[crowd] Get rid of our freedoms!
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-04 13:17:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> While I knew this administraiton would be anathema to American values, I am completely blown away by how fast they have been able to cut America down.

It's like there should be a political cartoon of Trump and his cabinet standing around the Statue of Liberty as she lies bleeding on the ground having been kneecapped with an axe. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-04 13:06:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So, no more shining city on a hill. Gotcha.

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Tillerson: Pushing human rights abroad 'creates obstacles' to US interests </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-04 13:03:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-04 12:43:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> His voters in corn and other ag export heavy states also did not fear he would in fact try to kill NAFTA.

But I somehow doubt the schadenfreude will be as great in one. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-04 09:49:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Depends on what the definition of "is" is. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-04 08:40:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Sounds like a pre-existing condition, to me. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-04 00:56:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> that's too much government regulation!

/s </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-03 23:31:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If your comment gets 100 upvotes, I'll watch it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-03 21:16:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Come on, everyone knows he only has dolls in his drawers. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-03 20:33:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> i was going to go with affluential </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-03 20:22:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You've misread Medvedev. That was all an act. At heart, he runs in the exact same circles as Putin. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-03 20:21:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> How? Who would even listen to Romney then? As SoS, he would have more influence on Trump. Who cares what the public would think of Romney criticizing Trump-elect? Trump certainly wouldn't. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-03 20:18:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> you forgot the /s </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-03 20:13:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Everyone heard about this months ago.

The news is that the FBI finds it credible enough to investigate.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-03 20:12:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  The whole email mess is because some people like to print out emails rather than read them on the computer.

OLD PEOPLE. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-03 20:10:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> For comparison, Vladimir Putin is 5'7".

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-03 20:08:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That was my big takeaway from this, too. That was Bill's fault, right? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-03 20:07:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Imagine if HRC *was* president-elect and they *did* find something on Wiener's laptop and that became know in the beginning of December?

Not worse than what we got, but in some ways, worse. Imagine the GOP obstructionism is that case and Chaffetz shit-eating grin on TV every fucking day.

At least with IncompeTrump in office, the Dems won on the budget bill. That bill would probably have been worse under Clinton, because the GOP would have shut down government over it, you know it's true.

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-03 19:54:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Everyone who came with Comey is so short!! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-03 17:29:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Expand and revitalize the popular 287(g) program

What is this program? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-03 17:24:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> King of the pumps? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-03 17:24:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Dude better write a book someday. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-03 09:01:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I think this is an good example of the free hand of the market. 

BUT, I also think that free hand is showing to advertisers that ad-blocking doesn't really hurt hm, because the overwhelming umber of visitors to a website who are going to fall for thoe ads, don't use ad-block anyhow. While at the same time, turning off access to the minority who do use ad-block *might* get some of them to turn it off.

It's all about the money numbers. Until the vast majority of people use ad block and advertising revenue actually srrinks because of this, ugly ads are not going to change.

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-02 20:09:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> *GOP enters stage left*

[GOP] Why thank you! We want - nay, need! more sick people so that our friends in the health insurance industry can charge them out the wazzoo for coverage in a high-risk pool. We are tying our best dontcha know! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-02 20:05:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So, not only do the Rebpulicans say preexisting conditions are due to people eating improperly, they also want to deny children the right to eat properly?!

I guess that is logical in its own twisted sort of way. And by that I mean if you are in the health insurance gangsters' pockets and want as many children as possible to have pre-existing conditions as soon as they are in the world trying to get their own coverage so that that coverage can be as damned expensive as those gangsters feel is their right endowed from on high, then sure, that would help the big bucks to keep flowing via their pockets into yours as a self-righteous, holier-than-thou congress-scum. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-02 09:06:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Damn there's an idea! Has there honestly never been product placement in a book? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-02 08:07:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> FWIW, this is precisely the same phenomenon which leads people to hate the MSM, believe Vaccine Truthers, and deny climate change.

Who needs experts, amirite? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-01 18:32:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Also, she and Podesta did not listen to Bill "It's the economy, stupid" when he told them to campaign in PA, MI, etc. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
