<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject4125</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Homo naledi is between 236,000 and 335,000 years old, almost a tenth as old as some had predicted. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-09 10:44:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Male mice exposed to nicotine before mating father offspring that are more able to withstand toxic levels of both nicotine and cocaine. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-07 15:18:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-25 19:54:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This press release on the journal website has some more information.
https://elifesciences.org/elife-news/press-package-dyslexia-linked-to-shorter-memory-trace-previous-stimuli </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Ants transfer chemical cues, growth proteins and hormones mouth-to-mouth in saliva. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-04 18:37:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-13 16:45:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This other recent study found similar results for human skin cells reprogrammed into neurons. https://elifesciences.org/content/5/e18648 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-13 12:04:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Link to peer-reviewed research paper [here](https://elifesciences.org/content/5/e17978)

Abstract
Robust preference for fermentative glucose metabolism has motivated domestication of the budding yeast *Saccharomyces cerevisiae*. This program can be circumvented by a protein-based genetic element, the [*GAR*+] prion, permitting simultaneous metabolism of glucose and other carbon sources. Diverse bacteria can elicit yeast cells to acquire [*GAR*+], although the molecular details of this interaction remain unknown. Here we identify the common bacterial metabolite lactic acid as a strong [*GAR*+] inducer. Transient exposure to lactic acid caused yeast cells to heritably circumvent glucose repression. This trait had the defining genetic properties of [*GAR*+], and did not require utilization of lactic acid as a carbon source. Lactic acid also induced [*GAR*+]-like epigenetic states in fungi that diverged from *S. cerevisiae* ~200 million years ago, and in which glucose repression evolved independently. To our knowledge, this is the first study to uncover a bacterial metabolite with the capacity to potently induce a prion.
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
