<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject4616</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The View from the Cheap Seats, by Neil Gaiman - A How-to Guide... </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-08 20:37:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm curious as to how other Redditors approached this title. Did you read it in chunks at a time? Pick out preferred pieces based on their title or the idea behind them? Burn through it in as few lengthy sittings as possible, as per Caitlin Moran's apparent suggestion on the cover?

I'd wanted to get started on Neil's non-fiction works, but hadn't realized what exact format the book would take, and I've found myself at a bit of a loss in terms of how to tackle it. Any suggestions would be most appreciated. :-) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-07 23:06:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It just seems like, in terms of UI/UX, Messenger is given a lot more attention to detail. Just look at chat heads for a start, not to mention transitions between the contacts list and Messenger Day, that kind of thing.

I'm not calling WhatsApp ugly by any means, but I will say that it's very... utilitarian... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-07 20:30:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Always reminded me of *The Matrix*, y'know... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-07 16:58:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> And pretty straightforward too! Following up with the armoured version next year could prove tricky, however... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-07 16:42:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  Still want to make my own homemade one though ;)

IKR?! I'm thinking it'll be *the* costume this Hallowe'en!

That said, I've been thinking of doing Daredevil's OG "work in progress" suit myself, provided I've come up to a healthy weight by then. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-07 16:33:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  Parker is a genius and should be able to do it himself, even on a meager budget.

But he did, which is the awesome homemade suit with the crazy goggles. 8-) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-07 16:13:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Interesting counterpoint, but I wonder if you could possibly elaborate on it - I'd be very interested in discussing those countries concerned, for example...

Also, I respect the fact that they've both got well-established user-bases, but I wonder why not just roll both apps into the one banner?Can you offer any suggestions? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-07 16:10:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Welcome, friend. :-) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-07 16:03:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The question is one word too long...

I mean, Facebook owns both WhatsApp and Messenger, and the pair share largely the same functionality, with the latter receiving many more features and much more polish than the former, so why keep both of them around? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-07 12:17:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Honestly, I've no idea what it was, but whatever my German Language teacher had set as her mobile's ringtone. Just struck my high school self as unparalleled... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-06 20:47:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Sounds like you'll need t'visit Display in Settings and switch off Ambient Display. (At least I think that's what it's called. For clarification, it's the setting that switches the device screen toward warmer and cooler conditions depending on the time of day, just like f.lux does for desktops...) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-04 19:03:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  If anything, it helps it because the iOS app is a pile of shit but the android app is a dumpster fire but people blame android instead of the app (sound familiar? Hint hint Snapchat).

Very lucid point, in particular that last word on Snapchat...

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-04 12:27:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Why would they relegate that SIM to an old and unused device, rather than simply transferring it to their new device as per the norm? Special discounts from certain networks for students, or something? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-01 23:29:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I saw him yesterday as an astrophysicist in *The Martian*, I'd say he could potentially pull off the role, albeit a heavily refined version...

Maybe the *Ultimate* version's assistant? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-01 23:28:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Most definitely one or the other...

Any idea how we might decide which? I've tweeted the relevant parties, but to no avail...

The cosplay community needs to know! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-01 22:48:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I can't agree entirely with your sentiment, but these downvotes are undeserved... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-01 22:40:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm wondering if anybody could offer me a hand with enabling notifications from Twitter Lite. I'm using Chrome Canary as my primary (well... only) browser, which I understand Twitter Lite utilises as it's a PWA. I've followed all of the relevant in-app instructions, but to no avail...

While I'm here, I might mention that I'm having difficulty with a lot of notifications; aside from Facebook Messenger, which also handles my SMS functionality, I either don't receive notifications at all or else they come through whilst I'm checking manually...

I've a Nexus 5x currently running the latest build of Lineage OS. 

Many thanks in advance. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-01 21:45:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Awesome wallpaper! I particularly love the cracked screen on his phone. Anybody got any idea what model it's supposed to be? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-01 02:20:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I've friends who flat-out avoid the 3D showings wherever possible... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-30 17:37:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  Really you need someone who's seen the same film on a full beans Imax somewhere and then the smaller one here to compare.

Solid advice, and just as solid phrasing! I'll be inserting the term "full-beans" into every conversation I possibly can now! XD </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> IMAX in Ireland - What are we really getting? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-30 17:14:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I just wanted t'ask /r/ireland for clarification on the whole IMAX/iSense thing that Cineworld and the Odeon crew have going, respectively. I'm not sure I can comment on the latter, but I've recently heard the former referred to as lie-MAX, as well as other, similarly negative commentary surrounding the experience.

I've been t'see some pretty huge big-screen releases in the Cineworld venue (*Captain America: Civil War* and *Doctor Strange*, for instance), and I'm currently trying to decide if it'd be worth it for *Guardians of the Galaxy Vol. 2*, or if I'd just be kidding myself into spending money that I don't have on branding...

I'd like t'be able to defend whether or not it's worth it if I'm inviting friends out, so any kind of information on what separates these IMAX (or so-called IMAX) experiences from traditional ones would be hugely appreciated.

Many thanks all, I'm looking forward t'hearing a pick 'n' mix of opinions and information! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-30 16:58:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So... y'gonna name the spot, or have us guess? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> LOGAN: James Mangold Confirms a Black   White Version is Coming to U.S. Theatres Next Month </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-29 18:23:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-28 21:35:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I realise so, but my initial impression was that you were talking about *Homecoming*. My mistake, of course. :-) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-28 21:19:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It might be the way you've phrased the question, but I was curious as to whether or not you meant after *Homecoming*. It's an equally good question, I'm curious as t'what I should do after the movie myself... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-27 23:06:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Have you a linky/guide to getting Magisk up and running? I've been itching to try Android Pay... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-27 21:48:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Chibi! I love it!

Any chance of reformatting the size t'suit mobile/desktop wallpapers? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-26 14:45:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> And the *Hello Kitty* pyjama bottoms? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-26 14:45:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Oh please. It's hardly unlikely that a kid of fifteen/sixteen would start a collection of shirts "related" to something they'd seen on a television show, is it? It's not unlikely that he'd even convince himself that he enjoyed *TBBT*.

I could certainly see myself having done both the latter and the former at that age, TBH... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-26 14:41:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If *Civil War* is anything to go by, you already know it! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-24 23:20:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So you reckon my best bet is to go ahead and re-flash that old nightly via TWRP, and start the process of updating again from there? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-24 23:16:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Having previously attempted to flash the Radio/Bootloader files via TWRP (and possibly messed up their partitions...) I've since flashed the Radio/Bootloader files via fastboot (and the Vendor image too, for good measure), but I'm still not able t'boot the devices beyond Fastboot mode/TWRP... How screwed am I? Fastboot mode appears to just crash after I select Start... :-( </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-24 23:10:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I didn't, and I *really* don't want to, as it's quite late where I am. Is that my only option? Starting from scratch?

Edit: I've a nightly from March 20th on my device, for some reason... Is flashing that my only option? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-24 22:51:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Many thanks, I've gotten said files, but I... *may* have impatiently attempted to flash the Radio/Bootloader files via TWRP, and now I can't seem t'boot past the bootloader/recovery.

Li'l help?

Update: I've since flashed the Radio/Bootloader files via fastboot (and the Vendor image too, for good measure), but I'm still not able t'boot the devices beyond Fastboot mode/TWRP... How screwed am I? Fastboot mode appears to just crash after I select Start... :-( </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-24 22:12:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I've flashed the same vendor image as OP, but have gotten the same error, and my fingerprint reader is also failing me...

I've not yet flashed the bootloader/radio files, but is this necessary? If so, can anyone advise on which partitions to install them to via TWRP? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-24 20:01:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hi Dr Lotto, and thanks for participating in this AMA. No specific questions or anything just right now, but I heard you speaking with Jonathan McCrea recently on the Futureproof podcast, it was a really great show, so thanks for that. :-)

Keep up the great work where scientific outreach is concerned. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-24 19:57:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So did you get this from that other post, or is it the other way 'round? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-24 19:53:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Interestingly enough, Facebook's [Messenger Day](https://www.macrumors.com/2017/03/09/facebooks-messenger-day-launches/) was designed to encourage this "spur-of-the-moment" behaviour, as opposed to Snapchat's documentation of the previous 24 hours. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-24 13:58:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> On the topic of cosplays, I'm wondering if we could confirm whether or not Pete's iPhone is a 3G or a 3GS? I've both... available to me, so it's no big deal, I'm mostly just curious as to how far the dumpster diver might get with the same device... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-23 17:10:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yes, I've picked that stuff up in the past when it's been on special offer. It certainly was my go-to, but I'm open to suggestions. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-23 16:28:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> As somebody who hadn't heard of *Guardians* before the movie was announced, I'm entirely happy t'let the good and honourable Mr Feige do as he sees fit. :-) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-23 16:20:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Awesome, thanks a bunch for all the advice!

As a side, I've actually bought the Prontissimo stuff recently, again on special, and it's not too bad at all... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-23 14:52:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  I say that as one of those wankers who grinds his own coffee.

Teach me your ways...

Seriously, though, cheers for your input, I'll look out for the Millicano stuff (I try to avoid Nestl for... political reasons...), but can you elaborate on what goes into the process of grinding your own? I can assume that you purchase and grind whole beans, right? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-23 01:50:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Delighted t'see devs jumping aboard the chatbot bandwagon, I'll definitely be checking this out!

Couple of spelling missteps you might amend, OP, but otherwise it's great t'see the effort! Well done! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-23 01:47:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'd been wondering about their whole setup of late. What, is it a serious effort by Centra to push their own brand? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-23 01:21:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Y'mean the coffee they make in Insomnia itself, or the "roll-your-own" kiosk stuff? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Instant Coffee - What Does /r/Ireland Recommend? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-23 00:27:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I know, I know, I'm a bad person, but sometimes you just don't have the time/money/willpower for anything classier...

What have you fine folks found offers the best blend of flavour and frugality when it comes to your instant coffee? I'm open to any and all suggestions, go right ahead. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-22 19:48:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Two questions:

1) How much?

2) Give it to me... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-22 19:47:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Pete, flashing back to uncle Ben's death, could be done as a One-Shot yo... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-22 19:41:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You blame a printing error, Stine blames a hangover and a due date... XD </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-21 20:15:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Awesome, I'll be looking out for it. :-) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-21 16:21:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Oh man, that *Daredevil* scene! I was so glad they included something along those lines, never mind the sheer lengths they went to!

Wish he'd kept the black suit a little longer, though, but I've yet to watch the second season, so maybe Mr Potts' efforts will grow on me... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-17 22:50:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  Side note: This is a cool little shout out to the flippy-floppiness that Peter goes through in the books...

That... is an awesome observation! So subtle too... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-15 22:13:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You... realise that that's a thing, right? In 616? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-15 18:23:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> We were doing Surface battlestations?! Any chance of a link to everything I've been missing? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-14 15:58:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> We've even got the perfect [cover art](https://images-na.ssl-images-amazon.com/images/M/MV5BNTk4ODQ1MzgzNl5BMl5BanBnXkFtZTgwMTMyMzM4MTI@._V1_SY1000_CR0,0,658,1000_AL_.jpg), and I'd venture a guess that we've more than a few tracks lined up... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> I can't be the only one who wants one of these for Homecoming... C'mon Sony, pretty please? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-14 15:56:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> "I don't believe this. I was actually having a really good day t'day, y'know Mr Stark?" - Peter Parker. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-12 21:37:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This line's been on my mind for the last day or so, and I'm wondering if Peter thought that maybe Tony had visited him with a view to taking him in and putting an end to his whole "Crime-Fighting Spider" routine? It'd go some way toward explaining why he was so secretive over things with someone who had clearly figured him out, and it'd make sense that Peter would be aware of the Sokovia Accords - him being a such a bright spark - and what they could mean for his new superheroic shtick?

Not that it's a huge deal, but it could certainly paint the scene where the two first meet in a new light, right? Peter's maybe a little more anxious about his visitor than we thought at first, no? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-12 21:22:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What in the blue heck is "z-metal webbing?!" </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-12 21:21:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> In comics? No...

In *Homecoming*? Maybe... What if him and May were divorced, or 
otherwise separated? Could create a **lot** of dramatic tension when it comes to Tony. Hell, maybe Ben knows he's Spidey... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-12 12:12:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Who? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-11 12:31:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Oh no, it won't be a test, it's just circumstances - believe me, if I could get a 6 or later instead I'd be all over that! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [Question] Advice for scraping by with an iPhone 3G/3GS? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-11 01:23:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So it's come to this...

I *may* soon be in the unenviable position of depending upon either of the above devices as a daily driver, for at least a couple of weeks, as a test, in a sense... I'm coming from an Android device (LG's Nexus 5X, to be specific, running Lineage), and while I'm quite capable on a technical level, I don't have a huge amount of experience with iOS.

I'm wondering what I could do t'make the most of my upcoming... experience. I'm open to hardware suggestions (I've access to a Mophie Juice Pack, for example), but for now I'm mostly interested in advice concerning software.

Anything in particular that I can/should be aware of? Any advice would be helpful, and is thoroughly appreciated in advance! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-10 21:35:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Oh man, I remember catching this clip before I saw *The Winter Soldier*, it just blew my mind that a scene featuring an arguably secondary character could be so pumped full of both action and suspense!

Really regret missing this one in cinemas... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-10 14:22:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I guess we'll have to wait and see how much focus is put on the specific device itself... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Spider-Man: Homecoming will see Peter Parker rockin' an iPhone 3G/3GS... </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-10 00:31:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> As per [these](http://www.looper.com/17116/exclusive-spider-man-homecoming-set-photos/) set photos...

What'd be the general consensus? Would there be any way t'tell whether it's a 3G or a 3GS?

Also, how in the heck would the dumpster diver extraordinaire manage t'keep such a dated device... usable? Don't suppose /r/iPhone would have any tips for the cosplaying community, no? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-09 22:11:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This is pretty great, especially when we consider combining it with DeX... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-09 21:49:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Is that what happens to *those* people? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-05 20:44:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Love the li'l Iron Man keychain!

What's up with those googles, though? How are they supposed to work? Are they some kind of welding equipment or other that Peter's repurposed, albeit in some minimal fashion? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-05 20:40:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thai place, eh? I sense a certain family dynamic coming along - not unlike the one Raimi's Pete had with the Ditkovitchs... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-05 16:02:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Here being... India? It's a pretty big place; can you be a little more specific with regard t'the services offered through WhatsApp? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-04 23:43:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What's the something, d'you reckon? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Peter's Laptop in Spider-Man: Homecoming. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-04 21:08:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> We're still not sure whether the phone Pete's sporting in trailer two is an iPhone 3G or a 3GS ([this](https://www.reddit.com/r/marvelstudios/comments/4qt3qe/peter_parker_has_an_iphone_3g_with_a_cracked/) set photo doesn't do much t'help...), but it occurred t'me today to take a look at what kinda laptop he's working with in the first trailer, [right here at 1:14](https://youtu.be/xrzXIaTt99U?t=1m14s)... Apparently it's not a Microsoft Surface, which I'd previously assumed. Anybody got any suggestions as to what kinda machine it might be? More t'the point, what the heck that thing taped t'the back of it is? The guy's gone through a *lot* of duct tape t'keep things together... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-04 17:52:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The thought crossed my mind this morning that the whole "mystery of Richard Parker" mess would've stuck around, so thankfully that's been jettisoned... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-02 22:17:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So... the Gear S2 should be receiving support, correct? Anything that'll take the place of the infamously awful S-Voice... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-01 21:55:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> From the hotel where Happy has Pete suit up, y'mean? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-30 00:49:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Quick question, actually: how do we know this is an iPhone 3G rather than a 3Gs? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-29 22:12:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Number 3, easily...

I feel like this is the one that really puts Peter's ingenuity on display; it wasn't a temporary thing 'til he put together the real costume later on, because as far as he was concerned this *was* the real costume, one that he'd committed to incrementally upgrading over time.

And then Tony Stark called... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-29 21:28:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thanks a bunch for this, much appreciated!

The funny thing is that I upvoted this at the time, apparently... :-/ </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-29 18:06:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Not a surprise though, considering they were Sony films... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-29 15:01:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What leads you t'say it's "most likely" an Xperia? The Sony thing? I really, *really* hope not, the branding relationship irritates me beyond reasonable belief in the *Bond* films... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Peter Parker's Mobile Phone... </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-29 14:42:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Did anybody manage t'catch enough of a glimpse of it during the trailer to decipher a make/model? Just curious, really, as t'what kinda device the dumpster diver finds himself rockin', since I'm something of an enthusiast. It's clearest in the scenes he shares with Stark; Pete seems t'be using it to record their conversation in the car.

It's certainly a grade or two below the lighter-than-air thing(s) that Tony himself puts to use, anyway... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-29 12:04:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> *Spider-Ganke... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-28 20:58:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Y'mean the white portions? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-28 19:22:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thank you so much for this explanation - it breaks down and details everything I asked in a clear and concise manner, I really appreciate it. :-) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-28 13:27:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> With regard to the philosophical theme you mention, I wonder would you have any links to reading material? I've only recently seen the original, and I'm interested in (eventually) watching the remake/adaptation, but I'd like to have an idea of what's missing and what's made it, if you know what I mean. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-28 13:16:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm also interested in hearing more about this... I've been thinking recently  that it might provide an environment that "protects" certain personalities, to an extent, and I'm wondering if I might be among them. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> 13.0 vs 14.1 - What Determines What? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-28 01:47:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Question in the title, really...

I'm curious as to why there's only a LOS 13.0 build available for Ghost, whereas Bullhead gets 14.1. Why bother developing for Ghost at all if it's gonna be an older version? Is it some technical limitation? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-27 18:30:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Not sure I'm totally happy with this apparent implementation of the Spider-Tracer... :-/

Really, *really* hoping my fears will prove unfounded... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-26 14:44:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [I understood that reference...](https://i.imgur.com/XS5LK.gif) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-26 12:49:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Very interesting observation, makes a lot of sense actually...

How do you propose they operate? Under what conditions do they work, say? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Quick question about the homemade suit... </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-26 01:10:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What, exactly, is the dealio with those goggles? Are they the kind welders wear, or something? They help him "focus," right?

I figured now that we've gotten those amazing images courtesy of Hot Toys, maybe we could start threading a few things together, if you'll excuse the pun... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-26 01:08:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> An eventual soft-reboot with Miles, truth be told, while keeping an older Tom Holland in the role of a more mature, adult Peter. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-25 21:31:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Absolutely *living* for the black   white cut, TBH...

How was *Mad Max: Fury Road - Black   Chrome Edition*? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-25 21:27:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I thought we rinsed/wiped 'em t'remove potential pesticides, no? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-24 21:12:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Very nice job. What's the fingerprint icon represent? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-22 19:29:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> :'-( </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-22 01:26:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> *Herc*, based on the recent *A.N.A.D.* series by Pak and Van Lente, please... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-20 21:51:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> As somebody who just discovered Caffeine via F-Droid this past weekend... *rolls eyes*

Should I go ahead and uninstall it? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-20 19:34:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Can't understand how leaving it spread out around your seat could possibly be any easier than keeping it all gathered together - hell, dumping it in the bin on the way out is optional, and even that's no effort. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-20 15:43:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Try the Science Gallery in TCD, OP; they'll either have it in stock there, or else they can direct you t'the maker shop offshoot they have 'round the corner. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-20 01:11:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Herc, based on Greg Pak and Fred van Lente's recent *A.N.A.D.* run, please... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-20 00:54:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's something t'do with BootMagic Check Fail, but I've no idea what that is, there doesn't seem t'be a clear consensus among the threads I've found... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-20 00:53:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> And how, exactly, does one go about accessing Download Mode? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-19 15:15:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thank you! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-19 15:05:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So... How does one go about pronouncing Dora Milaje, exactly? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-18 21:33:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> There's almost nothing in your post that I'd disagree with, OP, apart from the overarching fact that Hercules should get a solo Netflix series first, then, maybe, an introduction t'the team. It could be just like his most recent *A.N.A.D.* solo run... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> LOS on the HTC One (M8) - First Things First... </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-18 20:38:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hey all, absolutely loving the ROM on my Nexus 5x, not to mention my Nexus 7, and I'm encouraging others to jump aboard where they can, so kudos t'the devs for all of their hard work and support.

I've been hoping to install the ROM on my sister's unused HTC One (M8), which currently lacks an OS. I've got an unlocked bootloader, but that's about as far as I've managed to get. I can't seem to install TWRP, as fastboot throws up an error message. My understanding is that I'm limited to installing .img files rather than .zips via fastboot, at least until I can get an OS up and running on the damn thing, at which point I can flash a custom recovery and then every .zip I could ever want.

Anybody got any advice as to what my next steps should be? I'd hugely appreciate the help, as I have with everything the LineageOS community has provided thus far.

Cheers folks, many thanks in advance. :-) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-18 19:35:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So amped for this movie it doesn't bear thinking... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-17 18:24:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The homemade suit... Please, Funko, release a version without the mask... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-15 23:18:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I might be alone in thinking this, but I *really* hope *Spider-Man: Homecoming* gets its own "Music from and Inspired by" album... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-15 20:09:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm confused by [this](https://youtu.be/yJ-HwrOpIps) video's explanation as to how Archimedes established his limits for pi. Where did the 1/71 and 1/70 figures come from? Why stop at 96 lines? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-15 12:39:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If, hypothetically, I've was interested in such a feature...

[http://i.imgur.com/T9qGuiN.gif](http://i.imgur.com/T9qGuiN.gif) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-13 21:06:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Timely post, OP; I'll be very interested in seeing cosplays of the homemade suit Pete had prior t'the one Tony gifted him with... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-12 15:13:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The same reason that *Captain America: The First Avenger* wasn't released on the fourth of July, I'm guessing... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-12 15:04:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What kinda work, may I ask? Retail? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-12 14:45:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You seem to be describing the film as having events occurring to quickly, one after another. I felt this way about both *Civil War* and *Doctor Strange*. I think it's a symptom of many films, upon second and subsequent viewings, especially if you enjoyed them so much the first time 'round. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-12 14:38:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Is there any way I can swap between paying via card and paying via my service provider? For example, I might want a one-off app purchase t'be charged to my card, but I'd be happy t'let a Google Play Music subscription be charged t'my Three credit on the same day of the month that I top up...

Can you select a payment method on the fly, as it were? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-12 14:30:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> No need to apologise. I understand what you're describing - I think a similar effect was employed by the Tom Cruise's crew in *Minority Report* -  I'm afraid I'm not able to replicate it, though... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-12 13:58:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Any chance of a .gif demonstrating this feature, /u/Tomjr78? I'm afraid I'm not quite getting what you're saying, assuming I'm understanding you correctly... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-12 00:21:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm likely t'get downvoted for this, but I always get a kick outta the couple of seconds waiting for Miles' venom-sting t'kick in... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-11 17:20:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Don't suppose there's a particular guide to implementing/using Magisk that you could recommend, no? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-10 20:54:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Is there an official one? I mentioned it to a dev on here at one point, they seemed very receptive of the feedback... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-10 19:00:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I messaged the devs about it before. Still no sign? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-08 13:37:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Not the Nextbit Robin, apparently...  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-08 13:34:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Can I ask what courses you have tried? Thinking about pursuing something through these courses, don't wanna find myself wasting my time... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
