<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject2260</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-09 21:56:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Mad Squablz. Here's a video him rapping to five different old school beats. https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=qebD742D3Ms </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-09 21:40:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Butt stuff. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What stupid questions do people ask you on a regular basis? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-07 05:47:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-04 21:10:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'd argue Darkness Falls. The opening scared the hell out of me, but afterwards it's a piece of shit. I think it would've worked splendidly as a short film based on the first 10 min. It would go viral quick. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-04 21:07:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> When they shoehorn a lazy romance plot into the mix when it doesn't belong. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-04 21:05:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Convince people that there are more than two options in a given election.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What's the best example of "facts don't care about your feelings" that you've seen in the real world? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-02 18:54:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-01 22:06:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Just play with my hair and my legs will start thumping like a dog getting his belly rubbed.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-30 20:16:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The cameraman who insists on talking and commentating during the entire fucking video. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-30 20:14:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> DJ Khaled. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-30 20:06:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Going outside in general. I'm pasty-white, and under certain lights my arms look very red or pinkish. I look like a walking piece of cotton candy and people always ask if I'm sunburnt, but I'm not.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-26 02:12:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> John Carpenter's The Thing. My brother and I watch it every Christmas. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-25 06:04:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The touch of a beautiful woman. Rarely happens though.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-24 19:19:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That's a perfect example! I neglected to explain a crucial component of exposure therapy, which is a ranking system where you rank things that cause you anxiety on a scale of 0-100 (higher being more anxiety-provoking). 

You're supposed to start on the lower end and work your way up as you go. Going to that party was definitely up there. But yeah, keep at it, man. Be consistent, work your way up, and eventually you'll be unstoppable! 

Feel free to pm me if you want to talk about it more. I've been doing this for 4 years now and it's changed my life significantly. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-24 19:14:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Consider me jealous. She's a keeper for that reason alone. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-24 18:57:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Exposure therapy, which basically means putting yourself in anxiety-provoking situations. 

One time in college I went to a party where I knew absolutely no one. I didn't drink, smoke weed or anything that would've taken the edge off. As the night went on, I felt more comfortable and even started talking to some very nice people.

It's scary at first, but keep doing what scares you most and you'll make great progress. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-24 18:48:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I was hanging out with a girl I liked at the time. She was trying to get frisky, but I was too fixated on the tv because The Dark Knight was on.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-19 20:37:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Woody Harrelson. Rampart: The Sequel </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-19 20:21:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Tool. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-19 20:20:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Craft beer bottles. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-19 20:11:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> According to Wikipedia: 1926  Harry Houdini performs his greatest feat, spending 91 minutes underwater in a sealed tank before escaping. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Besides your birth, what historical event(s) took place on your birthday? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-19 19:57:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
