<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject9931</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> E-cigarette study in mice finds weight gain and lung damage linked to glycerine exposure </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-10 10:02:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-09 05:44:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> My SO did environmental science, but double majored in maths and stats (1 major) and ecology.
She has never been out of work. She has changed jobs 3 times (by choice). Always worked for govt/ngo/research institute. She has been offered consulting/ industry jobs but turned them down.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-09 03:02:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This comment is pretty much spot on. It sounds like the ACCC argued that when used as intended then the seller's claims are wrong. E-cigs are basically an evaporation condensation aerosol generator. So the thermal processes that occur are slightly similar to smoking. And produce similar compounds - albeit at much, much lower levels. 
If you had a purely mechanical (e.g. compressed air powered) nebuliser for e-juice you wouldn't get these chemicals.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-09 02:58:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I was involved in the study that (also) produced the results for the ACCC. We definitely didn't produce bogus results or overheat the coils. The settings we used were guided by friends who vape and forums like this one. I will put up a link to the full study when it is published.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-18 11:24:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> No most German bread is usually wholegrain, dark, heavy bread. Made with Rye, or old fashioned grains like dinkel. A lot have seeds or whole grains in the bread or on top. 
They have some light breads - usually treated with caustic soda to give them a hard shiny crust.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-18 11:21:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yes that must have been it.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-21 13:12:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> "ceaseless incontinence of free speech"  I need to work that into daily conversation. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-20 05:59:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Nice work. I came here to say that too.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-17 08:28:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yes (styrene), however that is not the worst part - see my post above.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-17 08:27:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That is a real possibility. Black ink/toner uses carbon black that has been produced in a sub-stoichiometric natural gas flame, so is full of a bunch of stuff like PAHs that are not great for you. 

It is very similar to diesel soot - which is a group 1 carcinogen according to the IARC.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-16 19:08:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I doubt you would survive a year in Denver without building a cabin. 
My strongest memory was one visit when there was 3' of snow and gale force winds that arrived all of a sudden in **mid April**! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-14 15:53:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> 10% per day here. So 10 days late, no marks even if it is perfect. 

EDIT: However my rule has generally been that if it has been handed in by the time I start marking the assignment then I won't apply a penalty.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-14 15:51:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I get your point, however having a standard policy around assessment extensions doesn't mean that the teaching staff are any less hands on with the students or any less in touch with their individual needs.
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-14 07:59:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Very cool. Looks like wheelbarrow wheels? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-14 07:52:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> In some ways I agree, however the theory is:

* It reduces administrative workloads from academics
* It removes inconsistencies in granting extensions </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-14 02:40:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The engineers I know who work in signal processing or noise and vibration use it every day.

I had 2 PhDs once, one did his PhD modelling and data processing in Matlab, the other used ridiculously complex excel macros for a similar task. 

Both ended up working for companies who didn't have excel licences.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-14 02:40:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The engineers I know who work in signal processing or noise and vibration use it every day.

I had 2 PhDs once, one did his PhD modelling and data processing in Matlab, the other used ridiculously complex excel macros for a similar task. 

Both ended up working for companies who didn't have Matlab licences. 
EDIT: typed wrong word </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-14 02:19:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Sorry. Too vague. Here it would either be denied or they would be referred to the university counsellor to get a medical certificate if the counsellor deemed the "personal reasons" sufficiently serious.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-14 02:17:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Where I am, all extension requests need to be referred to an admin officer who has a list of acceptable reasons and requires proof.  

"Overcommitted" is not on that list.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-14 02:15:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Open Source is the future...  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-14 02:14:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> As a professor, I can say that that guy was an Arsehole.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-14 02:13:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> **Lots** of professional engineers use Matlab every day for work. Many don't though - either because the field doesn't need it or their company won't pay the licence fees. 
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-14 02:10:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Indeed. However where I am we are only supposed to allocate 1hr per student per course for marking and feedback. So I can understand how people may adopt this approach to reduce an already strained workload. 

EDIT: Mainly for this reason I am glad I no longer teach classes... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-14 02:08:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This is the real LPT. Also the earlier the better. Not just a few hours before it is due. 

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
