<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject5571</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> New Zealand to scrap blasphemy crime after Garda investigation </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-10 13:27:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> New Zealand to scrap blasphemy crime after Garda investigation </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-10 13:27:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> New Zealand to scrap blasphemy crime after Garda investigation </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-10 13:27:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-10 13:24:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> As in I don't have an issue with advertisements with kids toys. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-10 13:24:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I think its a grey area. I agree with you on the whole diminished cognitive ability but at the same time I don't have an issue with kids toys etc. It's when kids shows and sports are suddenly sponsored by chocolate and soft drinks and alcohol. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-10 12:17:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hopefully but it's not always the case. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-10 12:01:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I think you're probably right. I imagine that most teens who are obese are so from a young enough age. However, and this is only anecdotal so it proves nothing, I see about 5% of our first years who have come in rather healthy looking and gain a lot of weight by 6th year. But that's just anecdotal. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-10 11:56:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  We all know what cheese is

Actually maybe that's an overstatement. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-10 11:54:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> How do we educate them? I completely agree with you but people say "This should be taught in schools" when schools already does plenty on this. And to be fair, these healthy eating programs etc largely do nothing if they go home and their family life does not promote healthy eating. Healthy eating is decided at home by parents. Making healthy foods more accessible and attractive to parents should be a priority. 

I'm not blaming parents. I just think that fast food and unhealthy options are allowed too much room to look attractive and "easy" to families and the government does little to deal with corporations. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-10 11:50:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Part of that is how it affects kids when they are young so that when they are teenagers and have purchasing power they have already been influenced to buy their products. It sounds very tinfoil hat but its actually whats going on. Also, some primary kids do buy stuff. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-10 11:48:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> One is Cheese, we all know what cheese is, the other is something advertised as healthy but isn't. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-10 11:42:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I get you, but anecdotal evidence doesn't really prove anything. Individual stories don't show that something is true or false. The larger scientific studies done on exposure to this type of advertising show that there is a negative impact being made on young people. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-10 11:25:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> There has to be moderation, and reason. There's a difference between fatty cheese and a sugary drink that's labelled "fruit juice" </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-10 11:23:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> * Category 1: Unhealthy (banned)
* Category 2: Manky (banned for under 18's)
* Category 3: Healthy but Manky (parental guidance - anything you buy from Longford)
* Category 4: Healthy  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-10 11:20:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I get you, I don't like the idea of a nanny state but what I believe a nanny state is may be different. When it comes to interfering with parents then I'm against it. But the fact that a child interested in sports cannot get away from Alcohol sponsorship in this country  is mad.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-10 11:18:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I can't tell whether that's sarcasm. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-10 11:18:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah I imagine there are going to be some crazy loopholes. Coke: unhealthy, Coke Zero: Healthy </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-10 10:35:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Absolutely, I mean its a good step of course but there's still a lot to be done. Why its seen as acceptable for Diageo to sponsor sporting events is beyond me. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-10 10:34:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Of course, that's an exception. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-10 09:59:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I wasn't expecting this [so soon](https://i.redd.it/3ah6k9okldoy.jpg) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Ireland first country to restrict unhealthy food sponsorship aimed at children </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-10 09:53:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-10 00:56:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Wow. Maybe I have to be American to get it but that's not right. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-10 00:38:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I imagine some fraternities almost become.like universities themselves then in terms of potential career opportunities. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-10 00:22:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Ah. Very clear. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-10 00:22:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Right. How? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-10 00:22:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Do they play any significant role in life after college? For example, I'm an alumnus of my university but that doesn't really mean anything here. Is there still a connection it has fraternities? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> As a non American I find the concept of college fraternities strange, what is the cultural significance for people? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-10 00:08:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-09 17:10:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Sure aren't we all tax paying donkeys? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Over 70 donkeys face death as Donegal sanctuary struggles </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-09 16:43:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Over 70 donkeys face death as Donegal sanctuary struggles </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-09 16:41:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-09 11:23:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It is a difficult question to answer. I guess it comes down to your own convictions and what you believe is right. I believe that whether a person is good or bad has nothing to do with membership of an organisation, a person's morality is a complex thing that is always evolving.

Like you, I would like to see a point where these groups are entirely separate from the state. I think that could only go to benefit the people, as well as the church and state themselves. No good is coming from the current situation. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-09 11:09:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That's it for sure. Its much easier to blame the Church as the sole perpetrators, probably the worst but they didn't act alone.

I imagine there were a whole range of people who failed the children, the State, Church, Schools, Hospitals, the Media etc. Its a can of worms nobody really wants to open. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-09 11:06:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I assume you're being tongue in cheek there. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-09 11:05:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I think it's their lack of willingness to recognise these sort of things is whats really damaging them. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-09 10:51:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  This had nothing to do with Catholicism but is simply something that happens in poor societies. 

I don't know if i fully agree there. Yes, there is truth in that but the Catholic system (along with many other religions) allowed for this to go on. I don't think abuse and Catholicism go hand in hand but the Church was the body that largely oversaw this abuse and I don't think it had nothing to do with them.

 the Irish Catholic Church was a reflection of the values of the time. 

I agree, but again they were part of a larger body who we now know knew (say that ten times) about it. I agree it isn't right to lump it all on the church because that lets a lot of other bad people off the hook, but I don't agree that it has nothing to do with the organisation. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-09 10:44:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You had one pick and you chose Madonna. For Christ sake. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-09 10:31:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> There is merit to what you're saying, and the Church has clearly done something to anger you and you're entitled to that. But I think there needs to be a separation between what is the Church as an institution and the individual. There are people working in the organisation, maybe only a small amount, that have done good for people because they are kind, hard working people, not necessarily because they are in the church itself. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-09 10:27:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  Stop acting like cunts if you don't want to be remembered as cunts.

Can't argue with that really. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-09 10:27:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Who would we even want? And sure isn't everyone Irish really? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-09 10:04:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Also, perhaps have a look at r/IrishTourism. There's an archived post [here](https://www.reddit.com/r/irishtourism/comments/2yr1dh/visa_application_advice_rireland/). </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-09 10:01:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It doesn't look like it matters that you are coming from a Visa required country. Have a look [here](http://www.inis.gov.ie/en/INIS/Pages/apply-for-asylum).

The Asylum process should be, by and large, the same coming from most countries, although I'm not an expert on this. would imagine what matters is your situation. Hope it works out. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-09 09:49:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You know what, I'm tempted to say something similar but I think there is truth here. The horrible deeds and missteps of the organisation has completely undermined any good done by smaller groups or people. Citizens have a right to vent and be mad but I do worry that the likes of Peter McVerry, who has done more good than anyone I know, might suffer in the backlash. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Catholic Church's good deeds are being erased, says archbishop </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-09 09:45:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> ASTI stance is affecting school choice, principals say </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-09 09:44:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-08 20:11:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That's true, I should have changed the title a little. Goes to show how often other countries do it. I didn't realise Joe made that mistake so often though. I'd be mortified and never do it again. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-08 19:33:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That's true, sorry for implying that you were a fool. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-08 19:23:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Ah man that's the one. Have you still got it? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-08 19:22:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Excellent work </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-08 17:51:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> https://youtu.be/EUy8rGVK2_o just at the very end. Really uncomfortable. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-08 16:45:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Should we call it article 32? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-08 16:35:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Good man. A a hearty handshake to you. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-08 16:34:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Two rather frightening men right there, all they need is Christian Bale. Christ working on that Batman film must've been a nightmare. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-08 16:32:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It has gotten a bit stale regarding TV shows but at the same time I agree with you. The clueless middle age guy going off somewhere foreign and being shite at it is an age old staple across all forms of TV. Its not Top standard television but its easy to watch (as long as you like the comedians)
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-08 16:30:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  His Alanis Morrisette joke was his Zenith.

You don't see that everyday </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-08 16:30:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I thought it was the Observer that started the famine, the Guardian was the one the ordered the assassination the Kaiser no? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-08 16:25:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Have changed thank you. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-08 16:19:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> More importantly, he's from Cork. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-08 16:18:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Rice crispies? No man the cornflakes one. Just A white bowl with a chicken on it. I would've given my left leg for the Snap Crackle and Pop one. *sigh* </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-08 16:16:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> He might be offered as part of Brexit negotiations. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-08 16:11:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I don't mind him as much as the likes of Jason Byrne or Delamere. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-08 16:10:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Is that what you get for being his best man? Christ I would have done that if I'd known. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> A selective list of Irish figures claimed as British by media in recent times. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-08 16:06:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> **Saoirse Ronan** 

* Sky News reporter Richard Suchet called Saoirse Ronan one of our own when she received a BAFTA nomination for her performance in Brooklyn.

* London Film Critics Circle (LFCC) nominated Saorise Ronan for Best British Actress.

**Seamus Heaney**

* Heaney  was famously included in The Penguin Book of Contemporary British Poetry. He responded to his complimentary inclusion like this:

*Be advised my passport's green.*

*No glass of ours was ever raised to toast the Queen.*


**Michael Fassbender, Colin Farrell   Brendan Gleeson**

* The London Film Critics Circle (LFCC) also nominated Fassbender, Farrell and Gleeson in their British categories. After the instant protests the LFCC reluctantly relabeled those categories as British and Irish.

**Emma Donoghue**

* The novelist and screenplay writer was nominated in the Breakthrough British Filmmaker of the Year category for "Room"

**Chris O Dowd**

* In 2001 during a red carpet interview for the BIFA Awards, Chris ODowd was referred to as a [British Actor](https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=71yVRPr4o4k) :

*Coming from being a British actor and working on something like Bridesmaids.*

*Irish actor, yep.*

*Irish actor, I apologise.*

**Conor McGregor**

* During a pre - Aldo fight interview, UFC president Dana White referred to McGregor as being from the UK.

*All of Brazil will be watching him defend his title [points to Jose Aldo], all of the UK will be watching (points to Conor McGregor).*

*Ireland will be watching.*

*Ireland, Ireland. I thought that was the same thing, apparently not.*

*It is most certainly not.*

**Cillian Murphy** 

* Cillian Murphy during an Interview for Inception

*You both are British*

*No, Im Irish.*

*Yeah I know, British.*

*No, no, no, Im Irish.*

*Oh, sorry.*

**Ruth Negga** 

* Negga was called a "British Rising Star" by Telegraph and Evening standard for her role in "Loving"

**Golfer Paul Dunne**

* BBC commentator Eddie Pepperell labelled him as British during the British Open recently

**Domhnall Gleeson**

* GQ, The Guardian, the Evening Standard and the Daily Mail have all praised his performance in a Burberry Advert referring to him as a British Actor.
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-08 15:45:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Do you not remember collecting the Kellog's Cornflakes tokens? He just collected a bunch of them and that's how he got the job. I only ever got a decorative bowl. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-08 15:15:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Wait, don't tell me they had something to do with the famine?!? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The Guardian calls Dara  Briain a 'white British' man </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-08 15:10:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> EPA fires members of science advisory board </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-08 11:19:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> EPA fires members of science advisory board </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-08 11:18:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The Teachers' Forum: A place to seek advice and share your experience </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-08 09:49:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> * Are you a newly qualified teacher looking for advice on the job?

* Are you simply looking to get in to the profession?

* Are you a wise owl looking to pass on your wealth of experience?

The Teachers' Forum is a place to share any useful tips you may have picked up along the way and seek help for those little things and big things too, speak your mind!
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-08 00:11:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm also anti people. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> I'm anti-gun because I live in a country that bans them but if moved to the states I would feel very unsafe without one. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-08 00:04:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Social media should have a "do not like" setting so that you don't like something accidentally. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-07 00:41:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-06 15:45:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> "I'm sure they would love to join Boyzlife" [citation needed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Keith Duffy: 'I'm sure they would love to join Boyzlife but we haven't invited them' </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-06 15:42:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-06 15:34:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> And if they don't it won't be followed through by the state. It's just procedure right now. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-06 15:03:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Also it's bollox. I imagine Fry will find this more amusing that anything. I doubt our state attorney will choose to prosecute. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-06 15:03:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Absolutely. No one was happy with this being done. I believe it to be another example of our state's continued fear of tackling the church on anything real. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-06 14:59:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Apparently it was brought in to act as as a stopgap. It was meant to be used as a means to get rid of the old legislation we had but so far nothing has been done. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-06 13:44:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> He's been a very naughty boy. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Garda launch blasphemy probe into Stephen Fry comments on 'The Meaning of Life' </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-06 13:16:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-06 13:12:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's not even an old law either which is what I really can't wrap my head around. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-06 13:10:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Will that be rounded up to 0.05? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-06 13:08:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I know. I thought it was am error when I saw it first. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-06 13:08:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That's blasphemous. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-06 13:07:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That's a fair point. I know plenty of people with great faith (not myself) who would never consider doing this because they don't feel the need to impose their faith on others through law. How sensitive is this person that they can't allow someone else to have a different opinion on their faith?

Would love to be there when Fry was told. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-06 12:25:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> IMO it reads like someone trying to show how ridiculous the law is. The person who filed the complaint said that he wasn't personally offended but that it simply qualified as blasphemy under the law. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Garda launch blasphemy probe into Stephen Fry comments in the Meaning if Life </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-06 12:21:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-06 00:13:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's not?!?! Then what's this all been for?

Simpson memes that's what. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-06 00:11:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I know what you mean. It's really hard to put into words because, while I really do not support this man or his views, I think he has done a good thing and deserves credit for that. Too many people have to fall on either he's scum or he's a great wonderful man. He's not. He's human like the rest of us. Not one I like but he seems to be doing some good. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-05 14:38:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I know, I think this should have received more coverage. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-05 14:37:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Imagine how pissed Leo would be if he presided over the country as Taoiseach and the repeal of the 8th amendment and WW3 starts.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-05 14:36:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I was at a wave pool with family and went to the bathroom before the wave machine turned on. When I came back out, everyone in the pool was watching their kids in the water making sure they were safe. However, at the other end of the pool in no more than a foot of water was a kid that nobody saw, on his back having an epileptic seizure under the water.

I ran and grabbed him to pull him out. The pool hall was incredibly loud and so I found myself shouting for about 2 minutes straight trying to get the attention of someone. Eventually another kid turned around and grabbed a life guard who then resuscitated the kid. In the end he was taken away by an ambulance but he was ok. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-05 14:31:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Christ that's a difficult situation to be put in. While I don't know what your president has in store for you all next I wish you all  the best. Stay well. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-05 14:26:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I know what your opinion is but you've told me to keep my opinions out of a title. I take that as an instruction. Look if you don't agree with me fine but people are going to post how they please as long as it doesn't break the forum rules.

Having said that, I understand that its a forum and nobody is being forced one way or another. I do apologise if my previous comments were somewhat antagonistic. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-05 14:24:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Having an LGBT Irish/Indian Leader might make for some big headlines internationally. Could give the country a bit of spotlight. Also could have no effect whatsoever... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-05 14:16:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> And you are more than entitled to your opinion on that but you don't have any authority to enforce your opinions here. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-05 14:15:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I feel sorry for them as much as anyone else. To have voted for him they must have felt so ignored by the establishment. Imagine thinking that your prayers had been answered and the new president hits you harder than the last one. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-05 14:13:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Good point, I had always wondered how Leo would get votes from within his own party when he's been so eager to give a soundbite at the cost of one of his own.

Ive noticed of late his reluctance to comment as much on trivial matters (as opposed to when he was in sport and would offer opinions on anything but) It must be for that reason. He's in with a good chance at this point I would imagine. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-05 14:10:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Was this something just taken on to step on Obama? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-05 14:09:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I would be interested to see how much of his voter base are losing benefits to this.

I meant if there is more money to spend elsewhere it might help his appearance by spending the money on something people like, like a wall? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-05 14:08:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Well said.[citation needed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-05 14:07:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Absolutely. The staff are usually quite good but its the system they use, nothing seems to be in communication.

Also you shouldn't have to justify being on it, if we demonize everyone for being in a difficult situation for a certain period of their life then were in trouble. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-05 14:05:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This subreddit is full of Titles with opinions. People talking about how nice the weather is, what songs they like.

What you mean is keep opinions you don't agree with out of here so you don't have to see it. That's a shame. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-05 13:54:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> How will this affect those who are currently insured? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-05 13:53:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah I understand that argument but you can't legislate for assholes, it isn't possible.

I imagine on the whole most people are just hard done by. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
