<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject3856</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-10 10:00:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I've never tried e-books and probably won't, their is just something I enjoy about seeing a bookmark slowly move through the book. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> I can't be the only one who hates reading books they don't own. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-10 09:55:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If I read a book or want to read a book I have to buy it, I'm not a fan of using library's as I like to display a book before and after I finish reading it. I don't just want to give it back when I'm done

Its strange and I'm the only one i know like it.

Anyone else like this? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-08 11:18:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> conner 4 real

from popstar never stop never stopping

that would be a great MD storyline </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-05 11:09:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> nope, i didn't make it. I found it on the cynicle brit official reddit and posted it here </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-05 10:35:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I've never actually heard of GMG until now. All my games come from steam or GOG </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> You wouldn't buy on G2A </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-05 09:55:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Code Vein - First Trailer (Weeaboo Souls) </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-02 11:42:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Am I the only one who thought this weeks monster look a lot like the one from the Torchwood episode "Meat" </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-30 14:14:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Just the shape, size and even the moans it makes just reminds me so much of the one in Torchwood. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-29 06:49:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thank you so much. I didn't even think of the ease she took out the guards, thanks for pointing that out to me.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [FEEDBACK] - The Pilot (Comedy, 23 pgs) </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-29 06:46:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hi guys, I have just completed my very first script. It is a mockumentary called "The Pilot" where we follow a newbie show runner Charlie as he creates the Pilot.

Because this is my first script I would like feedback on all aspects. Thanks for any and all feedback.

P.s be super harsh.

https://drive.google.com/open?id=0B-UNTLTkYWWbMlhPVl9GajZxQWc </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-29 05:24:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Book depository, its cheaper than anything here in Australia and its free shipping, win win.

Only issue is, it can be 2 - 3 weeks before i get my book </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> New to screenwriting. Is this a decent opening page? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-28 11:56:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I am about a month into writing scripts and was wondering if this opening scene is a good opening for a pilot I'm working on. 

The idea behind the pilot is time travel, the main part will take place in 2018 but this opening is about getting access to the time machine in 2047.

Thanks for any feedback.

https://drive.google.com/file/d/0B-UNTLTkYWWbUUl1bFk1ZndCY2s/view?usp=sharing </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-27 02:37:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I never had any luck with girls up until this point. I was 14 or 15 and this girl and I where in scouts together. I had a huge crush on her, when we went on one of out scout camps i decided that this was going to be the time to ask her out, problem was I couldn't find the right moment. 

On the second day of the camp just after we had done a bunch of aquatic activities in the lake my friend and I decided we should get a shower. Now before i go any further the showers where set up weirdly, basically there was a boys and a girls shower room, each of the rooms had 4 cubicles. But the rooms where seperted by a thin wall with a gap at the top so we could hear everything the girls where saying. My friend and I where having out showers when we heard the girl i had a crush on talking to her friends, I said stuff it and asked her out then and there. All her friends heard and my friend just couldn't stop laughing. She said no, while her friends where giggling in the background. The rest of the camp was awkward. 

But 5 years later she is not dating one of my best friends and they still bring the story up every now and then so it ended fine.

I learnt never to ask a girl out in the shower </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
