<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject4121</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Sup? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-10 15:18:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-09 19:07:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Kids.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-09 16:17:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The dad from 7th Heaven  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-09 14:54:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> "We love to fight and it shows" </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-08 23:54:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> They were in the 50s and 60s. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-08 18:32:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> They ALL suck, friendo.
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-08 18:20:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I can't stand any of them, whether it's Clinton, Obama, Trump, Sanders doesn't matter. They are all scum in various forms. They work together behind closed doors and promote discourse and tribalism via a failed 2 party system in order to divide and distract us from the fact we could be living such better lives if those parasites didn't suck us dry and use us as expendable pawns.

anonhq.com/gaddafis-threat-to-the-us-petro-dollar-and-why-he-had-to-die/

m.youtube.com/watch?v=wha9lTKN7Zg

theguardian.com/commentisfree/cifamerica/2011/apr/21/libya-muammar-gaddafi

herald.co.zw/petrodollar-system-fuelling-us-sanctions-of-mass-destruction/


Edit: I do like one mainstream person and that's Tulsi Gabbard.  She is a bad ass.
   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-08 17:49:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> gross </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-08 17:49:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I bet that would still happen today. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-08 17:43:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Unfortunately, yes. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-08 16:56:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This is amazing. How can I help? I have a lot of free time because I don't do anything.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-08 16:46:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> http://m.washingtontimes.com/news/2015/oct/20/hillary-clinton-state-department-approved-us-weapo/ </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-08 16:45:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> http://www.activistpost.com/2015/10/hillary-clinton-the-killing-of-ghaddafi-and-the-destruction-of-libya.html </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-08 16:45:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yup </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-08 16:42:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> http://original.antiwar.com/justin/2016/03/03/libya-how-hillary-clinton-destroyed-a-country/ 

"2012 Hillary Clinton Supplied Weapons from Benghazi to Al-Qaeda in Syria

I am not sure if people here know what really is going on with Hillarie's investigation and i thought everyone knew about it but it seems a lot of people are still in the dark. So i will go ahead and refresh everyones memory with a short description. 

I am not sure if you know what really is going on but the real issue are not the emails and having a private server with confidential documents (which is also serious). The real issue is what the emails uncovered about Benghazi. Hillary and the Obama administration supplied weapons from Benghazi to Al-Qaeda in Syria. The weapons shipped during late-August 2012 were Sniper rifles, RPGs, and 125 mm and 155mm howitzers missiles pdf. Then those missiles were used against US soldiers. Upon investigating the situation the congress found the serial numbers of the missiles and they tracked them coming from a CIA banker in Qatar. Then Hillary and Obama tried to retrieve the evidence and the other missiles but the terrorists blackmailed them. So they paid the blackmail and send ambassador Steven to retrieve the missiles, then i am not sure what went down (assume the terrorists were greedy) but Stevens got killed. 

The rest you know... Hillary blamed a video and Obama used his power to cover up the rest. Congress knows what happened, and they fought hard to get the evidence (or whatever Comey did not destroy so far) but they came short when it came for the other gov branches to do their job and take them to court. 

And Hillary also got paid to help some businesses receive contracts and benefits in Libya. This was discovered in the emails by that reporter (forgot name) that exchanged a lot of emails with Hillary. 

The media knew about this stuff, which makes sense why they went all in on this election. There's a video that Gowdy Trey basically shit on the media and letting it assume that its their fault for having the job to reveal this to the people but failed to do so. Trey Gowdy On Media

Also they paid the blackmail with taxpayer money ( i think its the first blackmail ever payed by the USA, the one that supposedly was paid on exchange for US citizens captured by the terrorists which i think we never got) - this is my personal opinion. U.S. Concedes $400 Million Payment to Iran Was Delayed as Prisoner Leverage 

Edit: i forgot to mention what was the piece that put everything together and let to this truth. It turns out that a stupid monkey terrorist did not know how to use the missile (i think he insert it backwards - don't remember) and he left the half blown pieces on the ground and thankfully the serial number was not destroyed. 

Clinton - the Saudis have exported more extreme ideology than any other place on earth"
October 2013 WS speech in which Clinton acknowledged that the Saudis have exported more extreme ideology than any other place on earth over the course of the last 30 years. 

Clinton - Trying To Vet, Identify, Train And Arm Cadres Of Rebels
In that same speech, Clinton noted that she wanted to pursue a more robust, covert action trying to vet, identify, train and arm cadres of rebels in Syria, that would have fought both the government of President Bashar al-Assad and the Al-Qaeda-related jihadist groups that have, unfortunately, been attracted to Syria. 

Benghazi - Security Support Team reduction
State Department officials in Libya apparently understood the dangers. As noted in the Interim Progress Report, on several occasions in 2012 Ambassador Stevens and others at the U.S. embassy stressed within the Department of State the inadequacy of security in Libya and outlined the need for additional personnel.39 In fact, however, in the weeks before the attack there was a decrease in the modest U.S. military presence there. For many months, there was a sixteen-person Special Forces unit, known as the Security Support Team or the Site Security Team (SST), at the embassy in Tripoli. This unit was involved with protecting the U.S. compound. In August 2012, however, DOD briefed that at the request of the Department of 40 State, this unit was reduced to four personnel and their focus changed to training Libyan forces. General Ham told the committee that this reduction and transition was done despite his offer to retain the larger number. 

Benghazi - President was informed of the "Terrorist Attack"
Defense Department officials believed nearly from the outset of violence in Benghazi that it was a terrorist attack rather than a protest gone awry, and the President subsequently permitted the military to respond with minimal direction. 

Clinton/Podesta - U.S. saw the rise of the genocidal Islamic State as an opportunity
Responding to the strategy outlined in the notes, Podesta said, I think we are headed down this path in Iraq. But Syria elements are vexing, he added. 

Agree but there may be opportunities as the Iraqi piece improves, Clinton wrote back.

The message also reveals that the U.S. saw the rise of the genocidal Islamic State as an opportunity. With all of its tragic aspects, the advance of ISIL through Iraq gives the U.S. Government an opportunity to change the way it deals with the chaotic security situation in North Africa and the Middle East, the document says, adding, The most important factor in this matter is to make use of intelligence resources and Special Operations troops in an aggressive manner. 

Report by the Citizens Commission On Benghazi 

The war in Libya was unnecessary, served no articulable U.S. national security objective, and led to preventable chaos region-wide. 

Muammar Qaddafi was an ally of the United States in the Global War on Terror. 

The U.S. facilitated the delivery of weapons and military support to al Qaeda- linked rebels in Libya. 

The Citizens Commission on Benghazi (CCB) has discovered, that the ensuing civil war may well have been avoided, had the U.S. chosen to permit it. 

Qaddafi expressed interest in a truce, and possible abdication and exile out of Libya. He even pulled his forces back from several Libyan cities as a sign of good faith. 

No positive affirmation of consent from Washington, D.C. to pursue Qaddafis offer. The war continued and ultimately cost tens of thousands of lives. The U.S. failure to even consider Qaddafis request for talks, and its determination to enter and pursue this war in support of al-Qaeda-linked rebels, presents the appearance of a policy intent upon empowering Islamic forces with no measurable benefit to U.S. national security. 

The White House campaign appears to have been well-coordinated with U.S. Muslim Brotherhood organizations as well as Islamic state members of the Organization of Islamic Cooperation (OIC), who all joined in condemnation of the video, and, even more troubling, issued calls for restrictions on Americans free speech rights. 

On the day of the attacks in Benghazi, whether or not there was an official order to stand down, the result was the same. There were military assets, for example, at the U.S. base in Sigonella, in Sicily, Italy that could have been brought to bear, and perhaps could have saved the lives of the two men killed at the CIA Annex, the scene of the second attack that night. The failure to attempt to rescue these Americans amounts to a dereliction of duty. 

The U.S. was fully aware of and facilitating the delivery of weapons to the al-Qaeda-dominated rebel militias throughout the 2011 rebellion. The jihadist agenda of AQIM, the Libyan Islamic Fighting Group (LIFG), and other Islamic terror groups represented among the rebel forces was well known to U.S. officials responsible for Libya policy. 

The White House and senior Congressional members deliberately and knowingly pursued a policy that provided material support to terrorist organizations in order to topple a ruler who had been working closely with the West actively to suppress al-Qaeda. The result in Libya, across much of North Africa, and beyond has been utter chaos, disruption of Libyas oil industry, the spread of dangerous weapons (including surface-to-air missiles), and the empowerment of jihadist organizations like al-Qaeda and the Muslim Brotherhood. 

After Qaddafis regime had been ousted, a delegation from the United Arab Emirates (UAE) traveled to Libya to collect payment for the weapons the UAE had financed and Qatar had delivered to the Transitional National Council (TNC) during the war. The UAE delegation was seeking $1 billion it claimed was owed. During their visit to Tripoli, the UAE officials discovered that half of the $1 billion worth of weapons it had financed for the rebels had, in fact, been diverted by Mustafa Abdul Jalil, the Muslim Brotherhood head of the Libyan TNC, and sold to Qaddafi. 

Clinton - Benghazi Emails 

Clinton to Blumenthal - Fyi. The idea of using private security experts to arm the opposition should be considered. 

June 10-August 8, 2011Time period where Secretary Clinton was heavily involved in Libya policy 

Daniel Nasaw - The former secretary of state has maintained that the real-time operational details of diplomatic security were handled below her level. But information on the logistics around a 2011 visit to Benghazi were forwarded to Mrs. Clinton, according to emails released Friday. 

Schwerin to Pedestal - The documents released by the New York Times also show that Clinton received numerous briefing memos about Libya from Blumenthal, a longtime friend of the Clintons who was not employed by the State Department. The New York Times reported earlier this week that Blumenthal was also involved with a possible business venture in the country at the time. 

Some Clinton Foundation / Clinton Income

CF - $12 Million As Quid Pro Quo For Morocco Meeting 

2015 Income - $10,745,378 income earned from giving public speeches..."
  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-08 15:58:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Gotcha. Yeah, VICE sucks ass too.
http://www.mintpressnews.com/vices-fall-counterculture-hipster-rag-neoliberal-government-mouthpiece/220431/ </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-08 15:52:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Probably because everybody is 16 and Pregnant ha </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-08 15:45:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Do kids watch that shit anymore? MTV has an agenda just like every other major television network. The crisis in Libya, I guarantee, does not fit their agenda so it will never be brought up.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-08 15:43:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I've been waiting all my life for someone to say that to me. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-08 15:42:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Maybe America should stop trying to replace other countries leaders with their puppets all together. Just look at pictures of how the middle east was until America decided to give it some "freedom". </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-08 15:34:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Of course not. It has nothing to do with a Kardashian, racism or diet Mountain Dew so why would they? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-08 15:32:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> masturbate  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-08 15:31:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> to every picture  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-08 15:30:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Nope. America fucked it up because of Gaddafi refusing to use the petrodollar. Other nations just turn a blind eye. 


http://grizzom.blogspot.com/2015/05/truth-jihad-radio-with-kevin-barrett_16.html?m=1 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-08 15:22:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Bourbon. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-08 15:19:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Doesn't everybody?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-08 15:11:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> There would be a lot more erosion and crop yield would suffer greatly as would space to live. We'd all basically be fucked. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-08 15:07:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Unfortunately, I think the whole country and it's resources are going to be divvied up just like when someone loses at monopoly. The only problem is that the only people left playing already have all the money. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-08 15:02:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> http://www.mintpressnews.com/sex-slavery-isis-illegal-arms-trade-libya-plunged-failed-state-us-invasion/227478/?desktop-version=on </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-08 15:01:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Tip of iceberg. 
https://www.theguardian.com/world/2017/apr/10/libya-public-slave-auctions-un-migration </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-08 14:26:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Is anything going to be done with Libya? Hillary and Obama left that place in shambles after Gaddafi didn't want to play ball and now what once was one of the most progressive African countries is now openly slave trading. It's saturated with human and sex trafficking and it seems like nobody cares at all. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-08 05:29:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I fucked my first grandma when I was 23...so right about then </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-08 05:28:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That's the only funny thing Amy Schumer has ever said. 

Edit: Jesus, I know that's Rebel Wilson "dumbasses". I was making a fat joke about Amy Schumer.  It might have failed damn it, but I know my blonde, obese female "comedians". </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-08 05:25:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I can barely tell which one is the photograph. You have such massive talent. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-06 23:15:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> All of it </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-06 21:38:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yup </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-06 18:45:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The dad from 7th Heaven </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-06 16:24:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> My happily aborted fetus.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-06 14:50:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Her blood sugar? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-06 14:50:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Probably just burrrsitis </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-05 22:34:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> They should put in Frogger instead. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-05 00:20:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> not the onion </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-04 22:38:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Mankind </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-04 21:35:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Myself. I'd call it..."Sigh, fuck". </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-04 21:33:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> A shooting in the theater. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-04 16:28:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> He looks like a hipster who just got off his high wheel in order to see the stage from afar for The Decemberists are playing. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What's a police officer's favorite Star Wars movie? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-04 16:10:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The Empire Strikes Blacks </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-04 15:38:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Now they can be....Booty Hunters </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-04 04:40:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The First Annual Pan-Asian Toddler Tossing Championship    </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-04 03:41:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Why? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-04 03:34:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That's pretty quick and all but I really wanna see him hit. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-03 20:30:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Amy Schumer isn't funny. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-03 20:27:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> FAST

Children Playing </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-03 20:23:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What does your bellybutton smell like right now? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-03 17:49:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah, but it was probably strutting around, naked right in front of him. That fowl slut was asking for it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-03 16:31:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I dreamt I was black once. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-03 16:27:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Like my bank account...insufficient buns  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-03 06:15:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah, but that's what a normal person would do. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-03 01:09:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You're probably right. I wouldn't have helped her just because knowing my luck, she would wake up as I was trying to shake the pizza back in and think I was stealing her pizza. Then I would awkwardly have to explain in 3 seconds that even though I look like a person who would steal your pizza, I am only trying to help. I would stumble on my words and say something like "I'm trying to help your pizza up". Then I'd spend the rest of the time thinking that she thinks I was stealing her pizza. That would make me feel anxious until the point I have to bring it back up in order to smooth it over but by the time I do this I have missed my stop and now I'm gonna be late to get my daughter for the weekend. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-02 19:57:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I am. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-01 22:43:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Cunt magic </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-28 15:36:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What does your bellybuttons smell like right now? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-26 17:03:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Cogs for Christ and his Leap of Faith </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-26 13:39:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Did anyone else actually think she was 18? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-26 13:37:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> fap, fap, fapping on my bedroom floor </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-25 19:05:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Kill yourself instead. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-24 19:02:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> He should play for the Denver McNuggets. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-24 14:21:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> A Kardashian? 


Edit: Au, shucks! Thanks for the gild kind stranger.    </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-21 22:40:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> They are actually quite common. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-21 22:22:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So are Jay Lenos.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-21 14:50:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> puke puke ba-doop
puke ba-doop
puke ba-doop ba-doop ba-doop

-Assault -n- Peppa Spray

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-19 22:46:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> More like, "a couple of boobs". </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-19 15:13:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Geez, Chris Kattan will do anything for attention. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-18 17:18:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Gross. Not surprising though. Hell, I remember years ago while looking for gifts for my daughter, saw 2 different Barbies with cameras in their chest. It's all about making spying appear normal. Sickening. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-17 23:28:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I wanna know what she does with the Nutella on the floor. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-17 17:26:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I was thinking it was Kinser, maybe not though. Looks like the same conditions we were in when we were locked down in the chow hall during a typhoon as the planes hit the towers on 9/11. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-17 14:26:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  Mike Tyson </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-17 14:25:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Looks like Okinawa </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Ba Da Ba Ba Ba... </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-13 20:42:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-12 22:24:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> gross </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Oh, Arnold </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-12 16:37:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-10 12:38:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's not always wrong but it is always unfortunate. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-10 11:40:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Voting. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-10 03:46:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Great White sharks with legs. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-08 19:46:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Saying something was a "False Flag" doesn't mean it didn't happen. Just that it didn't happen like "they" say it did and was done by people other than the ones that were suspected. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-08 07:48:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So you're just a "tracer"? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-07 13:33:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> the milk steak </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-07 03:58:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yep. It was obvious. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-06 22:12:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Trans fats aren't that bad. Just limit yourself and be active.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-06 21:26:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Because he was black.

Edit: /s </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-06 21:26:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That's what we thought. He looked like a bulimic Madea so we did this Madea : I Can Do Bad Interviews All By Myself thing that was funny for a month. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-06 20:36:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That's basically what happened. I was expecting Ashton to jump out but it never happened.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-06 20:34:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'd say it is. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-06 20:34:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Ha no. If so, I would have hired them on the spot ha </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-06 20:32:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I use "secretary" loosely. She did work in hr but all she did was prescreening. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-06 20:31:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It was not. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-06 16:50:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I was interviewing people for a marketing position for a big company in Atlanta. This guy came in and absolutely bombed. Spent only about 5 minutes with him. Three days later I interviewed him again but this time as a woman. It was extremely obvious it was the same person. He/She gave the exact same answers and interviewed the exact same way. I ended up firing my secretary, who was in charge of interview screening. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> People in Dubai don't like the Flintstones..... </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-06 04:17:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> but people in Abu Dhabi doooooo </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-31 16:46:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> My girlfriend asked me if I was ever going to stop singing "Wonderwall"....

 I said maybe </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-31 14:27:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Anybody else realize his name is Wally Wallington and he's moving walls? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-30 22:16:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Research what department at the Pentagon got destroyed by the missile. That will tell you why they did it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-21 12:54:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The sub only changes if you change. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-19 03:01:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Chuck Bury :( </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-18 04:21:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hopefully soon that cancer will be a distant mammary. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-17 19:19:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Ahhhhhh   C </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-17 18:09:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Donna Plump </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-17 18:02:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I don't believe you. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-17 14:46:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Holy cokenail, Patman! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-16 15:57:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Probably. It wouldn't take much to be smarter than a human. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-15 14:49:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm not so sure that's rain water. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-15 14:39:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Your gf might be getting some Juan on Juan action while you're gone. Have a good day.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-15 14:26:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Just go with the flow.

https://i.redditmedia.com/8ONoJJ5Y_ifixPGSe9M2BJ5GkIvwQB22r2RfP4zd52I.jpg?w=320 s=24e808e4356a3da5fee7f0b62a06165f </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-14 16:00:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It was creepy at first but after seeing it reposted every week it's no longer creepy. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-14 15:53:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> After never getting a chance to do OP's mom solo it was nice to finally have a chance to do her all alone. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
