<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject5587</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-10 06:22:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> We actually _normally_ run multiple LANs a year. However right now we're having issues with location stuff, so that's why our website doesn't have upcoming events to list ( http://lanified.com ).

Once we get location stuff figured out that's appropriate for LANs (the expo was not a LAN btw), we will be running more events.

Honestly though, it is taking longer than I'm comfortable with. Working with locations is extremely frustrating and time consuming. I hate it, but it's necessary, and to you (and others) I'm sorry it's taking so long.

Do you have any questions though about our LANs? I recommend you check out our facebook albums for pictures of our past LANs : https://www.facebook.com/pg/LANified-LANparties-114122358614861/photos/?tab=albums </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Spammers are usurping the FCC filing comments for net neutrality, and here's how you can tell. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-10 06:15:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Spammers are usurping the FCC filing comments for net neutrality, and here's how you can tell. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-10 06:05:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I just popped my head into the comments for the net neutrality finding to see what people had to say, and I am disgusted to see a pattern.

To find the filing, head to: http://gofccyourself.com , then click on "17-108" on the left of the list to look at the list of comments.

What I am seeing is that bots are spamming the comments with fictitious and potentially illegal comments. How can I tell?

1. The names are sequential, and this pattern is likely to change once someone discovers this. Sequential as in the last name increases alphabetically as you go through the submissions.
2. They say the exact same thing every single time.
3. The posts are one after the other done in batches.
4. This pattern is improbable and inhuman, especially at this scale.

Just take a look:

* Snippet of the list of submissions: http://imgur.com/a/NHzG8
* Content of what each of them say: http://imgur.com/9ZXMSoj

As far as I'm concerned this is usurping the democratic processes within the USA. I am not a lawyer, but I really doubt this is legal. And this most certainly is not serving the people.

Do your part, spread this word, don't let this fall under the rug. Fight for your internet, don't let cheaters prosper. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Spammers are usurping the FCC filing comments for net neutrality, and here's how you can tell. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-10 06:05:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Spammers are usurping the FCC filing comments for net neutrality, and here's how you can tell. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-10 05:53:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I just popped my head into the comments for the net neutrality finding to see what people had to say, and I am disgusted to see a pattern.

To find the filing, head to: http://gofccyourself.com , then click on "17-108" on the left of the list to look at the list of comments.

What I am seeing is that bots are spamming the comments with fictitious and potentially illegal comments. How can I tell?

1. The names are sequential, and this pattern is likely to change once someone discovers this. Sequential as in the last name increases alphabetically as you go through the submissions.
2. They say the exact same thing every single time.
3. The posts are one after the other done in batches.
4. This pattern is improbable and inhuman, especially at this scale.

Just take a look:

* Snippet of the list of submissions: http://imgur.com/a/NHzG8
* Content of what each of them say: http://imgur.com/9ZXMSoj

As far as I'm concerned this is usurping the democratic processes within the USA. I am not a lawyer, but I really doubt this is legal. And this most certainly is not serving the people.

Do your part, spread this word, don't let this fall under the rug. Fight for your internet, don't let cheaters prosper. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-10 05:07:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Dude, I've been on the internet since dialup, I can tell sarcasm from a mile away. It wasn't funny. Deal with it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-10 05:03:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The supposition that it does by default is a fallacy. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-10 05:02:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If governments fail significantly on something they're paid to do, there's repercussions. If a Church falls short, there's no accountability. While both can choose to do a poor job, only one will ever be held accountable, and that's not a Church. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-10 05:01:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Oh I saw the sarcasm, it just wasn't funny. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-10 04:57:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You can live without a god, you can't live without food (soup). Comparing the necessity of a soup kitchen to a church is not apples to apples. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-10 04:53:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> No I mean citation from an actual scientific study. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-10 03:55:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Barcode scanner? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-10 03:51:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Can you guarantee me that every church does that? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> SD card, local storage, "not enough space" </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-10 02:58:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm on a super hacked Samsung Galaxy S4, running 7.x

16GB internal, added a 64GB SD card, formatted it as local storage.

My understanding was this should "extend" the available storage to the OS. The storage section shows the ~73GB usable space total, and says over 60GB are "free". Yet Google Play keeps saying "not enough space to update".

I'm really not sure what to do about this, the whole point of slamming an SD card in here was to expand the storage. I don't have any need to regularly remove the SD card either, so I'm fine with local storage not being "removable".

What am I doing wrong? Please send help, the walls are closing in. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-10 02:56:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Citation needed. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-10 02:45:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> "most up to date"   "packages" will always be under contention. If you want the most up to date versions of software, you compile from source. If you want to keep current, there are a lot of software dev teams out there that run repos for their software, and typically that's a good way to get the "most up to date" versions. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-10 02:44:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> We have a lot of CS:GO players in our group : http://steamcommunity.com/groups/LANified

Check it out, post in our discussion section, I'm sure you'll find others looking to form too :D </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-10 02:43:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Well you didn't really describe the workload intended. Just that programmers are somehow involved, heh.

Another thought, are you using it and seeing poor performance for them so far, or what? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-10 02:38:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It also breaks down considering that there are people who don't go to church, or aren't religious. How is that supposed to help them exactly? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-09 07:46:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The new pogs. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-09 06:19:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> NOT AVAILABLE ON MY PART OF THE INTERNET. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-09 02:30:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Well, that sucks. To be fair I don't know Lethbridge really well at all, I'm used to big cities. :/

Wish I had more useful things to say here. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-09 01:44:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> As someone who's native to the area, your experience is very surprising to me. I'm not saying you're wrong, or a liar, just that I have not seen people squelch or treat people as you describe. I'm sorry that you're experiencing it. I would be cautious to say that it is typical for the region as a whole, as there are plenty I know of in the region who are perfectly comfortable with such things. Just like anywhere there are exceptions/bad apples.

Do keep in mind that there are a lot of people and regions in Alberta, so generalising like this is unlikely to be accurate across the whole.

Again, I'm not trying to attack you here, just sharing that I am surprised you're being treated like that, because that's not the Alberta I know. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-08 22:18:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Indeed, but I'm _concerned_ it may go in other directions :/ </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-08 22:17:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Actually I've donated to Ubuntu/Canonical and I provide professional support for it to my clients. So, you have no idea what you're talking about. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-08 21:10:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I don't like the sound of this turning into an IPO. Sounds a lot like Windows/MS to me. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-08 09:11:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Looks like there's ways to get force feedback going in Linux : https://github.com/Eliasvan/Linux-Force-Feedback/wiki/Supported-Devices

As for head tracking, surely there's a way to do it, but I don't have the answers just yet. The technology is way simpler to do than porting a 3D engine. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-08 04:21:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You know what I would throw my wallet at my monitor for? DCS: World native in Linux. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-08 01:47:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> T530 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-07 07:41:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hopefully this eases transition to Linux ecosystems ;) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-06 09:32:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  selling a piece of paper for $6.50 is pretty shameful

Selling a piece of paper you say, have you ever heard of... [this](https://www.ha.com/heritage-auctions-press-releases-and-news/amazing-fantasy-15-sets-world-record-price-in-heritage-auctions-5.7-million-vintage-comics-auction.s?releaseId=2898)?

 Don't you have something better you could be doing with your life?

I think you should take a long hard look in the mirror my friend. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-06 09:31:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Because why? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-06 09:27:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The use case would be for esoteric environments. You mount a zpool, but all sorts of data sets exist for different functions, so you want them to be mounted in different areas. Perhaps different applications expect different things in different locations, but you want it to be ZFS backed, by the same zpool. This could serve that.

Consider this, you could have a dataset for your /home folder, for /var/log, and you could have different parameters set for each dataset, such as compression, snapshotting, etc. This could be very flexible if true! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-06 09:25:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Why was it implemented? Because ZFS has been designed to be the _last_ filesystem you will ever need. And the devs are continuing to work towards that.

Good find buddy, now to see how well this holds up under scrutiny ;) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-06 09:25:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> No, mounting a dataset that isn't the root of the pool is different from changing the original mount point. What OP is talking about is distinctly different from changing the initial mount point of a pool. That is, if what they are presenting is correct. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-06 04:18:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's called bias. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-06 04:15:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> please see my edit, lol </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-06 01:27:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> ~~Except the couch isn't oriented correctly.~~

edit: I'm getting muddled up with American Dad. go me. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-06 01:24:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What if it was Julie's husband and it was an emergency? Or their boss? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-06 01:12:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Why do the lights still work? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-05 19:17:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> AMT relies on the ME to work. I'm not over reacting. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-05 08:30:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Because knowing the truth is important. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-05 06:01:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> try the tool htop too, it's real nice. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-05 05:30:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I find it really annoying when someone emails me WITHOUT MY CONSENT just because I abandoned a cart and happened to put my email address in. Also, it's illegal in some countries (like Canada). So keep that in mind.

UX is important, not just sales. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-05 05:29:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Tell us more? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-05 05:23:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> And prices still won't change... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-05 05:21:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> How generous of them to include only 2x USB ports /s </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> "Not enough space" Google Play Store... SD card local storage isn't enough? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-05 03:35:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-05 03:10:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Did you know that Donald Trump took an oath to protect the constitution and uphold it's values? Yeah, that really did happen. What a joke. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-05 00:24:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> No worries! Do let me know if you have any other questions :D </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-05 00:24:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This is a good one : https://libreboot.org/faq.html#intelme </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-04 23:10:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So? How exactly is this adversely affecting you? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-04 22:13:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What exactly about this is unprofessional? Every industry, private or public, does things like this throughout each year. That doesn't breach professional integrity whatsoever. It's extremely obvious this isn't real. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-04 22:12:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> hahahah! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-04 21:45:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Why I love Canada. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-04 21:44:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This probably is a standard form that takes maybe half a minute to fill out and hit submit. You really think any consequential amount of tax dollars are being wasted here? I challenge you to prove exactly how many. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-04 21:43:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's in other components too. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-04 21:42:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'd rather tend vegetables than GRASS. BORING. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-04 21:42:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> His hair suggests otherwise. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-04 21:36:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I work with ZFS for a living man, I implement it and solve people's problems. If you don't want to take my professional advice, so be it. Or you could be not sour. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-04 21:35:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Parts of the ME are in the CPU microcode </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Little girl shows off new prosthetic foot to school chums. (x-post) </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-04 20:14:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-04 19:31:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Oddly enough MS, on the same page, recommends making a snapshot to roll back to, to break their own activation, haha! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-04 18:54:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> No, because I know that there are no tools as mature or "set-up" in Linux as in FreeNAS. Show me a distro that can offer all the features FreeNAS can around ZFS and my tune will change. Until then, I recommend FreeNAS first. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-04 18:54:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Did you post that on the FNAS forums? Working with them can get such things fixed :) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-04 06:39:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> And Peggy hates Cotton. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-04 05:23:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Well, the best way for you to find out is to run it in a VM or something ;)

But you get SO much info, for example:

1. Charts based on network usage per interface, cpu usage, ARC hit%, ARC size, and SOOOOO much more
2. You can get arc stats to get even finer details
3. The webGUI is designed whereby you are expected to generally do everything through it, so the functionality takes that into account. As such you can easily instruct things like disk replacement, how the zpool is built, networking configuration, snapshot stuff, etc, etc, etc.

Seriously go try it and allocate a few hours or so to go through it all ;D </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-03 22:46:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> check your arcstats, ZOL might have taken RAM away from the OS, unsure. Things like this is why I recommend FreeNAS over Ubuntu for a dedicated NAS. You get useful info at your finger tips, instead of digging around like you are.

Should you decide you want to switch, you can export/import your pool into FreeNAS without losing data, btw ;o </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-03 21:49:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What determines the order is who placed better earlier on. If you get first place in an early map, you'll have advantage when matching points later on. It's commonplace to deal with point matching like this.

Source: I run tournaments professionally. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-03 21:39:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Man the Japanese sure live for experiences! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-03 21:10:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yes but it's not ME. I am pointing out the technical inaccuracy is all ;) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-03 18:07:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  Management Engine is in all **intel** CPUs

FTFY </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-03 18:07:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Are you accounting for vendors that aren't intel? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> PSA: STEAM SCAM WARNING - "Free DotA 2 Money" </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-03 06:29:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-02 18:59:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> But how do we account for dogs that are extroverts? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-02 18:11:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> SeSevenen </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-02 18:10:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Designed to survive 40yrs? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-02 18:08:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> "It's the network"

"prove it" </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-02 18:07:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Uh the brown is on the protruding peak of his cheek bone... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-02 17:52:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hmmm, yeah I can see the username/timestamp being good. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-02 06:26:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> AFAIK this breaks the AMT chain. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-02 06:25:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> 404'd </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-02 06:25:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Sure, after we finished tearing down at the Expo. Huff, I'm tired. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-02 06:23:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  a cleaver way

Hmmm... are you SURE that's what you meant? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-02 06:15:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> And how often do you find the entered text to be actually useful? And how often do you find it to be useless? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-02 02:41:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I like how the quality of the explanation in that article drops off late 2G and then fully at 3G. lol </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-02 01:09:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> How to gain anxiety... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-02 01:08:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Show of hands, who actually reads those logs? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-01 18:54:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Sounds like someone who got into bad habits and forgot where they were. Sometimes it can be easy to get comfortable in such settings, if it's your day job. Did they apologise? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-01 06:35:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> eHighFive! o/ </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-30 22:23:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  Licensing isn't that complicated really

hahahaha!

found the salesman ;D </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-30 21:43:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If you unban someone that is indefinitely banned, how can one ever trust "indefinite" again? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-30 21:00:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Because League of Legends is the only game with toxicity? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-30 19:32:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> lol </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-30 17:35:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> **OKAY** </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-30 17:35:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That doesn't necessarily mean vanity is involved. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-30 06:10:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This is solid! Giving me ideas ;D </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-30 06:06:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> wut </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-30 06:05:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> **WHAT?** </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-30 06:03:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> How is this vain exactly? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-30 06:01:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This is a shit post. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> League of Legends 5v5 tournament LIVE at Calgary Expo! (Saturday)  r/Calgary x-post </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-29 21:11:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> League of Legends 5v5 tournament LIVE at Calgary Expo! (Saturday) </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-29 21:09:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-28 18:19:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Which country are you asking for? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-28 06:42:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Not for me, I also found Linux to be worlds more stable than my friends mining on Windows. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-27 19:18:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Uh, a lot of mining was already done in Linux btw... are you aware there were multiple mining distros made over the years? I should know, I built beefy rigs with them ;) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-27 19:08:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Three kids. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-27 18:52:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> uhhh? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-27 07:40:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Learn ZFS. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-27 07:37:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Because Windows has actual market share. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-26 18:32:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> -windowed -noborder for starters </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-26 07:26:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hmm, so perhaps I am just coincidentally seeing this after trying to modify launch parameters. I hope that's the case! As in, that it's not me doing it wrong (SOMEHOW). </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Game ignoring launch parameters </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-26 07:01:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hi Folks,

I'm trying to use launch parameters to set windowed and norborder stuff. Despite my best efforts it is ignoring any and all launch parameters I set in STEAM, and this appears to be the only game doing this.

Can anyone please advise as to what could be interfering? I suspect a config file, but this seems very asinine. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-26 04:49:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Did you know the Cake is a lie? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-25 19:46:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> lol </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-25 19:33:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [GG Volibear](https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=f7sL16yQGYg) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-25 08:19:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Do you do sys admin or data recovery at all? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-25 08:19:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> lol idiot. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-25 08:18:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Uh no, I'm not. I'm pointing out fact. You're the one spinning a story. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-25 07:15:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> lol, you know, I've found NTFS way more reliable than their previous FAT32. But nothing like ZFS ;) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-25 06:03:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This is a logical fallacy known as the reduction to the absurd. I'm sticking to reasonable, provable, and scientific basis. Meanwhile you are reducing my position to the absurd by presenting an absurd comparison.

If one cannot conclusively prove that it ACTUALLY causes problems, then it should not be reliable.

Take into consideration, I have seen zero evidence to support that insufficient screws for drives leads to premature failure. Does that mean I'm right? Not necessarily, just that I have contrary experience, without actual tangible evidence.

That's what studies are for. To provide a means whereby you can prove or dis-prove something without a shadow of a doubt. So you (and others) can plan around such things, and know the information is reliable.

Meanwhile, neither my experience, nor the presented information thus far, is conclusively reliable. As such, nobody should plan around any of it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-25 05:51:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That's proof that vibration impacts disks.

1. That isn't a study. But it is a valid point.
2. This does not conclusively support the position that "Improper mounting can lead to premature failure.".

This is why there are peer-reviewed studies, so things like this can be conclusively proven or dis-proven. Again, what you have presented is speculation and conjecture. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-25 04:53:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I wonder if it will be possible to add this to a pool that already exists. Neat find! :D </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-25 04:50:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Because politics I'm sure. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-25 04:48:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yet another reason for on-prem. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-25 04:47:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That's speculation. Unless you can actually systematically prove it, it will be nothing more. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-25 04:43:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Ratios are so 90's, seriously it's just a punishment for some so others can get ratio. Ratioless is the future. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-25 04:40:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Citation needed. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-25 04:38:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> more like File Exploder amirite? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-25 00:54:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If you're at all interested, Stan Lee will be at the [Calgary Expo](https://calgaryexpo.com/) this coming weekend.

Full disclosure, I do not work directly for Calgary Expo. I own and operate LANified! and we provide gaming services to the Calgary Expo. As such I just wanted to share a recent event whereby you can see Stan Lee and all that. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-24 23:22:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So what about that Iced Tea? Or are we talking about you hiring the player? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-24 22:17:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Why not start a post in /r/calgary ? That would also probably get more ppl involved too. I don't know anyone _specific_ this very moment, but RL is super duper popular still, so should be able to figure something out.

Just link me to the /r/calgary thread once you post it and I'll help :D </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-24 19:04:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Up until that shit gets yanked down by the weight from your power strip. GL with that impacted platter brah. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-24 19:04:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Bye Bye Battery </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-24 18:56:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Fuck this man. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-23 18:17:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Dusty2Pecker, [a new bird band](https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=zDuls0I50is). </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-23 18:06:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Do you want to change that? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-23 18:05:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That actually doesn't surprise me with how good they are! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-23 09:42:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Those are really awesome masks! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-23 09:41:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You don't need certs to start your lab m8, that's the whole point. Find some computing at your disposal, and find tasks you want to do with them, then figure out the steps to get there. I recommend you start with Proxmox VE, you'll get all the features without having to pay, and there's plenty there. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-23 09:35:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hey look, the train estimation is working! Fancy that. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-23 09:34:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I lost my fucking **MIND** to this one! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-22 23:35:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Well there we are then! Thanks ;) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-22 22:17:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Forza lol? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-22 22:14:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Okay now show me what it's like after a collision happens. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-22 22:12:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You'll spend less building a system to use with FreeNAS, and get so much more. Features, performance, it's all there! Make it hap'n cap'n! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-22 21:15:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Shit like this is why Police are so attentive to details. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-22 20:37:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> NOT AVAILABLE TO INTERNET USERS, AKA, WHERE I AM. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-22 20:36:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I've watched this whole thing so many times over, and I never knew, until now, what either of those two said, let alone who they were. Dang, context! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-22 20:23:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah I get that, but if you mess up the crimping, how do you recover, just the slack? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-22 20:22:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The worry about warranty is for advance failure. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-22 19:59:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> FreeNAS makes things very easy, I would say much better than Synology. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-22 08:59:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Shit BIOS if it fails a USB boot and then DOESN'T go to another boot option. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-22 08:44:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That depends on the components used. There are industrial systems based on computing that has a lifespan of 20 years, or more. But things built around silly popularism tech like ipods/ipads will have an extremely short lifespan. It's very silly to go with decisions like that just because they're familiar.

I mean, there's tonnes of office automation based around computer tech that's designed to last as long as the building too. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-22 08:34:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Synologies suck. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-22 08:30:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What happens if you try to get Warranty from WD for those drives? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-22 02:08:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Well, I don't so much mean the crimping, more judging lengths for such complex installations. With so many terminations, it looks like doing it _that_ well, you need to take a lot into consideration. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-22 01:56:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So why no ESRB rating? And I actually did read through the page... while you've pointed out it is there, if I couldn't easily find it while _trying_ to look, that means it's too easily missed. The whole point of the ESRB rating is to make it _EASY_ for people to find if it's appropriate or not. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-22 00:07:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm hoping to better understand how one would arrive at such skill. I agree if you suck, something else might be better. I'm not an electrician, I'm a Sys Admin, but I would like to get good like this! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-21 20:59:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Why doesn't it say that anywhere on the STEAM store then? That's the kind of thing you should know _before_ purchase. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-21 20:58:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [I think this is mesmerizing myself](https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/3/3b/Franz_Anton_Mesmer.jpg) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-21 20:01:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> How inconsiderate of her. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-21 19:06:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The door is push because you can't see the hinges on the inside. Think about it logically for a moment.

edit: you guys are downvoting me? wow, learn how2door. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-21 19:03:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Sure, but you aren't just born able to do this. What about when you're on the other end and there's no more slack left over? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-21 09:21:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> heh I like that not gibus reference, solid. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-21 05:39:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> EDGE </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-21 05:38:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> lol how long did this take you? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-21 05:36:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Holy crap why is their site so slow! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-21 05:30:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Storage. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-21 05:29:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Sick!

You can tell they're likely working on something, since the client takes way less work to get going than before! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-21 05:25:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I don't think there's enough people playing to warrant placement IMO. Hard enough to get matched up already. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-21 03:10:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Um, care to explain more please? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-21 03:09:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> My preference is the Zimbra OSE web interface. /shrugs </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> TF2 comp MM/match making, cheating   overturned matches </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-21 02:54:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> In CS:GO if a competitive matchmaking match had a cheater that was punished in it, the match results are overturned.

I'm not really seeing that as a thing in TF2. Is it? If not, why not? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-21 00:53:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Age restriction? This isn't even ESRB rated. What are you on about?

This game looks totally kid friendly, why you gotta NIMBY this shit? Cmon guy, get over it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-20 20:44:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I myself use FreeNAS, and the snapshot setup in there. I haven't really seen a need to use an alternative just yet. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-20 20:33:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Assemble a bunch of computers in such a way that you can simulate all kinds of IT setups without having to worry about breaking it. When you think of home lab, what do you think of? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-20 20:08:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [I Love you Phillip Morris](http://www.imdb.com/title/tt1045772/)

It's actually a fabulous Dramatic from Jim Carrey! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-20 19:36:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Is this the new Crysis engine? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-20 09:12:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Someone please tell me, if you fuck up one of those cables when making it... how do you... recover? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-20 09:01:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Wow Mr Lieu took that guy to the fucking cleaners!

This video is awesome, and incredibly enlightening! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-19 19:16:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Can we flash them into IT mode? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-19 07:17:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> How in the fuck is this Artisinal? This does not belong here. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-19 07:15:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So... Heroes of the Storm? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-18 19:27:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Get one with a handle, or is light, so you can take it easily to LANs. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-18 18:08:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> And two milleniums. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-16 23:08:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You can setup ZFS to help recover from crypto shit. Snapshots baby. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-16 19:18:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Fraid I can't wait that long :( </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-15 20:06:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That's because they're delicious. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-15 20:04:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I bet the Engineers behind this had a blast. This looks so neat! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-15 18:53:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> 2.4-staging with CSMT on, I get like 50-90FPS regularly, 960GTX. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-15 18:52:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Why not return it to where you bought it?

If you're going to sell it like this, you should consider dropping it $10 as the buyer can't reasonably return it to you if the disc has any issues with it. Whereas they could if they bought it from retail. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-15 18:45:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Mumble. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Alcohol vs Marijuana, driving in the (possible) future Canada </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-15 18:42:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I've been trying to keep abreast of what's going on with the Marijuana law changes, and I recently heard some things that seemed rather... off. In this case, driving under the influence of Alcohol vs driving under the influence of Marijuana.

As of April 13th 2017, the new relevant legislation will have an upper punishment of **10 years in jail** for driving while under the influence of Marijuana.

* http://www.theglobeandmail.com/news/politics/liberals-table-marijuana-bill-that-includes-crackdown-on-impaired-drivers/article34696586/

Meanwhile driving while under the influence of Alcohol, has a maximum sentence of **18 months in jail**.

* http://legalbeagle.com/6114545-dui-penalties-canada.html

I tried to find statistics around how _specifically_ marijuana impacts traffic collisions/incidents and such, but I was not able to find such refined statistics as it seems most of the time they are lumped in with other "drugs", and simply labelled "Drug-impaired driving". Thus far it makes it hard to find reliable stats that are _only_ for marijuana.

* http://www.statcan.gc.ca/pub/85-002-x/2016001/article/14679-eng.htm

Meanwhile we have fairly good statistics for drunk (alcohol) driving.

* http://news.nationalpost.com/news/canada/canadas-drunk-driving-death-rate-worst-among-wealthy-countries-u-s-study-finds

It also seems that a substantial amount of people believe that driving while under the influence of Marijuana is not "as bad" as while under the influence of Alcohol. Take note the source here is from a group that is _against_ "drugs", which is not an impartial source.

* http://madd.ca/pages/programs/youth-services/statistics-links/

It seems to me that some interesting conclusions can be arrived from this information. Perhaps you can draw your own, but some thoughts of my own:

1. We don't have enough actual (impartial) statistics to prove/disprove the effect Marijuana has on drivers. Yet substantially more information is available for Alcohol.
2. The punishment slated for legislature is not balanced when comparing Marijuana vs Alcohol.
3. How do these new punishments affect people who take Marijuana medicinally? Are they just no longer allowed to drive any more?
4. I think we as Canadians can do a better job than this, namely through getting better facts to guide our plans.
5. Marijuana prohibition is costly in its current form, and new costs can arise from the new legislature in its current form.

Do with this information as you will. I've tried to present this as impartially and fairly as I could. Any parts that could be subjective, I tried to clearly state them. Sorry if I fell short in any ways of such. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-15 08:52:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Interesting, but definitely not enough information! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Want - stock CPU heatsink - AMD FX 8320, or similar </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-14 22:40:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Looking to pick up one of these : http://ep.yimg.com/ay/outletpc/amd-fd8350frhkbox-fx-8350-125w-am3-eight-core-4-0ghz-desktop-cpu-37.jpg

It is an AMD stock heatsink for CPUs, normally found with FX-8320, 8350, and other similar CPUs. It's meant for CPUs that produce about 130W of thermal dissipation (TDP).

It doesn't need to be new, but it needs to be in good working order. Fan works, etc.

Looking to pay cash, easy sale, if it's the correct part. Post here or PM me if you have one. I need one real soon, so I'm not going to wait around for long. So if you have one, let me know right away. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-14 21:03:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Typically the worst drivers I see in Calgary are cab drivers. And I worked for them a while back (taking calls). There are good ones out there, but there are some seriously fucking garbage ones out there too. Calgary's Taxi Oligopoly is bullshit. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-14 18:12:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> 1. Install media codecs? Does this article not realise that's an option during installation?
2. System cleaner tool, wtf is this, Windows?

They forgot a step...

 18.. Import your openVPN config file... oh wait you can't because **NETWORKING MANAGER IS STILL FUCKING BROKEN AFTER 7 YEARS** : https://bugs.launchpad.net/ubuntu/+source/network-manager-openvpn/+bug/606365 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-14 07:50:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> OH MAN Battling Tops! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-14 07:45:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Kind of like Aircraft Carriers do? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-13 22:03:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Um... why exactly? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
