<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject6388</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What is your life story? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-09 21:16:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Happiness in sadness </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-09 19:01:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This is worthless. This is hopeless. I am worthless. I am hopeless. This is wrong. This is unfair. I am wrong. I am lazy. I hate myself. I hate everything. You annoy me. Happy people annoy me. I just want to see you suffer. Yes, my so-called best friend, my so-called loved ones, my so-called girlfriend, and my readers. I want everyone to suffer.  

I wasnt like this before. I remember I was such a lovely, innocent and cute kid. I had a fragile body but I had a kind soul and a heart of gold.  
My dad was an alcoholic. I thought he was a nice guy because he used to say so. I believed him. After all, he was my dad. It didnt bother me he stopped working so that he could spend all day with his love- alcohol and drugs. What bothered me was the fact that after getting drunk he used to beat my mom. I and my brother would intervene but only to face his wrath. Studying became difficult because locking doors, being a prisoner in your own home is difficult. Constant yelling and fighting becomes the cherry on top and there goes your mind in a spiral of negative thoughts.  
This went on for years. Day by day it became difficult to put a smile on my face and pretend everything was normal. I lived in a good area. Everyone is middle/upper middle class here.  
In 12th grade, it was the first time I had the urge to see everyone suffer. To see what it feels to suffer. Theyd then develop empathy and compassion. Yes, I wanted to see them suffer.  
  
I noticed I started envying my best friend when one day he showed me the DSLR camera that he had bought. I wanted one so badly but due to being poor I couldnt even afford it in my dreams. I was annoyed. I felt guilty but the feeling of envy was too strong.  
I decided to go to his home later that day. I told him wed chill and watch movies. I arrived at 4:00 PM at his house. I rang the door bell and we went to his room. We decided to watch Conjuring because I love horror. Before we started the movie I asked him to grab some snacks. He went to his kitchen and I thought this was the moment. I reached to the stool on which his camera was resting. I grabbed it and threw it out the window next to me. My friend asked what was that sound? I told him I dont know.   
I turned off the lights and rationalized to him that true fun of horror is in the dark. He agreed.  

After the movie finished I came back home. Next day, he told me he cant find his camera anywhere. I acted concerned but deep down I was ecstatic. Seeing him sad made me happy.   
I slowly started envying when I saw people having fun and posting pictures on Facebook. I needed to see someone suffer. I met my girlfriend and she told me she will be playing guitar in a local competition and I had to be there. I always wanted to play guitar but I never had a knack of it. I was jealous of her talent.  
She was looking forward to the competition. A day before the competition I went over to her house. I thought about pulling a string of her guitar but knew she could find a replacement of that. I needed something more permanent.   

I took a needle and started playfully scare her. I made it seem look like an accident and managed to stab her left index finger. She started screaming and crying. She was bleeding a lot. I brought some chilled water to wash the blood and later band-aided her finger. It all seemed like a prank gone wrong and that I didnt do it deliberately. She forgave me but was dejected because no way she could perform next morning because she couldnt even play the chords properly with her injured finger.  

I felt amazing. I acted as if I was sorry and I gave her a passionate kiss. She was still dejected because she was so excited to play at the competition. I felt ecstatic once again. Deep down I was thrilled and seeing her sad made me happy.  

So now Im writing this as I crave that ecstatic feeling once again. Are you enjoying reading stories here? Well, well see how you will read tomorrow when youll wake up with your eyes stitched. Im coming for you.
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-09 12:57:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> We need to revolt right here right now. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What are the opinions you hold that might offend others? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-09 12:40:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-09 12:20:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I want a happy life. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Why do people not talk about death? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-09 12:18:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> They grieve like crazy when someone close to them passes away but that is how nature works. The goal should be to make sure the younger ones are independent and can sustain themselves. I know death is an uncomfortable thing to discuss but what's the point of avoiding inevitable? If people were more open about it instead of pretending it won't happen then things might become easier when it finally happens. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [Serious]What are the things you have to avoid talking about with your significant other? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-09 11:48:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> I am outraged </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-09 10:23:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Controlling myself but I feel like smashing everyone's head because I am so depressed, I am angry, I am outraged. Why me? I want a good life. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-09 10:14:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The thing is they have clearly stated they've other friends and they WON'T hang out with her. They're so adamant. Yet, I'm being called the negative guy when I'm being blunt. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-08 22:31:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Because while it makes sense it also is quite depressing. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-08 22:29:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This realization is both a boon and a bane. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Everyone annoys me </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-08 22:28:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Every happy person annoys me. Hate it when I am told I am being negative when I am actually speaking based on facts. I would consider that realism. Example, two friends(male) have admitted they don't want to hang out. Third friend(female) says she wants to. I tell her nobody will come. She says I am negative. Well, the fuck? The guys have admitted they don't wanna hang out. How does that make me a negative thinker? I am blunt and answers straight forward. I am a realist.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-08 21:52:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Glad I'm not from US of A. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What do you feel about the great Facebook? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-08 21:48:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-08 21:42:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Blimey! OP is drunk as hell. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-08 18:47:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> She perhaps won't read it anyway. If I knew for sure she's gonna read it then I'd be more polite. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-08 18:45:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Being forgotten.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What is your favorite Nosleep story? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-08 18:42:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-08 18:41:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> But if she consented then she shouldn't blame him. Being hurt is understandable but she shouldn't blame others for her own actions. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-08 14:37:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I was negative and self-loathing.  
Now, I am even more negative and self-loathing.  
Life's great. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What are the questions that triggers you? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-08 14:35:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-08 14:33:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> haha </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-08 14:16:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> We're all guilty of this. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What would you do if you were Donald Trump? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-08 14:12:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Checking my username out, what are the new experiments I should do? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-08 14:11:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-08 12:19:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Fuck her. Tell her to fuck off. She consented and now you're the one who needs forgiveness? Fuck her man. If she decided to do it then she is responsible. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-07 22:13:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Exactly. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> My life is over </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-07 22:01:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Not committing suicide but my future is hopeless. No details but my future really has no hope now. Let's drink some water. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Lonely people of Reddit, what do you do to cope with it? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-07 17:41:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-07 16:40:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Nice try mate, nice try. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-07 09:38:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Stupid bot. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-07 08:53:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I see where you're coming from. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-06 16:12:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's not always true though.  
And anyway, OP has the evidence so why is he reluctant to show proofs to the police? There's no way police won't take him seriously if he has proofs. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-06 12:56:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What if you're actually imagining stuff? She hasn't killed you even when you were defenseless and vulnerable. Why?  
And if it's actually happening then you do have lots of proofs now. How about the cell phone number you're getting calls from? The scratching on the door? The note? The fact that she's killed her family and is schizophrenic? There's no way police can't trust you with all the evidence unless it's all unreal and you're hallucinating due to stress and trauma. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-05 15:47:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That was a bit too much. He didn't deserve any of it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-05 13:25:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Joseph is manipulating you. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-05 12:49:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Well I wouldn't feel jealous about that. Marriage is a big commitment.  Once you have kids, it's no longer about you. You lose a lot of freedom and gain too many responsibilities. I say look at the bright side. You've a lot of time for marriage and kids. Figure yourself out first. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-04 13:45:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> My point is only parents have the ability to love unconditionally. NO ONE ELSE.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-04 10:10:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You clearly are a troll. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-04 02:28:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Really. I am getting downvoted but I wrote the truth. Being depressed is understandable but it doesn't get you anywhere. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-04 02:25:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Look I understand all this Red pill thing but people are still people. Some people are just not comfortable with things like this. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-04 01:34:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Long term relationship. No casual hookups. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-04 01:29:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Is it possible that she is simply uncomfortable with it? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Is being Alpha enough? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-04 01:07:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> A chick can cheat even if you do everything right. I am not sure if I  should take this sub word for word because everyone's situation is different. Thoughts? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-04 01:01:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Whoa! Are you a troll? I literally said you had a cool date and you're still pissed. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-04 00:32:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Well, I guess it went fine. Alpha or Beta, don't care. It's really not necessary to fuck the girls all the time. I would say so far so good. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-03 21:49:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What happened to those 8 pizzas? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-03 20:49:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Asking the real questions. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What are the hobbies that can be tried without money? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-03 19:38:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-03 18:46:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So, I don't really want to risk myself getting hurt. My plan is to talk to her only when I am free and not taking time out to chat to her. Basically, I won't make her my priority. Is this a good plan? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> I feel like I am not good enough for her </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-03 15:49:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> She's just a friend not even close yet it hurts. She keeps saying other mutual friends don't reply her only I do. It makes me feel like I am not enough for her. Maybe if other starts replying she won't care about me anymore. I can't help but feel I am not good enough for her. Advice? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-03 11:48:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I see where you're coming from and it's hard. Just keep going forward. If you stop then nothing will happen for sure. Don't give in without a fight. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-03 11:34:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You've to change. Stop feeling sorry for yourself man! I know it's hard. It's happening to me. I am 19.  
I have realized everything is earned in this world. Parents are the only ones who will love you unconditionally.   
Rest is earned. Money, friendships, cars, girls, house etc. Every single thing out there is earned.  
I recommend lifting, running, reading, try to not talk about your actual feelings to women. It's a turn off.  
Be mysterious. Appear as an interesting guy. Remember, no one wants to involve themselves with a negative person and a negative  life. So, talk about things that people may find interesting.  
I am same as you and I intend to apply changes in my life.  
We can all wallow in our sadness till the end of life but the truth is talking won't get you anywhere. It's the actions that count. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-02 20:53:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I hear you. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-02 20:32:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Exactly. Are you diagnosed with depression and anxiety? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> My problems have no meaning </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-02 20:31:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Lots of trauma, lots of abuse, no money for years.  
Solution: Get a job. Get money. Good life.  
Wanted to inspire people with my life story.  
People work to get a better lifestyle. 
So, ultimately if I work good for me. But my tragedy served no purpose. It has no meaning. I faced trauma and abuse for no reason.  
No rewards, no appreciation, good for you, no one gives a fuck. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-02 20:18:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Listen to Eminem. That dude knows our pain. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Deactivated my fb account </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-02 19:21:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It was just making me miserable but now I fear I have no one to talk to. Not that anybody actually spoke to me there anyway except one or two people. But I hated the attention that others were getting when nobody was even replying to my messages.  
I guess it can be a blessing in disguise as well? Maybe now I should focus on meditating, eating right, exercise and then look for a job? FB wasn't the solution to depression, anxiety, isolation or loneliness anyway, no? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What should I do? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-02 18:44:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Does TRP apply to Western culture or is it universal? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-02 16:04:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I don't think all suggestions will work in Asian/Indian culture. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-02 12:26:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What's your greatest fear? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-02 12:18:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Come on! You know some people don't look good. That's just truth. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-02 11:39:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> SJW. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Ugly people of Reddit, what are the struggles attractive people can't understand? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-02 10:45:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-01 20:59:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Well...*coughs* ...Why are you all looking at me? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-01 20:44:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> She's the one with issues. Fuck her. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Who is the one person you'll always remember? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-01 20:32:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-01 20:30:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Are you me? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> How do you kill someone who is already dead inside? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-01 20:10:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> How did you figure out what makes you happy in life? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-01 10:47:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What can you do for your country? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-01 09:33:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-30 21:34:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Time to play the game- Motorhead. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What are the things to say to a girl while you're texting? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-30 20:58:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-30 17:44:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yes they think I need to shut the fuck up and man up. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-30 14:18:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I don't do anything because I am constantly hating myself mate. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Got back from get-together </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-30 13:39:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I just got back from a get-together.
Well, my brother and cousins were having fun, talking about movies, songs, singers, stupid shit etc. They were genuinely happy and having fun. I was genuinely depressed and anxious and pretended to be happy.
I always do a bad job at this. They know I am not having fun and interested but the thing is I love them but hate myself and my life. I do put on a smile but I have nothing to speak.
My brother watches GoT, Breaking bad, lots of movies and he has so many things to say and on the other hand, I am constantly depressed and don't do anything so I have nothing to say.
I hate it because I don't want anyone's sympathy.  
I feel so left out everywhere I go. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-30 13:36:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I just got back from a get-together.  
Well, my brother and cousins were having fun, talking about movies, songs, singers, stupid shit etc. They were genuinely happy and having fun. I was genuinely depressed and anxious and pretended to be happy.  
I always do a bad job at this. They know I am not having fun and interested but the thing is I love them but hate myself and my life. I do put on a smile but I have nothing to speak.  
My brother watches GoT, Breaking bad, lots of movies and he has so many things to say and on the other hand, I am constantly depressed and don't do anything so I have nothing to say.  
I hate it because I don't want anyone's sympathy. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Should I talk to this girl? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-29 20:10:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I have a female friend. She chats with me a lot and we have been talking a lot lately. Thing is we chat during the night and sometimes even till about 2-3 AM. She has joked about making me her boyfriend twice although I understand why she was so desperate because she said she feels lonely.  
The second time she did this I told her it is extremely disrespectful  to joke about these things. The problem is now I feel I shouldn't text her to entertain her all the time. She texts me because she feels lonely and I can't help but think I am the one who will keep entertaining her and one day a guy will come and reap the rewards of my hard work.  
He'll get companionship, sex and what not from her while I would have wasted my time texting her all day and night. I think I shouldn't entertain her if all she wants is this from me. What do you guys think?  
Don't tell me I am a prick because I can use this time to sleep, chat with others, study etc. instead of entertaining her. I do not want to waste my time. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> My online friend is tired of my shit too </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-29 19:39:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Well, he is a guy in his 50s and he lives alone. Even he is tired now. He says "be positive", "just try harder" etc. Well, you know those token bullshits. Everything costs money and I don't have it. It's a vicious cycle. I just can't help the situation. Fuck me. Even online people are tired. Where do I go? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-29 19:17:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Unfortunately, there is no way a person will ever love us for being us. We gotta fight our way and earn them. Yes, I mean even the people as well. There is a girl I saw who loves a "great guy" who just happens to be a "CEO". Imagine that dude being homeless. The "great guy" will suddenly become a loser. It's so easy to manipulate people's mind but this is the truth.  
In this world, you have to play it like a game and earn everything. Food, cloth, shelter, water, house, love, girls, cars, friendships etc. Everything is earned and nothing is given. It's depressing and I get depressed thinking about it as well but hey, this is just the truth.  
As I wrote this comment my friend tagged me on a facebook photo. His cousin made a sketch of him and it's good. But, I hope he soon realizes I don't really care either. Nobody cares about me. I don't care about them either. It's annoying when people like him just wants everyone to care about them but give no care in return.  
This dude never asks me how I am doing and what I have been up to. Keeps tagging in his facebook posts, talks about himself and then cry no one gives a fuck about him. Well, give a fuck about others and people will give a fuck in return. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-29 18:42:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Our reality is different from theirs. Even if you did all the right things people would find a way to bitch about you. Just do your own things man. People are assholes anyway, most of them. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-29 18:39:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I get you. I don't like chatting either now. I want physical and real interaction. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-29 18:11:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I feel the same man. Fuck society. In fact fuck the whole universe. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-29 18:07:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Exactly. Exact-fucking-ly. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-29 18:07:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> No. There will be no liquor. My plan is to talk less and focus on some food and stick close to my family members and chat a little with soon-to-be sister-in law's family members. Glad it's only about one day right now. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-29 18:02:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I have always been like this. Yeah, once I get there I might even enjoy. Let's see what happens. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-29 18:00:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Now I wonder why did I get downvoted?  
I won't actually stab someone. That was only an example. What I meant was it's not so easy. You can't just be "happy". </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-29 17:57:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Can't back out. My cousin brother is almost like a real bro. He has seen me growing up and cancelling is just not a choice. Well, it is just one day so I guess I'll power through it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> I hate family get-together </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-29 17:39:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Tomorrow I am going to the house of my soon to be sister in law. Well, there will be many people. They are 8-10 years older than me and I can't relate with them. They're good people but I am depressed and find it tough to pretend to be happy.  
Ughhh.. just want to get done with it. It gives me anxiety to be in the large crowds as well. I am used to stay at home. Can anyone relate? Anybody hate family get-together? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-29 17:26:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I can relate to some things you wrote. These people never had any real trouble yet this is why they say things like this. It makes my blood boil when they think the solution is "don't worry, be happy". Fuck. I'll stab you with the knife then say "don't bleed, forget pain". </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-29 17:23:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah if it was truly this easy we wouldn't be depressed. I know it's hard to understand if you aren't experiencing it yourself but it's not that we are "negative" by choice. I truly wish they could understand but a person who has never seen real troubles will find it extremely hard to understand.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-29 13:13:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I wonder if Mary is still alive. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-29 10:50:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I see where you're coming from. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-29 01:58:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Well if you really were there you can at least show some compassion? You know the feeling. You can understand. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-29 00:39:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> No I apologize because I have hurt people around me. I know nobody likes us "negative" people. I don't like myself as well. I just wanted to convey, those miserable people around you might think they're a burden on people like you. They probably wish they never existed. I   just wanted to say I know it's hard for you but it's hard for us as well. It's just *tragic*. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-28 19:07:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> We can argue all we want. The truth is poor suffers and middle/upper middle/rich pretends we are doing well.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-28 19:05:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Don't go on the literal meaning. You guys very well know that as a species we have fucked up big time. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-28 19:03:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> They're not wrong but I can't tell you what to do. So, wish you the luck. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-28 18:17:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> They wouldn't be wrong though. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-28 18:16:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Are you from a rich family? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Why do you think government of any country cannot actually solve any problem? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-28 18:15:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-28 17:57:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hey I am depressed and having a rough life. I realize people don't really care but I just need to speak to someone from time to time. Sorry it bothers you, it bothers me as well. It's just that sometimes if I don't reach out I feel like killing myself.  
I'd take professional help but that costs money. I don't have it. I can get a job but some days I am so depressed it's hard to even go out. It's a vicious cycle. Apologies for being depressed. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-28 17:40:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> But I was desperate to rant. What should I do now? Who'll understand me? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-28 17:23:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yes but I listened without judging. When it was my turn she called me lazy, negative and what not. That pissed me off. I am barely keeping myself alive and the least trouble she has is her boyfriend not talking  for a day. The magnitude is clearly distinct and yet I understood and tried to listen as much as possible. She didn't do the same for me. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-28 14:29:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> No I don't live in USA. I live in a culture where living away from your parents is not a thing. Even if I get a job I won't make enough money  to rent out a place and fulfill my basic needs as well. I am kinda stuck here. It's all a vicious cycle but for others saying "get a job" is so easy. Well, if it was that easy I wouldn't be complaining and would have already found the solution. Like I said even a job wouldn't warrant living away just yet. I will at least need a BA before I can even hope to find a decent job so it's just not that easy. I dropped out from college this semester and will pursue a degree but that will take 3 years to complete.  
It's all a vicious cycle and there's no way I can get out of it so suddenly. I just wanted someone to listen to me but as it turns out I am alone in my battle. Anyway, no one can take away my problems from me no matter what, even if they listened. I just don't know what to do anymore.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-28 14:12:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yup and I have listened to her problems so I know they can't be compared with mine. Her main problem usually is "My boyfriend is not talking to me, my life is SO hard uaaan" whereas mine is "I live with an alcoholic, unemployed, drug-addict, abuser of a father who spends money on drugs and working is not that easy for me because I have seen abuse and trauma while growing up and now my throat is dry, rapid heartbeat, shaky hands and I am always thinking about suicide, I am worthless and hopeless".  
I may be wrong but my guess is my life is *slightly* harder than hers. But hey I might be wrong. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-28 12:46:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Happy birthday dude. Know it sucks but I don't know what else to say. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> I listened to all her problems </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-28 12:45:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I have a girl best friend and I have always listened to her problems. Last night I shared mine and she called me I am always negative and I am lazy, doesn't work hard etc. and my problems can be solved so easily. Well, fuck her. I trusted her and she just thinks I make excuses. Sigh.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-28 12:10:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yup truth makes you unpopular. Ever wonder why these politicians, counselors etc. lie? Can't blame them. They just say what people wants to hear. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-28 12:09:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Pro tip: Avoid large groups of people if you can. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-28 10:58:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I love it that you understand but suicide seems so easy now. I am not sure if I want a good life anymore...but death seems like a gateway to  end my misery..*it's so contemplating* </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-27 17:33:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Enlighten me, who'll pay the bills? Also, lots of us don't have the talent/drive/resources/support network etc. to do what we "love". Honestly, people think everyone has it easy and tells us not to complain. Well, when we're having a shitty life the least would be to allow us to complain. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-27 17:18:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Well, what can I tell you? I have been declared a negative person and lost all respect from everyone. Annoying thing is if I die they'll wonder why I never shared my problems. When I share them they call me negative and I should be more positive. Sigh. What to do? Even if I become positive and successful it will be so sad to see people coming to me only because I'll be their ideal person.  
No one will ever care about me the way I am. Be yourself they say. Well, no, I'll have to modify my behavior to please others no matter  what I am thinking. Sigh. What a life!  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> I am negative </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-27 16:57:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Everyone these days just say I am negative and can't stand me. Final nail in the coffin was when just few minutes ago my best girl friend lashed out and said how I am always negative. I am lazy, I make excuses etc. Who will like me if I keep being negative(that's true).  
Well, my situation is my dad has been unemployed most of his life. He's an unemployed, alcoholic, drug-addict abuser of a person. I saw lots of abuse and trauma growing up and I am so exhausted and my mind is fucked. I feel worthless, hopeless and do not want to exist.  
Friends tell me to suck it up and work hard. But I am drained, my mouth is always dry, rapid heartbeat, shaky hands etc. Feels hopeless.  
They lash out at me for being negative. Well, guess they'll only care when I am gone. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-26 21:53:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> And a tinge of hope keeps you still alive. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> I have found comfort in my sadness </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-26 21:49:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Strange feeling. I am so used to be like this that I have found comfort in my melancholy. Strange indeed. Not sure if I even want a happy and fulfilling life anymore. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-26 21:47:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I read books, write blogs, run, I am interested in learning DAW etc. 
Basically, I do have hobbies but these days I am very down. I see no  point in anything and I am hopeless. I am used to isolation as well and that is what I think makes people think I am a weirdo as well. I didn't talk much with my classmates when I was in college due to home issues before I dropped out this semester. I feel they might think I am a weirdo because I used to be so quiet.  
Well, I am  alone these days. Nobody really cares about me except  my mom. Also, I have found comfort in my sadness. Happy people annoy me now. Strange phase of life. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-26 21:16:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I can relate so hard. I worry so much about future now that I don't even act in present. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
