<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject4858</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-10 10:48:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Old labour politics of envy. Didn't work in Thatchers time, Blair got rid of it and it won't work now. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-07 12:18:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Except The Obamas would be considered right of centre in the UK despite their words, deeply immersed in the military whatever complex, the system of global banking/finance and corporate exploitation. The fact that they used it only shows the lack of choice and illusion of democracy. Do you think Goldman Sachs/Silicon valley billionaires really care if it is Trump or Obama? To them it makes no difference.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-02 21:56:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What is an alt-account? What nonsense? And some people leave the house during the day.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-02 21:42:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Many of you will not know that several regional police forces have been amalgamated into a single force, sensible considering the population is less than London. But promised economies failed and about the only thing cut have been police officers instead of streamlining back office departments.  

http://www.spf.org.uk/2017/03/shock-stats-reveal-police-morale-has-hit-new-low-as-just-1-in-10-cops-back-the-forces-future/

http://www.bbc.co.uk/news/uk-scotland-39208096

http://www.express.co.uk/news/uk/745370/scotland-police-body-blunder-scandal-claims-incident

https://www.thesun.co.uk/news/1860602/scottish-cops-told-not-to-nick-criminals-because-of-a-police-staffing-crisis/

https://www.theguardian.com/commentisfree/2015/aug/02/policing-in-scotland-shambles

http://www.heraldscotland.com/news/14537102.Police_Scotland_finance_chief_leaves_force_after___85m_budget_black_hole_row/

http://www.express.co.uk/news/uk/708696/Transport-cops-Sturgeon-merger-Police-Scotland

https://www.thetimes.co.uk/article/the-very-blue-line-morale-at-police-scotland-hits-a-new-low-v6b97892

There is a mix of reporting and sources, all critical of the implementation of the change not the idea of the change itself. Plus chat with some cops morale is not super high. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-02 10:08:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Why was he tased? Why didn't 2 cops just walk over to him arrest him, put him in cuffs etc?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-02 09:56:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Worse in Scotland where the Scottish Government has really messed it up. Edit: Oops better not say that the Scottish Government has done anything wrong. Must be the only country in the world that has a perfect goverment that can do no wrong. Grow up and hold politicians accountable not just pretend everything they do is wonderful because you support their party. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-27 09:06:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That explains Florida then. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-26 21:33:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> STAY WOKE KANGZ </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-26 21:18:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> "let" </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-24 23:53:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Most of those countries are quite happy under someone elses nuclear umbrella. UK nuclear missiles have nothing to do with USA command and control systems, the deterrent is independant but ultimately depends on US mid to long term support to remain viable, nothing to do with pulling the trigger. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-24 23:48:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Weapon of mass destruction is fueling on the bunker/silo maybe nuke maybe chemical all you know is it could destroy a whole city within 6000 miles. You know where it is but it is surrounded by effective air defence and in the middle of enemy territory so no plane or cruise missile or ground forces can get to it.  Unless they admit to "rods from god" space weapons, a trident or similar missile would be one of the few ways to deal with it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-24 20:13:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The crown is literally the head of canada, soviet comnunism (hammer and sickle) was not gay friendly so this is the sort of thing an edgy  preteen would make. Hope they grow out of it or at least become more coherent. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-23 10:51:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I always assumed that if Snowden was prepared to ruin his life and release publicly then the Russians/China probably had it all anyway from someone who took cash and carried on quietly in secret. Same with the Manning stuff, if a low grade soldier with serious issues can access the network, then pretty sure Russia/China had it all already. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-22 09:28:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hint of death star mixed with east german prison guard.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-21 08:34:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Can't defeat ISIS in failed states. So Trumpy will be there for a long time. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-21 08:09:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Credit for business projects but the title reads like it is subsidizing fossil fuel burning. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-20 09:09:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yvette cooper didn't she used to hang around with Blair? Wasn't her husband Ed Balls? Wasn't she at the heart of the Government during Iraq? As long as May doesn't get dragged into a trump ground war in Syria or any war against Iran or NK she will always be more trustworthy than anyone closely involved with Blair. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-18 09:45:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Triple council tax for short term lets/air bnb in specific areas. Double council tax on second homes in high density areas ie cities. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-18 09:41:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> At least BTL have an interest in having people living in the house. Ban short term lets, Air bnb, party flats and crack down on house of multiple occupancy abuses. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-17 18:45:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I don't really know what your point is? Your scale is way off if you are comparing race riots needing the military to be called out and individual racist attacks in the UK. Also explain what you mean by little speech? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-17 17:56:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So true in fact most of the people who rage against him only know of rivers of blood and suppose he was a nazi white supremacist. They know nothing of race riots and massacres that happened between different cultures in the 60s which shaped his views.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-17 17:43:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Not a strawman and wasn't even addressed to you. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-17 11:47:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So this. Many people assume that there was a utopia before a foreign empire took over and that utopia would have just kept getting better if there hadn't been intervention.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-16 19:28:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Nerve agents but in thick viscous liquid form that stick to everything like a form of death glue.

"A special form of persistent agents are thickened agents. These comprise a common agent mixed with thickeners to provide gelatinous, sticky agents. Primary targets for this kind of use include airfields, due to the increased persistency and difficulty of decontaminating affected areas."  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-16 19:15:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The second an enemy was an actual threat to the US it would be old school rules very, very quickly. USA just hasn't fought an existential threat for a long time. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-16 16:05:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Tory Scum!!!!! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-16 15:59:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Transwhite obviously. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-16 15:36:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Pepsi. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-10 18:42:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> There was a reason Martin Luther nailed a message to a door and it wasn't an evil plot to create a British Empire hundreds of years later. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-10 18:36:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Gosh your reasoned argument, constructive tone and facts total destroyed his argument. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-10 18:31:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> They are the WASPs. They made the USA and they don't need to hark back to some imagined heritage to make themselves feel special, they control the most powerful country in the world. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-10 18:27:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Roman Catholic church was the Sith of Europe. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-07 08:57:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Iraq WMDs, never forget. NATO bombing of Serbs in Kosovo and estimates of effectiveness. Every estimate of US trained local forces before pulling out. The continued unstoppable inflow of drugs and illegals into USA. US Intel isn't magic, real life isn't a TV show.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-07 08:48:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Did the TV news tell you that? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-07 08:46:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> There is no proof they launched chemical weapons? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-07 08:45:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> To be fair you did lend money and expect it to be repaid, whilst fighting global evil, and then systematically dismantle the old European colonial influence around the world while attempting to create USA hegemony.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-07 08:44:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Is there a source because if it was chlorine then it was clearly anti Assad forces and the whole thing is a less than subtle plot to go to war. The whole premise was that sarin was to complex to store and weaponise by ISIS etc but they have been documented using chlorine in the past. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-07 08:36:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> AQ and ISIS have all used chemical attacks and ISIS is now using drones, there is military equipment on both sides. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-07 08:33:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I suppose they can't bomb Assad's bases by "mistake" anymore it might look suspicious. http://www.foxnews.com/world/2016/09/17/us-halts-air-raid-after-learning-syrian-forces-may-have-been-hit.html

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-05 20:43:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> https://www.montane.co.uk/womens-c15/clothing-c30/womens-windproof-jackets-c22
http://www.needlesports.com/2674/windproofs.aspx#  0E3t8feJj81g/HUGZqkNCzC7aCpo369GrrIEzhLnTEDDT0EXd+HhzEnTiG1HMkQ4teaEvA0qQiCqrhMQhIDl8pUIqDsJUHEoolEMQEpxwMizqq8B2nQamr7HNMCxExf/PJ4Eww==

Particularly anything thin and pertex only not fleece lined etc for warmth. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-05 09:32:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Sleep inside a plastic bag and you will be soaked in the morning by your own condensation, sleep inside a goretex/breathable bag you will not.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-05 09:23:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> leggings will be fine just have some paclite goretex pants to pull over for heavy downpours, your feet will get wet just make sure feet are in the warm dry at night. Try a pertex top under the precip for real wind protection and it will be more breathable/comfortable for wind protection in the dry.    </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-05 09:01:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Because protesters often try to provoke over reaction by cops to show one sided video of "brutality". For example shouting and swearing into cops faces maybe threatening them or spitting on them or someone behind the front line trowing stuff to hit the cops then when the cops arrest the front of the crowd the protesters only show the pepper spraying and arrest using selective editing. But probably not these protesters who seem to be LARPing antifa college edgy white kids.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-04 20:42:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  Science, technology and rational thought freeing the universe from a self selecting autocratic elite and their religious knight enforcers. The Empire is the revolution and the rebels are in fact reactionary, often monarchist forces. Defend the revolution, death to the counter revolutionaries.

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-04 18:24:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I would put some money on the fact they were not STEM students. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-04 09:48:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Some other subs must now have to go next level because what would have been tinfoil a few years ago is reality. I suspect this has validated many "predictions" and if they were right about it all then, I hope they are wrong about the lizard shadow government. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-03 20:43:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Service guarantees citizenship. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-01 08:25:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> http://oga.org/

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-01 07:50:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Now can the rest of us reclaim the rainbow? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-25 09:15:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It is normal. There was a small gap after IRA types stopped and the Muslims started attacking the UK but even then there was the gay pub bomber. Uk swerved most of the radical left terror in the 70s and 80s that dominated Europe, instead we had the Troubles. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-24 20:46:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Worse than pedophile sex tourists from the mainland? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-24 20:22:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Your articles are excellent and your kovea spider review lead me to try to get one but being in uk it was easier to get a vega. Keep up the good work. Honest reviews not based on ad space in the press are rare nowadays and I know your efforts are much appreciated. Thanks for the content. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-24 09:06:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> http://bushcraftusa.com/forum/threads/welding-goggles-used-as-glacier-glasses.35101/

Opinions are mixed. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-24 08:45:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If you want a lightweight stove for winter try Optimus vega, you can invert the fuel so use it well below freezing. It is 178g so not lightweight for summer but for winter and the mountains it is functionally lightweight where ultralight stoves might struggle. https://www.optimusstoves.com/us/us/9-8018505-optimus-vega
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-22 10:32:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> There is a reason lots of left wing people are against globalisation and voted for brexit beyond "racism" and they believe in a duty to the working class British worker who they feel kinship/responsibility for. They think that free cheap labour from abroad has removed the monied class from having any interest in training, education or things like apprenticeships for indigenous workers leaving them to die in ghettos on benefits, destroying traditional communities and also "stealing" trained workforce to the detriment of  Eastern Europe. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-22 10:22:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It is like Jon Stewarts take on the US media, about how maybe they could do their jobs now instead of the constant obama is "so hot right now" because he was cool they did not hold him to account at all. You might have the same problem in Canada but that hair and did you see his casual suit and look at the foreign women looking at him.... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-22 09:17:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=s5mGNRgKFOI disco is not dead, disco is life. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-22 09:15:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Clean coal was Scotland's SNP's big shout for a few years, then sensibly they dumped trump and went big on wind. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-20 16:44:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If I quote reddit irl I am potentially weird and risk being judged but if a journalist makes a whole clickbaity article on reddit stuff they get a career, salary and real life points not just karma.

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-20 16:00:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thinking like this lead directly to Gulf War 2. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-20 13:52:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> By paying for protection you mean lending money and charging interest? Or do you mean being allowed to base nuclear weapons and an airforce in the country for YOUR cold war with the Russians? Yeah thanks for the selfless giving. Often I think what would Jesus do and am surprised at how similar the wonderful Americans are in their pursuit of universal peace and love /s. Now, off you trot to Trumpton. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-16 13:02:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Obama was pretty quiet about water in fact I think he even passed laws protecting water. It is like he wanted the russians to have easy access to USA. And people say Trump is with the Russians but no one talks about Obama and the russia water highway. Hope Trump will finally do something about the water or at least not protect it so much. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-16 11:04:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> But they could be bi-winning. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-16 10:15:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Western Europe doesn't build its military to fight China and dominate the Pacific. So has plenty of runways and supply depots to fight the Western Russia area plus Russian forces are much depleted since Red Storm Rising days. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-16 10:13:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I doubt they would be able to fully staff both at the same time if they don't instantly mothball or sell the second one. With the terrible record for the latest builds, subs and ships, lets hope the carriers are done better. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-15 11:03:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Nice deflection from the tyrant.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-15 11:00:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It will probably not break up as Trump people go on about but there is the real chance of the Eurozone collapsing over the next few years if Germany stops paying for Greece/Italy/Spain or Greece defaults and comes out of Euro the currency might be dissolved. The EU is probably going to change over the next few years even if gert and le pen don't win. The genie is out the bottle and the mainstream politicians have begun to take note eg mainstream Holland taking a harder line against Turkish political activity inside Holland. The irony is after some EU reform it might become just as Uk wanted it but just in time for Brexit. Edit : assumed people would know Eurozone wasn't the EU. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-14 10:04:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Sounds like the kind of govt overspend, overreach and waste that Trump would cut to the bone. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-10 19:02:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Very, very few Brits revel in "post-imperialist syndrome".  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-10 11:52:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'd bet cop would have let him drive off to park if he hadn't been a dick and played the race card. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-10 11:26:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Trump, Hillary, Obama you still got Goldman Sachs and the rest.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-08 21:54:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I will watch it but it does slightly make a mockery of all the earnest fan love in this thread to find out that after all the blah blah feminism changed my life, I wrote a thesis, and semi intellectualizing; one of the producers, leads and a driver behind this project is part of a cult that is semi fascist and obviously made up.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-07 09:43:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The numbers are total killed in action (inc IEDs) not just shooting. Wounded in action in iraq was 31952. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-07 08:54:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Last minute after some troops have died and the generals and government are embarrassed into upgrading/getting the right stuff. 
Edit : SA80 A1 was utter rubbish and only rebuilt after questions were asked in Parliament about why soldiers were going into war with the rifle. Total lack of armored vehicles for years in Afghanistan and Iraq leading to many deaths until the press raised such an issue and questions were asked in Parliament. Body armour decades behind the times before upgrades despite other nations having the good stuff. 

Infantry dramatically out gunned by the enemy and years before things like light machine guns (SAW), grenade launchers, sharp shooting rifle, better sniper rifle, effective anti tank weapons, shotguns, LAW etc. Radios a decade behind the curve, mortar computers that were only fit for artillery not light mobile infantry, boots that melted, crap helicopter support for years and years despite its use being doctrine. 

Total failure of RAF global logistics despite warnings for years. 

The real issue is that all of the deficiencies were known but ignored for a long time and people suffered as a result. When people say last minute UOR, generally that means 5 - 10 years too late. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-07 08:51:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Private companies maximizing profits, governments changing priorities and budgets, top military hesitating and failing to commit and produce clear timely requirements (many end up working for the companies that get such an easy ride). It is a big club and no one likes to rock the boat for the others because of pensions and future jobs.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-07 08:46:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Epic problems with T45 severely limiting their already limited capability, Astute subs still not dependable and requiring constant work, no missiles, questions over the ability to develop Trident replacement etc. There isn't even the budget to man the carriers if they ever complete with the limited number of F35 pilots. No direct Nimrod replacement yet years after it was scrapped. The list goes on, and this is just the obvious reported failings it is easily imagined that the shore installations have been equally cut.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-07 08:33:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> More Porsches and yachts for BAe (and other providers) Execs and shareholders. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-06 21:31:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You thought you ordered cake but we were all out of cake. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-03 18:16:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> More fake news from the Indy. Clicks Ahoy!!!! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-03 16:22:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Perhaps they should work harder to become citizens, add value to the community rather than leeching off real citizens hard work. Edit : jesus, in a sub about movies talking about starship troopers didn't realize /s was required.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-03 16:18:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Looks like you are ready to do your part but whats up with u/lankist?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-03 15:30:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You asked why it was relevant and at the top of the sub. I don't think it is relevant but it fits a narrative being put about at the moment so it gets noticed and reported on. I specifically said it might be indicative ie this is what some people might say does not mean it is true. But Labour is dead in Scotland. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-03 14:59:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Because it might be indicative of the death of Labour because of Corbyn or further back Blair, some might say the party has become over concerned with identity politics and issues of importance to middle class left wing intellectuals. It is dead in Scotland for the same reason, after 40 years of taking the "workers" for granted they are now being rejected.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-03 13:27:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Fucking Independent spamming their shit everywhere like the Daily Mail. Clickbait bullshit. They know exactly what they are doing and it is all about getting noticed and ad revenue. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-03 10:59:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> They will be told that China is the best, everyone is out to do China down including foreign media that just want to stir things up with fake news. By stopping the foreign fake news they are protecting China and the Chinese way of life which has radically improved in the last 10 years. So they are patriots and in the long run everyone will benefit. - is what they are told. Or they are thugs getting paid by the local powers that be to maintain their position and control. A mix of both.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-03 10:52:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You seem to have issues but you know the cooks, blanket stackers, drivers, signallers are also professional soldiers and I am pretty sure they don't do surviving for a month in the jungle, call in artillery etc Not everyone is like a character in COD. Nip down to the stores in your ninja unit and get the storeman to nav to the RV in the jungle whilst doing CAS missions...thought so. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-03 10:24:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Soviets did fine in Afghanistan until the Mujaheddin were given anti tank missiles, anti air weapons and training.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-02 13:07:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Can't help but think this is not the way to go for data security. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-02 10:19:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It always appeared to me that some idealists/radicals were manipulated by the rich and powerful to shape things to suit themselves. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-02 08:50:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> And? So is the military but you go with what you have. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-01 19:54:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> TBH the UK is one of the largest donors helping hundreds of thousands of displaced Syrians actually survive by giving money to aid agencies and UN etc. This is actual money not tied to buying uk produce, not tied to uk employees but given to UN aid agencies to buy tents food water etc.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-01 19:50:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The military employs a very small amount of people, local government, government bodies and the NHS employ millions. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-01 10:00:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Or just have more and better secret service agents. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-01 09:59:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Roosevelt vs Putin death match needed. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-01 09:56:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> A climber friend rates them, I have Millet prolighter 38+10 and the brand is good build and top quality. I think the trilogy 35 is top loading no top lid. If that works for you it is a good bag. Cilogear bag looks awesome though but probably more expensive? My only concern about Millet bags is if half full it can be hard cinching them down to make a tight pack stopping them being a bit "wobbly". </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-01 09:10:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Narc detected, informing copblock </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-01 08:51:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Soft and hard power combine to ensure victory. The military in the cold war achieved parity preventing old school military victory. In the end it was an economic and cultural victory that lead to the collapse of the soviet union.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-28 10:45:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The Lords (unelected) itself recognises it does not exist to challenge the supremacy of Parliment (elected). Edit : sorry to annoy how someone feels and get dv but this is the key reason why the vote went the way it did. The Lords is there to help amend govt legislation so it complies with law and there are no glaring unintended consequences. It is not a second chamber to block things people disagree with. It is not like USA.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-28 09:08:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> In the UK looking down the scope of a rifle at people to see them better, for example thieves or poachers 600m away, can be viewed as assault leading to lose of guns and a conviction. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
