<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject9714</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-10 14:12:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So you are a child. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-10 13:57:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Flynn hasn't been charged with anything at this point in time.  Congress has learned their lesson with Oliver North.  He was given immunity then got off scot free when new revelations came up.  That will not happen with Flynn. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-10 13:52:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> For a foreign minster to meet the President at the White House breaks protocol.  It is one thing for equals to meet (no problem), but for lower rank person to meet the President, this is huge.  No conspiracy here, no? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-10 13:46:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Are you a child? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-10 13:44:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> "Lock her up!"  Today, they are supporting Hillary.  Funny! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-10 13:42:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Your argument is weak.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-10 13:35:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I don't count calories.  I eat to satiety.  For example, for breakfast I make a bowl of 4 eggs, 1/2 pound sausage, large cooking spoon of olive oil (about 8 tablespoons), 4 tablespoons of butter, and some veggies like carrots, and kale.  This is probably about 4,000 calories or so.  I eat as much as I can until I can't eat any more.  Typically, I will eat about half of it and save the rest for later.  Point is that I'm not hungry again for 6 hours or so.  This meal is nutrient dense and satiating.  I don't "diet" on feasting day.  Hormones are more important than calories.  If a person is hungry, they will eat.  If a person eats sugar and carbs, in an hour or so, they will be hungry again.  Regulating the hormones is very important. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-10 13:19:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm not aware of any Democrats stating Comey should be fired. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-10 13:15:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Trump says "lock her up!" about Hillary, and now he supports her in firing Comey.  WTF!! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-10 13:13:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The thing with cover-ups is that they don't get easier as time goes along. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-10 13:11:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Trump says this, but he also says "lock her up!"  WTF!! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Comey Firing Spurs Calls for Special Prosecutor in Russia Probe </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-10 13:08:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-10 11:58:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Since changing my diet, I have found how much eating sugar and carbs makes a person hungry.  If I eat carbs, I am hungry again in an hour or two.  I was eating 6 times a day just because I was hungry.  That was crazy.  The food corporations like it.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-10 11:38:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I hope Price and Conway are okay...you know being yelled at and all. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-10 11:36:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> "I'm not a crook!"
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-10 11:33:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> ["I'm not a crook" Trump is a genius.](http://i.imgur.com/BWmeRKm.jpg) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-10 11:26:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Nixon lasted less than a year after firing the investigator.  Tick-tock. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-10 11:25:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What does the Master suggest that I do next? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Trump to meet Russian Foreign Minister Sergey Lavrov at the White House </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-10 11:12:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Signs promoting diversity in Delano Public Schools face community pushback </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-09 20:35:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-09 20:30:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Having a good command of the English language is generally a sign of intelligence, no? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> A lot of research shows that putting 13 male senators in charge of a health-care bill is a lousy idea </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-09 18:44:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-09 15:41:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Conservatives are champions of fake issues #bathrooms #sharia #voterfraud #Benghazi #Ebola #PlannedParenthood
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-09 14:28:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That is just like your opinion man! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-09 14:21:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Every time I see "Donald Trump says..." I know either he is lying or he is wrong.  WTF!! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-09 14:18:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Obama didn't want Trump to hire Flynn.  Trump hates Obama so much that he hired Flynn.  To fire Flynn would prove Obama was right.  That's gotta hurt.  Oh, well.
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-09 14:14:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Fox News is in the "Business of Anger".  What should you be enraged about today?  There's an entire business...a huge industry, actually...that bases all that it does on getting you p!$$ed off! They are all variations of the same thing: people in an industry who want you to believe their function is to "move the public dialogue forward" or to "make an opinion count on your behalf"...blah blah blah. But NO!

Their sole function is to make you angry. That's right. Get your dander up. Get you riled up and feeling as though you're right and all those other asses are wrong - and stupid! In turn, they hope that you'll pay more and more attention to them - while they reinforce your growing anger and disillusionment - and give them big ratings and more money from their advertisers. It is a business.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Jurassic Coast, Dorset </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-09 14:10:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Forget Taxes, Warren Buffett Says. The Real Problem Is Health Care. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-09 14:09:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Forget Taxes, Warren Buffett Says. The Real Problem Is Health Care. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-09 13:55:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-08 17:36:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Trump says he hires the best people.  WTF!! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-08 17:32:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Putin wanted him in the WH? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-08 17:29:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> All Trump does is lie! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-08 16:59:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Well, there still is the British Commonwealth. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The Value of Crossing the Difference Divide Between People in Different Tribes </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-08 14:58:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-08 14:19:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> "Your eyes are lying to you!"
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-08 14:18:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> After seeing Trump and the USA, France woke up and smelled the coffee.
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-08 12:17:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> How do humans make it through famines without destroying their liver?  WTF!! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-07 17:12:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Breakfast is like dessert.  When I was eating low fat, I was hungry all the time.  I ate every 2 - 3 hours.  WTF!!!  Food corporations like it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-07 17:09:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Many women love sexy legs.  Spending some time on a bike will build leg muscles.  

Carbs make a person puffy.  Low carb, and/or keto diet will get rid of the puffiness. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-07 17:04:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The record is something like 382 days.  If a person has a lot of body fat, it is doable.  Good luck! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-07 16:54:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If a person feels low energy or lethargic, this is a sign of low electrolytes.  I dab a little salt on my tongue and let it melt when this happens.  In minutes, I feel much better.

Further, after 2 days norepinephrine increases and so does metabolic rate.  This will keep a person amped up.  It makes it hard to sleep.  [Fasting Physiology](https://intensivedietarymanagement.com/fasting-physiology-part-ii/)

[Fasting Myths](https://intensivedietarymanagement.com/fasting-myths-part-5/) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-07 16:47:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> A person would have to write an book to answer all the questions.  Dr. Fung has done just that.  [Complete Guide to Fasting](https://www.amazon.com/Complete-Guide-Fasting-Intermittent-Alternate-Day/dp/1628600012/) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Bill to declare Israel a Jewish state back on national agenda - "A ministerial committee approved a revised version of a bill first proposed in 2011 that declares the "State of Israel is the national home of the Jewish people"..." </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-07 16:30:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Health Care Vote Takes Away GOPs Offensive Campaign Message </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-07 14:43:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-07 14:34:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Donald Trump is a good fellow. He is said to occasionally wave as he passes by in his chauffeur driven limousine. "The common man is revolting" is his favorite saying.
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Did Macron Outsmart Campaign Hackers? - "part of the Macron campaign strategy against Fancy Bear (also known as Pawn Storm and Apt28) was to sign on to the phishing pages and plant bogus information." </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-07 14:31:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Republicans take aim at school nutrition standards, opening bigger debate </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-07 14:30:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Did Macron Outsmart Campaign Hackers? - "part of the Macron campaign strategy against Fancy Bear (also known as Pawn Storm and Apt28) was to sign on to the phishing pages and plant bogus information." </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-07 13:48:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-07 13:43:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Ken Ham is delicious! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Creationist Ken Ham: Intolerant Atheists Are Bullying Christians By Asking For Equal Treatment </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-07 13:43:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-07 13:39:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Exactly!! In court, the prosecution should prove the god exists before they can prosecute a person for blasphemy, no? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-07 13:38:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> In court, the prosecution should prove the god exists before they can prosecute a person for blasphemy, no? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-07 13:36:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Eugenics - aims at improving the genetic quality of the human population.  WTF!! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-07 13:32:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> In the Republican world, we need to kick the poor to the curb and give the rich more money.  Stop being poor! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-07 13:27:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Dems need to target a few Senators to block getting 50 votes.  The Senate Republican healthcare plan will still be a disaster.  Republicans have already proven they don't have a heart. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-07 13:22:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It is a good idea to vote for the person the Russian hackers oppose. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-07 13:19:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Trump bans people from entering the USA except if you are rich and not brown. WTF!!! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-07 13:18:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Trump bans people from entering the USA except if you are rich and not brown. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> That other time President Trump got his Civil War facts all wrong </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-07 12:52:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> That other time President Trump got his Civil War facts all wrong </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-07 12:49:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-06 17:39:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> A person doesn't need to exercise to lose weight.  Just sit on the sofa and watch TV.  If your insulin is low, body fat will melt off.

The best exercise that I know of, the biggest bang for least effort, is lifting weights.  A person can do in 30 minutes, 5 exercises, 5 sets, 5 reps a set and get real results in a period of time. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-05 19:01:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Actually the cost of universal healthcare would be much lower than what people are currently paying for health insurance. Instead of paying $500-$1000 a month for a family, it is around $50-$100 a month for a family. This is what my friends who live in other countries pay for healthcare for a family and they are getting the same thing Americans get, but we pay more. We also have to pay 10%-20% of the bill. WTF!! Their overall costs per person are lower because the insurance pool is much bigger when everyone is in it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-05 16:09:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The GOP is heartless.  It is also very bad politics.  WTF!!! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> ACLU won't sue, says 'religious freedom' order was 'elaborate photo-op' </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-05 14:51:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> ACLU won't sue, says 'religious freedom' order was 'elaborate photo-op' </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-05 14:50:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Jesus Shouldve Started With an Appetizer </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-05 14:39:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What Happens To Obamacare Repeal Now In The Senate? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-05 14:36:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The difference between calorie restriction and fasting </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-05 14:34:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-05 14:22:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Before fasting, for a couple days eat an avocado a day. I eat half at a meal. They have a lot of potassium.  This will compliment the salt. It will help the body keep homeostasis. 

For sleeping I found this supplement to work very good. [Coral Calcium] 
 (http://www.wellnessresources.com/products/coral_calcium.php)
It is a mix of calcium and magnesium.  The magnesium will relax the body.  The calcium causes neurons in the brain to fire randomly.  I have good deep sleep and dreams when using this product.  I love it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-05 14:15:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> To keep going, it is okay to eat a little something.  Perhaps protein with butter, coconut oil, and MCT oil.  It can keep the train going down the track.  Carbs make a person hungry. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-05 14:12:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This broth tastes very good, but it is expensive. https://www.barebonesbroth.com/shop.html
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-05 14:07:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Trumpcare is heartless.  It is also very bad politics.  WTF!! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [Science] David Ludwig, MD, PhD -- Which Comes First: Overeating or Obesity? - Good video contrasting the calorie model with the insulin/carb model of obesity. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-05 12:22:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=Zpi5Lir_eJs
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Every Republican who voted for this abomination must be held accountable </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-05 11:46:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-05 01:20:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What are the people who voted for him thinking? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-05 01:16:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> People will die quicker thus saving money.  Sad! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Roger Penrose On Why Consciousness Does Not Compute </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-04 18:03:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-04 16:37:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Back in the day when I was born, my parents costs was $500 and my mother was able to stay in the hospital for a couple days.  Things have changed. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The First 162: Byron Buxton - "Buxton has 2.7 WARP through 162 games without hitting." </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-04 16:20:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> U.S. jobless claims fall, continuing claims hit 17-year low </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-04 15:03:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [Science] A Low-Carbohydrate Ketogenic Diet Combined with 6-Weeks of Crossfit Training Improves Body Composition and Performance </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-04 14:39:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> https://www.clinmedjournals.org/articles/ijsem/international-journal-of-sports-and-exercise-medicine-ijsem-3-054.php
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Science Nerd Hopes to Unseat Congress' Most Detested Science Denier </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-04 14:36:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> New Calls for Public Access to Secret Congressional Reports </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-04 14:24:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The painter Pierre Bonnard has not seen a cat in real life. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-04 13:13:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-04 12:55:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It is their healthcare plan...bootstraps for everyone. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-04 12:52:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> "Obama was born in Kenya." </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-04 12:50:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> A really shitty healthcare bill is a win??? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-04 12:48:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Keep Trump busy with other things, he won't notice.  The man has no plan. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-04 12:45:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Republicans are boot-strappy people. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-04 12:38:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> She is good with empty platitudes. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> In a day of frantic tweets, a senator pleaded with Trump to stop a deportation. It didnt seem to work. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-04 12:29:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-03 17:22:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Bone broth is good. This stuff is good, but expensive (https://www.barebonesbroth.com/shop.html).  I make cheesecake with almost no sugar.  I eat a little with MCT and coconut oil. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Mississippi Funeral Home Sued After Allegedly Refusing to Transport and Cremate Body of Gay Man </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-03 15:08:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Why the U.S. pays more for health care than the rest of the world </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-03 14:53:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Trump: FBI director Comey gave Clinton 'free pass for many bad deeds' </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-03 14:37:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> How the Affordable Care Act Drove Down Personal Bankruptcy </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-03 14:34:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-03 11:33:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [It's all that...](http://i.imgur.com/Fs5sFjM.jpg) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-02 15:50:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> And frankly they should. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-02 15:48:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That is not funny. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-02 15:47:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> "Patriotism is the willingness to kill and be killed for trivial reasons." - Bertrand Russell  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-02 15:45:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What power does Ivanka really have? She doesn't have a budget or anything so she will not be able to do hardly anything in Washington. All she can do is go to meetings and give empty platitudes. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-02 15:44:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It his bubble, people don't tell him that the things he is saying are stupid and don't make any sense.  He doesn't have any friends. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> How the Omnibus Became a Democratic Wish List </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-02 14:37:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-02 13:46:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Joe Mauer will make $23 million this year playing baseball.  WTF!! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-02 13:44:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> "My IQ is one of the highest  and you all know it! Please don't feel so stupid or insecure; it's not your fault." - Donald J. Trump. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-02 13:42:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> "When is the next pee party, Boss?" </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-02 13:40:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It is clear, Republicans have no heart. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-02 13:38:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Joe Mauer will make $23 million this year to play baseball.  WTF!! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-02 13:35:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If GOP passes this shitty healthcare bill, I'm sure Democrats will not use this in the next election against them.  /s
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Congress Allocates $120 Million for Trump Familys Security Costs </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-02 11:35:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-01 16:54:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [Snowflake!!!](https://i.imgur.com/LVpQl0o.jpg) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-01 16:51:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Apparently, he didn't even read the Cliff Notes version. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-01 16:50:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> "Inevitable"??  Seriously, Trump is not an idealogue.  He appears to like the attention and doing rallies.  But, judging from his actions, he doesn't really know what he is doing. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The Daily: An Illuminating Drive Across Venezuela - "Mr. Casey gives his close-up account of what has gone wrong in Venezuela, and he tells us the story of a drive across the country that illustrated the problems." </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-01 16:45:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The Daily: An Illuminating Drive Across Venezuela - "Mr. Casey gives his close-up account of what has gone wrong in Venezuela, and he tells us the story of a drive across the country that illustrated the problems." </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-01 16:44:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-01 16:31:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> "My IQ is one of the highest  and you all know it! Please don't feel so stupid or insecure; it's not your fault." - Donald J. Trump. [Link](https://twitter.com/realdonaldtrump/status/332308211321425920?lang=en) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Minnesota Republicans attempt to skirt environmental review of new tar sands pipelines </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-01 16:25:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Neil deGrasse Tyson, Without Saying Atheist, Told CBS Why He Doesnt Believe in a Creator </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-01 15:13:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Today, May 1st is Labor Day in just about every country on Earth except the USA. Funny thing, it started in the USA at the Haymarket Riot in Chicago where people were striking for a 8 hour workday. WTF! </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-01 15:11:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Haymarket_affair
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-01 14:41:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What power does Ivanka really have?  She doesn't have a budget or anything so she will not be able to do hardly anything in Washington.  All she can do is go to meetings and give empty platitudes. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> How Trump Became the Vacillator in Chief </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-01 14:37:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-01 13:59:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Electric cars can't get here fast enough. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-01 13:58:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Would Trump golf with Stalin to grease the wheels to get a new hotel in Moscow? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-01 13:56:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Wall Street is not really into long-term financial progress.  Show me the money! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Ellison's losing bid to run Democratic National Committee came with heavy price tag </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-01 13:53:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-01 13:50:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This is why I am a liberal democrat in JFK's words: "If by a liberal you mean someone who looks ahead and not behind, someone who welcomes new ideas without rigid reactions, someone who cares about the welfare of the people-their health, their housing, their schools, their jobs, their civil rights, their civil liberties...if that is what you mean by "liberal", then I am proud to be a liberal."
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-01 13:47:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If the GOP passes the Trumpcare bill, it should be easy to take the House...one would think.
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Where Totem Poles Are a Living Art (and Relics Rest in Peace) </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-01 12:25:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Something I found that made fasting easier for me. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-01 12:16:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Take That, Washington! Texas Looks To Nullify Federal Laws </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-01 11:38:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-30 20:39:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> A person has to be careful when refeeding on an extended fast.  Karen Carpenter died when she was taken to a hospital and they started to feed her.  The food pulled electrolytes out of her body and she died.  Eat slow after a long fast. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Amid hungry, violent looting, Venezuelan shopkeepers fortify their businesses </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-30 17:34:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-30 12:55:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What a cry baby. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Analysis shows declining engagement with Trump's tweets </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-29 17:02:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Non-profit group says Lonsdale sports complex partnership violates constitution </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-28 23:12:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The City of Knoxville (TN) Plans to Spend $2 Million on a Christian Sports Complex - "The Emerald Youth Foundation describes itself as a Christian, urban youth ministry that desire[s] to raise up a large number of urban youth to love Jesus Christ." </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-28 23:09:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> How a tariff on Canadian lumber could backfire on the U.S. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-28 16:44:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> As GOP Tax Overhaul Shapes Up, Democrats Push To End The Tax Return </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-28 16:23:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-28 15:27:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> John Oliver uncovers the truth about Ivanka and Jared: [Youtube](https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=wD8AwgO0AQI) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-28 15:19:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It just shows that he really doesn't put any thought into anything he does.  Right now, he just cares about how things are going play on Fox   Friends. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-28 15:14:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> "Capitalism: God's way of determining who is smart and who is poor." - Ron Swanson </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-28 14:19:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I like Obamacare more than the Republican "I Don't Care". </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-28 14:18:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I think he just likes going to rallies. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> A Saudi Arabian man has been sentenced to death after insulting Muhammad on Twitter </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-27 18:46:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Michael Flynn didn't just break the law in taking payments from Russiahe was warned in advance </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-27 18:39:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Texas mayor blasted after she says lack of faith in God causes poverty </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-27 16:45:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Texas mayor blasted after she says lack of faith in God causes poverty </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-27 16:44:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-27 16:19:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> In school they say Christopher Columbus discovered America, but there were already people living here when he arrived.  WTF! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Trump Says U.S. Will Terminate NAFTA if Talks Fail </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-27 16:14:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-27 15:21:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> "My IQ is one of the highest  and you all know it! Please don't feel so stupid or insecure; it's not your fault." - Donald J. Trump.

[Source](https://twitter.com/realdonaldtrump/status/332308211321425920?lang=en) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-27 14:59:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> "My IQ is one of the highest  and you all know it! Please don't feel so stupid or insecure; it's not your fault." - Donald J. Trump.

[Source](https://twitter.com/realdonaldtrump/status/332308211321425920?lang=en) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-27 14:54:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> How many Russians have condos at Mar-a-Lago?  Lots!

https://www.usatoday.com/story/news/world/2016/12/15/donald-trump-russia-wealthy-condo-buyers/95464922/
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-27 14:46:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> When Trump's tax acts get passed and spending is not cut, the USA will be like Kansas.  Good luck!  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-27 14:41:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> "Capitalism: God's way of determining who is smart and who is poor." - Ron Swanson </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-27 14:35:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> How much work would it be to vet these guys before putting them on the air?  Further, they look kinda puffy to be "fitness experts".  TV news people are so gullible.
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [Science] Hungry stomach hormone (ghrelin) promotes growth of new brain cells </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-27 12:21:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> https://www.newscientist.com/article/2128695-hungry-stomach-hormone-promotes-growth-of-new-brain-cells/

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-26 17:19:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If a family has many children, how would they pay for school? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-26 17:16:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The USA should match what Mexico will pay. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-26 17:15:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Is this really what people want?  It will put Republicans in a death wobble. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-26 15:23:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Donald Trump is winning! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-26 15:21:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Donald Trump is a good fellow. He is said to occasionally wave as he  passes by in his chauffeur driven limousine. "The common man is revolting" is his favorite saying. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-26 14:51:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Cha-Ching! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-26 14:50:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Never let the truth get in the way of a good story. - Mark Twain </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-26 14:49:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> "Let them eat cake!" </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Should Democrats Turn to South Carolinas Special Election Next? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-26 14:17:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-26 14:14:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Trump is winning! /s

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-26 14:12:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> "I don't know what it means to be complicit" - Ivanka
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-26 11:55:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I like Obamacare more than the Republican "I Don't Care". </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-26 00:45:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Snowflake!! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> State Department uses government website to promote Trumps private country club </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-24 23:05:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> USS Carl Vinson begins drills with Japanese destroyers </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-24 19:35:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-24 18:42:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> We need a President who can put sentences together to make a coherent thought. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-24 18:39:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Who knew being President was so complicated? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-24 18:38:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> People will need to buy some boot straps.  /s
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Obama To Deliver First Post-Presidency Speech In Chicago </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-24 15:51:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Shutdown Under GOP Control Could Be Historic </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-24 15:36:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-24 15:24:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> "Mexico won't pay for it. Democrats hate it. Border-state Republicans don't like it. Congressional Republican leaders would rather not undertake it. There could be an avoidable government shutdown over it."  Looks like if it happens that it will be Trump's Folly. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The first brick hasnt been set, and Trumps border wall is already going south on him - "Mexico won't pay for it. Democrats hate it. Border-state Republicans don't like it. Congressional Republican leaders would rather not undertake it. There could be an avoidable government shutdown over it." </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-24 15:22:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Report: Mystery Shell Company Snapped Up 11 Trump Condos Before Election </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-22 15:11:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-22 15:03:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If they don't cut spending too then it will be like people using their credit card.  It cost money to borrow money. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-22 15:00:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Some friend.  Didn't invite him to his funeral.  WTF! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-22 14:58:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Don't think Trump will listen to Raygun.  Raygun called Russia the evil empire. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-22 14:56:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Christians are used to being lied too. How do they tell which parts of the bible to follow, and which parts to ignore?

Matthew (27:52-53) "The graves were opened; and **MANY** bodies of the saints which slept arose, and came out of the graves after his resurrection, and went into the holy city, and appeared unto **MANY**." 

Hello historians! How'd you miss that? Zombies. Roaming around. Seen by **MANY**!!

Not a fucking peep about it anywhere but Matthew.

Seems legit.

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Dem senator: Trump's border wall 'just a stupid use of money' </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-22 14:42:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-22 14:42:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This is why we can't have good things. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-22 01:55:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Russian propaganda is strong with this one. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-22 01:51:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> West coast liberals do very good too. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-22 01:47:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Or religious law? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Winning! Trump, GOP Congress Are 0-4 On Major Campaign Pledges </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-21 15:20:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-21 15:19:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> One nation, under Canada... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Chaffetz Departure Opens Coveted Oversight Chairmanship </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-21 14:07:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> South Korea to Trump: Weve never been part of China </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-21 11:47:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-20 15:49:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Venezuela is a beautiful country and the people are very nice. To bad they have to go through this shit. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-20 14:51:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Donald Trump is a good fellow. He is said to occasionally wave as he  passes by in his chauffeur driven limousine. "The common man is revolting" is his favorite saying.
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-20 14:16:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Why are Trump's ratings low?  Everyone can now see that he is irresponsible, unrealistic, naive, petulant, childish, vindictive, prejudiced, bigoted, racist, Islamophobic, anti-Semitic, misogynistic, fascistic, authoritarian, insensitive, erratic, disturbed, irrational, inhuman individual.  WTF! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-20 14:08:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If you can't do the time, don't do the crime. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> D.C. Home Rule Advocates to Continue Fight After Chaffetz Retirement Announcement </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-20 12:05:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-20 11:59:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> He must be a joy to live with. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
