<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject3414</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-12 13:46:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-09-14 07:20:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This bikini looks great.
Tell me where I can buy it already!!!! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-09-09 01:56:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Oh really, hrmm I think im going to have to invest in getting some.
How did it last throughout the day?
I get the worst oily nose after around an hour of having foundation of, despite trying numerous primers..  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-09-08 05:22:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> How do you go using the Kat Von D foundation?
Would it be good for oily skin?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Starting a businesses for detailing any ideas on a good name? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-09-03 04:17:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-08-21 08:55:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Are you running spacers with this? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-08-20 05:39:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Can someone explain to me what all these 'Epic Rewards' posts are about??  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-08-19 03:47:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> LOVE this!
Looking at doing this change myself, starting tomorrow!
How did you go with putting the colour on top of the brown? Did you bleach it first?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-08-03 02:54:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You can get a straw though it, thats crazy!!  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-31 05:00:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yes can confirm I have boobies and a vagina, and I am a girl. 
I drive an impreza, but looking to get an Evo 9 soon. 

Oh why thank you, thats so nice of you to do that!
Looking at something more small and dainty in gold, but thats great, good work!  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-31 02:29:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> life partner, its my boyfriends car.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> My partners Nissan Silvia s15. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-30 04:12:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-30 04:05:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> blend blend blend blend blend!
This has the potential to be a beautiful look!
The three colours you've put together look really good, just blend them all together for a smooth transition between colours :)  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-01 02:01:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Maybe I'll look into it some more!

Oh really, I've heard of Insanity, but i'm always a bit like hrmm is this just a gimmick? So thanks! I might get it!  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-29 08:31:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Did you find calorie counting hard, it seems like such a hard thing to do to me haha 
Do you have any of the programs you used for the HIIT and strength training?!  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-29 05:21:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Wow!
This is fantastic! It took you only 8 months to lose it, this is amazing to me! What changes did you make to get rid of it weight?!!  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-02 05:15:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Can you please do a youtube channel of your looks!
They are amazing, and im so obsessed with all your posts!  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-22 03:40:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Oh thats good to hear!
I want to wear it down straight away, but like two days later i'm going to have to put it up for work, so im hoping it wont be too hard to force it up for a few weeks after that!  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-22 02:40:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thank you for posting this!
I such a doing anything remotely good with eye shadows. And this actually really helped me. 
It was super simple and I actually kinda did some decent eye stuff this morning!
Also, love your septum! Did it hurt when you got it done?
Im thinking of getting mine pierced. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-18 05:13:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You need to post this in r/makeupaddiction!
Its amazing and they will love it! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-07 02:23:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thanks for being honest! Much appreciated!  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-07 02:23:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thank you for your honesty!  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-06 06:56:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That looks really good! 
What size is yours?
Im reading about all these different sizes/gauges, and I'm only wanting something small.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-06 06:29:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I wouldnt say your face looks crowded at all!
You look amazing :)   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Wanting to get my septum pierced, do you think it will suit? (xpost r/piercing) </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-06 06:26:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-06 06:18:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> How did you find it getting it done?
I'm so nervous about the whole thing. Havent got my appointment booked yet, but I am really considering it!  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Wanting to get my septum pierced, do you think it will suit? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-06 05:14:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-05 05:07:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Ahhhhhmazing. 
Im thinking of getting my septum pierced because of this now. Looks really classy, yet still a bit edgy. 
LOVE LOVE LOVE! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-16 11:59:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I just left everything behind, my family, my friends, my job, everything. All for someone who I thought was going to be this great amazing guy. He is still a good one, but I dont think he is for me. 
And now after moving (1 month living together now), I feel its too early to back out.. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-02 04:12:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-27 05:36:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Such a great idea. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-27 05:11:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Oooo! LED collar is a great idea as soon I will be introducing our dog to camping :)  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-27 05:11:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> No budget, just nothing overly expensive. 
I do go with my partner, and we by boat and 4WD.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-27 03:48:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This is actually a really really good idea!
Thank you!! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Camping gift ideas? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-27 00:01:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Wanting to get a couple gifts for my partner that are camping related.
I'm new to the whole camping thing and have no idea what would be a good present to get.
If you have any ideas it would be much appreciated! :)  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-16 05:43:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Fit it with a lip from a DC2R because thats what I read on heaps of forums, but its not :( 
The article says its a custom made lip front, but the owner wont tell anybody! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Can anyone tell me what this front lip set up is? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-16 04:38:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-08 23:57:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Jesus christ, you are absolutely stunning!  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-07 06:48:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> ooo! Give me your secret! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-07 06:27:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Also still in Australia.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-07 04:37:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Still a better love story than Twilight.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-12-03 01:02:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Im so glad I kept scrolling and saw this comment. 
Thank you! I think im too focused of finding 'the one'. I need to enjoy the relationship Im in now, and take it each day as it comes. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-12-02 01:56:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I say that we are just 'together'. Like i'll send him a text and say something along the lines of "cant wait to be together on the weekend babe x". But now that you've brought it to my attention it does me sense that he would feel that way as we do just chill out. So thank you for commenting, because I hadnt thought of it that way!  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-12-01 23:33:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I've been on a weight loss journey for a while now, lost about 6kgs, and did not lose any of my boobs, just make sure you do some chest presses to keep them up and perky! :) 
I found mine have been sitting nicer since doing chest press  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-12-01 01:47:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yes.
We dated on and off for two years. It took him a very long time to be open with it, and once I realised, it became more obvious to me he needed help which he would not seek. 
There was a lot of deceitful things on his behalf and was the end of our relationship. 
He cheated on me with his ex, to whom he was engaged to before he went into the military. I think in the end he was trying to get the life he had back before the military.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-12-01 01:41:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> When he says "Cant wait to hang out on the weekend". 
We are in a long distance relationship, I feel like Im one of the boys when he says 'hangout'. In my eyes we are together on the weekends. Friends 'hangout', not couples.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-11-27 06:07:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You should become a doctor.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-11-24 02:20:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> In case anyone is wondering. 
I am his third owner, his previous owners did not have the time to give him the attention he needs. 
He is Rottweiler x German Shepard, and he is 3.5 years old.
Biggest gentle giant i've ever met, loves to give all the cuddles, and always is smiling. 
Very grateful to be his forever mum.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Adopted this guy yesterday, Reddit say hi to Brax! </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-11-24 01:15:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-11-18 22:44:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Ahaha dont worry, i'd totally forgotten too!
Thank you :)  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-11-05 22:51:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yes please! That would be great :) 
What kind of beef cut did you use?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-11-05 05:08:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This looks amazing! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-10-31 02:07:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  It wont be till sometime next week or a bit later, but I'll inbox when Im ready to place the order :)
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-10-31 02:07:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thank you!
It wont be till sometime next week or a bit later, but I'll inbox when Im ready to place the order :) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-10-31 01:44:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yes please! 
Omg yes! :)))) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [REQUEST] ColourPop Cosmetics Lippie Stix to Australia! </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-10-31 00:11:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hey ladies :)

Just had a cart full of ColourPop Lippie Stix only to find they dont ship to Australia. Is anyone willing to purchase and send me what I was after, and I will tip the user who does. 

Thanks Xx </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-10-31 00:05:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Oooo! Thank you :)  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-10-29 23:19:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I have only just heard of Colourpop from your post. Went on their website, racked up a cart over $200 worth...... Annnnnnnd they dont ship to Australia. DEVASTATED!  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-10-24 02:55:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Im so sorry for your loss. 
3 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-10-22 00:19:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Short hair really suits you! :)  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-10-14 04:42:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> At first I was like "wow, this person has had the same experience as me!", then I saw your username. Well played. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> To those who chose their career over love, how'd it turn out? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-10-14 04:23:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-10-09 02:37:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Once born, the only certainty is that you're going to die.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-10-02 07:45:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I constantly compare my current relationship to my last one.
Safe to say its making things difficult.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-10-01 02:52:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Ah, my hometown Mildura! 
Yeah, magpies here are cunts. 
There isnt really anything that will stop them, they will swoop you no matter what.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-09-30 02:39:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> seriously, what are your thoughts about what has happened?


Australian here, I have no idea what you are even talking about, what has happened?   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-09-30 01:21:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Ahaha MCM is awesome hey! They guys do great stuff!
What a shame, but its one of those things that going to happen at car meets, everyone wants to show what they can do. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-09-29 08:56:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> As someone who is in a long distance relationship thinking i've found "the one", this scares the crap out of me. 
Hope you are doing okay, and here if you need a chat, always! x </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-09-29 07:47:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Great video man!
Wish Australia could do something like this without cops defecting everyone. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-09-25 07:18:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I cant be the only one who buys high-waisted shorts to help smooth over my lumps and bumps right?? 
As soon as I put them on, I feel like my 'love handles' are not noticeable anymore!  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-09-25 03:02:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What did you say to the stylist once you saw how bad it was? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-09-25 00:56:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I would be devastated if that was me :(  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-09-24 08:28:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I also tried for the first time on the weekend. 
Oh, the pain. Never again.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-09-18 08:29:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> YOU GO GIRL! 
I'm the exact same (20yr old btw). My lower back. SO MUCH PAIN.
I need to get them reduced.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-09-17 08:15:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Im going through this process at the moment and so confused what to do. 
Normally I've been able good vibe on how my SO is feeling or thinking, but with my current boyfriend, I cant get anything from him. Worries me that there is still something there, and he's not owning up to it. Makes it worse when we do distance and his ex and him live in the same town with a small population.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-09-17 07:56:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I guess you could say shes like riding a new kind of pony.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-09-17 01:12:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Everything you're saying is so damn spot on!
Guess Im just a bit paranoid about it all. 
Thanks :)  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Do you follow your head, your heart, or your gut? (x-post r/askwomenadvice </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-09-16 02:08:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-09-16 01:11:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Well I have some sort of trust issues due to an ex. 
So im not sure if i'm over thinking things and freaking myself out or not..  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
