<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject6257</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-07 20:49:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If it had "Death Wallet" instead. damn. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Manga english release? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-07 01:26:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Could the manga get a English release? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-06 21:52:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I wrote Arifureta Shokugyou de Sekai Saikyou (Manga) in the section that said "What series do you want Seven Seas to licence?" 

Is it good like that? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-06 21:30:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> How? Can you please link me? 

Or can you open a forum or something with a poll of votes that want a english licence? You know if this subreddit got a group together to advertise (lol) the manga so it gets populair so english publishers could notice the amount of people who talk about it on the internet. Maybe then a cheeky licence? (I'm desperate for the manga @_@) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-06 21:23:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Oh shit. I STILL HOPE FOR DAT ENGLISH LICENCE DOE i wanna have a physical releases of the manga so bad. I LOVE THE ART HOLY HELL AND THE PLOT it's my fav manga at the moment. (Wished it got weekly released doe -.-) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-06 15:53:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Wouldn't that damage the port? Lol wtf </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-06 15:43:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> How do i clean it then? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-06 15:36:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Huh? What do you mean? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Problem with Iphone 6s sound </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-06 15:16:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> My sounds (the stereo) reverses sides sometimes i mean like some songs start from my right ear, but sometimes if i put the earplugs jack into my iphone 6s the stereo reverses and starts on my left ear (NOTE: same song)

It it because my iphone 6s sound card is broken or my earplugs? (Is the earplug's jack broken?) or is my iphone 6s headphone jack broken OR the soundcard thingy? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-06 12:48:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thanks!

Also still, the mang art used for an animation would be amazing doe. Holy hell it would get so much attention so quickly.

Also i don't think the scanlators would drop this series and on batato the scanlator's get paid right? (With ads, batato gives the money they earn from ads to the scanlators, i read that somewhere on reddit) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-05 20:31:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> 7 years? LOL that's so unfair.

Also i've read somewhere that bell has the power (is it because of the realis phrase off  does he have other secret power?) he can make his own skills by will. I mean like he wanted to be a hero so he got the argonaut skill? So is his power to develop skills by will (things he wants to achieve?) and also can he create infinite amount of skills? )i read somewhere he is a person that's born once a thousand years)

But still that is OP af creating the skills by willpower op shit </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-05 20:17:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This dude is gaining up on everyone, instoppable force. Once he reaches lvl 6 and higher, the stacking of the s/ss's of the other levels + his skills are going to make him OP af. lol i feel like everyone is going to hate bell when they find out he has the realis phrase skill, they are going to envy, hate and be jealous of him.


lol </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Bol.com or book depository </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-05 19:07:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I've been buying manga from book depository for a long time now. I wanna buy the Dragon ball/DBZ Vizbig editions, but the price is the same on Bol.com (for the dutch manga collectors, here's a question): are the manga from bol.com new or do they use old ones? (I mean like i've heard they use old books from people who returned their broken down old manga and sell them as new) so should i use bol.com for my Vizbig editions or book depository?

Btw: (i wanna use bol.com ONLY for my vizbig/omni bus and box set's because they have the same price and i won't have to wait for the shipping from book depository lol, the normal manga from book depository are like 5-8 euro's while bol.com is like 10-12 euro's, but the omnibus/vizbig and box set's stay the same price. book depository is cheaper (and brand new quality) for buying single volume manga's) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Questions again </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-05 16:10:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> - Could the manga get a english release? I mean like it's getting really populair
- Also while it gets this licenced, maybe a Anime adaption? I mean like the manga art would be awesome as a anime adaption (i really love the manga art it's beautifully done)

- ALSO could someone estimate how many days for chapter 12 to be released? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Manga questions: </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-04 21:59:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> 1: The manga is released montly, right?
2: The Manga is really getting populair huh, i mean the anime is making it really populair, any chance it could get licenced in English? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-02 02:28:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Is it a physical or digital release? (I would prefer physical).

Also, anime studios never adapt from manga adaptations of light novels. That's just not how it works. Otherwise, the manga is pretty generically rushed honestly when compared.

i know but still, the way the manga is set (the art and stuff, would be amazing as an anime adaption, I really love the art style damn).
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-02 02:17:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I hope this manga gets a english release, also the LN aswell. This series has alot of potential. An anime adaption of the manga would be awesome (i mean like the manga is already drawn so taking the art style and images and animate them, yes i know anime adaptions always happen from the LN but the manga could be a bit different, haven't read the LN yet and the manga could be better to adapt from, because studios always cut alot of material out (they leave alot of material out with other series).

Basically Manga adaption  LN adaption for an anime adaption. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-01 21:47:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Oh shit. FUK yis thanks :)

I saw on the wiki, this dude has alot of skills. But i still don't get, how did he get the iron stomach skill?(he inherits the powers of the monsters he eats) 
(he is called a new demon race "The Predator" 

Did he get the skill from that twin tail monster + the holy water thing? Or was it his own inherent power?or was is a coincidence that he got that power?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Manga questions </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-01 19:07:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> 1: Is this manga montly released?

2:I f there's a LN of this series, do yue and hajime end up together? 

3: do hajime and yue get to the surface and do his classmates see the new badass hajime_v2 (lol)  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-30 15:05:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Oh yeah TOTALLY forgot that they adapt the LN over the manga (if there's a LN of a series) (LOL i'm such a failure)..

Puttin that aside, does the Manga exactly adapt the LN, i mean the Text and stuff? Have you read the LN's? How close is the manga to the anime and LN? I haven't read the LN yet, i planning to buy 1-5 of the LN (the volumes the anime has adapted, i wanna check how much the anime has left out) and after that i'm buying 6-8 (i use bookdepository) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-30 14:46:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> IF the author decided to make it a weekly series...dude it could get famous af. I always say this, i've seen/read alot of animes/manga's, people think danmachi is that simple generic SAO-like series but it isn't..danmachi has alot of potential to become really populair.

IF the author just decided to focus more on the manga, he could get anime material out of the manga too.. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-30 13:55:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> "Too far"? 

A few chapters more lol (bell vs that invis guy and the black goliatj) after that it's after anime-material </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-28 01:58:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Np

But still i myself am not sure if it's 100% sure, you never know they may cancel it or whatever happens. (The best thing to is wait, time will tell :p). </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-28 01:35:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The Wikipedia page says it. (Not the fan Wikia btw. The actual wikipedia page Look [here](https://en.m.wikipedia.org/wiki/High_School_DxD) after the OVA Phoenix, it says:
**Studio: TNK**
**Original run: 2017 - scheduled** </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-28 01:16:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So if we get a season 2 will it cover volumes 6-10? :DD </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
