<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject419</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-08 06:22:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Urinals in england are on a timed flusher thing, say once every 5 minutes or something. Dno the actual time. I was freaked the first time i saw someone flush a urinal in a film. Thought he was just patting the pisser </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-05 02:59:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Any chance of a guide or something for the villager sorter? I had loads of trouble last time i tried, couldnt get one to work at all </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-05 01:28:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> R/unexpectedrunescape </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-03 22:37:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I really dont get how to make any sense from those numbers :/  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-03 19:50:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I wish they did! Or there was some clear  information easily found on the internet. I barely know what to put in a prospective budget, yet alone what they cost </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-03 19:38:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Cos we poor as shit so live in a council house with tiny kitchen </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-03 19:38:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Its a lot more expensive there. A 1 bed flat above a shop is 650 up ther vs like 400 here </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-03 17:42:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Is it enough to rent a house though? Wih everythig included? If you read another of my comments youll see i live in a dining room with table and fridge and such  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-03 17:35:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I dont understand </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-03 17:28:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> 40 quid a mont bike insurance, 27 phone, 80 work travel, 30 debt repayments and like 20 in game subs i think </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-03 16:10:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I live in greengates, bradford and work in knaresborough. Its a 40 mile day commute. I car share with my step dad so cant go too far from here, need to be in walkig sistance of my mothers still </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-03 16:09:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Literally just got a pay rise. I literally live in the dining room with the table and fridge and such </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-03 15:03:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I work shifts, really cant see a roommate working out too well. I think 1 beds are about 400 to 500 near me </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-03 14:52:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> At present i live at my mother and only pay 200 quid a month hiwever when i try and guestimate monthly outgoings for my own place it never looks right good. I dont know if its me beig pessemistic or not knowing what im doing or what honestly  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-03 14:51:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I live in west yorkshire, currently in my mums dining room paying 200 quid a month. Obviously thats not ideal so im trying to work out what i can afford to move out to </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> How do i live on 19k? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-03 14:48:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hi, im a 23 year old male with first propper full time job. I earn 19,420 a year before tax. I should note im bad at money to begin with, but iv sat down with a few people and tried working out a budget but it always ends up looking quite dire. Any help anyone could offer? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-01 19:40:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> In my experience thatl be the hardest thing then. Keeping your own company and keepig yourself motivated. Id also say you perhaps need to do a little more planning if you are asking these questions a week before you set off. I dont mean to put you off or anything but its a big thing for a first solo trip </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-01 19:35:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You planning on going solo? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-26 06:10:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I havent done it. I have 17 quests left to do and thats right at the top </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-23 11:58:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Whats autistic banter? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-22 16:28:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Max </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-22 04:38:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Could you imagine trying to learn a new keyboard though? That would be difficult  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-20 01:42:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Who hasnt done this with their best friend?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-19 13:07:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What sort of pvm? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-19 11:34:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> How so? Im over 2500 total, played for 12 years and my total wealth is less than 400m </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-19 11:09:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Lend me 1.3m xp for 99 plis </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-18 22:47:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I had an ileostomy for a year. I didnt have sex for a year. I couldnt imagine beig comfortable enough with a one night stand to do so </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-16 04:03:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Is it pc now? I thought itwas cw until  tommorrow </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-15 13:37:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> More like only time to ones self </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-14 15:42:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That was already my plan, to go ironman. Are there any new qiests? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Anything like a crossover guide? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-14 15:20:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Iv played rs for about 13 years and went the rs3 route when that all happened. Im now curious about oldschool and wondered if there was a sort of guide anywhere for rs3 player changing over? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-13 16:10:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I have a six fingered glove that a player found and a chance of a random encounter when someone wearing it for inigo montoya to appear and just say his piece while fighting. It hasnt happened yet but my rogue is wearing the glove so soon </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-12 14:18:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I find this works for most things, my desk is my favourite place </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-11 22:57:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I think a way to do it is to have then level 1 and tone the boss down too, it would make sense he grew in power as well as the pcs </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-11 18:29:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I wanted to do it this way cos it sounds like a cool story to me. The next part would have them in the middle of nowhere and spending time adventuring to find somewhere. The responses are all seemig pretty negative, perhaps its time i had a rethink  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Is this a bad idea? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-11 18:16:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I hD an idea for a way to start my new campain. Basically i tell my players to roll level 15 characters and we start fighting the bbeg second in comand. When they come close to winning the real bbeg teleports in, teleports the players away and strips them of gear. They basically revert back to level 1. From there they have to work there way back up, recruit npcs to help with the final battle and such like. Im worried that people will hate me for givig them so much power in the first session and then taking it away and that theyll leave straight after. What do you all think? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-11 13:07:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You used that website for this right? How did you do the paths? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-09 18:26:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Also got this noted down so they get chased by guards or someother suitable comeupance  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-09 18:25:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The absolute best thing is that the 2 guys roleplayed it wonderfully, the crazy monk who spent 25 years lost in the underdark and the high elf ranger who looks down on any other race just bouncing off each other beautifully </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-09 18:23:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I love this but would be extremely loathe to do this to a book. Would have to be like a duplicate of somethig i think </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-09 18:04:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The story was one of my party, a crazy monk, went to a woodworker and asked to see his greatest work. This turned out to be a ornate desk in the townmasters office. The desk didnt fot through the door so they had to dismantle it to carry it. The 2 of them carried it to the shop but the keeper recognised it. Refused to buy. They qent out and the monk carved his name into it and went in and bluffed his way into awllig it dor 250 gold. It was a nice desk. There was also goblin ears and a scared mayor  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-09 12:31:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I was so glad the desk thing happened. That was so much more fun than combat. We roleplayed everything and it was just awesome.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-09 09:34:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Not listening to that voice is one of the hardest things for me. But this is all helping so much. Im running this and also designing my own campain at the same time that the guys are guna do after weve finished. Im just surprised how much fun it is being dm, i always figured it would be rubbish  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-08 17:29:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Is that a runescape reference? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-06 15:22:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Mine seems to contract into a little circle. Or lay on his back legs akimbo so i wake up to his balls an inch from my face </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-06 15:03:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I have a bagle like this, except the whole size thing </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-05 21:20:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I spent over 300 quid on spuns and bonds in february </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-04 21:01:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Wow! They look ace! How long have you been designing monsters? Hows about something a little more mundane to fit a low fantasy type setting next, like different human variants or something  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-04 20:40:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I feel really bad but would really appreciate it! Thanks so much for all this, its awesome! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-04 20:14:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thanks a lot for this! Would you say some trigger for shapeshifting is needed? If so what would you suggest? Also the elk form seems a little week, having like 10% the hp of the others or something. Oh, whats paragon fury, or whatever it was? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-03 20:28:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Theres actually been very little shown of him. I read some homebrew i think, rules about a blighter. I liked the idea of an undead form and also summoning random undead animals every few turns. Other than that it should be dark and stuff lol. Id very much appreciate if you would make one :) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> How to balance the bbeg </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-03 17:02:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The bbeg for my campain is a evil druid but im struggling how to balance it to make him seem truly boss like. For a party of 5 level 15 players. Im wanting him somewhat similar to the blighter from 3.5, ie a twisted druid that gains his power by draining it from the earth, destroying it in the process

Forgot to mention, this is for a 5e campaign </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-02 12:04:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Shit the bed. Thats more than iv ever owned in my ten plus years </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-02 11:29:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Y do you care. Id have backed out right there. What did you get? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-02 10:31:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Im at 60 or so tries, a mix of 3 direct 1 powerful and either 1 bandos or 1 undead </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-01 23:49:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Am english, i use mm for anything crafts like or diy, also engineer so for work. However still use yards and miles for walking or driving distance </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-01 11:34:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Wtf even is dice gear? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-01 09:41:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Uing roll20 cos im the undociable type snd struggle to maintain relationships so i dont actually need pants! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-31 22:46:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Data. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What could i have forgotten </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-31 20:28:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Im dming my first game tommorow and starting to get very nervous. Im trying to think of what i could have forgotten in preparation and coming up dry. Any ideas what i may have overlookeds or any ither general tips for tomorow? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-31 19:57:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I use this except scavengig and looting instead if efficient and devoted </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-31 18:50:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> How long would you guess it would take to get just doing daily slayer rings? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-31 18:48:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Sos is staff of sliske? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-31 01:26:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah but is there a figure n the arce journal or something? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-31 01:06:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> How do i see the arc list?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-30 23:23:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That makes a lot of sense, given the month ahead say itd be found monday  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-30 19:26:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Ribbed for her pleasure... euwww </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-30 09:46:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Floating turtle... discworld? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Must have books for any home library </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-30 09:41:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Top 3 must haves </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-30 01:13:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What would be the top 3 books that everyone should have on there shelf in your opinion? Im looking to broaden my own collection and figured this might be a good way about it </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-30 01:10:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I havent read that in quite some time. A reread may be needed </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-29 12:13:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Cocaine </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-29 12:12:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If theres a load of washing up someone left its instant shit day </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-29 10:49:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> How can you not be good at screenshotting? You press the printscreen button... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-29 01:33:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> How do you commission these sorts of things? They look great by the way </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-28 17:46:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I think im guna go with something like witch hunters. Im trying to get a grimdark ttpe setting for this and that seems to fit </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> How to give impression of magicless world </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-28 14:29:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Im wanting my party to end up in an alt dimention where theres no magic, its all humans and evil emperer sorcerer god taken magic for himself. 

How could i portray this without gimping all the magic users in my party? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-28 00:58:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Theres like 7 things isnt there? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Homebrew item help </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-27 23:30:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So im starting a campaign as dm this weekend and ny group has no healer. To combat this i was considering throwing an item in for them fairly early on. The item is: Jims 6 figered glove of healing.
It gives the wearer a less powerful version of lay on hands, being 2x total level rather than 5x paladin level. It also makes the wearer grow a sixth figer. Requires attunement otherwise everythig you do that uses your hands has disadvantage. You also have to roll a d100 once a day for a chance of an npc to appear who is hunting the six fingered man who killed his father. If he finds you, you gotta scrap or reason your way out. 

My question is do you think this is a good idea? I think that it will help my players feel a little safer and add some fun! I arent sure on balancing though and not sure if its too weak or anything </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-27 13:52:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What is this ring? I cant find anythi g about it but heard multiple mentions </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-27 11:42:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> 2 hours out mate, should be midnight doing daily divines at reset </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-26 21:09:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Saw it yesterday </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-26 08:32:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Its all relative though init </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-26 07:51:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> To share the achievement it looks like </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-25 20:19:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This sounda ace, hows about making it a multi player boss, where by one person can run round dissabling the enemy guys, somethig akin to caches. But more like traps and potions that slow and stuff like that </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-25 17:10:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Its shit hot mate </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-25 17:09:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Superier though... canny sell them lads! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-24 16:56:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Is your grandad a yorkshireman? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-24 16:52:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Loool. Is this the price i must pay to maybe become slightly fitter? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-24 16:41:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Im just tryna work out the logistics of it all </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-24 16:39:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Err how do you poop standing up? That sounds rediculously messy </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-24 16:31:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> But the stairs... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Squats recovery </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-24 16:29:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So iv just started tring to get fit and on monday i did some squats, just body weight. I figured it would be easy. The next day i could barely walk at all. Even now, on friday im still struggling. Legs still wobbly lol. Is this normal? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-24 15:20:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hmm. Im uk and chrome. Its all rather iritating </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-24 15:14:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Where are you if you dont mind me aasking? Also wht browser do you use? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Runemetrics </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-24 15:00:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Have any jmods addressed the issues with runemetrics? Its been problematic dor weeks now and seems every time i try to log in it just goes back to the log in page. Im getting really fed up of paying for something i cant even use </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Pie chart auto updating </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-23 21:07:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I want to make a pie chart that updates automatically every time i put new data into my spreadsheet. At present i can get the chart to show current but any update requires a new chart to be made. Is this possible? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-23 19:05:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Your kitchen looks bigger thAn my house  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Im DMing my first game next saturday... </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-23 05:17:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Im guna be DMing my firat game starting next saturday. Im doing the lost mines of phandaldanpdandlanler and i have 4 players. Im shitting myself! Any tips of thigs to bear in mind? Im hoping to just try kid my way through and make them think i know what im doing... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Can i dm with no experience playing? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-20 08:06:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Iv been incredibly interested in dnd for a long time. Iv been looking on roll 20 for a while trying to find a gamr that fits my schedule. Its proving rather difficult due to me working shifts. So i was thinking about maybe running my own game. I however have no experience of the game at all and its a rather daunting thing to face. What would be a sensible option? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-18 12:46:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Iv walked in that area for years. Im a yorkshire lad born and bred. I was foolish that day. Had my phone with the map on it and a bottle of water and some sandwitches. Everything else was with my tent at the pub. I was stupid and left the path and completely lost my bearings. I couldnt find north and my phone map was useless to me. When it got dark i used ny phone for the torch. I phoned the police about 20% and told them all i could see was a fence. They said to follow it so i did. I aparently followed it the wrong way, going further into the moors than out. Once it got too dark to be safe i could sdo nothing but lay down in a bit of a depression to get out of the wind. Puull my hood up, hands in pockets and try to sleep. Rose with the sun and started movig again. The blasted grouse kept laughing at me! It was entirely my own fault for being ill prepared and thinking i knew what i was doing. In hind sight, without the stress, it was a bloody good walk. I found an old mine entrance, a new trig point and an old building of some sort the had crumbled. Sought shelter there for a while. I proved i could do it to myself whih is good. I wish i hadnt had to though. And i cant stop kicking myself for being so stupid </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-18 12:26:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I actually found search and rescue in the end. They had stopped for some lunch by a trig point. I was waiting by the trig point as you know, high ground for the helicopter. We was basically about 100 yards away from one another for a while until i heard a laugh carry on the wind. I started yelling and looking for them, eventually stumbled across them. They gave me a mars bar and some water. I was lucky in that it was a very mild night for a january. I had to sleep in nothing but the clothes in my back. When i had been fed and watered they gave me the choice of walking out or a helicopter lift out. I felt well enough to walk so did the 6km or so walk to the nearest point, a pub. (Tan hill inn, highest pub in britain). I was examined in an ambulance and questioned by the police. I suffer from depression so my home was searched for a suicide note by the police  some of my vitals where wonky so was questioned about any substance use. I was more or less fine other than being cold, tired, hungry and thirsty. It was really rather scary and people thought if i was found, is be found dead </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-18 12:17:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I shall. Theres a couple spot local enough </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-18 12:09:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This may sound counter productive and incredibly shallow but all the walking clubs iv seen local have been almost entirely retirees and i am 23 ya know </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Help with my fear </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-18 11:59:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I was walking on the north york moors in january. Iv been walking for many years and usually pride myself on my good senses and stuff. That day i got lost. I was on the moors over night with no gear. I phoned the police and there was search helicopters and mountain rescue out looking for me. I was lost about 20 hours before being found. Very cold. I havent been walking since. I love walking but i am struggling to get over that fear. I darent even go camping now even with friends. Has anyone has a similar experience and help with how they got over it? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> General tips for pvm improvement </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-18 10:25:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I am max combat, 99 herb 99 sum and curses. I have a nox bow and full pernix. I still suck at pvm. Any tips for generally improving my abilities? I feel im missing a lot and youtube makes things like rax and telos look so easy </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-17 09:51:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Never in my life... never have i been so honoured </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-17 07:48:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Your up too early  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-17 06:18:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> How often are you going to run into the same 100 folk is what i dont understand? If they are that annoying, mute em then remove once youve moved away from that spot </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-17 06:05:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thats what im wanting to do now. Iv just come back after a year almost and when i left i deleted everything </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-16 23:55:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> My first 9 are from like 2 years ago i cant remember now lol. Thanks though </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Order of 99s </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-16 23:40:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Is there a way for me to check the otder in which i got my 99s? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-16 23:28:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Any reason for the.logs? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-16 16:33:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I dont even know what a sos is lol </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-16 14:47:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Iv got my brother who no longer plays, mychildhood best friend who i havent spoke to in about 6 years and my best mate now on my frienda list. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-16 14:18:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Exactly! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-16 13:24:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Correct </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-16 12:22:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I like hearing stuff about my mother. Its good to know the woman who borthed me is out there somewhere at least </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-16 10:05:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> How do you have 100 people on ignore? I imagine you go around antagonising people then ignoring them when they defend themself or something. I dont think iv even spoken to 100 people in my 12 years or so </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-16 08:58:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What tribrid gloves are there? Do ironmen have access to minigames? And if so thaler? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-15 16:12:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Iv seen this mentiond a few times, what actually makes akrisaes netter? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-15 11:48:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I was guna say this </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
