<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject9914</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-10 17:38:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> "The comments seem to be posted by different people, with their addresses attached. But people contacted by The Verge said they did not write the comments and have no idea where the posts came from.

That doesnt even sound like verbiage I would use, says Nancy Colombo of Connecticut, whose name and address appeared alongside the comment.

I have no idea where that came from, says Lynn Vesely, whose Indiana address also appeared, and who was surprised to hear about the comment." </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Fake anti-net neutrality comments were sent to the FCC using names and addresses of people without their consent </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-10 17:35:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-10 00:47:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Can someone explain to me how does commenting on the FCC website help steer the decisions of Ajit Pai?  Can't he just say "F you" and ignore what people say?  He isn't elected, he has no constituency to be beholden to.  How does this help our cause?   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-08 17:54:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> you should do your homework and find the original poster. just because everyone else is a plagiarist, doesn't mean you should be </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-08 17:50:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> My departmental focus is actually on gene editing, and I'd have to disagree with you. My current research is focused on using CRISPR to correct congenital diseases in dogs. Previously I worked with engineering mouse disease models. To me, genetic engineering is a great benefit to humanity.  I just think a lot of the fear comes from laypeople not understanding the science.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> World Record Paper Airplane </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-07 23:04:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-07 22:47:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I know there isn't a consensus. But my personal, somewhat professional opinion is that it's safe in general. Of course you have to go on a case-by-case basis. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-07 22:24:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That's what I currently try to do.  I'm a biologist living in Berkeley and lean center-left, but I read Breitbart and listen to conservative talk radio to try to see the arguments on both sides.  But the signal-to-noise ratio is sometimes overwhelming.  And I just don't have the energy to track down every primary source nowadays.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Is it futile to look for "real" news? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-07 22:15:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Where does one go for non-partisan reporting?  We got CNN on the left and Breitbart on the right, both have been caught distorting the truth or willfully omitting certain details. I once thought Wikileaks was a neutral party, but it now it smells like even they have their own agenda.  It's enough to make me throw my hands in the air and want to give up.  Where do we turn to for the truth?  Or does it not exist anymore in this day and age?   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-07 22:05:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Low hanging fruit shitty joke </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-07 22:02:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Didn't anyone watch this and think Project Dark Storm? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-07 22:00:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> As a biologist by training, I wholeheartedly agree with that sentiment.  There is nothing inherently bad about GMO's, but the business practices of companies like Monsanto are abhorrent.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-07 21:56:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Should have called it Miss Melanin </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-07 18:31:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It is normal to see the pixels, even at 4k.  The technology is not quite there yet </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-07 06:22:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What an arrogant, unhelpful thing to say. Downvoted </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-06 18:21:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yes I also have AT T S8+ and have seen this issue once.  Probably a bug </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-06 04:10:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> In other words, men can now do what women have done for centuries </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Billboard calls out legislators who voted to allow ISPs to sell user data </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-05 00:27:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-04 23:22:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Blizzard please fire the Xelnaga </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Maine legislature rejects proposal that would cripple municipal broadband </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-04 17:59:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Verizon definitely supports net neutrality </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-02 22:35:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Verizon shamelessly lies to America about net neutrality </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-02 22:25:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-28 02:47:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So double the price of a ps4 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-28 02:46:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> More than just Witcher 3

Gj reddit </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-27 19:01:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This is the reason why Samsung Pay isn't as convenient still as just plastic.  The amount of effort you have to go through to get them to let you try is not worth the convenience of leaving your credit cards at home.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-27 19:00:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Does it work for terminals that have chip readers? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-27 18:58:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Sorry noob question.  What is RISC bar and how do frame traps build it? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-27 01:39:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You don't understand what he's saying....  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-27 00:55:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If you watch the video, he says that those stats don't add up to 100% and it's vague where the missing power comes from </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-27 00:53:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You must be new to reddit. Comments that veer way off topic are the norm here </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-27 00:14:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Chinese speaker here.  There are many ways to alter spoken inflection without altering tone, such as rhythm, volume, consonant vs vowel emphasis, etc.  Also, in Chinese, tones are relative to the beginning and end of a syllable, not absolute.  For example, "second tone" is where the syllable starts low and ends high.  If I raise the entire syllable higher, it is still "second tone" because the relative position of the beginning and end of the syllable are maintained. In this manner, I can make a particular word higher in pitch relative to other words, but that word itself still carries the same relative tone when comparing the beginning and end of the syllable.    </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-26 23:53:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This guy is right to be skeptical of these claims.  Going from 20% degradation to 5% degradation is a huge leap.  I've worked in materials science, advancement doesn't usually happen that fast.  There is a legit argument though that the technology was already available, and it was more of a cost/benefit issue for putting it into cell phones.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-26 19:15:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Isn't this harmful to other drivers like handicapped people and firefighters? Just seems wrong...part of the money should go to the people being screwed </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-26 19:09:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Don't know why you're being downvoted, what you said is exactly true </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-26 19:08:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It won't fix it.  It'll never look as good as a perfect panel </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-26 19:06:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Rich people screwing everyone else again </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> ELI5: Can a sufficiently rich person park in "no parking" spaces and just keep paying the fines? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-26 19:00:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Provided it's not a tow away zone, can someone with a lot of money just keep parking illegally and pay the fines forever?  Will he eventually lose his license or face jail time? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-26 17:45:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Their "fix" is nothing more than an increase to the color calibration range </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-25 22:05:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This is great! Been meaning to watch recreators. This will be helpful </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-25 05:37:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> No no.  When I scan my iris initially, my face wouldn't appear in the center unless I tilted the phone  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Misaligned iris scanner? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-25 03:06:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> When I use my iris scanner, I have to angle my phone's screen a bit to the left in order for my face to appear centered.  If my phone is lying flat on a table, I have to look at it slightly from the side. Does anyone else have this issue?   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-24 21:29:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Sorry to say this man, but people cheating the system like this is the reason we can't have nice things.  The more people committing fraud, the more the rest of us have to pay for insurance.  I have half a mind to report you to the companies you listed. Please don't ruin things for the rest of us  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-24 20:11:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Do you guys have BxActions set to google assistant working reliably?  When I press the button while my phone is locked, half the time it summons google assistant correctly, but half the time it does nothing </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-24 00:45:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What am I supposed to be looking at?  What part is original and what part is remastered?  Why is there a sharp line across the top right?   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-23 22:35:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So selfish </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-22 04:08:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> pretty sure Yamato Cannon is actually a play on words from Camato Yannon </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-21 04:26:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Prismatic Alignment slows the Void Ray by 40% while active.

Love this change.  You'll have to make an informed commitment to use this ability now, rather than just spamming it whenever possible.  Prismatic aligned void rays can now be kited more easily.  Really subtle but elegant nerf IMO </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-21 00:11:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It actually works better for Asians. People with light eye color have been reporting problems with the iris scanner.  Glad that I have dark eyes  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-20 03:10:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I just sent in a PDF of my confirmation email.  I never got a physical receipt.  Will this work? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-20 02:49:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> We need a battery life comparison </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-20 02:45:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> um wut </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-20 02:37:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I was specifically addressing that charges that he wants them to be "locked up."  He doesn't. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-19 22:59:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So you think we should not have punished the tobacco industry? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-19 21:19:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Sounds like he is advocating punishment of corporatists that knowingly lie about the effects of climate change for their own benefit.  He doesn't want to punish the people who genuinely are skeptical about climate change.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-19 21:07:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Bill has never advocated punishing science deniers </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-18 06:40:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Oh yeah?  Damn that means the s8 plus is worse definitely... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-18 06:05:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> wait really?  what do you mean exactly? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-18 05:02:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> yes, but actual testing  logic.  I was hoping someone has tried it </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Which is better for VR, S8 or S8 plus? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-18 04:54:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> On one hand, the s8 plus has a bigger screen, so it would span your field of vision better. But on the other hand, the s8 has higher pixel density, which should look sharper, especially at close range.  So which do you guys think is better for VR? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-18 04:44:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> finally a snapdragon 835 test, thank you man </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-18 02:07:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You are a true hero.  good luck on getting it to work! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-17 05:31:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> tatami gaeshi is a play on "tsubame gaeshi" which is a famous sword technique used by Sasaki Kojirou </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-17 05:29:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> No battery life tests for SD835 version : / </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-16 21:14:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Cool! Thanks! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-16 21:11:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I tried a demo unit too before preordering.  But demo units don't tell you battery life, unfortunately : ( sighh  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-16 21:08:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> everyone you've seen was exynos </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-16 21:03:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What I'm saying is, it was a difficult choice, and they made it harder by embargoing the review </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-16 21:00:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Then we don't get a free VR headset : /  It's catch 22 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-16 20:56:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> And what determines the voice sample usage?  Stage?  Who you are fighting against? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-16 20:53:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Not SD835 version </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-16 20:53:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I can't stop laughing lmaoooo </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Baiken says "Tatami gaeshi" in at least 3 different ways in Rev2 </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-16 20:48:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Exhibit A: https://youtu.be/QhCeT1LR9v8?t=27s

Exhibit B: https://youtu.be/QhCeT1LR9v8?t=4m52s

Exhibit C: https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=F8bfBlxVnPU feature=youtu.be t=33s

What's going on here? Is this something every character has and I've just never noticed?  I've already figured out it's not due to air vs ground, as you can clearly hear the same inflection used for both air and ground versions.  I actually think it's a stage-specific thing, because the way she says "tatami gaeshi" sounds the same for the entire duration of a match, but it sounds different across different matches.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-16 20:08:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> AT T charges a $45 restocking fee : / </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-16 20:02:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This is a really bad omen for the SD835 variant. Samsung doesn't want bad press to affect American presales. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-16 17:41:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> i actually love the way he speaks.  its like a form of asmr to me </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-16 03:30:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Saw this in the MyUPS app as well!  Estimated delivery is 4/19. So excited!  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-15 08:10:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> FUCKING LASERS </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-15 05:00:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> same here :c at t take their sweet time... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-13 21:18:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Shade cooldown nerf is fair!!! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-13 08:53:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Can the MAC address be found on the label on the box?  Or do I have to find it in settings?   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-13 06:58:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> 2H - Just IB it and option select fuzzy forward jump back airthrow every single time. If he does mist finer, just react 

OF COURSE How did I not see it before?
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Why Starcraft rules (and killed) the RTS genre </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-13 01:50:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-12 17:36:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I don't mean to sound snarky, but how does one keep the battery cool during charging?  Put it near an open window or something?   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-12 16:47:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> May I ask, how do you get a Japanese app store account?  Do I need a Japanese credit card?  Can I have both English and Japanese apps on the same device? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-12 08:04:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I read with my ipad, and multitasking makes it pretty easy to read and look up at the same time~ </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Best app to read manga in Japanese? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-12 07:47:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Anyone know of a good app for android or ios that allows you to browse and read raw manga?  Something that doesn't require me to supply my own files?  It can be paid, free, subscription, or whatever, I'm just looking for a convenient way to read raw manga.    </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-11 22:42:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I can't place another order because I financed it using AT T next, upgrading from my previous phone.  I would need to open a new phone line to order another phone this way.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-11 21:10:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> They tried 3 different computer systems.  The order was already locked in because it's considered "preparing for shipment."  Only way to cancel is to refuse delivery or return to the store without opening it.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> How to redeem preorder gifts? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-11 20:47:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I preordered the galaxy s8. However, I changed my mind and want the S8+ instead.  AT T won't let me cancel the order, but they'll let me bring it back for a refund and then I can get an S8+.  What I'm worried about is, since my S8+ isn't technically a preorder then, will I lose my free samsung VR?  Is there a way I can redeem the gift using my original order? What do I have to actually do to redeem the gift?  Do I have to cut out and send a UPC or something like that?    </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-09 20:55:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Please let us know the fit snugness when you get to try it out </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-09 03:02:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> i still have nightmares of reposts </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-09 00:45:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Anyone do a battery life test of the SD835 versions yet? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-08 23:47:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I can't believe I read half a page of buildup, only to find out the article is just complaining about the position of the fingerprint reader. As if this wasn't covered to death already.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-08 22:35:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> the pain of unending reposts </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-08 19:31:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> old school Lara is missing the pyramid tits </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-04 09:27:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> what does this mean for the end user? does this mean my phone will perform better? sorry i know nothing about this </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-02 00:23:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thanks! let us know if you uncover anything </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-02 00:20:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thanks for the tip, I'll be avoiding tempered glass for my s8 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-02 00:18:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Worked pretty well on my note 7.  Was faster and more convenient that finger print even.  Especially because I often wear gloves.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Can you remap the bixby button? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-02 00:15:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm probably not going to use bixby...is there a way to make the button do something else? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-01 22:30:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Do those speakers have to be bluetooth 5 speakers or any Bluetooth speakers? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Does bluetooth 5.0 provide any benefits to existing devices? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-01 22:27:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So the galaxy s8 will be the first phone to have bluetooth 5, but as far as I know, there are no bluetooth 5 accessories out yet.  Will this provide any benefits to older bluetooth devices? Like will my signal strength improve for my bose QC35 or anything like that? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-01 22:02:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This is the problem with everyone, especially zerg players, complaining about skytoss.  Protoss is already the weakest race, played by the fewest people.  If you nerf skytoss, you have to buff something else to compensate, at the very least </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-01 22:00:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> laser, blazer.... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> ELI5: Is it possible to make a phone screen that is both scratch-proof and shatter-proof? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-01 21:57:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> On one hand, you have super hard materials like diamond that are unscratchable, but would probably make a brittle phone screen.  On the other hand, you have materials like plastic that basically can't shatter, but scratch easily.  Nowadays we have materials like gorilla glass that try to find a good middle ground.  My question: is it theoretically possible to have the best of both worlds, given unlimited budget?  A material as scratch-proof as diamond, but as shatter-proof as plastic? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-01 20:30:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> But who is the bigger scam artist, Murray or Molyneux? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-01 20:13:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> are those the zero animations from megaman x?  nice! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-01 20:11:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I must have not paid attention but I've never noticed anyone hating on feardragon.  What sorts of things were they saying? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-29 19:37:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You seriously believe that? They are trying to make themselves look good. Gullible </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-29 19:22:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I 100% don't believe EA would ever say "you can have 5 more months" </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-29 18:06:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> there was a former bioware animator who tweeted about this, his last name is Cooper I think.  He speculates that the team used the algorithm on everything at first, and then planned to go back to hand tweak the animations. But time ran out so they left a bunch of them as is.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-29 18:00:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> the problem is as bad as people say it is, and i'll be happier the less people give EA money for this insult to the series </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-29 17:58:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> when you don't do it by hand.  a lot of the ME:A facial animations were done by an algorithm </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-28 08:38:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's undeniable that Andromeda is a step backwards in animation compared to any of the previous games in the series.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-28 07:45:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> perky perky </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-28 07:38:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's gonna be an alternative ending for Brood War HD where Kerrigan doesn't get infested, then she and Raynor get it on while riding off into the sunset </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-28 06:59:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I will thanks </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-27 21:55:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's my favorite phone. I've disabled updates long ago.  Never turning it in.  My happiness takes priority over the miniscule risk it poses to people I don't care about. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-27 18:29:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> 

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> I-No Cosplay </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-26 10:13:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
