<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject8234</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-10 03:38:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hello, thank you for your submission. Unfortunately it has been removed for the following reason(s):

*It doesn't include peer-reviewed citations. All submissions must cite peer-reviewed research.*

If you have any questions or feel this was done in error, please [message the moderators](https://www.reddit.com/message/compose?to=%2Fr%2Fpsychology subject= message=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.reddit.com%2Fr%2Fpsychology%2F). </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-10 03:37:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hello, thank you for your submission. Unfortunately it has been removed for the following reason(s):

*It doesn't include peer-reviewed citations. All submissions must cite peer-reviewed research.*

If you have any questions or feel this was done in error, please [message the moderators](https://www.reddit.com/message/compose?to=%2Fr%2Fpsychology subject= message=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.reddit.com%2Fr%2Fpsychology%2F). </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Study finds PTSD diagnosis is associated with increased risk of dementia diagnosis, and preliminary evidence that psychotropic drugs prescribed for PTSD may influence the risk of future dementia diagnosis </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-09 20:20:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Psychologists studying the works of artists over time find preliminary evidence that early, undiagnosed signs of disorders like Alzheimer's Disease can be detected through subtle changes in art styles </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-09 00:13:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-08 20:01:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hello, thank you for your submission. Unfortunately it has been removed for the following reason(s):

*Video submissions must be accompanied by a comment listing the relevant peer-reviewed citations.*

If you have any questions or feel this was done in error, please [message the moderators](https://www.reddit.com/message/compose?to=%2Fr%2Fpsychology subject= message=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.reddit.com%2Fr%2Fpsychology%2F). </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-08 19:35:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hello, thank you for your submission. Unfortunately it has been removed for the following reason(s):

*It has a sensationalized/clickbait title.*

If you have any questions or feel this was done in error, please [message the moderators](https://www.reddit.com/message/compose?to=%2Fr%2Fpsychology subject= message=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.reddit.com%2Fr%2Fpsychology%2F). </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-07 21:02:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Grad student in cognitive neuroscience here. This title is misleading- they did not find that damage to the ventromedial prefrontal cortex or the dorsolateral prefrontal cortex was linked to an increase in religious fundamentalism. Actually, they found that regardless of whether patients had damage to the vmPFC or the dlPFC, they still exhibited religious fundamentalism. Instead, the takeaway from this article is that the vmPFC may contribute to fundamentalist beliefs via cognitive flexibility. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-07 19:34:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This study is a meta analysis that set out to clarify causal directions of the analgesic effects of alcohol, as previous literature had been divided. This meta-analysis identified 18 previous studies to include in analysis. Studies included met five different criteria: (1) adults given a controlled dose of alcohol, (2) a comparative no-alcohol group/condition, (3) medically and neurologically healthy participants, (4) an experimental pain stimulus, and (5) were published in international peer-reviewed journals or conference abstracts. Studies with patients with a history of alcohol abuse were excluded. Pain threshold and intensity were utilized in various paradigms by all included studies. The results of this meta analysis showed overall pain threshold was elevated following alcohol administration, although this was a small effect. There was a much larger effect of reduction of pain intensity. Additionally, every .02% increment in blood alcohol content was associated with heightened analgesia for both pain thresholds and intensity. Authors note that the heightened reductions in pain intensity following alcohol administration likely explain why people with chronic pain abuse alcohol.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Study finds that alcohol is as effective as opioids at reducing pain: a new meta-analysis found that people with a blood alcohol content of .08% had moderate-to-large reductions in pain intensity, comparable to pain relief from opioids </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-07 18:54:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-06 22:11:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> thank you for the help! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-06 21:34:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> so I requested it six days ago and it still hasn't accepted the invite. Is there an estimate of how long it takes to accept the request? sorry for the trouble. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Study finds that over 10 years, bullying and related behaviors have significantly declined, and student perceptions of safety and belonging have increased, in a sample of nearly 250,000 students in 109 Maryland schools </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-06 20:24:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-03 21:13:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hello /u/jgpsych,

Your submission was removed because it does not contain reference to a peer-reviewed study. Please follow our submission guidelines, found in the sidebar, for future submissions.

If you feel as if this was done in error, do not hesitate to contact the mods.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-30 06:28:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I have toolbox. This modqueue has not been touched for years, and probably has thousands of items. I've tried going through it with RES (to load a lot of queue items) and using toolbox to mass remove, but i've barely made a dent. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Clear all items from modqueue? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-30 06:22:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hey guys,

I saw that this has been asked a few times over the years, but I just got added as a mod for a sub that has a modqueue backed up for years. I'm wondering if any of you know an easy way of getting the modqueue cleared out. I saw that there's a bot called /u/approve_modqueue, but it seems to be inactive.

I'd appreciate any advice you could offer! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-30 02:17:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Check this book out:

Biological Psychology (Critical Thinking in Psychology Series) https://www.amazon.com/dp/0857256939/ref=cm_sw_r_cp_api_EZsbzbDNPK6RW

It's a really quick and easy read, covers most areas of neuroscience and will let you know if you're interested in this as a possible career or not. If you'd like to talk sometime, feel free to PM me! I'm a grad student in cognitive neuroscience right now </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-25 04:25:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> MOD ABUSE </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-23 23:04:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> They note in a comment at the bottom of the page that doing this didn't change the results of any of the studies they reported. I'm guessing that they excluded these people for missing data, as missing data is often a problem with online studies, where people start a survey and don't ever finish it. Sometimes, there's reason to believe that a bot completed the questionnaire, which has been a problem on M-Turk, so that may be another reason why.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-23 22:53:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I think that there is still some debate on how to use M-Turk samples. Most people advocate caution with M-Turk samples, because data from M-Turk isn't always reliable. [Here's](https://www.researchgate.net/profile/Steven_Rouse/publication/268803960_A_reliability_analysis_of_Mechanical_Turk_data/links/54ecbd330cf27fbfd7717b49.pdf) a study detailing some of the issues with M-Turk data. I think we might want to be more careful about generalizing results from this study, but I don't think using M-Turk is a "deal breaker" or anything. It is pretty widely used in social science research, from what I can tell. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-23 22:32:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It looks like most of their sample was US-based, recruited from Amazon's M-Turk. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-23 22:19:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I believe they use bias to refer to a propensity to see one race as larger/more threatening than another, regardless of whether this perception is valid or not. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-23 22:12:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> As I noted in a reply to a similar comment, this study was concerning the *perceptions* of physical size in whites and blacks. The authors noted that they conducted this study to try and understand the reasons behind some incidents of police violence.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-23 22:11:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I described studies 1-4 above. Studies 5-7 were largely replications of 1-4, which is why I didn't reference those.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-23 22:09:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This study concerned the *perceptions* of black men vs. white men. While we might see differences in actual physical ability, that's beside the point. The authors wanted to see if there were differences in perceptions, in large part due to police violence. I'm not sure if you can see this, but [here's](http://www.apa.org/pubs/journals/releases/psp-pspi0000092.pdf) a PDF of the full article. The cultural values I was referencing were noted by the authors as a possible reason for this disparity in perceptions of whites and blacks. Hope that helps! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-23 21:54:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This study was conducted by researchers who hypothesized that a person's race would influence perceptions of his physical size. This study was conducted in a number of sub-parts. In the first part, participants were given 200 photographs of male faces (100 white and 100 black) and were asked to estimate the height and weight of each person. They found that black males were consistently rated as being significantly taller and heavier than white males. In another part, participants were given faces of white and black males, and asked to choose a body that would match each face. They found that black males were consistently given more muscular bodies than white males were. In a final part, participants were shown white and black male faces, and asked to rate how strong they thought each person was, on a scale from 0-7. They found that participants, on average, rated black males as being stronger than white males. The authors noted in their discussion of results that even black participants showed this bias, although to a lesser degree than white participants did. They suggest this may be due to a partial internalization of cultural values.

EDIT: [Link](http://www.apa.org/pubs/journals/releases/psp-pspi0000092.pdf) to PDF of article </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Study finds that black men are seen as physically larger and more threatening than similar-sized white men </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-23 20:48:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Study finds that people who have weaker social networks and higher levels of loneliness were significantly more likely to report more severe common cold symptoms </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-21 20:37:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-21 16:05:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hello- thanks for doing this AMA!
I'm interested in the pathophysiology behind spatial disorientation, and whether multiple types of dementia present with this problem. I've read that spatial disorientation is not a memory problem, which would rule out medial temporal lobe atrophy. Do you normally see patients with spatial disorientation that have frontal lobe atrophy? I'm also wondering whether certain types of dementia are more likely to involve spatial disorientation. Are there any treatments that help with this issue? 

Thanks for your time! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-13 03:31:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm a first year PhD student and I live in a pretty cheap townhouse with 2 other roommates. They're nice enough, but they're super religious and I'm not, which has made it awkward with me indulging in the occasional tall cold glass of satan water (beer). I'd recommend living on your own, but when you get to the university, get involved in graduate student societies, and try and do things now and again with your cohort </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Study finds that hobbyist beekeepers often have twice the mortality rate and increased disease contraction rates in their colonies as compared to professionals, which may be contributing to declining honey bee populations </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-10 18:53:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-07 18:58:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> As a psychology graduate student, I hear about the replication crisis a lot. Most I've talked to feel like the replication problems come from smaller-than-ideal sample sizes. One thing I've been trying to push in my own research is a priori power analyses. My current project is a neuroimaging project, so we did a g*power analysis and came up with a sample size large enough to have sufficient statistical power. I really hope this sort of thing becomes more common in the future. I think most of the problems with sample size and selection could be helped by doing these types of power analyses.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-31 19:11:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You can get in touch with your local march and see what you can do to help them! I live in the Western US and won't be able to attend the DC march, so I've gotten in touch with a few of my local marches and am helping that way. [Here's](https://marchforscience.com) the list of satellite marches. Hope that helps! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-31 19:06:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If you check out the [March for Science] (https://www.marchforscience.com) website, they have a list of satellite marches that you can get in touch with to see where you can help. Hope that answers your question! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Study finds evidence that non-Black physicians with higher levels of implicit racial bias use words that reflect social dominance and anxiety when talking to Black patients </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-30 20:35:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Study of nearly 80,000 people finds that heroin use has significantly increased between 2002 and 2012, especially among whites and in people aged 18-29 </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-30 18:44:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Study finds people recently released from psychiatric facilities face a 16 times greater risk of premature death within the first year after discharge </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-28 18:37:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Study using real-time fMRI neurofeedback successfully helps patients with PTSD downregulate activation in the amygdala, a brain region associated with fear response that is often hyperactive in PTSD </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-16 17:48:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Study finds increased marijuana use associated with decreased volume in the hippocampus, a subcortical brain structure important in memory formation; additionally, it was found that HIV status and marijuana use had significant interactive effects on brain structure and cognition </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-16 17:43:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-02 20:20:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Anyone have any idea when this PTR will go live? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-02 05:11:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> if you're on console and get OW, feel free to add me on xbox one, I can show you the ropes. pm me for my username :)  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-02 04:39:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Overwatch is SO much better than IW. Essentially, as you level up, you get loot boxes with random skins/customizations and coins to buy the ones you want. Competitive is really fun, you work your way through the ranks and are given points for each game you finish. Using these points you can buy special golden weapons for your favorite heroes. There are lots of game modes and they just added custom servers so you can really play how you want to. Blizzard is constantly adding content, rumors are that a new hero is coming pretty soon. I feel like there's enough heroes that I don't get bored and if I ever do, I switch to another hero I'm not as good at to practice and freshen things up. I'm about 100 hours in now and i'm still not bored with things. COD pales in comparison IMO. Overwatch is 100% worth the money </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Study finds that physicians prescribe antibiotics more often when they perceive that their patients are expecting to receive them, which may be a factor in over-prescribing of antibiotics </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-01 18:52:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-01 01:43:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I would check with professional organizations. Psi Chi honors society has student grants, as does Phi Kappa Phi. You might also find funding through neuroscience organizations. Usually the regional and state psychological associations will hand out grants as well.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-27 09:25:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It floods over every winter. I was out there in October and it was the same way. The official state park website talks about it I believe  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-27 08:54:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> As someone who just did this: you'll be fine in applications. 

However the one thing I recommend doing is taking a gap year between your undergrad and starting grad school. I just graduated in May 2016 and started a cognitive neuroscience phd in August 2016 and the burnout is real. Take a gap year, work some, enjoy yourself and apply for the next year.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-25 19:54:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Cognitive neuroscience. I'm actually enjoying the methods and stats classes </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-18 21:12:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hi! Thanks for doing this AMA. 

I've heard recently theories that think that the microbiome might influence development through the production of certain neurotransmitters. I've even heard some who think that the microbiome might be linked to disorders like autism. Is there any substance to these theories? Do you have any ideas about what further research might find?

Thanks!  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-17 18:55:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hi! Thanks for doing this AMA. As a neuroscience graduate student this is completely out of my wheelhouse but I'm wondering what a real world application of your work could be. Is it out of the realm of possibility to use this to help prevent incidences of Zika infection?

Thanks! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Study indicates that people who are overweight can increase functional connectivity between brain areas that control of appetite for high-calorie foods </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-15 22:04:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Study suggests that those who are politically conservative and deny climate change science do so out of a desire to conform to traditional conservative values </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-15 18:45:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-14 21:47:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You sound like you like the same types of books I like. Check this series out! It's fantastic. 

http://www.goodreads.com/book/show/3618420-path-of-glory </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Path of Glory by Bret Funk- a coming-of-age fantasy novel </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-14 21:45:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I cannot recommend this book enough! I first read this book (and the rest of the series) when I was younger. Now, as a graduate student, I picked it up again to read in my spare time and I am continually amazed at how well the author builds the world around his characters. If you're looking for a great fantasy novel, look no further!

http://www.goodreads.com/book/show/3618420-path-of-glory </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-14 05:20:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Sure, PM me and let's meet up </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Study finds use of medical marijuana improves cognitive performance, contradicting previous studies that found cognitive decline with marijuana use </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-14 04:35:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-14 00:09:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I think in this study they're referring to restricting the number of calories you intake daily. So you're not cutting off all calories, but restricting the caloric intake to a certain amount daily.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Study finds that long term calorie restriction promotes cellular fitness, which in turn may lead to increased longevity </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-13 19:35:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-13 09:24:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I've heard it's bad there even for Mormons. Really happy I'm not there haha </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-13 09:23:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Not really into partying but I do like social drinking. Pm me and maybe we can meet up sometime! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-13 06:21:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hahaha this is great. My best friend and his wife live in Denver, so I make it over for a long weekend once every few months. Every time I go, and come back to SLC, I wonder why the fuck I live here.. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-13 06:06:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So I'm a non-mormon taking classes at BYU. Last semester, my prof was talking about how a student sent him an anonymous email about how they were having doubts about the church, but they were afraid to leave the church, for fear of getting kicked out and not getting their degree. My entire class thought that the guy should just leave and risk his degree, no sympathy whatsoever. I spoke up and said that I was in the same position with my former church and that it was heartless of them to say those things about someone trying to be true to themselves. Did not go over well. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-13 06:03:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah, I lived in the Michiana area for about 10 years. Definitely weird. Where abouts in Indiana are you OP? I can give you some recommendations! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Non-mormon at BYU </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-13 05:59:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hey guys,

I posted here a while back. I'm a grad student at BYU who isn't mormon. The culture here is kind of driving me crazy. I know coming to BYU as a non-mormon probably wasn't the greatest idea, but I didn't know any better at the time. Are there any ex/non-mormons on here who'd want to meet up sometime? I really want to meet some normal people again. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Study finds that engaging in mentally stimulating activities, even late in life, reduces risk of mild cognitive impairment </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-09 02:55:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-03 20:00:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hi all, 

Thanks for doing this AMA! I'm a graduate student in psychology and have been studying some replication studies of classic psychology experiments. Although this is not your field, I wanted to ask your opinion on how much you think replication problems in science, not purely psychology or social sciences, relates to lack of understanding of methodologies/statistical tests. How can we educate researchers to conduct better/more robust studies? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-27 19:52:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hi Duncan_gholas, your submission has been removed for the following reason(s)

It does not include references to new, peer-reviewed research. Please feel free to post it in our sister subreddit /r/EverythingScience. 



*If you feel this was done in error, or would like further clarification, please don't hesitate to [message the mods](http://www.reddit.com/message/compose?to=%2Fr%2FScience message=My%20Post:%20https://www.reddit.com/r/science/comments/5qisb9/a_video_of_four_directlyimaged_exoplanets/).* </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-11 18:17:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hi benbrum, your submission has been removed for the following reason(s)

It has a sensationalized, editorialized, or biased headline.



*If you feel this was done in error, or would like further clarification, please don't hesitate to [message the mods](http://www.reddit.com/message/compose?to=%2Fr%2FScience message=My%20Post:%20https://www.reddit.com/r/science/comments/5ncv7s/could_eating_a_hamburger_kill_a_rare_bird_big/).* </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-11 18:14:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hi recentfish, your submission has been removed for the following reason(s)

It is a repost of an already submitted and popular story.



*If you feel this was done in error, or would like further clarification, please don't hesitate to [message the mods](http://www.reddit.com/message/compose?to=%2Fr%2FScience message=My%20Post:%20https://www.reddit.com/r/science/comments/5nd6r9/researchers_uncover_sexual_relations_between_a/).* </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-11 18:07:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hi Public_Fucking_Media, your submission has been removed for the following reason(s)

It does not include references to new, peer-reviewed research. Please feel free to post it in our sister subreddit /r/EverythingScience. 



*If you feel this was done in error, or would like further clarification, please don't hesitate to [message the mods](http://www.reddit.com/message/compose?to=%2Fr%2FScience message=My%20Post:%20https://www.reddit.com/r/science/comments/5nctc8/the_irreversible_momentum_of_clean_energy_obama/).* </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-15 10:18:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> His wife actually wrote an article about their struggles. It's heartbreaking. 

http://www.neurology.org/content/87/13/1308.full </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-07 08:49:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hey OP what part of Louisiana are you from? I grew up in Baton Rouge and I've never heard of this before.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-07 04:57:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Looks like there was an n of 120.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-05 00:00:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Nope. I didn't play either 1 or 2 and I still loved it. There are some videos online that summarize the events in 1 and 2 if you're interested in the lore. The beginning of the game lets you either enter the decisions you made, or turn it off and have access to all the characters and content. I think if you played 2 you might have more appreciation for the side characters and history, but honestly 3 stands on its own perfectly fine.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-04 23:59:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I don't really agree. I've done three full playthroughs, changing the decisions I made in the side quests and found it a lot of fun. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-04 18:27:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Okay, let's be real here. Skyrim is great. It's fun. But IMO there's not much substance. Plus, the game has been out for five years so chances are you've played it already. 

Witcher 3 is quite possibly the best RPG I've ever played. Everything is so intertwined. Even the side quests have ties into other side quests and the main storyline. The characters are so developed you feel sort of empty when they disappear post game. The blood and wine DLC adds 40 hours of gameplay and is actually better than the main game in my opinion. If you haven't played witcher, you need to.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-01 23:43:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I don't know if I'd go that far. The problem is incentivizing research that has novel findings instead of replications. I don't think people are making things up, but I do think they are doing things like running analyses and throwing in variables until they hit the p.05 threshold. We need journals to incentivize good research instead of novel research.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-01 23:35:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This definitely isn't just a psychology problem. I recently read a paper that found that up to 76% of cancer studies were unable to replicate.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Study re-analyzing 100 replications of psychology experiments finds that current statistical standards are not stringent enough to ensure replication success </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-01 22:04:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-23 23:31:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You should probably shoot the professor an email telling him this and asking for advice on the paper. I've found that to be pretty useful, as I'm in the same situation as you- first year straight from undergrad. 

In my opinion this is just anxiety. In my experience second and third years might have a bit more knowledge than first, but you're probably going to be fine. I WOULD NOT count on him grading you any differently from anyone else. Put in the time and effort, do your best, and use your professors suggestions to do as best as you can on it. Follow the rubric and instructions, maybe get advice from people who have taken the class before. You'll be fine.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-16 15:42:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hi Ira! Thanks for doing this AMA. 

I'm a graduate student in psychology- lately I've been concerned about the anti science rhetoric in our government, especially coming from President-Elect Trump. He has mentioned that he'd like to stop funding things like social science research. As someone who works to bridge the gap between the public and science, do you have any thoughts on what we as researchers can do to combat this anti-science attitude among not only our government officials, but the public? How can we make our work more accessible and help others realize its importance?

Thanks! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-10 18:24:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hello,

Thanks for doing this AMA! 

I have a family friend who was diagnosed with glioblastoma multiforme last year. In the course of his treatment, he was given a new therapy technique that involves the use of a skull-cap with electrodes that emit a static electric field, combined with a new drug, to try and halt tumor growth. This technique was written about in this paper: 

http://jamanetwork.com/journals/jama/fullarticle/2475463?resultClick=3

So far, it looks like the therapy has stopped (for the most part) the growth of the tumor. I'm wondering what your thoughts are on new treatments like these- are there any other promising treatments for cancer on the horizon? How seriously should we take these kinds of treatment? 

Thanks for your time! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-03 01:04:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I think it's important because being accepted as a science has some wide ranging implications. It not only would allow psychology research to be taken more seriously and given more scrutiny, but I think it also influences psychologists ability to do research, such as getting government grants/different types of funding.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-02 23:57:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> One of the things I've faced most often in my education is the idea from other people that psychology isn't a science. I think this is hard to stamp out because lay people generally don't/can't hypothesize/make conclusions about the properties of an atom, or quantum forces- psychology is a field that is accessible enough to the lay person that people make assumptions about the field, and subsequently what is/isn't true about people, and this causes other scientists to conclude that because of this science/public interaction, all psychologists really do is guesswork, because(in their view) the entire field is based off of subjective self-reports. I think this actually puts psychologists in a unique position, though- because psychology is somewhat accessible to the public, public outreach might actually do something to quell common myths and stereotypes (like the 10% brain myth). With other fields, like medicine, the processes underlying certain practices (like vaccines) are so mysterious that people automatically assume something nefarious is going on, and because people aren't physicians, they don't truly understand why this isn't the case. I think if psychologists focused more on public education, we might actually be able to gain some respect among other scientists and combat this idea of psychology being a pseudo-science.
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-31 21:17:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> OP where can I get one? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-31 00:50:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If you don't mind a bit of a drive, Avery in Boulder is one of the coolest breweries I've ever been to. New Belgium is super cool too. A small brewery down in Loveland, Co is Big Beaver, they're pretty small but definitely have some good beer there. 

The Mayor of Old Town has 100+ beers on tap, and great food. definitely recommend checking them out.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-28 16:55:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thanks for doing this AMA!

Recently on Reddit there was an article posted that discussed how academia fosters an environment of hypercompetition and subsequently lowers the quality of science being done. Do you think that the environment of academia (the publish or perish attitude, etc) plays into this bullying phenomenon you discussed? If so, do you have any recommendations on how I, a future PhD, and others, might combat this?

Thanks!  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-25 22:28:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Here, they're referring to American football. This is especially relevant right now because of all the discussion in the field regarding multiple concussions and research into Chronic Traumatic Encephalopathy, or CTE, in people who play American football. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Study finds working memory deficits and white matter changes in children after playing a single season of football, despite lack of diagnosed concussions </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-25 21:57:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-24 03:59:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This study examined activation of the anterior cingulate gyrus and the orbitofrontal cortex, before and after injection of a common method of birth control, Depo (or Depo Medroxyprogesterone Acetate). Using a 3-T MRI scanner, participants brain activity was examined in response to high-calorie, low-calorie, and neutral stimuli. These scans were performed before injection of Depo and 8 weeks after a 150mg dose of Depo. Researchers noted that there was increased activation in the orbitofrontal cortex and anterior cingulate gyrus, areas associated with reward and food motivation. While no fat mass increase was noted post-injection, this study could be important because it links injection of Depo to increased activation in food motivation and reward areas. This could be a mechanism in which subjects find themselves more prone to eating more after a Depo injection. 

Link: http://www.sciencedirect.com/science/article/pii/S0010782415302122 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-23 22:00:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Sure, but I don't think that's what the study is suggesting. Its been found that certain birth control medications can be associated with weight gain- this study just demonstrates that this particular method of birth control may be partially responsible for weight gain by increasing the activity in the orbitofrontal cortex, an area commonly associated with food motivation. Of course eating is the cause of weight gain, but change in eating habits may be linked to birth control.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
