<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject8754</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [I Ate] Otoro Maguro Don </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-10 10:19:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-08 20:47:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I absolutely love the styling of recent Lancias. That grille. Sorry everyone... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-07 14:54:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Seems like it doesn't really matter. Whatever you can overclock it to it'll still drop back down to 2025MHz when gaming. Even across other OEMs 2025MHz seems to be the maximum clock 1080 Tis are willing to stay at when gaming. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-07 14:40:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Don't use it. Look at the other thread, the newer version lowers the stock clocks. Why not just enable voltage control in Afterburner by modifying the .oem2 file, rather than downloading the BETA version? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-07 14:29:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Haven't tried the beta Afterburner but after hearing your experience with it, I probably should wait till a more stable version is released. 

And I realized I've been an idiot. When I said +200 on memory it's actually +400 since Afterburner doesn't show the Double Data Rates. I've managed to get a stable +85 on Core and +210 (2) on Memory without overvolting now. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-07 11:40:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Let's see how liberal it really is. Fuck religion. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-07 05:19:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> My Aorus Xtreme's quite quiet, but I don't really have a reference point other than it being much quieter than my previous 970.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-06 07:56:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So it's normal for the CPU to overvolt very high when running IBT? In normal use, I don't see VCore exceeding 1.280V but it's still higher than the 1.275V I set it to.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-06 05:24:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Haha I used to live there. My god the place is overrun with Indians. Now the place is being rented out, to an Indian.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-05 18:12:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> No in my BIOS settings there's override and there's offset. Auto seems to make overclock unstable (unless you meant for the VDROOP offset?). I'm using IntelBurnTest. 

I can't really be bothered to run long stability tests since it heats up my room too much (31 degrees ambient room temp). If it doesn't crash in games, encoding or in daily use its good enough.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-05 17:26:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Oops I meant 'override'. It's on 'override' now. Sorry about that error.  

Is the LLC option the same as VDROOP Offset Control? I have it on auto now and it seems too aggressive. I've tried setting it to 12.5% (the lowest I can go, there is no disable), but it's pushing core voltage even higher than when left at auto. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Very high CPU VCORE, above setting in BIOS? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-05 15:30:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm trying to overclock my i7-4790K with the MSI Z97 Gaming 5 motherboard. I've set the core ratio to 46x, ring ratio to 40x, CPU Core voltage mode to Offset Mode and Core voltage to 1.275V.  

Everything runs smoothly and doesn't crash but when I check HWMonitor/HWiNFO, the CPU VCore actually shoots up to 1.296V when running IntelBurnTest. How can I prevent this? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-05 08:24:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> There's nothing wrong with restriction the number of degree holders. Not everyone is equal in terms of academic ability, and it's time we stop pretending it is so. People should do what they're good at, instead of wasting money on Kaplan or SIM. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-05 08:12:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Cause they're mostly sad losers who can't succeed in life and instead of looking inwards, they blame society and the government for their inadequacies. After their shift, they meet up at the coffee shop with their mates and continue with their echo chamber, rather than realising they themselves are to blame. 

Is this the answer you want?

Edit: Why am I being downvoted? People can't handle the truth? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-04 18:20:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Is this why every French person I talked to warned me of Saint-Denis? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-04 04:29:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The author's right. Why pay when you can get it for free? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-03 13:44:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I just find McLarens boring. They all look roughly the same, and I can't help feeling if you're going to buy one, they'll have a new one in 3-6 months that makes yours look outdated. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-03 12:33:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I don't get the hate with this device. The design is clean and attractive, and the price honestly isn't too bad. Of course you can get better specs with other brands, but most students I know in University don't even have a concept of what RAM or how much you need. It's just Microsoft's attempt to break the MacBook monopoly in tertiary education markets.

And there's touchscreen. That's a selling point that MacBooks don't have. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-02 17:54:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Maybe ambulances should have bull bars installed to ram those who intentionally block them.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-02 09:38:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Jonathan Woss.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-01 21:07:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Good.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-01 20:57:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Seems like it's only dropping in benchmarks. In games it'll happily stay at 2025 it seems, even at stock voltage. I only need to overvolt to increase memory beyond +200.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-01 20:51:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's usually 2025MHz in games. The Aorus Gaming Engine allows for overvolting. Just click the lock to unlock voltage control.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-01 20:18:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> There should be plenty of headroom. It's a Seasonic X-850. I've just tried overvolting the GPU by 15mV, now it does +80 (Core) and +300 (Memory) fine. Haven't tried higher. I definitely lost the silicon lottery. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-01 19:12:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hmm, using Heaven's worse. What was stable in Superposition is crashing on Heaven. Lol. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-01 18:09:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Was a stay-out clerk. OTed most days till 10pm and had to work overnight on many occasions. Had one month where my taxi claims were above $400+ even though I lived like 15 minutes away.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-01 18:06:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Very well connected road network.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-01 16:37:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Haven't tried. Is Superposition not a good test? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-01 15:38:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Just tried reducing core clocks to increase memory clocks. Even +250 on memory causes artifacts in Superposition. Seems like I've hit the limit on both. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-01 12:51:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hmm let me try that. I have 6 fans too. 2 in front, 2 on top, 1 at the rear and one on the bottom. But it doesn't help that most of them max out at 1000-1100rpm to keep noise levels low.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-01 12:11:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's not too bad. In-games at 60FPS with V-Sync, it rarely goes above 75C and 105% Power Limit. Does core or memory overclock benefit framerates more? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-01 12:06:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yup can't overvolt through Afterburner. Can't set Priority to Target Temperature either. I tried overvolting using the Aorus Graphics Engine but even with a +10mV increase, I can't increase any of the clocks (+80 Core, +200 Memory).  

Even without overvolting, the GPU hits 84C in Unigine's Superposition. I guess I shouldn't overvolt (my room temperature is 31C). </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-01 06:16:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's funny that Volvo calls a lot of engines Driv-e, including my D2. I get 60mpg on average.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-30 18:01:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> They definitely run on CNG. A lot of them go to this place called Smart Energy, where they lift up the hoods to fill their CNG tanks.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-29 14:46:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Seems like if it's 99% GPU usage, it downclocks. But in most games, it stays at 2035MHz or so (+80). I can only overclock memory by +200. Anything beyond that I get artifacts immediately.

It already has very good cooling. There's a fan directly beneath the GPU for more airflow. And then there's two on the front of the case not that far away. Should I try overvolting? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-28 19:25:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> There's no point overclocking higher then? Since it always goes back down to 1999 or 1987? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Aorus 1080 Ti Xtreme overclocks not sticking? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-28 18:30:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I've overclocked my card to about 2035MHz (through Afterburner) but it seems like it's always slowly downclocking back to 1999MHz or 1987MHz when running Unigine's Superposition benchmark. Power limit and temp target are both at max. Anyone facing similar issues?

Edit: it's only downclocking in benchmarks. I'm using an overclock of +80 on core and +400 on memory at stock. Funny thing is that +250, +300 crashes, but not at +400.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-28 13:15:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Got it working. Swapped to the first monitor's cable, set it up successfully, and back to its own cable. And that worked. How strange.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-28 05:04:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Maybe someone can upload [these](http://www.movie-blog.org/2017/04/27/planet-earth-ii-s01e01-german-dubbed-dtshd-dl-2160p-ultra-hd-bluray-hdr-x265-nima4k/) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-28 04:24:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yes I mean adapter. I'll try to switch the cable from the other display to see if it works (DVI to DVI). 

I'm using those two with my 27" 1440p display. I'm not insane.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-28 03:19:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm using a Logitech mouse though.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-28 03:18:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Romania has tons of old Mercedes... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-27 20:29:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Lol. Really rich people don't take taxis. Where's the exclusivity? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Custom Resolution dependent on cable/port? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-27 20:13:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I just got a new 1080 Ti and I'm trying to get custom resolutions working.  

I have two 17" monitors with a native resolution of 1280x1024. My goal is to run them at 1440x1152 rotated to match my 27" 1440p monitor on both sides. The one using a DVI-DVI cable does 1440x1152 perfectly using NVIDIA Control Panel.  

However, the other monitor using a DVI-DVI-HDMI (Converter) refuses to do 1440x1152. NVIDIA says test failed, custom resolution is not supported by your display.  

Funny thing is, that exact monitor was doing 1440x1152 for the past year on my old GPU (970), but on a DVI-DVI cable.  

Is there some kind of restriction on what cables/ports are supported for custom resolutions? It's a shame my 1080 Ti only has one DVI input. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-27 18:26:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thanks for the explanation. I'll probably get that cable. My other two monitors are on the GPU's DVI and DisplayPort. My previous card had two DVIs and that was do much more convenient.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-27 18:19:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm interested. Please put it up on the Steam Workshop in one package! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-27 18:17:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hmm what if I got a DVI-D to HDMI cable? Would that work? Are there active/passive categories for that? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-27 18:15:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Your rape van can be the Vito, the Sprinter or even the Unimog.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Drop-down menu bug? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-27 17:42:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm having this problem in the Settings app where drop-down menus will automatically close-out after 1-2 seconds, making it impossible for me to select anything. Is this a known bug? This only started happening after the Creator's Update.

**[Video](https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=lSTJ7Ct2eAg)** </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Cannot connect 3rd monitor? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-27 17:29:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> ###Troubleshooting Help:

**What is your parts list? [Consider formatting your parts list.](http://www.reddit.com/r/buildapc/wiki/pcpp)**

[PCPartPicker part list](https://pcpartpicker.com/list/gw8qyf) / [Price breakdown by merchant](https://pcpartpicker.com/list/gw8qyf/by_merchant/)

Type|Item|Price
:----|:----|:----
**CPU** | [Intel Core i7-4790K 4.0GHz Quad-Core Processor](https://pcpartpicker.com/product/6vzv6h/intel-cpu-bx80646i74790k) | $339.49 @ SuperBiiz 
**CPU Cooler** | [Corsair H110 94.0 CFM Liquid CPU Cooler](https://pcpartpicker.com/product/p94gXL/corsair-cpu-cooler-h110) | $89.99 @ Newegg 
**Motherboard** | [MSI Z97-GAMING 5 ATX LGA1150 Motherboard](https://pcpartpicker.com/product/2fYXsY/msi-motherboard-z97gaming5) |-
**Memory** | [Corsair Vengeance Pro 32GB (4 x 8GB) DDR3-2400 Memory](https://pcpartpicker.com/product/FdphP6/corsair-memory-cmy32gx3m4a2400c11r) | $267.99 @ Amazon 
**Storage** | [Samsung 840 EVO 500GB 2.5" Solid State Drive](https://pcpartpicker.com/product/7MLypg/samsung-internal-hard-drive-mz7te500bw) | $299.88 @ OutletPC 
**Storage** | [Western Digital Red 1TB 3.5" 5400RPM Internal Hard Drive](https://pcpartpicker.com/product/RwW9TW/western-digital-internal-hard-drive-wd10efrx) | $63.77 @ OutletPC 
**Video Card** | [Gigabyte GeForce GTX 1080 Ti 11GB AORUS Xtreme Edition 11G Video Card](https://pcpartpicker.com/product/bd2rxr/gigabyte-geforce-gtx-1080-ti-11gb-aorus-xtreme-edition-11g-video-card-gv-n108taorus-x-11gd) | $759.98 @ Newegg 
**Case** | [Fractal Design Define R5 (Black) ATX Mid Tower Case](https://pcpartpicker.com/product/sjX2FT/fractal-design-case-fdcadefr5bk) | $104.99 @ SuperBiiz 
**Power Supply** | [SeaSonic X Series 850W 80+ Gold Certified Fully-Modular ATX Power Supply](https://pcpartpicker.com/product/JQbp99/seasonic-power-supply-x850) | $107.99 @ SuperBiiz 
**Optical Drive** | [LG BH16NS40 Blu-Ray/DVD/CD Writer](https://pcpartpicker.com/product/WXK7YJ/lg-optical-drive-bh16ns40) | $98.80 @ OutletPC 
**Operating System** | [Microsoft Windows 10 Home OEM 64-bit](https://pcpartpicker.com/product/wtgPxr/microsoft-os-kw900140) | $88.58 @ OutletPC 
**Monitor** | [Dell U2713HM 27.0" 2560x1440 60Hz Monitor](https://pcpartpicker.com/product/kfQypg/dell-monitor-u2713hm) | $679.00 @ Amazon 
 | *Prices include shipping, taxes, rebates, and discounts* |
 | Total (before mail-in rebates) | $2920.46
 | Mail-in rebates | -$20.00
 | **Total** | **$2900.46**
 | Generated by [PCPartPicker](http://pcpartpicker.com) 2017-04-27 11:25 EDT-0400 |

**Describe your problem. List any error messages and symptoms. Be descriptive.**

I can't get my third monitor working. It's connected via a DVI-D to DisplayPort cable (DisplayPort on GPU). Windows and everything on Windows detects the display but the monitor won't turn on. I can even set to extend desktop to the display but again nothing is actually shown.

**Provide any additional details you wish below.**

The monitor is a Dell 1708FP with only DVI and VGA ports. Not going to try the VGA. Don't have VGA inputs on my GPU anyway. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-27 05:42:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That's true. It's hard to pull to the side when no one else does it. I've tried to but I'm limited by the car next to me. If only Singaporeans could do the amazing traffic split on one of those German ambulance videos.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-27 05:27:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Mercedes. They have a car for everyone.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-27 05:24:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Well it's free. There must be some compromise. Funny thing is, I have a paid VPN which stopped working for a site recently but Hola still works!  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-27 05:21:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> We can't pull to the side because our kerbs are much higher than those in Europe. Emergency vehicles don't even blow through red lights here. I once stopped on green to let the oncoming ambulance through his red, but the driver hesitated for a long time (after I used my high beams to signal to him) before he proceeded. I guess it's just the culture here. Even in driving school, I was only told to not obstruct emergency vehicles. That's about it.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-26 14:49:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That's not too bad. I think we have to compare that with other congested cities around the world. London's 7.8mph.

It really depends on your commute. I average 60-70km/h on my daily commute across Singapore. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-26 12:17:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Same. The price dropped to $749.99 for some short periods but usually run out of stock before I hit checkout. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-26 06:54:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Only in ATS at the moment. But I'm sure that ETS2 will get it sooner or later.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-26 06:34:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> They aren't separately controlled. They are automatically managed but not directly in relation to your steering input. For example, when you're stopped and you turn your wheels, the trailer wheels won't turn. There's some other mechanism at work to steer it so that it tries to follow the front track.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-26 06:32:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's mine. It's part of their closed beta.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-26 05:28:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Their pianos are far from high quality.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Steering axles </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-25 15:51:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-25 13:29:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Soon </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Heavy Cargo </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-25 09:13:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-24 17:44:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> No it's not. The paint's nice but it's always sad for me to see classics slammed.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-24 17:41:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What an ugly car.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-24 17:40:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Not elegant enough for an Aston. The strange wheel/bonnet thing at the front really ruins the look. It looks aftermarket. The body's also too narrow for the car's width at the wheels.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-24 06:26:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Just a guess but I think it's doubly more difficult to get licences since chassis and bodies are from different manufacturers most of the time.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-24 06:20:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Only Mozart is worth listening to. Salieri? Nah.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-24 06:04:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Samsung? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-24 05:47:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Don't understand why people would give money to a manufacturer who has shown time and time again to neglect the rigourous testing of their products.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [I Ate] Chilled Slipper Lobster </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-24 05:33:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-23 17:44:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Okay will try to do so.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-23 11:51:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hmm I do have a multimeter at home but I don't really understand the procedure to check the voltage. I paid someone to build the PC so I'm not familiar with the PSU cables and plugs. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Symptom of failing PSU? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-23 10:15:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> ###Troubleshooting Help:

**What is your parts list? [Consider formatting your parts list.](http://www.reddit.com/r/buildapc/wiki/pcpp)**

[PCPartPicker part list](https://pcpartpicker.com/list/nBYXGf) / [Price breakdown by merchant](https://pcpartpicker.com/list/nBYXGf/by_merchant/)

Type|Item|Price
:----|:----|:----
**CPU** | [Intel Core i7-4790K 4.0GHz Quad-Core Processor](https://pcpartpicker.com/product/6vzv6h/intel-cpu-bx80646i74790k) | $339.49 @ SuperBiiz 
**CPU Cooler** | [Corsair H110 94.0 CFM Liquid CPU Cooler](https://pcpartpicker.com/product/p94gXL/corsair-cpu-cooler-h110) | $99.99 @ Amazon 
**Motherboard** | [MSI Z97-GAMING 5 ATX LGA1150 Motherboard](https://pcpartpicker.com/product/2fYXsY/msi-motherboard-z97gaming5) |-
**Memory** | [Corsair Vengeance Pro 32GB (4 x 8GB) DDR3-2400 Memory](https://pcpartpicker.com/product/FdphP6/corsair-memory-cmy32gx3m4a2400c11r) | $259.99 @ Newegg 
**Storage** | [Samsung 840 EVO 500GB 2.5" Solid State Drive](https://pcpartpicker.com/product/7MLypg/samsung-internal-hard-drive-mz7te500bw) | $299.88 @ OutletPC 
**Storage** | [Western Digital Red 1TB 3.5" 5400RPM Internal Hard Drive](https://pcpartpicker.com/product/RwW9TW/western-digital-internal-hard-drive-wd10efrx) | $63.77 @ OutletPC 
**Video Card** | [MSI GeForce GTX 970 4GB Twin Frozr V Video Card](https://pcpartpicker.com/product/2j4NnQ/msi-video-card-gtx970gaming4g) (2-Way SLI) | $494.89 @ OutletPC 
**Video Card** | [MSI GeForce GTX 970 4GB Twin Frozr V Video Card](https://pcpartpicker.com/product/2j4NnQ/msi-video-card-gtx970gaming4g) (2-Way SLI) | $494.89 @ OutletPC 
**Case** | [Fractal Design Define R5 (Black) ATX Mid Tower Case](https://pcpartpicker.com/product/sjX2FT/fractal-design-case-fdcadefr5bk) | $104.99 @ SuperBiiz 
**Power Supply** | [SeaSonic X Series 850W 80+ Gold Certified Fully-Modular ATX Power Supply](https://pcpartpicker.com/product/JQbp99/seasonic-power-supply-x850) | $107.89 @ Newegg 
**Optical Drive** | [LG BH16NS40 Blu-Ray/DVD/CD Writer](https://pcpartpicker.com/product/WXK7YJ/lg-optical-drive-bh16ns40) | $98.80 @ OutletPC 
**Operating System** | [Microsoft Windows 10 Home OEM 64-bit](https://pcpartpicker.com/product/wtgPxr/microsoft-os-kw900140) | $88.58 @ OutletPC 
**Monitor** | [Dell U2713HM 27.0" 2560x1440 60Hz Monitor](https://pcpartpicker.com/product/kfQypg/dell-monitor-u2713hm) | $679.00 @ Amazon 
 | *Prices include shipping, taxes, rebates, and discounts* |
 | Total (before mail-in rebates) | $3162.16
 | Mail-in rebates | -$30.00
 | **Total** | **$3132.16**
 | Generated by [PCPartPicker](http://pcpartpicker.com) 2017-04-23 04:12 EDT-0400 |

**Describe your problem. List any error messages and symptoms. Be descriptive.**

I don't know if my PSU is starting to fail, but here are some problems related to starting it. Sometimes after pressing the on button, it takes 10s before the computer starts. 

Twice, after I've gone on a 2 week long holiday, the computer fails to boot but power cycles. The power LED will turn on for a few seconds (with fans and everything on), and then shut down again by itself, before trying to start again. This happens over and over and seems to resolve itself randomly after a few hours. Opening the case up and toggling the PSU on and off doesn't seem to help. It just works randomly. After successfully starting, it's fine until the next stint of not being turned on for 1 week. 

Are these problems symptomatic of PSU failure, or motherboard issues?
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-23 08:52:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yup. Feels off on a luxury car. I guess I just don't like the spoke design. It's not clean and elegant.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-23 08:48:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I must be the only one that find them quite gaudy.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-23 04:54:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Oh sod off. How do you even jump to the conclusion that I've never heard of Carl's Jr? Isn't it painfully obvious that I'm referring to the more mainstream ones? Or are you just trying to deny the issue by pointing out the exception, rather than the rule? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-22 20:36:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I love Operas! What are your most performed roles? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-22 20:02:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Well can't complain. Not having a terrible life does not deny me from providing an anecdotal example of how we put up with one another.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-22 18:00:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> 'Level the playing field'.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-22 17:58:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's racial tolerance. I have to tolerate the fact that I can't get proper bacon at fast food outlets.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-22 17:55:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> According to [here](http://forum.aorus.com/forum/gaming-graphics-cards/42302-aorus-geforce-gtx-1080-ti-11gb-video-card) the Xtreme has a larger copper back plate. But I read in reviews there's isn't much difference. Seems like ZOTAC's AMP EXTREME has even higher clock speeds and can overclock to 2,075MHz. So many choices... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-22 15:13:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Which GTX 1080 Ti should I get? I live in a very hot country so I'd prefer the one with the best cooling capability. I'm looking at the Aorus GTX 1080 Ti vs the Aorus GTX 1080 Ti Xtreme. Is there any significant difference between the two? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-21 18:35:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> They fit into the gas stations fine. You have to be quite skilled though, taking super wide turns.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-21 12:23:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I would say yes, technically. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-20 10:29:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yea, some are saying that the D2 can be raised from 115HP to 140+. Seems too good to be true. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-20 04:47:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Progeria? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-20 04:35:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I wonder about the same for my D2. Don't know if those RaceChip things actually work.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-19 20:17:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Do you speak Cantonese? English standards in HK are much lower than in Singapore.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-19 16:13:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Wow, never heard of them. I'll keep a lookout, but their webpage is a mess. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-19 11:59:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I know about those excerpt performances but I'm really more interested in full-scale opera productions. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-19 11:58:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You can't see anything at all, especially when you're short. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-19 09:24:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Seems like you went the wrong way? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-19 07:35:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I saw that one too. It was just one of the arias IIRC. Honestly, it wasn't such a good performance.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-19 05:47:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm quite surprised how cheap tickets are here. For that production in Vienna I paid 200+ for seats in the third section.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-19 05:39:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Can these coilovers be softer and provide a more compliant ride than OEM setups? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Any opera buffs here? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-19 05:37:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I wonder if any of you love (western) classical operas like I do. It's disappointing that we don't get much of an opportunity to enjoy this genre of music here in Singapore. The SLO always plays *Cosi Fan Tutte* but not more exciting (if I may say so) ones like *The Marriage of Figaro* or *La Traviata*. It's so exciting for me to have had the opportunity to watch the former in Vienna. If only we could enjoy more of such amazing works here.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-17 12:04:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I see. The term must have succeeded what was previously just known as 'presentable'.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-17 09:55:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Reminds me of a piece I read about drunk Dutch people (Dutchmen?) lifting Smart cars and pushing them into the rivers. There are always black sheep around, but are those in Singapore really statistically more significant? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-17 09:53:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Since when did Instagrammable become an acceptable word to be used by publications such as this? Not complaining, just intrigued by the usage.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-17 07:07:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Please post this to /r/india </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-17 07:01:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I have the same case! I just use the two white fans for the front. I have 3 other Noctuas 140mm (2 for the Corsair H110 radiator on the top) and one Corsair 120mm on the back.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-16 20:31:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Playing the piano.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-16 17:59:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Haha anonymity. I use Reddit because I want to express my opinions, which seem particularly controversial in this subreddit.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-16 05:48:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> There seems to already be a lot of HKers here. I wonder how many. My parents are one of those.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-15 20:39:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The road seems like it went slightly downhill. Would this have affected the result significantly? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-15 08:44:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I think what's more important is the rpm at 90km/h.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-15 06:33:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I don't think there'll be much of a difference. The longer gear ratios will be cancelled out by the shorter diff ratio.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-15 05:50:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm located in Singapore. It's funny that the entry-level S90 is more expensive than the equivalent E-Class and 5-series. I can't believe they're increasing the price for the MY18 when it's made in China.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-14 18:08:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hmm it's made in China now. I hope the prices will drop significantly. My local dealer's charging a ridiculous markup of 60% now.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-13 18:30:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Maybe not at the same time.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-13 12:21:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Don't you have Jake brakes or a retarder? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-13 12:16:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> They fit just fine.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
