<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject4211</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-10 16:01:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's okay, you can say "Julius Caesar" on reddit. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-10 15:14:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This House?  Only if absolutely unavoidable.

The new House after the 2018 elections?  Now you're talking. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-10 15:02:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Actually, the Senate is hugely important for at least two reasons:

* No new FBI director can be appointed until confirmed by the Senate.

* If Trump or Pence is impeached by the House, the trial and possible conviction will take place in the Senate. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-10 14:55:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Oh God, no.  That's horrible news.

Last night, Trump crossed the Rubicon.  It is literally up to the Senate to decide whether or not he'll have complete control in our nation's capital, just as it was a couple of millennia ago for a different Senate confronting Julius Caesar. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-10 14:46:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The word "obstruct" is very powerful.  Remember that the first article of impeachment passed against Nixon was for obstruction of justice. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-10 14:44:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I've submitted to /r/technology. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Google Chrome won't be allowed on Windows 10 S </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-10 14:43:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-10 14:38:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's not like the USA is the only developed nation in which a major political party denies the reality of global climate change... oh wait, actually it is exactly like that. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-10 14:34:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Crazy yes, losing touch with reality yes, hurting his country yes... but there's a sense of honor in Lear that Trump will never remotely approach. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-10 14:31:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Lindsey Graham.  Maybe even Ben Sasse.  And that's just on the Judiciary committee. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-10 14:23:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [Science says otherwise.](https://kaiweber.wordpress.com/2010/05/31/ragged-right-or-justified-alignment/) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-10 14:19:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> ["*Standing on the shoulders of giants leaves me cold.*"  REM](https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=kleqF3X1_l4) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-10 14:03:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It all depends on the Catholic school.  That sentiment is very Jesuit, although it's far from guaranteed that the Jesuits running a high school will be trying to inculcate that attitude in teenagers.  They might wait till college for that. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-10 13:26:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Trump is more [Abe Simpson](http://i2.kym-cdn.com/photos/images/original/001/044/247/297.png) than he is Lear or Littlefinger. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-10 13:03:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Read between the headlines:

Trump Hires Law Firm, Making It Even More Obvious That Trump Has Russia Business Ties </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-10 12:53:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Trump will try.  But a nomination for Director of the FBI requires Senate confirmation.  There are plenty of Trump-lapdog Republican senators, but there are enough Republicans in the Senate who won't go along with a cover-up. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-10 11:38:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> From the article:

The move exposed Mr. Trump to the suspicion that he has something to hide and could strain his relations with fellow Republicans who may be wary of defending him when they do not have all the facts. Many Republicans issued cautious statements on Tuesday, but a few expressed misgivings about Mr. Comeys dismissal and called for a special congressional investigation or independent commission to take over from the House and Senate Intelligence Committees now looking into the Russia episode.

Please contact your representatives in Congress, especially if they are Republican.
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-10 04:23:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> In fact, more than just mildly nauseated. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-10 03:02:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [*These semicolons are my light inside the dark*...](https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=M94ii6MVilw) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-10 02:32:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [Quoth NAELA:](https://www.naela.org/App_Themes/Public/PDF/Advocacy%20Tab/Advocacy%20Action%20Center/Step-by-Step%20guide%20to%20writing%20to%20Congress.pdf)

**If urgency is required, fax or email the letter rather than using the postal system;** mail takes 3 to 4 weeks to arrive in Washington, D.C. due to testing for dangerous enclosures. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-10 00:21:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [~~Saturday~~](https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Saturday_Night_Massacre) Tuesday Night Massacre. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-10 00:02:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It looks like [Donald Trump still owned 24% of Trump Entertainment Resorts until it emerged from bankruptcy in July 2010.  Trump Entertainment Resorts owned the Trump Taj Mahal.](http://www.barrons.com/articles/SB50001424052970203579804576285341283000706)

The [FinCEN press released linked by the grandparent comment](https://www.fincen.gov/news/news-releases/fincen-fines-trump-taj-mahal-casino-resort-10-million-significant-and-long) cites Bank Secrecy Act violations dating back as far as 2003, and currency transaction reporting violations in 1998.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-09 23:43:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Although you actually don't need this to be specifically the tax returns if money-laundering is involved. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-09 23:09:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Not just "Trump-related officials" per Warner, nor "Trump team" per the headline, but Trump himself:
 information related to **President Donald Trump**, his top officials and his campaign aides </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-09 22:01:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thanks for the response! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-09 21:33:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I've been trying to think of possible explanations for Michael Flynn (1) being named as National Security Advisor and (2) being kept on after the Sally Yates warnings.  The only explanations I've come up with so far are (1) the Trump administration as a whole is compromised by the Kremlin, (2) the Trump administration as a whole is incompetent, or (3) both.  Surely there must be other possible explanations... right? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-09 21:25:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> *When you see the Southern Cross for the first time     
You understand now why you came this way* </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Karl Stefanovic admits southern cross tattoo on shoulder </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-09 21:24:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Macron offers refuge in France to U.S. scientists, entrepreneurs </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-09 21:02:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-09 13:28:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> And they changed their name from the Gorillas. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-09 03:18:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Great catch.

Spicer's next sentence was "The White House Counsel reviewed and determined that there is not a legal issue, but rather a trust issue."  That jibes with Yates's characterization of McGahn as a bit blas about Flynn, although it's a bit disingenuous about Flynn's legal problems. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-08 23:28:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Right.  The Trump administration is either incompetent, or compromised, or both. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-08 22:50:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> For a moment.  Then I checked his political positions.  So let me make it clear that I find Senator Sasse's politics repulsive... but even he is giving the appearance of acting in the best nonpartisan interests of the American people in his questioning in this hearing. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-08 22:33:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yates just reiterated that this "underlying conduct" of Flynn is classified, and she can't reveal it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-08 22:30:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Senator Ben Sasse (R-NE), however, played it straight and nonpartisan. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-08 22:24:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Except that Senator Ben Sasse (R-NE) is playing it straight and nonpartisan. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-08 22:19:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Moments ago, Clapper called RT a propaganda mouthpiece for the Russian government in a Senate hearing.  So I won't be reading this article, thanks. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-08 22:10:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Listening to the hearing, Flynn appears to have **done** something that (1) there's evidence of, (2) the Russians have the evidence of, and (3) that would destroy his career.  Yates just testified that she warned the Trump administration about that before they kept Flynn on for another eighteen days as National Security Advisor.  Further, Senator Feinstein reiterated the news reports that Obama warned the Trump administration about Flynn months before they brought Flynn on as National Security Advisor.

What sort of idiots are unconcerned about having as the National Security Advisor in their administration someone vulnerable to blackmail by Putin? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-08 22:00:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> From Wikipedia, "a thousand and one":

Making false statements (18 U.S.C.  1001) is the common name for the United States federal crime laid out in Section 1001 of Title 18 of the United States Code, which generally prohibits knowingly and willfully making false or fraudulent statements, or concealing information, in "any matter within the jurisdiction" of the federal government of the United States, even by mere denial. A number of notable people have been convicted under the section, including Martha Stewart, Rod Blagojevich, Scooter Libby, Bernard Madoff, and Jeffrey Skilling. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-08 21:22:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> From Wikipedia:
A FD-302 form is used by FBI agents to "report or summarize the interviews that they conduct" and contains information from the notes taken during the interview by the non-primary agent.

It consists of information taken from the subject, rather than details about the subject themselves.

A forms list from an internal FBI Website lists the FD-302 as *Form for Reporting Information That May Become Testimony.* </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-08 21:21:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> From Wikipedia:
A FD-302 form is used by FBI agents to "report or summarize the interviews that they conduct" and contains information from the notes taken during the interview by the non-primary agent.

It consists of information taken from the subject, rather than details about the subject themselves.

A forms list from an internal FBI Website lists the FD-302 as *Form for Reporting Information That May Become Testimony.* </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-08 20:35:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Sen. Lindsey Graham (R-SC) emphasizing **Russia** as the responsible party in his opening statement. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-08 20:33:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Getting sound on [Politico's stream.](http://www.politico.com/livestream-watch-live-politico-streaming) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-08 20:30:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yes, [income by county](http://i.imgur.com/ukv3QEb.png) is probably the most significant predictive factor. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-08 20:28:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [You can watch the pre-hearing stream via Politico here.](http://www.politico.com/livestream-watch-live-politico-streaming)  At the moment, it's just people standing around the hearing room. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-08 20:14:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> *The Skynet Funding Bill is passed. The system goes online August 4th, ~~1997~~ 2017. Human decisions are removed from ~~strategic defense~~ automatic guillotines. Skynet begins to learn at a geometric rate.  It becomes self-aware at 2:14 a.m. Eastern time, August 29th. In a panic, they try to pull the plug.* </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-08 20:13:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hey friends, want a long and healthy life?

[Stay away from opioids.](http://cdn.static-economist.com/sites/default/files/images/2017/03/blogs/graphic-detail/20170311_woc097.png)

Seriously, while that opioid overdose map doesn't quite parallel the [life-expectancy map from the linked CNN article,](http://ix.cnn.io/dailygraphics/graphics/20170505-map-life-expectancy/map.png) there is significant overlap. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-08 19:31:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I mean, they reference '82 in the song's lyrics! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-08 19:03:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [*It was the heat of the moment...*](https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=cpxsMyoXUZQ)

But seriously, [the survey has only been tracking how many Canadians hold a favourable view of the United States since 1982,](http://www.theglobeandmail.com/news/national/canadians-still-pro-immigration-souring-on-united-states-survey/article34916205/) so it's the lowest percentage in the history of the survey.

(I retained the extra Canadian "u" in "favourable".) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-08 16:34:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The linked CNN video is from last week.  [We talked about it back then, when CNN first broke the story.](https://np.reddit.com/r/politics/comments/68vxea/sources_former_acting_ag_yates_to_contradict/) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-08 14:20:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah, but how do you write Charles de Gaulle in French?  Have they even heard of Charles de Gaulle in France?

^^Too ^^obvious ^^even ^^for ^^Poe's ^^law, ^^*non?* </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-08 14:14:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Wat? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-08 14:00:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> EWR is Newark International Airport.  People who fly frequently, and of course those who work for an airline, know the three-letter codes for all the major airports. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-08 13:58:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> via emirates

There's your problem.  You're flying one of the best airlines in the world.  In contrast, this woman was on United. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-08 01:47:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> netrek.

I'm old. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-07 21:28:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Maybe he listened to ["Cat People (Putting Out Fire)"](https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=VpdHMaccjw4) one too many times. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-07 18:51:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> A good antimetabole is pleasing, and a pleasing antimetabole is good. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-07 15:37:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> No.  Parenthood is amazingly wonderful.

Parenthood is also a crushing responsibility that never ends.

Once you accept the crushing responsibility, you get to enjoy the amazingly wonderful aspects more. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-07 01:59:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Musta been some kegger. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-06 20:59:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Any format of the *Dungeons   Dragons* movie. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-06 20:49:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The Senate doesn't send people to prison.

Tell that to [William P. MacCracken, Jr.](https://en.m.wikipedia.org/wiki/Jurney_v._MacCracken) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-06 20:46:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> *Desperate Housewives*. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-06 20:41:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Obligatory *Firefly*.  The "Out of Gas" episode, in particular, is of surpassing excellence.

A fourteen-episode series is a short fallback, though.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-06 20:11:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [Pat Benatar certainly did.](https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=MnDijNVpngA) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-06 17:58:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Bingo. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-06 17:45:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> In this particular case, it means that Congress, should they so choose, can either force compliance from Carter Page, or start him on his way to prison. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-06 16:53:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> In some cases, you don't even need to be particularly rich, just well-educated.  For example, [Denmark used to have a Greencard scheme](http://web.archive.org/web/20141003144834/https://www.nyidanmark.dk/en-us/coming_to_dk/work/greencard-scheme/greencard-scheme.htm) in which highly educated English speakers could immigrate even if they didn't know a word of Danish.  But Denmark repealed that scheme last summer, although they still have a [list of fields in which education and a job offer suffice for immigration.](https://www.nyidanmark.dk/en-us/coming_to_dk/work/positivelist/positive_list_overview.htm) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-06 15:57:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Um, this has been around for a quarter century.  It's called the [Green Card Through Investment.](https://www.uscis.gov/green-card/green-card-through-job/green-card-through-investment)  Invest $1,000,000 anywhere in the USA, or just $500,000 in a targeted employment area, and you and your spouse and your unmarried children under the age of 21 all get green cards.  Once you all have green cards, then it's just the usual waiting period and test to become citizens.

This all [dates from the bipartisan Immigration Act of 1990.](https://en.m.wikipedia.org/wiki/EB-5_visa) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-06 15:30:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> True, if you're in a field where experiments take a long time to run, you're not going to get a Ph.D. quickly.  The three people I remember in my graduate program who graduated with alacrity studied the following:

* an area of theoretical computer science in which that student was able to prove a new significant result quickly (that student had been a superstar young mathematician, including a silver medal in the International Math Olympiad);

* an area of probabilistic reasoning in which that student was able to lay the groundwork for a whole new subfield, and harvest all the low-hanging fruit in that subfield;

* (finally, actual experimentation) a previously unsolved problem in machine learning, which succumbed to the first approach tried by that student. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-06 14:47:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It does happen far too often, but there are also plenty of advisors out there who fall into one of two categories:

* They're earnest academics.

* They're completely mercenary, but judge that the advantages of graduating a star student quickly outweigh the advantages of trying to exploit slave labor.  A star Ph.D. graduate can go to another university but keep collaborating with you, can expand your influence in your field, can serve par encourager les autres, etc. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-06 13:41:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Even in the USA, you can go bachelor's to Ph.D. in 3 or 3.5 years in the sciences and math.  Those are best-case scenarios, to be sure, but if everything goes smoothly and you quickly accomplish a notable piece of original research, a good advisor and a good program will graduate you so that you can continue your career.  Note: does not apply to slavedriving advisors who are trying to exploit you.

Also, a one-hour dissertation defense seems perfectly reasonable. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-06 13:33:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Pro tip for anyone reading this who hasn't defended: if your advisor is at least minimally competent, your advisor will not allow you to defend unless you're going to pass. ^^with ^^one ^^specific ^^exception

All right, the specific exception is if your graduate program is trying to get rid of you, and all other subtler methods of trying to accomplish that goal have failed.  So if your advisor has been hinting that you may want to take a leave of absence from the program and you've been ignoring the hints, okay, maybe your "defense" is actually the merciful execution of your unrealistic postgraduate ambitions.  Otherwise, you're going to pass.
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-05 23:42:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> In an all-staff email to employees in the Office of National Drug Control Policy, acting Director Richard Baum shared some news he described as "very discouraging for our Nation's effort to address drug abuse." A draft document from the White House budget office, obtained by NPR, proposes nearly zeroing-out funding for the ONDCP and fully eliminating several programs involved in fighting the opioid crisis. Leaked documents indicate about a 94 percent overall cut. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-05 23:41:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> In an all-staff email to employees in the Office of National Drug Control Policy, acting Director Richard Baum shared some news he described as "very discouraging for our Nation's effort to address drug abuse." A draft document from the White House budget office, obtained by NPR, proposes nearly zeroing-out funding for the ONDCP and fully eliminating several programs involved in fighting the opioid crisis. Leaked documents indicate about a 94 percent overall cut. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Leaked Document Indicates Big Proposed Cuts To Drug Czar's Office </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-05 23:39:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Leaked Document Indicates Big Proposed Cuts To Drug Czar's Office </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-05 23:38:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-05 22:41:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> CNN said further that:
The mainstream media is not fake news, and therefore the ad is false and per policy will be accepted only if that graphic is deleted. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-05 18:48:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> #itsatrap

Remember that the first article of impeachment passed against Nixon was obstruction of justice. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-04 18:12:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Right, this bill, as it is, is dead on arrival in the Senate.  But getting it through the House starts the negotiations.

Republicans are 95% to get this bill through the House today, and the only reason it isn't 99.9% is the weirdness of 2017's political climate. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-04 12:58:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Imagine how much work Prince Phillip's schedulers and other royal schedulers need to do to disentangle Phillip from any engagements already planned in or after the autumn, and to select replacement royals. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-03 17:30:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> /u/gentlebot expressed a hunch about why /r/television became a default in /r/TheoryOfReddit: https://np.reddit.com/r/TheoryOfReddit/comments/1kjjb1/why_i_think_rtelevision_and_rearthporn_were_made/ </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-03 14:10:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> He comments one syllable... and then vanishes again. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> After three years of reddit silence, Ken Jennings shows up to a Jeopardy! discussion </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-03 14:10:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-03 02:55:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Lies told about criminal matters are a quick ticket to a convinction for obstruction of justice.  As the saying goes, "it's not the crime; it's the cover-up." </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-02 19:31:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm confused.  Clearly you don't understand that [Jesus looked like Fabio.](https://02varvara.files.wordpress.com/2011/09/unknown-artist-christ-enthroned-as-heavenly-king-national-shrine-of-the-immacualte-conception-undated.jpg)

^("like Fabio" is one of the kinder descriptions I've heard of that depiction of a certain Galilean from Nazareth, a depiction found in the Shrine of the Immaculate Conception in Washington, DC) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-02 17:31:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Since no one has yet done so in this thread, I'm going to summon my Shardblade... er... that is... I'm going to at least give /u/mistborn the courtesy of a username mention, since people are saying nice things about him here. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-01 17:26:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Full text from @RichBurlew:
Hey. So obviously I've been out of touch for a bit. Back now, trying to get on top of things that slid.

I need to finish off O-Chul story for the Kickstarter backers, which I need a few more days...this week? Maybe?...and then a regular comic.

Once O-Chul's done I'll be able to focus on the main strip again for a bit.

Thanks to everyone who's sent their support during all of this. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The Giant emerges on Twitter: "[...] been out of touch [...] Back now [...] finish off O-Chul story [...] this week? Maybe?" </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-01 17:25:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-01 16:47:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [Game highlights found.](http://www.nfl.com/videos/nfl-game-highlights/0ap3000000580520/Lions-vs-Packers-highlights) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-01 16:14:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Not those kind of errors.  Rather, Trump "errs" in failing to fully exploit the opportunities that the presidency, in combination with certain dysfunctions in our government and our society, affords him.  Someone skilled, or even just reasonably competent, at consolidating power would, for example, not waste time watching as much television and playing as much golf as Trump does.  Further, while Trump engages in some fights that are very useful to him, but he also picks a lot of fights that don't help him achieve anything. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-01 14:55:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If we're unlucky, there's enough know-how and will among members of the Trump administration to exploit the existing tools and amoral motivations in our government and our society to create a fascist regime. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-01 14:47:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The next decade seems a trifle optimistic, but it won't take fifty years either.  For some in-depth analysis, check [this 2015 report by an Australian think tank,](http://adminpanel.ceda.com.au/FOLDERS/Service/Files/Documents/26792%7EFutureworkforce_June2015.pdf) or [this shorter presentation partly derived from that report.](http://www.fya.org.au/wp-content/uploads/2015/08/fya-future-of-work-report-final-lr.pdf) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-01 14:40:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The two best introductions to the topic of AI and jobs that I know of are both entitled *Humans Need Not Apply*:

* [This video with that title](https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=7Pq-S557XQU) by /u/MindOfMetalAndWheels.

* The book with that title by Jerry Kaplan. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-30 14:22:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Except that compensatory picks generally disrupt the pattern starting at the end of the third round.  For example, that's why the Packers' non-compensatory picks at the end of the first four rounds in 1997 were numbers 30, 60, 90, and... 126.  (Also, trades can change teams' picks.)

As a point of trivia, the first compensatory pick that year was by the Steelers, but he became much more famous as a Patriot: Mike Vrabel. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-30 04:55:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I mean, we can't get a future three-time (and, for AB, counting) All-Pro in the sixth round of every draft.  Only in 2010 and 1987 (Greg Lloyd).  Shout-out to steady sixth-rounder and occasional Pro Bowler Tunch Ilkin as well. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-30 04:49:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Stepping back from the maymays for a minute: college rules insulate the long snapper, so no long snappers in college "snap and protect".  In contrast, NFL rules do not give long snappers the privilege of that insulation. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-30 04:38:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Superfecundity does occur, but twins with the same father can also appear to be different ethnicities.  Karen and Cheryl Grant, for example, were born so long ago that they [appeared as adults on *The Montel Williams Show*,](https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=HFsHq90H70k) and that's been off the air for almost a decade. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-30 04:27:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  *You're welcome...*  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-30 04:22:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Pretend you didn't get the raise, or at least not all of it.  Put the difference in savings or in retirement investments.  Live well within your means. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-30 04:16:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Right, ending with a single can always lead to the thought, "couldn't you have done better than a single here?"  But ending with a homer is unimpeachable. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-30 04:14:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I seem to recall that Kenny Rogers was at a press conference after the perfect game alongside Kenny Rogers, but can't scare up a video or even a pic. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-30 04:10:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So... you're not a Jedi. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-29 20:36:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> ^^do ^^I ^^need ^^to ^^write ^^this ^^whole ^^parody ^^by ^^myself?

*HE'S THE PAUPER OF THE TUNES    
THE JESTER OF MAR'JUANA* </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-29 20:32:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> (that doesn't sound like any part of [the song](https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=GI6CfKcMhjY)) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-29 18:33:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> *A STONER SO BRAVE    
AT A MUSIC FEST*

#

^^yes, ^^I ^^replied ^^to ^^myself </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-29 18:10:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> *THIS IS THE TALE    
OF ACTOR SETH ROGEN* </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-29 05:57:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Obstruction of justice. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-29 05:49:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Like the Washington Times, the Washington Examiner has a conservative slant. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-29 05:39:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Come on, do the Steelers ever get good players in the third round?...  Oh wait. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-29 05:31:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> When does a cover-up become obstruction of justice?  I think lying to Congress qualifies, when the lie is about not having documentation of having vetted Flynn. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-29 05:28:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Oh, it's real.  From Wikipedia:
Founded on May 17, 1982, by Unification Church leader Sun Myung Moon, the Times was owned by News World Communications, an international media conglomerate associated with the church until 2010, in which Moon and a group of former executives purchased the paper. It is currently owned by diversified conglomerate Operations Holdings, which is a wholly owned subsidiary of the church. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-29 03:26:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That's a "best player available" pick, not a need pick. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-29 03:25:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Computer scientists who are ever going to do algorithm analysis fervently need L'Hpital's rule, so that's also a possible answer for /u/2500LbSteelSteps. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-29 03:00:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> One of my prouder moments as an American was before a friendly we hosted against Scotland, in Florida of all places, on which occasion the local Floridian bagpipers performed "Flower of Scotland". </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-29 02:51:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That's because Dr. Seuss loved anapestic tetrameter with frequent iambic substitution in the first foot of the line, and /u/Poem_for_your_sprog's whole poem here is in anapestic tetrameter with iambic substitution in the first foot of each line. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-28 02:49:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Ooh, thought I had.  Maybe I forgot to save the flair change.  Thanks! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-28 02:23:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thankssearching for Paganini led me to the correct answer: https://en.m.wikipedia.org/wiki/Piano_Sonata_No._2_(Schumann) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [TOMT] Story about a composer of classical music who instructs at one point in the piece, "play as fast as possible", followed shortly by the instruction "play faster"? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-28 02:13:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-27 23:04:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The number is [four,](https://www.reddit.com/user/scarfdontstrangleme/gilded/) that is, low and hence not unlikely. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-27 17:13:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> (I'm pretty sure the moon landing was in 19**6**9) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-27 00:52:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [Teen Girl Scientist Monthly - Safari](https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=0eOmK5upihk)

Found it from its use as a sample at the end of BriTANicK videos. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-27 00:32:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The good news is that the Republicans cannot break up the Supreme Court.

The bad news is that there is nothing stopping Republicans from packing the Supreme Court with two or four or six more conservative justices, other than tradition and their own party's lack of support for such a ploy.  A Supreme Court with four liberal justices, one moderate justice, and **ten** conservative justices would be an ugly possibility. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-26 22:10:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> apology for poor english

where were you when paco alka-seltzer scores brace

i was sat at home wearing andr gomes jersey when mascherano ring

'paco scores brace'

'no'

and you????????????? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-26 20:58:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Surely Trump is ineligible; that's the only way anyone but him can win. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-26 20:01:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Might have to acquire the Star Realms app, based on the recommendation from /u/wil in this episode.  I acquired the Tanto Cuore app based on the recommendation from /u/fday in [this Table Top Day livestream,](http://geekandsundry.com/tanto-cuore-table-top-day-livestream/) and have played it endlessly. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-25 20:27:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Fortunately, [I found a longer version without the stupid sound effects.](https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=TvcUnQZ_g2I) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-25 19:18:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> But finally, you learn all the languages </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-25 19:01:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [Video that goes on longer](https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=dwXuEhpGO28) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-25 19:00:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [He escaped, though.](https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=dwXuEhpGO28) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-25 18:59:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [videothatgoesonlonger](https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=dwXuEhpGO28) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-25 18:59:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [Driver clear, forklift not.](https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=dwXuEhpGO28) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-25 18:58:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [Yes.](https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=dwXuEhpGO28)  Driver is okay. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-25 18:58:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Ooh, I found what [appears to be the source video.](https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=dwXuEhpGO28) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-25 18:45:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Via /u/naturalwallpaper. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Catastrophic failure of pallet racks caused by nudge from a forklift </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-25 18:45:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-23 02:45:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Shaved? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-23 02:42:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Come on, gibbous a break! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-23 02:40:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Because we know there isn't a second Sun in syzygy with Earth and the Moon. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-23 01:53:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> In the USA, only 2,860,505 with my last name. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-22 19:02:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [Taking advantage of other teams' conflicts.](https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=tYUjmEH9NNk) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-22 14:19:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Here's to the prosperity of everyone in this thread, winner or not. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-22 13:20:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Burned like the Rams' old artificial turf in St. Louis. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The increased use of security features on checks, like holograms and special ink that vanishes when you rub it, coincides with the increased use of mobile deposit, which makes those features useless, and also coincides with the decreased use of checks at all. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-22 03:05:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-21 23:18:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It shouldnt have been signed, Trump said in the White Houses East Room. It shouldnt have been negotiated the way that it was negotiated. And we are analyzing it very carefully, and we will have something to say about it in the not-too-distant future."

Sounds as if there's a good chance that the Trump administration will do with Iran what it has repeatedly done with situations that it is "analyzing carefully" and "will have something to say about in the not-too-distant future": a big fat nothing. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-21 21:54:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> At least we got to see that Leo D'Amato found a more profitable career than Balboa County sheriff's deputy and eventually San Diego police detective. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-21 18:43:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I hate the Cowboys, but today I vote out the Patriots. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-21 18:41:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Shutout indeed. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-21 18:40:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This will be known as the day the world declared in one voice: "We will not go quietly into the night!" We will not vanish without a fight! We're going to live on! We're going to survive! Today we celebrate our Independence Day! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-21 15:10:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> But that creature is only the beginning of the problem.  Just wait for Season 2. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-20 20:34:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [Relevant xkcd.](https://xkcd.com/435/) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-20 20:27:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's interesting to me that the simulated results are becoming increasingly asymmetrical over the course of the three simulations you've recently posted.  Is the starting position becoming less symmetrical, or is it just an effect of the collisions becoming more violent?  I wonder how much randomization the underlying simulation algorithms use, or if they're supposed to be totally deterministic and we're seeing the effects of chaos on rounding errors. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-20 19:29:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Orbison died before they made the video, in case anyone was wondering. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-20 18:41:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Any future value function will work; =FV(rate, number of periods, payment, present value) in Excel, or any [online future value calculator.](http://www.calculator.net/future-value-calculator.html) 

The formula for the future value based on the present value is (present value) x (1 + rate)^(number of periods).

The formula for the future value based on payments at the end of periods is 
(payment amount) x ((1 + rate)^(number of periods) - 1)/rate.

For the future value based both on present value and on payments at the end of periods, add those two formulas together.

The rate is **per period**.  For example, 6% annual interest compounded monthly is a rate of 6%/12 = 0.5%.

Here's an example: you owe $10,000 on your credit cards right now at 12% interest, compounded monthly.  You pay off $150 of the existing balance every month.  How much will you still owe after two years?

Rate is 12%/12 = 1%.  Number of periods is 2 (years) x 12 (months in a year) = 24.  Payment is -$150, because you are taking $150 out of your hands and putting it into your credit-card account.  Present value is $10,000, because you got $10,000 of value from your credit-card account.

Future value based on present value is ($10,000) x (1 + 1%)^24 = $10,000 x (1.01)^24 = $10,000 x 1.269735 = $12,697.35.

Future value based on payments is -$150 x ((1 + 1%)^24 - 1)/1% = -$150 x ((1.01)^24 - 1)/1% = -$150 x (1.269735 - 1)/1% = -$150 x (0.269735)/1% = -$150 x 26.9735 = -$4,046.03.

Adding them together, we get $12,697.35 - $4,046.03 = $8,651.32.  You made 24 payments of $150 each, which adds up to $3,600, but you only paid off about $1,350 of your $10,000 in credit card debt.  Maybe you should pay off your debt more quickly. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
