<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject983</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-05 21:16:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That's super convenient. Thanks for the images  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-05 20:16:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Does the website make it clear which stores charge a markup and which ones do not? I tried looking at the site but it won't let me see anything without creating an account  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-05 18:18:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If it's only $6 for fees + tip, how much is the markup on the regular goods? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-03 15:58:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I just upgraded from a GTX660 to a GTX1080. I don't know how I didn't do this sooner  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-30 02:11:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thank you very much. I don't know how I missed that  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> How to download Battle.Net desktop app? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-30 02:06:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I just purchased a new gaming PC, and I'm in the process of re-installing all my games. I'd like to install the battle.net desktop app to manage all of my Blizzard games (Overwatch, Diablo, Hearthstone) from, but when I do a google search for battle.net desktop app and click on the appropriate link, it just redirects me to my account homepage.  What steps do I need to take to get the battle.net desktop app back? 

Edit: This is the link I try to visit that redirects me to my account homepage: us.battle.net/en/app </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-25 23:35:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I built a comparable machine on PC part picker (same parts from description/images where possible, replaced the msi areo with another one of similar price as the aero wasn't on pc part picker, tried for generic parts for parts not identifiable) and it comes out way over what the microcenter build costs 

https://pcpartpicker.com/list/6qk7qk </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-25 21:22:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I agree the cases aren't the best looking, but if the price is right, its a compromise I'm willing to take.  I can always transplant it in 6-12 months to a new case as well </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-25 20:49:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> my current desktop has a 8350 bulldozer and a gtx 660, so there's nothing worth saving from it from it, besides maybe my gaming ssd.  I'd been living at home (just moved out) and sharing it with my dad, so he has a bunch of financial documents on it so I'm just gonna leave it with him.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-25 20:40:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I live very close to a micro center which is what is making this appealing.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-25 20:27:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If you click on the photo of the open side case, looks like evga b or bq power supplies, and it looks like some variant of the CM 212 for coolers  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What is r/buildapc's opinion of Microcenters Powerspec pre-built PC's? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-25 20:13:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm considering getting a new computer, and while browsing I came across Microcenter's powerspec PC line, and based on the parts used it seems like a great deal. 

The original one I was looking at was [this one](http://www.microcenter.com/product/473495/G419_Desktop_Computer), which is $1300 assembled, but when on PC part picker and attempting to build a similar machine I was getting $1450 minimum for the same parts, and often a bit higher.  (Don't have the PC part picker build, its on my home pc).

I also just saw [this machine](http://www.microcenter.com/product/475436/G350_Desktop_Computer) which also seems like a really good deal. 

Would looking at one of these machines be a good idea for my next buy? Looking to spend in the $1000-$1400 range. Machine will be used for gaming and programming. Will be looking for 1080p/1440p gaming.  I have a 1080p monitor I will use for a bit, it doesnt have freesync or gsync but it is serviceable for now, and I'll be looking to upgrade the monitor down the line.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-15 18:45:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I sent the form on Monday for overnight usps delivery by noon Tuesday, so they've had it for a bit. I would think I would have an account by now. Just frustrated my account got locked for no reason  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-15 17:00:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> No, because when I originally applied online I clicked set up payment later, but then when they rejected it online and they made me send it in by paper, they had a page on there with a few lines saying that I elected to set up payment later with nowhere to indicate setting up a direct deposit or for a check payment  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-15 06:18:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Does one in particular have an easier application process? Want to make sure I'm in by the deadline. Also, which one would be better for a 3 fund taxable brokerage?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Is there a way to get in contact with Vanguard via phone over the weekend? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-15 05:47:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I tried to apply for a vanguard IRA last weekend and they electronically denied me, requiring me to send in a paper form, which I sent Monday.  Today I tried to log into my account on personal.vanguard.com, as I needed to see if the account was created and it locked me out (first login attempt, use last pass so I know I had the correct password).  The problem is, is that in order to unlock it, after providing my basic info/ssn/etc, it is asking for an account number, which I have no way to access since I'm locked out of my account! Does anyone know if it's possible to get in touch with them over the weekend? I still need to put the money into my IRA account for 2016. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-26 03:42:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Kill me </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-20 03:13:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Oh nice, thanks. I tried googling to see if anyone had a similar situation as mine but came up with nothing  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-20 03:07:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> My first CLI with them 3 months ago wasn't a hard pull. They said they would ask for permission to do a hard pull when I did the CLI this time if it was not instantly approved, but instead for asking me for a hard pull it went straight to a rejection and sending a rejection letter, which I've only gotten when I was denied applying for credit before (I applied for mid tier cards for my first card not knowing you needed prior history) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-20 02:36:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I guess that would make sense. I remember reading on here somewhere that someone recommended doing one every month with discover it, which is why I did one after 3. I'll make sure to wait 6 in the future  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-20 02:22:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Card almost a year, 3 months since last CLI </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Discover It credit increase instantly rejected with no hard pull prompt </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-20 02:20:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I just requested a credit limit increase for my Discover It card which is currently at 4k, and it immediately sent me to a screen that said they cannot offer me a credit increase at this time and would send a letter in 3-5 days explaining why.  However, the prompt for a hard pull never appeared.  Did they do a hard pull behind the scenes? Or what else could have caused them to issue an immediate rejection? 100% ontime payment history, 10-20% utilization.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-14 20:54:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Will you be posting VODs? I'm planning on writing an open source indexer on the JVM (most likely scala) and I'd definitely be interested in seeing your approach </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-13 15:02:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> By data transfer are you referring to computation time on the index server (IE serialization/request wrapping), or total round trip time from sending the request to getting the response over the network?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-11 22:20:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Think I mis-read the conversation, was on mobile and might have jumped threads  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-11 18:41:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If renting would be $2000 for a place per month but buying is a $1500 per month for a mortgage, you would actually save $200 a month that could be invested compared to renting, assuming the same $300 per month in maintenance and other expenses.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Writing my own indexer - Relational Database vs NoSQL DB vs Search Engine </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-10 19:37:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm thinking of writing my own indexer as a side project, but I'm not sure what type of data store to pick to hold it.  

My goal is to write a high performance general indexer that could then be used by other projects to write the data to the index, then they would write their own tools to access the data. I'm also considering writing connector libraries to easily provide a structured way to access the data in a variety of languages. 

Since I have no experience with the GGG API or handling data streams/searches in the fashion required for a stash index, I figured I would ask what design considerations I should keep in mind, based on experiences that you guys have had. 

The biggest area's of contention for me is I'm not sure if elasticsearch's added benefits are necessary compared to a NoSQL solution for storing the JSON data, and I'm not sure if the ACID guarantees provided by a relational table are necessary, or if the eventual consistency for a NoSQL store or elasticsearch will be fast enough for a general purpose index, given that it seems each change id adds about 1000 items (I read that on this forum somewhere but don't have a link to the post).

My goal is to also make the indexer easily extensible so that others can easily change what's being indexed/stored, which may be a bit difficult with a relational table if they are adding/removing fields.


  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-04 17:32:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> F </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-26 23:54:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I can see that now. I'm up to level 37 on my ranger now, and I'm starting to get much better drops </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-26 19:29:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I've been picking up the majority of my blue drops to sell, that's probably why I'm wasting so much time going back </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-26 19:15:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> By newer item bases do you mean white items with better gem sockets than my current weapon? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-26 19:09:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thank's for clarifying, I thought unique would always be BIS </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-26 19:08:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thank you, I'm gonna go check them out.  I've been having a really hard time finding support gems.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-26 19:06:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thank you, this is exactly what I was looking for.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-26 19:02:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Main reason I'm concerned is I'm about to start cruel, and none of my gear has any good elemental resist.  I figured I would need mainly all yellow items in order to get the resistances, but I could be wrong.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-26 18:59:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I thought there was no ingame AH.  Do you mean poe trade? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Diablo 3 player trying out POE, have some questions </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-26 18:52:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I've played a decent amount of Diablo 3, but I'm looking to give POE a try.  I'm at level 30 on my first ranger and its going ok-ish, but I have a bunch of questions about the game that aren't really answered in any of the new player guides I've read.  A lot of my questions will compare against Diablo 3 for reference, not because I'm hating on POE, but because it's the only game of the genre that I've played before.

Questions:

What are the gear/level benchmarks for this game? I.E., I started a seasonal D3 character a couple days ago and by level 20, I had had four legendary drops and was full yellow geared.  In comparison, on my level 30 ranger, I currently only have five yellow items (jewelry and 2 armor pieces), rest blues, with no unique drops.  At what points in POE (on average) should I be fully blue geared, fully yellow geared, and when should unique items start dropping?  

Loot drop rates: In D3, whenever I kill a blue pack, yellow monster or a unique, I usually get a blue or yellow drop.  However, in my experience with POE so far, over half of the yellow, blue and uniques I've killed have dropped no loot or just whites.  Have I just been super unlucky, or is loot just harder to come by in POE?  At what rate should I expect to get gear upgrades (on average)?

At what rate should I be receiving skill gems, and how should I be getting them?  In D3, you just get skills/runes/passives per level.  In POE so far, the only gems I've gotten have been from quest rewards, which can lead to long wait times, or sometimes from monster drops.  However, the majority of the drops have been unusable by my build.  How often should I be getting new skill gems, and are there other ways of acquiring them that I'm missing out on?

Is there a way to auto-scale the difficulty on the zones?  In D3, I can take my time and do all the content in an act and it will automatically scale it to me.  In one of the POE guides I read, it said to avoid doing content in zones where your character was more than 3 levels over the zone level.  Since I'm new to POE, I'm spending time doing all the optional quests, as well as having to usually clear most of each zone since I don't know the routes through it, which usually leads to me being 4-5 levels above that of the zone.  If there is not a way to scale the content and this happens, what should my course of action be to get back to zones that are my level? 

Is there a way to expand my inventory? I find myself wanting to pick up a lot of loot to sell, since I'm new to the game and have no currency, but I can usually only pick up 10ish pieces before I have to teleport back. 

EDIT: Thanks for your help all, all of my questions have been answered.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-07 02:08:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> As a follow up question, what are peoples favorite linux distros? I'm currently running arch but its a bit much maintenace to get stuff working on a laptop that I mainly use for open source software development.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-04 19:16:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Awesome, thanks. Just started using react and I'm trying to figure out the best practices  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-03 01:09:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Is credit karma actually 100% free? No hidden fees or anything like that? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-02 21:06:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Why is function name inference considered bad? Every tutorial I've seen on stateless functional components uses the first way with arrow functions, so I'm curious why they prefer the second. 

// bad (relying on function name inference is discouraged)
const Listing = ({ hello }) = (
  div{hello}/div
);

// good
function Listing({ hello }) {
  return div{hello}/div;
} </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-29 08:37:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Check out guitar center/reverb/other sites that sell used gear, you can find great deals on less popular brands.  I got a Paolo Gregoletto Signature BC Rich warlock 5 with EMG pickups and a spalted maple top that retailed for $1300 new for $450 from guitar center with a hard shell case. 

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-14 22:39:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Bass fitness is amazing. I use it to pick out all my warmups/skill exercises  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-05 16:15:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> How do you handle backup instruments? Do you have two copies of the same bass or do you have one with a similar preamp/pickup situation? 

I'm usually hesitant to take just a single bass to a gig in case the instrument fails </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> How do bassists that use multiple different basses in a live show manage their rig? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-05 05:56:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> For those of you that have basses with radically different pickup/preamp selections, how do you manage your live tone? 

Right now I have a BC rich warlock, which has two EMG musicman pickups with no active tone shaping, just an active preamp (two volumes and a tone knob). My second bass is an Ibanez which has Bart MK1s and a full active preamp with tone shaping. Both basses have different output levels so it makes trying to set up my signal chain to get a decent sound out of both of them difficult. A situation that another player might have is that they have an active bass and a passive bass and are trying to get good sounds out of both of them. 

How do you guys handle a situation like this? Some sort of level balancing pedal, multiple preamps with multiple feeds to FOH, single preamp and settle with a just OK sound? I'm looking for ideas on approaching this in a way that is friendly to the sound guy.  

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-31 18:36:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Name a windows laptop with a trackpad even remotely comparable to Apples.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-23 01:04:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Just took multiple photos  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [IL] Dented passenger door </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-23 00:57:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hi all, currently sitting in my parents car in a parking lot while my mom ran into a store to buy a gift card for Christmas. A car pulled up in the spot next to my passenger door and the driver threw open his door, swinging into my closed passenger door and making a loud thud. He made no attempts to signal me or apologize in any way and walked into another store, and when I got out of the car to inspect it my parents car now has a dent in the side of the car. 

I am currently still in the parking lot next to the car. Should I call the police? Wait until the gentleman comes back and ask him for his insurance information? Is there something I should do now to ensure possible legal recourse? I'm not sure what I should do in this situation. Thanks  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-06 01:17:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Is the server lightweight enough that you can run one on a laptop? I'm thinking of getting this game, and since I ride two+ hours on a train per day as part of my commute I'd love to be able to set up a local dev environment to run on while I'm on the train and then be able to push my changes to the main server when I have an internet connection.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-05 01:04:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> AI basically just swarms you on higher difficulties. It can be useful for learning the game, but the real meat and potatoes of the game is multiplayer.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-04 22:19:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Really great game, but extremely hard to learn.  I wouldn't call it a learning curve as much as I'd call it a learning cliff, where the games places you at the bottom of a cliff and you have no equipment, yet are expected to scale it.  However, once you get the hang of the game, it has some of the most extremely rewarding and fun gameplay of any strategy game I've ever played.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-28 20:25:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Start grinding dark zone levels before 30.  Waiting until 30 to start has made it a pretty painful grind </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-24 23:28:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Check your memory usage while in game. I have 8gb ram right now, and since 1.5 dropped I'm usually 100% capped on memory, and the performance hits come once the game has to start using paged memory  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-23 20:13:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm having issues with memory leaks as well.  I have 8gb RAM on my windows 7 system (I'm getting more over black friday, dont worry).  My strategy for playing the division is close out of everything except uplay and the game.  In 1.4 my memory usage would hover around 80-90%, rarely any paging.  With 1.5 my memory usage is constantly 100%, and massive page swaps are occurring every 30-60 seconds.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-17 16:28:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Does anyone have a good resource for analyzing the DPS of weapon drops?

I've been selling all of my SMG and most of my AR drops since none of the listed DPS comes close to the 135k dps of my G36 or the 160k of my hungry hog (because most SMG drops I've been getting are around 100k dps and other AR's in the 110-120k range), but I read on here recently that the sheet dps is meaningless. Is there a guide somewhere that outlines what a good vs great roll for a weapon would look like? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-12 18:36:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Awesome, thanks! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> A couple of questions from a fresh 30 </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-12 18:14:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hi guys, just hit level 30 and have a couple of questions. I read the fresh 30 1.4 guide but these weren't covered. It basically boils down to being unsure about the credits/crafting endgame. 

Firstly, should I be disassembling or selling unwanted weapons? The guide didn't say if buying gear with weapons or if crafting was better. 

Secondly, should I spend credits on gear at all pre-229, or should I just stockpile them for once I hit 229? 

Lastly, what should I spend Phoenix credits on? Not sure what the most optimal buys are.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Logged out of uplay for inactivity while in the middle of playing the division </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-12 04:20:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I was just in the middle of running a mission and I got kicked from the game due to a uplay not running in the background error. The game automatically exited and when I restarted uplay, it told me I had been logged out for inactivity. Has anyone else encountered this, and is there any solution? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-11 19:33:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thanks for the app recommendation  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-11 19:33:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thanks for all the resources! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-11 04:16:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> By Persian do you mean Farsi? If so how are you learning it?  My girlfriend is Persian and speaks fluent Farsi, and I really want to learn some to surprise her, but only knowing English I have no idea where to start.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-12 20:40:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If I can just get the wifi card for $10, I'd rather just grab it rather then risking flashing my bios.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-11 23:48:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thanks, exactly what I was looking for </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Where can I buy white-listed X220 wifi cards? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-11 22:51:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Does anyone know where I can buy a Intel NIC that is whitelisted by the X220 BIOS? 

I was looking at http://www.ebay.com/itm/Thinkpad-T430S-X230-X120E-T530-60Y3253-Intel-Centrino-Advanced-N-6205-wifi-card-/281146143478, but I'm not sure if there's anyway to verify that it'll work since all my google searches about the X220 whitelist have yielded answers on how to mod the BIOS. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-24 16:24:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I ended up switching to xubuntu and doing 150% scaling through virtual box, and it's been working great. Last time I tried xubuntu I tried to do it through the OS and it was a total mess  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-17 04:46:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I think a corrupt virtual box could have been my problem, I just restarted my computer after installing windows updates and virtual box now just crashes instantly when I launch. I'm definitely gonna try migrating to VM ware </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-17 02:39:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Awesome, thanks  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-17 00:55:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What exactly is a tiled window manager? I've never heard of it.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-17 00:50:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'll give that a shot, definitely might help </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-17 00:32:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yup, virtual box  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-17 00:29:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Graphically heavy, I've been getting a lot of lag on cinnamon with the vm. When I tried xfce the scaling didn't work that well (this was over 6 months ago for xubuntu so maybe it's better now). I've also been experiencing a lot of random VM crashes with mint. (One maybe every 10 hours of VM use) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-16 17:00:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I've been able to get Mint setup and it seems to be running nicely, although it is a bit heavy resource wise. Would doing something like Stock Debian and then installing my own packages for the VM sound like a good idea?

And if so, what does anyone have recommendations on lightweight desktop environments to use, that are still usable on the surfaces's screen? I had tried xubuntu in the past which worked great, but the screen didn't scale well with the surface and everything was tiny.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-16 16:57:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Sorry, I meant if I myself was capable of using VIM.  I've never been able to get my head around it.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-16 00:18:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If I could actually use vim that seems like it would be an amazing tool  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Distro for Surface Pro 3 VM </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-15 22:10:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What distros have people had the most success with for VM's on the SP3? I tried using Ubuntu but was getting logs of display lag.  I'd prefer to stay within the Debian sphere if possible.  The main purpose of the VM is for software development.  I can't go full linux on my machine since I need windows for Visual Studio  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Language for Node JS code generator </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-15 04:56:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I have a really cool idea for a code generation tool for node. By code generation tool, I mean that I can create something like an XML or JSON file and the script will generate source code files based on the contents.  However, I'm not sure what the best way to approach generating the code is. Should I do it in javascript using something like a yeoman generator? Or would using a language with strong file and string manipulation libraries be my best bet?  I've never really done something like this before so I'm not sure what the best approach is </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-13 19:52:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I think the idea is great, but I've never seen a software home button that looks perfect when it's a circle. It's always a bit pixelated around the edges and it's never a clean circle  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-13 18:49:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Would it still be a physical entity for the home button or a software simulation? I've found simulation buttons can be pretty horrid </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-13 14:44:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What would the benefit be of removing the home button?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-05 01:49:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What about a sticky grenade option? This would be useful for removing jammers/batteries on external walls in favela that are above ground level that otherwise have no ledge or anything to throw the grenade into  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-05 01:41:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yup, NA PC here </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-02 17:30:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Even if I'm only 23, would you still recommend going bond for the Roth? Since I'm so young I thought stocks would be better. I'll definitely consider diversifying it with international stocks though  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-02 16:27:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Ok thanks. I'm definitely over the limit for traditional IRA's but I'll still be able to contribute to roths. My 401k through my work has a .27 expense ratio on their s p 500 like account (their lowest expense ratio, it's through T Rowe Price), so my best bet would probably be to contribute to the match max for my work then put the rest into a Roth IRA via something like vanguard, right?   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-02 00:41:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Wait the IRA deductions are the same as Roth IRA contribution maxes? As in my salary (which puts me in the zero deduction IRA bracket) means I can make zero Roth IRA contributions? Is there any point to even investing in anything but my 401k then?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-01 01:04:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So if I make over $70,000 as a recent college grad and expect my salary to go up from here (software development), would a traditional IRA be best? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-23 02:23:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I like using one when playing fingerstyle hard rock/metal live. It makes it so I can have some fun on stage w/o having to devout 100% of my attention to having perfect dynamics.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [PC] has anyone else been having matchmaking issues? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-14 16:17:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I've been having an issue where in every other game that I queue up for, it will find me teammates and a team to play, but once we're on the screen with both teams and all the players displayed it will just sit there and try to create the game but it will never get created, and eventually people start leaving, and the spots never refill, so the only way to fix it is to leave. Is this happening to anyone else? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-09 14:37:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> r/hailcorporate </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-06 19:25:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> r/hailcorporate </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [mySQL] Problem with logs </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-22 15:53:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm not sure if this is the right place to post this, but I'm having some trouble reading mySQL logs.  

The project I'm working on is using the Liferay Java web framework, and it auto generates some SQL queries.  We've been running into issues where in a couple cases its generating queries that are extremely large and slow, so I'm trying to debug them.  However, when I look in the SQL logs, I see stuff like this:

 "SELECT JournalArticle.id_ as id1_414_0_, JournalArticle.uuid_ as uuid2_414_0_, JournalArticle.resourcePrimKey as resource3_414_0_, JournalArticle.groupId as groupId414_0_, JournalArticle.companyId as companyId414_0_, JournalArticle.userId as userId414_0_,  [truncated, 1.6 KB total]"


The logs seem to be auto-truncating the query being logged, and its making it impossible to debug this issue.  Does anyone know how to make it so that SQL will log the whole query no matter what? I've tried looking through the log settings in mySqlWorkbench but I can't seem to find any setting relating to this issue. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-19 15:27:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Look into getting the book bass fitness. It starts off pretty simple but after that it has a bunch of fun exercises. I think it's less then $10 on Amazon and I think there's a free pdf version floating around out there too. I started out with the pdf but ended up buying the book since I was using it so much  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-13 05:56:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Sorry if my post wasn't clear, I'm looking for video lets play series to watch on my way to work, not just factions to play  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Does anyone know any good non-beginner lets plays? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-13 05:35:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I've been looking for some good lets plays to watch on the train on my way to work.  However, it seems like a lot of them are aimed at newer players. I don't need to hear an explanation of what the council members do every time, I'm mainly looking for fast paced ones that are focused on the gameplay itself and not explaining game mechanics. Does anyone have any suggestions? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-01 00:15:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That makes a lot of sense - I work for a consulting firm so our process is we have our project manager (all of our project managers come from coding backgrounds) sit down with the client and they translate the business requirements into technical requirements and from there into jira stories which are then assigned to the developers  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-30 21:20:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Since I'm guessing that the MMR is based on a mathematical formula, they could have worked out test cases by hand for the expected result and then run the functions with those data points and compared the real result vs the expected result. 

I guess what's baffling me about this is that my small software team of 3 developers/3 person QA team has more exhaustive testing than a multi million dollar company  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-30 21:18:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I know it deflates your losses as well, but consider my situation. My one KOTH loss is balanced out by one of the KOTH wins, so I basically won for KOTH and lost 4 payload. Therefore I saw an extremely low benefit from 4 four wins but large MMR hits from my four payload losses. I'm by no means claiming I should be mid to high 50's, with a 6/4 record averaging 2-3 golds a game I thought I would have ended up right around 50  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-30 20:45:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> How so? As in a large percentage of people are developers themselves and have opinions on topics/issues? Or they know nothing about software but feel like they have to defend their favorite developers?

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-30 19:02:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's absolutely on the developers as well.  I'm assuming that they have functions that calculate the MMR gain or loss based on whether it is a win or loss, as well as the other factors, so unit tests could have easily been written for those to verify that the MMR functions were working correctly. If they run the unit tests before building to production and they fail, then they would know something was up  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> How do you use you use stat tracking sites to get better? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-30 18:08:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I've never really used stat tracking for any of the games I've played before so I'm not entirely sure what I should be looking for and how to use the stats to get better. Also, it seems like there are at least 3-4 stat popular stat tracking sites out there, how do you pick which one to use? 

For my situation, In case it matters for which stats to track/site to use, I'm currently ranked in the low 40s (Won 5 placements on KOTH, lost 4 on payload and one KOTH), I estimate my skill w/o the KOTH bug would be 45-50ish, which is where I'll most likely stick around for awhile.  I usually play an hour a day after work + some more time on weekends so I'm not trying to get hyper competitive, just better at the game, so it'd be cool if the discussion could talk about how all players could use stats to get better, not just those looking to be in the top 1-5% of players. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-30 17:17:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I went 5-5 and got rank 45. All wins KOTH all losses payload except one KOTH. Top kek  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-30 17:00:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> There's a difference between ironing out kinks and a failure of software development and testing. As a software developer myself, if they had an even halfway decent regression test script or automated tests in place this KOTH bug would never have existed. The fact that a game mode only gives you 20% of the amount it should WHEN THE WHOLE PATCH WAS ABOUT COMPETITIVE MODE speaks volumes to the incompetence of their QA team. On the software project I'm on right now (3 developers, 3 man QA team) we are moving into testing right now for a product for one of our clients. We're running a full regression test 2x weekly on top of our unit tests, plus spending any time not spent fixing bugs trying to break the product. Any halfway competent QA team could have caught this MMR bug for KOTH </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-30 16:39:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yupppppppp. Went 5-5, all five wins KOTH all losses payload except for one KOTH. Ended up at 45. Lose two more payload maps after and I've dropped to 41 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-30 16:38:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Went 5-5 got placed at 45. That seems like a huge jump for a one win difference. All my wins were on KOTH though with one loss on KOTH and the rest of the losses on payload so I bet that had something to do with it  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-30 16:07:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> How is this affected when you switch heros multiple times per match? 

IE if I switch to Winston for the last 30 seconds defending the payload to surprise their backline, how is my 30 seconds of gameplay being compared to people who played winston the whole game? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-30 13:18:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I thought the performance gain was relative to other players though, and if you're performance was lower then other players you lose more if you lose or win less and you win. IE say we were defending and I switched to Winston in the last 30 seconds to hold the point better, blizzard might be looking at those Winston stats compared to others on the map who've played Winston the whole game, so it would think my performance was really shitty compared to them  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-30 06:22:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I think the ranking system is horseshit. Here's a summery of what I've experienced so far: 6-4, got rank 45. Total BS. Reason for my anger? 10 matches: five all solo queuers (5-0). My team all solo other team 2 premade of two two solo (0-2). My team one group of two rest solo enemy team two groups of two two solo (0-1). My team all solo enemy team four man and two man premade (0-1). My team all solo enemy team 4 man premade 2 solo (0-1). 

How the hell is it fair that 4/10 placement matches were vs premades with my team all solo and one mismatched premade size? 

To make things worse, 6/10 placement matches I played were KOTH, which apparently is bugged in MMR. So of the games I won/lost, all five I won were KOTH, one I lost was KOTH, the other four I lost were payload, which probably lowered my MMR even more. 

I've played three games since then, lost all three. All payload. First I had 4 golds, (all but heals, 3 announcered quadras), two I had one (obj time, tank). Last game I lost I had four gold medals (all but heals). In those three games I dropped from 45-41. 

Another thing that might be keeping my MMR low is that I like to switch characters a lot to counter pick. I know blizzard said your performance is factored into your rank, and if they're doing it based on the whole match per character it could be affecting my ranking, so if I want to rank up I guess I'll have to pick a char per match and stick with it.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-30 05:14:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> 6-4, got rank 45. Total BS. Reason for my anger? 10 matches: five all solo queuers (5-0). My team all solo other team 2 premade of two two solo (0-2). My team one group of two rest solo enemy team two groups of two two solo (0-1). My team all solo enemy team four man and two man premade (0-1). My team all solo enemy team 4 man premade 2 solo (0-1). 

How the hell is it fair that 4/10 placement matches were vs premades with my team all solo and one mismatched premade size?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-30 03:15:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> My first 6 games were flip flops between me getting stomped and us stomping them. One of the games it was my team of all solo Q's vs a team with a 4 man party and a 2 man party where we got utter wrecked. All the groups on the other team were level 30-40 bronze star and my team was mostly 50-65 no bronze stars. I'm not even sure why that game was allowed to happen  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-30 02:45:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Tbh, I don't think that's a fair comparison since in the basketball league you'll keep playing with the same people while in overwatch, most likely you won't match with the same people  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-29 21:41:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Ah that makes sense about voice comms. My mic is currently broken so I was thinking about text only. For voice, yeah I definitely agree  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
