<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject2372</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Back up generator? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-25 14:56:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I live in the UK and I'm moving onto a canal boat in the next few months. I'm in the process of designing an off grid solar system for it at the moment. I've noticed that a lot of inverters have an auto start system for back up generators when the battery levels get too low. 

As the weather in the UK doesn't tend to be too great in the winter I'm probably going to need a back up generator sometimes but I'm having trouble finding a small generator which would be compatible with this auto-start feature. I'm only ever going to need between 1-2kw but all the generators I can find in this range are recoil start. Can anyone recommend a back up generator with auto start functionality in this power range? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-20 18:43:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> what kind of format do you expect for hard copies? Individual portfolio pages or a bound document? What sort of size? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-20 17:40:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> of the people in the year above me at my school that graduated last July (over 100) only a handful have managed to find placements. Also the job sites pretty consistently have at least twice as many part 2 vacancies whenever I look at them, regardless of the time of year. 

Obviously I would prefer to work in an architecture practice, I'm just trying to be realistic and prepare for the worst eventuality so that I can move onto my part 2 as quickly as possible.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-20 17:17:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> according to the website: " 'Qualified professional' will be an architect registered in the territory where the experience is being undertaken, or a chartered or similarly qualified member of an appropriate professional body" 12 months do have to be under the supervision of an architect but you can also do 12 months under another qualified professional in the construction industry if it proves difficult finding a placement with an architect. Thinking about it more now labouring wouldnt count as there wouldn't be a chartered professional that could supervise you but other suggestions in this thread could work. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-20 16:53:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I want to switch schools for my part 2 for several reasons. All the schools I want to switch to are pretty insistent about part 1 experience. I'm just trying to be realistic and look for a backup plan because the part 1 vacancies are consistently sparse. There's usually plenty of people looking for part 2's but the part 1 vacancies are much harder to come by. My dad is a retired civil engineer though so maybe some of his old contacts might be able to help find something more fitting than general labouring. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> UK Architects - Does anyone know if working on a building site as a labourer can count towards PEDR? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-20 16:32:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm about to finish my part 1 and thinking of this as a possible backup while I'm looking for a part 1 placement. The PEDR website states "experience within the construction industry under the supervision of a qualified professional within the relevant field". Would working as a labourer count under this definition? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Matt Hoss v. h3h3 lawsuit: Summary Judgment Day </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-28 10:27:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> A Warning To Trump Fans After Media Ban </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-25 16:27:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The Truth Behind Trump's Sweden Terror Claim </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-20 17:51:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Tiny Trump Had an Accident </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-19 21:07:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> "You are an ill-made, spiteful little creature full of envy, lust, and low cunning." </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-19 20:31:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> 'The Trump Administration Are Not At War With The Media But The Truth' </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-19 12:55:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
