<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject404</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-10 05:43:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That pink center!  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [Homemade] Chunky Mango-Corn salsa </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-10 05:09:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-09 19:06:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Do we have the same grandma?? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> TIFU by buying things from the dollar store to save money and not washing my hands after cutting up jalapeos. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-26 23:27:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-26 04:43:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'd give him the window seat! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-26 04:40:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Call who? Is there just one company to rule them all? If I choose a utility I.e. Water I don't think WE energies can set me up with that. I was more or less curious about what utilities I'd be looking at setting up, just trying to make a list of everything I have to set up before the big move day!  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-26 04:37:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's a multi family home and utilities are not included. There are existing tenants on the other floor so I'm also a little confused on how the utilities would be separated? That's something I'm sure I can ask the utilities company but just expressing a concern  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-26 04:34:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Very helpful thank you! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> New to utilities, halp! </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-26 04:20:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If there's already a thread for this I'd love to be pointed in the right direction but as for now these are my questions!
What utilities do I need and what do I do?
Vague I know but this is the first time I'm renting a place that doesn't have them included so I never had to set up accounts for electricity/gas/internet, I asked my new landlord but I didn't want to seem unprofessional or give any negative impressions as a tenant. she told me pretty much how to set up electric but i feel like there's more to it, maybe I'm just over thinking it. Any advice in general for someone who is renting or moving to another state (moving from NY to WI) would be abundantly appreciated! 
Thank you!  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-21 15:54:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> "Say your prayers" </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-04 02:31:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [](https://i.imgur.com/K8kLN2m.jpg) 
There's a color difference and no tampering on the return compared to the one that comes with the system </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-04 02:29:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [](https://i.imgur.com/K8kLN2m.jpg) 
[](https://i.imgur.com/GBGaszU.jpg) 

No sign of tampering and also different colors  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-04 02:27:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Wanted to add that the ones that don't come with the console are slightly see through I compared the 2 there's also no signs of tampering 

[comparison ](https://i.imgur.com/K8kLN2m.jpg) 

[no signs ](https://i.imgur.com/GBGaszU.jpg)  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
