<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject3042</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-10 16:30:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> huh, what? how? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-10 16:02:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> OP, have you even seen his movies before Prisoners or are you just listing the ones where you don't have to read subtitles?

But my favorite part is when you list a movie that hasn't even opened yet and a movie that isn't even filmed yet to support your argument that he is improving. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-10 15:28:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> But was it intentional or were the writer and director subconsciously struggling with their own sexuality? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-10 15:28:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> what is this from? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Is there any reason besides budget why European movies tend to favor longer takes, steady shots and wide angles, whereas Hollywood movies tend to have more cuts, more camera movement and more closeups? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-10 10:44:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I realize European movies have smaller budgets and more shots mean more setups, which translates to more expensive filming, but is that the only reason for this trend? I think European movies are often generalized as being slow-paced (boring?) art house because of the way they are shot. Is this a deliberate style that happens to also save money or is it more along the lines of working with what you got? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-10 10:25:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I like how the title of his movie is All Eyez on Me and that mummy has a weird double eye. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-10 09:44:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> what is confusing about it? seems pretty straightforward to me </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-10 08:40:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Why do these "Scorsese says cinema is dead" articles crop up every month? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-09 13:04:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Considering the current trend I would say the probability is higher than in the last 5 years. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-09 11:38:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Definitely seeing it as a kid made all the difference. I'm sure I'd feel the same way about it as you if I watched it for the first time today. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-09 09:57:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> definitely /s </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-09 09:14:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Halloween and Halloween 2 scared the living shit out of me as a kid and that feeling continues to this day. There's something about that creepy mask, those hollow eyes and the fact that Michael is relentless and unstoppable that I find terrifying. The way he slowly moves. He doesn't have to run after his victim, he'll get them eventually because there's no escaping him. Just the idea of seeing his silhouette at the end of the street is something that bugs me. Any other killer, you could just run away. But him? Nope. He's going to get you no matter what. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-09 08:47:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  cheaper actors kinda movie...

I was not aware that Ron Perlman is a big-name expensive actor (or anyone else in the Hellboy cast, for that matter) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-09 08:45:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> TIL Guillermo Del Toro is the only person in Hollywood who does practical effects </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-07 12:28:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I remember when 1970 was just 30 years ago. Damn.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-07 12:26:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [this one](https://www.reddit.com/r/movies/comments/69by9z/official_discussion_guardians_of_the_galaxy_vol_2/dh7yloe/) though it's got some upvotes now </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-07 00:01:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I did actually agree with most of your opinions and yeah, the downvoting is really annoying. This is supposed to be a discussion so I don't see how clicking a downward pointing arrow when you disagree with someone's opinion helps to facilitate that discussion. My slightly negative comment about the movie is currently being downvoted by fanboys, too. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-06 23:49:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  he should have actually made some of the "weird" shit he alluded to

he made Pac Man </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-06 23:46:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  Finally, Rocket knew he gave Yondu a spare suit (and I think a thruster?). He should have known to look for Yondu and Peter right after the crew escaped the planet. Instead, his one line after stunning Gamora made it seem as if he knew there was no chance for Peter to be alive.

Yeah that was really weird. Almost as if those two scenes weren't meant to follow each other. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-06 23:43:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Despite the first movies great effort to bring the Guardians together and establish them as a team, in the sequel James Gunn decided to undue that by making everyone even more quarrelsome and splitting them into two plot lines. And ignoring the first films effectively simplistic story revolving around a central common goal and a MacGuffin, Vol. 2 seems to meander rather aimlessly in the first two acts and its not easy to summarize what the film was actually about. Not that multiple plot lines or a less streamlined structure are bad things, but neither seems quite appropriate for this type of movie nor is it executed in the best possible way. But its stilla very entertaining film with many jokes (some forced, some genuinely funny), great visuals and even some depth (there is quite a lot of emotion and groundwork for characterization, though its often hard to take it seriously given the nature of the movie). Dave Bautista steals the show as Drax and Rooker stands out as the actor most capable of pulling off drama. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-05 09:00:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  you're not going to be happy about The Q and the Grey...

Watched it yesterday. Oh boy. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-04 16:51:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> this subreddit needs more Panis jokes </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-04 16:26:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> /r/woahdude </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-04 08:50:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I bet shazam could </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-04 08:49:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> me too </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Yokohama Landmark Tower turns evil at dusk </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-03 19:25:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> I created an instagram account for my collection of beer coaster (I have around 300 of them) and I'm updating it regularly with new pics </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-03 18:38:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-03 16:43:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  They border on absurd

in a good way or a bad way? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-03 16:41:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Branagh's mustache is a bit too much </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-03 16:37:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Child protagonist discovering a new magical world? Beams of light in the sky? Global destruction? This is such a tired formula. Pass. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-03 16:34:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [can confirm, he is all over the place](http://imgur.com/a/Mz2yO) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-03 16:30:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> so how did you like Miyajima? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-03 16:27:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> every elevator in Japan that I have been to has this </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-03 15:54:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> "It took me four years to paint like Raphael, but a lifetime to paint like a child." - Pablo Picasso

I guess the dude just got worse at drawing. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-03 13:45:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> damn that hairline never moved

good genes </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-03 13:43:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I had no idea Clint Eastwood was this good </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-03 11:07:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  Spontaneous Human Combustion

Did you know that Spontaneous Human Combustion is just a time traveller who burns up on re-entry to his time period? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-03 09:34:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Child protagonist discovering a new magical world? Beams of light in the sky? Global destruction? This is such a tired formula. Pass. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-03 09:00:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Shooting has been seen as a male sport, as it is an extension of hunting and to some extent warfare (to put it simply, historically women did not shoot) so it started out as a sport with only a men category. When women were allowed to compete, they did not merge the categories and kept them separate. This way at least more people can compete. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-03 08:52:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Why? I found myself really enjoying it even the third time around.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-02 15:40:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  stop shitposting

tell that to the BBC </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-02 15:14:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Out of those you mentioned, I only really find Lessons from the Screenplay to be genuinely insightful for me, because I don't read scripts and they often show and talk about the stage directions and other things I don't get to see in the movie from just the dialogues. Nerdwriter is utterly hit and miss and his tendency to stretch a single point, which could me summarized in a sentence, to a five minute video is maddening. I also find many of his points either very far fetched (or at least not entirely supported by the examples he gives) or very obvious. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-02 15:10:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Totally gonna do that. It's been on my list for years. Good think I waited so long, now there's a 4K version to enjoy. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-02 15:06:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Not that I was looking for an action packed movie, I was just curious how misleading the trailer is in that regard. Your answer is pretty much what I expected, so thanks for confirming that.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-02 14:59:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I wouldn't know, I never played video games. 

But the thing about movies is that just when you think you saw every good American movie, you discover European cinema and then Asian cinema and you end up with hundreds and hundreds of movies you simply need to see. Like, even if you only watched the top 10 movies from every European country, that's more than 400 movies. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-02 14:39:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  Unsubscribe to Now you see it.

Any particular reason for this subtle hate? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-02 14:36:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Too bad the trailer was only 1080

I have not seen this movie yet. Is it as action packed as this trailer suggests? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-02 14:16:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Unless you want to actually study cinema (in film school or by reading books on your own) a good way to get started is to watch movies with audio commentary from the director/writer and to watch making of documentaries. This way, you can get at least a general idea about the choices made during filming and the techniques used to achieve certain things. 

What I like to do is to pause a movie at some point (usually when there is a particularly beautiful or intriguing shot or a practical effect) and just think about all the things that had to happen and that had to be done to get what I'm seeing on screen. Like, pause Star Wars on a shot of R2D2 on Tatooine and think about what you see on screen and how it got there. The process of designing and creating the R2 prop, the actor inside, all the wires and stuff that's outside the frame, the whole huge production in a desert in Tunisia, the sound effects added in post that had to be created, how those were done, etc.

As for analyzing story, it's always good to also read a lot of books to really be aware of various storytelling techniques, tropes, etc. Also, as you watch a movie, start by analyzing it in a basic way. You don't have to find a huge hidden meaning on your first try. Start by dividing the movie into acts and look at how information is communicated to the audience, how the plot progresses, when there is rising action, what leads to a climax, etc. Try to think why a certain scene is in a movie and how it contributes to the story and what would happen if that scene was cut out of the movie. Would anything change? Would you have less information? Would characters have less information? 

I suppose the important thing is to have fun. I mostly analyze movies for myself. I'm not about try and compete with Lessons From The Screenplay or Every Frame A Painting (I don't even have video editing skills or a powerful enough computer to make a video essay like those guys) but there are always things I pick up on my own and things I discover in movies that make me appreciate the craft and understand the choices. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-02 13:57:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Not to belittle your progress, but 250-300 only sounds like a lot. I've already seen 70 movies this year and I wasn't even trying very hard. You still have a long road ahead of you if you genuinely want to see "a great deal of movies," 
especially considering how many movies get made a year (around 600 in America, though, granted, a lot of those are probably garbage). </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-02 13:50:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> How is this a bombshell? As long as he gives a good performance, I don't care if he memorized the lines or not. If anything, this would make acting more difficult, as it implies a total lack of preparation, so to still be able to give a good performance would be pretty impressive. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-02 13:44:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Take small sausages, turn them into one huge sausage and then cut up that huge sausage into smaller pieces. Yeah, that makes sense. Definitely better than just keeping the smaller sausages. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-02 13:07:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> There were two reasons to rob graves and both of them don't apply anymore.

**1. Stealing bodies for research:** 
People would steal fresh bodies after the funeral and sell them to doctors for their research  or for teaching. And I don't mean Frankenstein-type weirdos, I mean respectable doctors and teaching hospitals that simply lacked cadavers to use in anatomy class. Nowadays this is no longer a problem since a) we need less cadavers to study because we already know the human body, and b) donating bodies for scientific purposes is a thing now.

**2. Stealing valuables from graves:** 
People used to get buried with all sorts of valuables like jewelry. This is no longer a common practice and even it it were, people in general are way more rich than they used to be, so it's easier to rob a random person in the street than to dig up a body hoping to find something which might not even be there.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-02 11:36:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  If you bomb a factory it might take a few months to rebuild the buildings but most of the machinery and tooling would survive.

I find this very hard to believe. Do you have a source for claiming that machinery within bombed factories was intact?

 So the destruction done to the industry were only temporary and could be fixed. 

Most of that fixing requires enormous resources, though (manpower, machines, material) which must have all been in very short supply. So any sort of rebuilding was strongly dependent on (and thus influenced by) support from the winning countries.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-02 11:17:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  You're being paid 30+ millions of dollars through this contract

At this point I think he would do it for free if that would mean he could sit in a competitive car </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Quick question before I watch the Elements miniseries </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-02 10:55:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Which previous episodes should I brush up on before I get into the Elements miniseries? The thing is I don't really remember much about the elementals so I would like to be caught up with the mythology to fully enjoy and understand the miniseries.

Thanks! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-01 17:34:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The creator of the show doesn't neccesarily have to be involved in it later on. For example, JJ Abrams was the creator of Alias, Lost and Fringe but he did not run the shows, contributed only a couple scripts mostly in the earlier seasons and had zero involvement in them by the time the shows ended. I remember people citing or questioning Abrams about the sixth season of Lost when the last episode he had a writing credit on was in the beginning of the third season. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-01 17:30:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I would say that a director's celebrity is the result of this, not one of the causes. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-30 00:24:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Except this is a text-based discussion forum and not a TV channel </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-30 00:03:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>   more posts like these should be discussed on this subreddit

The problem is that unless you make a video, no one here is going to take the time to read and appreciate a lengthy post with arguments and thought put into it. You're likely to get downvoted or simply ignored just because of the length of the text as users will ignore the time, effort and thought put into such posts. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-29 14:19:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The original Trek series is basically about a submarine in space </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-28 18:22:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Apparently the city was a last minute addition in the script and so they didn't have time to prepare any set, model or matte painting. Still very lame, though.

Ugh don't tell me Q will return </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-28 18:17:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Threshold was Shakespeare compared to The Thaw or False Profits (which I watched yesterday). Preserve that for future generations. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-28 12:52:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Bottom right with Nezer written over it?

That one isn't from any country. Not sure where they got it, maybe it was in a magazine. Nezer means don't eat too much, and they're constantly on some diet, so that's why they have it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-28 12:47:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You got me there. You're absolutely right.

As for Q, well, I just don't trust him. He strikes me as that magic monkey paw that grants a wish but there's always an ironic catch. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-28 10:02:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> For me, this subreddit is movienews </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-28 09:47:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> To be fair, Kes' pleading is what made up her mind and I would never trust Q to do what he promises. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-27 17:30:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Unfortunately, no. I wish I did but it only occurred to me afterwards. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-27 16:56:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Where do you think the huge bull head is from? :) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-27 16:52:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Honestly </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-27 16:03:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Some of those are pretty old and not all of them are from their own travels (friends and relatives give them magnets as gifts from vacations) so I don't know about Turkey. But I guess if you go to a vacation spot on the coast, that's still pretty safe. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-27 15:53:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I am sure that burning that black tape must be very healthy </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-27 15:36:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Slovakia
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> My parents have an impressive collections of souvenir fridge magnets </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-27 13:27:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-27 11:59:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Brad Dourif is an amazing actor. His breakout in One Flew Over the Cuckoo's Nest is astounding and really owns any role he does. Grima in Two Towers is probably his biggest gig but he was super creepy in The X-Files, that is my favorite performance of his. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-27 09:33:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> oh no, he can't afford the health care bills! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-27 09:02:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> In such debates, I will take the "yeah, she kind of is, but whatever" side! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-27 08:47:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The Jump Street movies, John Wick, Deadpool, Logan... all great movies. I'm not saying the rating is what made them better, but I will say that sanitizing them to PG13 would have made them worse. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-26 22:55:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I am sure they have plenty of blueprints and 3D models stored somewhere. It's not like they recreated that set from screengrabs from a Prometheus dvd. 

Sets are torn down for two reasons. One, they take up a lot of space. Two, they aren't really built to last. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-26 22:15:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> There have been a couple of bad episodes but overall I am having a blast. Go for it! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-26 21:48:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So most people don't enjoy it? I'm really curious about opinions on that episode. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-26 21:47:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I am now at a point where I feel nothing but indifference toward her.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-26 21:46:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Oddly enough, The Right Stuff is a very widely unknown and underappreciated movie despite a great cast, story, effects, and direction. 
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-26 20:47:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I know better than to click on any links people give me when I mention arachnophobia. I can see in the bottom bar of the browser what you are actually linking to and all I can say is that I do not wish you a pleasant day and I hope you are proud of yourself. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-26 20:01:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> IIRC Hopkins said he was inspired by spiders when he approached the role. Seeing you mention how Lecter is erratically shown from different sides makes me think of a spider caught in a jar and quickly moving along the glass walls. (Also, since I have arachnophobia, I am now itchy, nervous and paranoid of shadows.) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-26 19:56:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I will probably watch it anyway, out of curiosity and loyalty to the franchise, but if it has bad reviews I will wait for a home video/netflix release and not pay so much money for the cinema. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> I just finished Season 2 of Voyager. Here are some of my thoughts on each episode </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-26 19:31:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I began watching Voyager and I decided to write down some short opinions on each episode. Since my write-up of [Season 1](https://www.reddit.com/r/startrek/comments/60vrwc/i_started_watching_voyager_here_are_my_thoughts/) met with positive reaction, I am back with Season 2. It took me a while to finish it, but it was worth it. I'll be moving on to Season 3 immediately, but for now,  **please keep the comments spoiler-free for seasons 3-7.**


**201 - The 37's**

**Summary:** Voyager encounters a 1936 Ford pickup truck floating in space, which leads them to a planet where they find eight humans in suspended animation. One of them is Amelia Earhart.

**Opinion:** At first I thought this was going to be one of those episodes like TOS's Metamorphosis, where they found Zefram Cohrane to be still alive in remote space, or Requiem for Methuselah, where the guy appears to be multiple historical figures at once. But nope. This episode surprised me with an emotionally resonating idea of the crew giving up on home and settling a planet already inhabited by humans. It strongly reminded me of the time on Battlestar Galactica when they found New Caprica and the fleet divided into people who wanted to stay there and those who didn't. (You'll notice that I tend to invoke BSG from time to time in these write-ups, because the more I watch Trek the more I discover its influence on BSG.) It was fun watching Janeway meet Earhart, and it was a strong moment when Janeway told her she is the captain of a starship. It actually gave me a few goosebumps to think about the gravity of the first female pilot to cross the Atlantic meeting a woman from a future where not only is interstellar travel possible, but women are also equal to men. The episode went from average to great and overall I liked it quite a bit. Three things though: 1, So Voyager can just land on a planet? No big deal? Building a starship on Earth, as seen in the JJverse, suddenly seems less dumb. 2, Why did Earhart's navigator wear a suit and tie? Were they crossing the Atlantic so he could go to a job interview? 3. I can't believe they didn't show us those cities the humans built.


**202 - Initiations**

**Summary:** Chakotay's spirit ritual is interrupted when a young Kazon warrior attacks his shuttlecraft in an attempt to pass his initiation rite. But Chakotay destroys his ship and saves his life, causing the boy to loose face in their warrior culture.

**Opinion:** The Kazon are not my favorite villain. I don't understand why they are portrayed as a nomadic warrior tribe opposed to modern technology when they have huge spaceships and some advanced weaponry. You're either a Mongolian tribe or you're a space-faring civilization. Pick one. I also don't find them to be very internally consistent. One minute the leader talks about dying in battle and bravery vs cowardice, the next minute when Chakotay takes him hostage he suddenly orders everyone to stand down so he comes to no harm and Chakotay can escape. Uhm, what happened to dying in battle? With their warrior attitudes and bumpy brown foreheads, the Kazon seem like a poor knock-off version of the Klingons. Can you tell I didn't enjoy this episode very much? Also, couldn't they get another actor to play the young Kazon instead of Nog from DS9?


**203 - Projections**

**Summary:** The Doctor must question reality when he is summoned after a devastating attack on the ship but appears to be human while the rest of the crew are mere holograms

**Opinion:** I love these sort of mindfuck episodes where things are not what they seem. It reminded me of TNG's Remember Me, Frame of Mind or even Future Imperfect. And speaking of TNG, Broccoli is back! Not that I missed him, but he wasn't half as annoying in this episode as he used to be on the Enterprise. Anyway, it was a fun standalone episode that gave the doc stuff to do - for the first time this season. I only hope they will actually set up hologram projectors in different parts of the ship so he can leave sickbay irl and not just in this episode's fake reality. 


**204 - Elogium**

**Summary:** Voyager discovers a huge swarm of space insects and Kes has severe munchies that turn into early-onset puberty, which prompts her to consider conceiving a child with Neelix.

**Opinion:** "We need to start having babies," BSG's president Roslin exclaims. "But first let's ponder the implications," replies Janeway. Once again I was reminded of Galactica by this episode's overall theme of having children. Was this really the first time it occurred to anyone on the ship that the 70 year journey back home just *might* require them to procreate? Apparently so. In true Trek fashion, instead of sexing it up, they talk it up. The result is an odd episode that attempts to be funny and deep at the same time, mixing double entandre and comedic puberty with serious discussions of parenting and commitment. Not my favorite episode, but at least we got the second funniest line of the show, courtesy of Tuvok. "It appears we have lot our sex appeal, captain."


**205 - Non Sequitur**

**Summary:** Kim wakes up in San Francisco, having never gone on Voyager's faithful mission. He's in Starfleet R D working on a new runabout and he has a fiance. Confused about this alternate reality, he seeks out a drunk Paris, who also never boarded Voyager.

**Opinion:** I always enjoy these "specials" which are focused on just one character thrown into a weird time travel/alt reality/mirror universe scenario. After twenty episodes this also marks the first time Kim has anything interesting to do and is more than just a forgettable supporting character. Since he was featured so much in the pilot episode, I expected more from him. 


**206 - Twisted**

**Summary:** A mysterious region of space distorts the insides of Voyager, making several crew members lost in a maze of corridors and the doctors trapped in the holodeck.

**Opinion:** This was another one of those inconsequential filler episodes that could happen whenever, but it was fairly enjoyable and engaging. It reminded me of DS9's Move Along Home.

**207 - Parturition**

**Summary:** Paris  schools Kes in shuttle piloting and falls for her, making Neelix extremely jealous. When a conflict escalates between them, Janeway sends them down to a planet with a poisonous atmosphere where they hope to find food and Neelix decides to take care of a freshly hatched pterodactyl-like alien. Meanwhile, Voyager fights off a ship.

**Opinion:** This was definitely my least favorite episode so far. It had elements of DS9's The Ascent, but where that episode had a great questing beast dynamic between the wonderful Quark and Odo, here we have a forced love triangle between uninteresting characters who have little else to do, not to mention that ridiculous subplot with nursing the alien back to life. The other part of the episode that had Voyager face off against an alien ship felt extremely forced, as if they just had to give the rest of the cast something to do. The only intriguing part of the episode was the fact that they had to look for food supplies in order to survive - something they should have focused on more in-depth instead of doing the love triangle.


**208 - Persistence of Vision**

**Summary:** The doctor orders an overworked Janeway to relax on the holodeck, but she begins to hallucinate her holonovel's characters IRL and a sinister alien poses a threat to Voyagers when others begin to see things too.

**Opinion:** This was a pretty good "nothing is what it seems" type of episode. I like it when the writers use these sort of special circumstances, like hallucinations, to reveal new things about characters (such as that Torres wants to bang Chakotay). And Kes actually had something to do and her as yet poorly defined and underused psychic abilities came into play a bit. I'm curious to see if that ever gets properly developed. As a side not, this is the third time (I think) that Janeway's Victorian ghost story holonovel was interrupted by trouble - is this a running joke of the show?


**209 - Tattoo**

**Summary:** The search for fuel takes Voyager to a planet where Chakotay discovers markings from his Native American culture, which leads to an encounter with his ancestors.

**Opinion:** Flashbacks to Chakotay's youth (they picked a pretty bad actor, btw) show us he wasn't always the spiritual man and traditionalist he is today and while this episode wasn't particularly entertaining, at least it fleshed out the character. Also, apparently his tribe's Sky Spirits were actually ancient aliens who jump-started progress on Earth when they visited cavemen in the ice age. Who would've known.


**210 - Cold Fire**

**Summary:** After 10 months of wandering in the Delta Quadrant, Voyager finds a space station occupied by an Ocampa colony in contact with the dead Caretaker's counterpart, Suspiria. 

**Opinion:** This was an unexpected episode. At first I thought that after a couple of heavily standalone episodes they were finally going to deal with that whole stranded in the Delta Quad situation, but it turned out to be an episode focused mainly on Kes. She receives Jedi training Tuvok but is lured to the dark side by the Ocampan leader Tanis, who shows her the full potential of her dormant powers in order to.. what? Seduce her, I guess? He definitely wanted her for himself. There were some intriguing parts and that scene where Kes almost boiled Tuvok alive was badass. I got a couple of Event Horizon vibes from some of the scenes, like when the child caretaker had Torres and Tuvok suspended in the air and dripping blood on Janeway. Or when Suspiria turned into a purple tentacled blob. This wasn't half bad. More like this one, please.


**211 - Maneuvers**

**Summary:** Chakotay's traitorous ex from 110 is back, helping the Kazon to steal Starfleet technology and attack Voyager. Chakotay goes rogue to stop them.

**Opinion:** Unlike the more abstract and unnecessary episode Tattoo, this story centered on Chakotay was actually engaging and pretty close to that classic Trek rivalry with a recurring character. Not that Seska is as badass as Gul Dukat, as memorable as Khan, or as whimsically menacing as Q, but at least I have something to look forward to when she returns.... with in a fucking baby?? I did not see that coming. Hopefully the writers do something interesting with that.


**212 - Resistance**

**Summary:** An undercover away mission to procure fuel goes wrong when Tuvok and Torres are imprisoned and Janeway is injured and looked after by a crazy person who confuses her for his daughter.

**Opinion:** The cold open gave me some serious Star Wars vibes with the costumes, sets, and overall feel. It was like the crew visited a wretched hive of scum and villainy and got attacked by by helmeted troopers. The episode itself wasn't bad per se, but I had trouble connecting with it. The crazy dude who took care of Janeway thinking she is his daughter did nothing for me. I wasn't interested in the character and his craziness was kind of boring me. I often have trouble connecting with these one-off characters unless they somehow profoundly influence the core cast. I guess the emotional ending of the episode redeemed a bit but I'm not a fan. 


**213 - Prototype**

**Summary:** Torres gets emotionally invested in (and then abducted by) a broken down silver robot they found floating in space.

**Opinion:** Despite the robot's 1950s design and equally dated mask/costume, I really liked this episode. Data from TNG was name-dropped, issues with the Prime Directive were argued, themes of AI and its rights were discussed, and the episode focused on one of the main characters in an interesting way. Two thumbs up for a classic Trek story.


**214 - Alliances**

**Summary:** Voyager gets its ass kicked by the Kazon, prompting Chakotay and other Maquis crew members to lobby for a change of tactics. Janeway is reluctant to give up the Starfleet way of doing things but enters negotiations with the Kazon and their enemies, the Trabe.

**Opinion:** This might be my favorite episode of Voyager so far. There was a lot going on and all of it felt relevant. Although nothing really changed by the end of the episode, it didn't feel pointless and standalone. Just like I said about 116 in my season 1 write-up, this episode was exactly what the whole show should have been. There was a lot of tension between the Starfleet and Maquis crew members and the fact that Voyager is very far from home and kind of in a hopeless situation came across very clearly. I always enjoy instances when Starfleet officers struggle with whether or not they should follow their rules and directives and Janeway had a lot of that going on in Alliances. Also, Neelix was useful and relevant and not at all simply comic relief. My one beef with this episode is that Seska and Chakotay were kept completely apart and the fact that she impregnated herself using Chakotay's DNA wasn't mentioned at all despite that stuff happening 4 episodes ago. Instead, Seska makes a passing reference to her as yet invisible pregnancy when she mentions to Cullah that she is carrying *his* baby. What?


**215 - Threshold**

**Summary:** In order to speed up Voyager's return home, Tom Paris acts as test pilot for the first experimental flight to breach the transwarp barrier and achieve warp 10. However, the historic flight has unexpected (and potentially lethal) side effects.

**Opinion:** I already liked the episode when it had serious The Right Stuff vibes but then it suddenly turned into a combination of The Fly and Altered States and holy shit I did not see that coming! Not only does the crew perform some top notch sciencing and Paris becomes the Chuck Yeager of space when he reaches *infinite velocity* but then the episode takes a 180 turn into body horror territory and becomes straight up crazy, culminating in Janeway and Paris turned into *lizards in a swamp that just had baby lizards together.* I am genuinely curious what people think of this episode and how audiences originally reacted to it. This was.. uhm.. different. And awesome. But putting aside all that, I liked that this episode fleshed out Paris a bit and gave him a self-loathing inferiority complex. Also, and I did not expect this sort of continuity, the traitorous dude from the previous episode, who contacted Seska, gave the Kazon instructions how to achieve warp 10. I wonder if that will ever be mentioned again.


**216 - Meld**

**Summary:** Violent Betazoid engineering crewman Lon Suder murders someone for no reason and Tuvok performs the Vulcan mind meld on him to find out his motive. But the meld transplants Suder's violent nature onto Tuvok.

**Opinion:** I guess I'm in a streak of great episodes because this did not disappoint. I love Vulcan struggles with emotions and Tuvok really delivered. Great acting, great insight into the Vulcan mind and a great way to do something interesting with a character. Also, Brad Dourif! I find it kind of hard to accept that Lon Suder was somehow unseen until now, after something like 30 episodes. It makes little sense to do special guest stars like this on a show where new crew can't just show up out of nowhere when the ship is docked at a space station. But whatever. I hope we'll see more of him in future episodes, because from now on I will always keep in mind that no matter what dangerous thing is happening with the ship, somewhere inside there is Lon Suder brooding in his quarters under house arrest.


**217 - Dreadnought**

**Summary:** It turns out that a powerful Cardassian missile with AI that was reprogrammed for Maquis purposes by Torres was transported to the Delta Quadrant along with Voyager and is now headed to destroy an innocent planet unless Voyager can stop it.

**Opinion:** This episode had some intriguing ideas and it was another good Torres episode somewhat thematically similar to 213 (in that her creation turned into a force of destruction) but in the end it was kind of pointless. Given the nature of the show, it was completely obvious that Voyager would not be destroyed and the missile would be successfully stopped, so there was absolutely no tension during the final act, even though it was probably meant to be tense.


**218 - Death Wish**

**Summary:** Voyager accidentally frees a disgruntled and suicidal member of the Q continuum and a tribunal is held to determine whether or not he should be allowed to commit suicide.

**Opinion:** If I hear the word continuum one more time, I swear to God...
...I was never a big fan of anything related to Q and so I did not enjoy this episode one bit. Well, I guess I did enjoy seeing Riker again, and the actor playing the suicidal Q was pretty good, but other than that, I was glad when it was over. Here we have these two infinitely powerful beings and no one thinks to beg them on their knees to be sent back to the Alpha Quadrant? Q taunts Janeway with the prospect of returning to Earth (and having sex together, apparently) but that's about it. I guess that streak of good episodes is over now.


**219 - Lifesigns**

**Summary:** The doctors falls in love with a Vidiian woman dying of the Phage. Paris' recurring attitude problems get him in trouble.

**Opinion:** There's not much to say about the main storyline. It was charming but a bit boring and while I'm happy for the doc, I'd much rather watch stuff of more consequence. Like the traitorous informant who is till in contact with the Kazon. Or the fact that Seska craves Voyager and plans to attack it. And what about Paris? Starting with 216 there were instances where he was late on the bridge or had serious attitude problems, especially towards Chakotay, and now that culminated in him striking a superior officer and getting locked up in the brig. It's interesting that the show has these two serialized and recurring plotlines but chooses to be completely standalone in every other respect. I wonder what's in store next for Paris and that traitor dude.


**220 - Investigations**

**Summary:** Neelix becomes an investigative reporter and a disillusioned and demotivated Paris decides to leave the ship and try his luck elsewhere. Or does he?

**Opinion:** I really enjoyed this episode. But I do feel like it could have been much better. The twist was that Tom isn't actually leaving the ship. He's on an undercover mission to flush out Voyager's mole and his recurring insubordination of the past couple of episodes was all an act. That's great. Except I think the cover story was much closer to Paris' character than the heroism of the actual plan. As evidenced in 216, Paris is a guy who's been at odds all his life. He has trouble finding himself and finding a place where he would fit. He *should* feel demotivated and uneasy on Voyager. He *should* want to leave and take on the whole Delta Quadrant all by himself. He *should* do for real the things that were just a ruse. I never saw Paris as a self-sacrificing cookie-cutter hero but this episode definitely turned him into one. I think it would have been much more interesting if no one on the ship had any idea there is a mole, but Paris, having actually left to find his luck elsewhere, somehow finds out and decides to return to save Voyager when Seska attacks (which I assume is going to happen in the finale).


**221 - Deadlock**

**Summary:** While trying to avoid a fleet of the organ-stealing Vidiians, Voyager flies trough a spatial scission that creates an exact copy of the ship. One Voyager is doing fine while the other is on the brink of destruction.

**Opinion:** I found this episode to be reminiscent of TNG's Yesterday's Enterprise, a favorite of mine. It had some intriguing stuff going on, including the deaths of a newborn baby and the untimely and matter-of-fact demise of ensign Kim, which were both pretty dark for Trek. I also love the fact that everyone is terrified of the Vidiians. They are such a cool villain and frankly much more intriguing than the straightforward Kazon. Not only are the Vidiians fugly, they're after your organs! What a sick and terrifying prospect to be used as a lab rat in a leper colony. The meeting of two Janeways created intriguing dilemmas and I feel like it wasn't dealt with deeply and thoroughly enough. What a thought-provoking thing it is to sacrifice your dying ship so that your copy can survive. I also thought it was both amazing and very weird that they sent Kim and the baby from the soon to be destroyed version of the ship back to the version where they died. At the end of the episode Kim mentions that it feels weird because although everyone is exactly the same, they also aren't. Everyone he knew died and he returned to a ship where he also knows everyone, but their experiences are only 99.99% the same. He will be an alien, a visitor, a replacement. This was perhaps the first episode of Voyager that really left me thinking about it and contemplating what I just saw. 


**222 - Innocence**

**Summary:** Tuvok crash-lands on a habitable moon where discovers three children who claim to be in mortal danger. Meanwhile, Voyager makes contact with the race that inhabits the planet orbited by that moon, who are not pleased with Tuvok's involvement in their affairs.

**Opinion:** I guess I see what they were going for with this episode, but I can't say that I liked any of it. Tuvok's interactions with the kids were neither funny nor revealing of a new aspect of his character (I find the fact that he is a father intriguing and I think this episode did nothing particularly interesting with it). The whole story reminded me of a standard, rather mediocre OS episode, as if they found an unused spec script from the sixties and just adapted it to Voyager.


**223 - The Thaw**

**Summary:** The crew find three miners in asleep in stasis and plugged into a virtual reality where an AI is holding them hostage and feeding on their fear of clowns.

**Opinion:** Three guys in stasis. Ok, sure. They're plugged into the Matrix. Ok, cool. Kim and Torres are plugging into the Matrix to go save them. Ok, yeah, you got my interest, get the plot going already. The Matrix is filled with court jesters, acrobats, and Queen's Innuendo album art come to life. Ugh, really? And I thought the previous episode was reminiscent of the original series. I had great trouble finishing this episode and I consider it a waste of 45 minutes.


**224 - Tuvix**

**Summary:** Tuvok and Neelix are merged into a single person during a transporter malfunction caused by an orchid. The new being, Tuvix, starts a new life on Voyager much to Kes' dismay.

**Opinion:** At first I thought this was going to be another dumb episode. As if Neelix himself wasn't enough, Tuvix looked like something straight out of Red Dwarf and did not fit in visually with the rest of the show (though, granted, the make up job was really good). Also, I thought this was going to be a dumb comedic episode. But by the time the credits rolled, Tuvix actually became really interesting. I loved that he cried bloody murder when they took him off the bridge to be separated back into Tuvok and Neelix. They really were killing a sentient person (essentially a new form of life) and the moral dilemmas were great. I also loved the fact that the doctor refused to do it and Janeway had to be the one. Even Kes was interesting for once.


**225 - Resolutions**

**Summary:** Chakotay and Janeway are left to live out their lives in quarantine on a picturesque planet after they were infected with a virus from an insect bite. However, the crew have a hard time accepting Captain Tuvok's orders.

**Opinion:** What a good episode this was. Chakotay and Janeway had pretty good chemistry together and their inevitable romance was handled nicely. It also said a lot about their characters that Janeway refused to give up research while Chakotay was already having the time of his life in the great outdoors. Tuvok's command predictably didn't go all too well, especially when he vehemently followed Janeway's order not to ask the Vidiians for help. I expected there would be mutiny but in the end it wasn't so dramatic, and I guess that's for the better. Mutiny is really not in Starfleet's nature. But if other the previously displayed lack of continuity is any indication, Chakotay's and Janeway's experiences will not affect them in any way going forward and their brief affair will be forgotten.


**226 - Basics, Part I**

**Summary:** Seska uses her newborn baby as bait and lures Voyager into a perfectly planned trap. Meanwhile, Lon Suder wants to be helpful.

**Opinion:** Unlike the previous season's last episode, this was a proper finale and thank god I have Netflix and don't have to wait all summer for the conclusion. Seska's plan was really good and I loved the moment when the computer was unable to initiate the self-destruct sequence and Janeway realized why the Kazon targeted a specific, seemingly non-essential part of the ship. I also loved the fact that this was communicated to the audience purely by Janeway's expression and not some verbal explanation. I guess Suder and the doctor will save the ship all by themselves now. (One thing about the self-destruct: Janeway initiated it at least once before and since then I've been bothered that she is able to do so on her own. Should this be a command that needs consent of another officer?)
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-26 14:45:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It wasn't literally a 4th wall break, but picture something like this: The movie is over, the big bad alien defeated, and then in the last minute of the film the characters learn that there are even bigger and badder aliens out in the universe and there's also an alliance of species devoted to fighting them and since humans were able to defeat this bad alien, they are going to spearhead the universe-wide effort, so everyone looks at each other and nods in a determined way and they go 'Yeah, we can do this in the sequel!' </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-26 13:33:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I love how it just bends like it's made out of rubber. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-26 10:28:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah I've been looking forward to a trailer (or at least a teaser) for months </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-26 08:50:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I don't know about the movie but the book is anything but slow-burn. There's a lot of stuff happening, many twists and a couple of action scenes. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-25 18:22:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I had the same experience. I thought he is a God and now I think he's hit and miss at best </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-25 18:19:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> When I remember Alias and look at what a star he is now, I am impressed </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-25 18:18:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> He was also pretty good in that JFK assassination movie but I can't remember the name </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-25 16:51:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  2nd Honda team

is that like being second in a human centipede? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-25 16:11:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Science question time!

What period of time are we looking at here? Is this oxidation or is it decomposition as in the half life of tin? What is the material that is left at the end? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-25 16:09:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> yeah, and then all those another Ridley Scott movies happened and he never recovered </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-25 13:34:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> no, but my girlfriend gave me a warning and I immediately left the premises </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-25 13:06:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I especially like how "No spoiling the appearance of the area." pretty much just sums it up at the end. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> There are a lot of things you're not allowed to do in certain streets in Tokyo </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-25 12:49:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> I guess we're posting images of Japanese streets. I took this in Kyoto two weeks ago. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-25 12:26:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-25 11:10:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That tease was the most cringeworthy wink at the audience I have seen in a very long time </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-25 11:04:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Wow, that doesn't look appetizing at all. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-25 11:00:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Oh, I get it. It seems like all that will do is increase torrenting.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-25 10:49:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Michael Mann directed the shit out of this movie. I love it. It is very subtle, tense and dramatic. Also probably Russell Crowe's best performance (though he had me in tears in A Beautiful Mind). </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-25 10:38:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  thing that really kicks a la carte streaming into high gear, which sounds frustrating at the consumer level.

you lost me there, mate, can you explain please? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-25 10:31:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I was surprised The Force Awakens is on Netflix but I guess that makes more sense now </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-25 09:59:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Doesn't Disney already own everything? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-25 09:59:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It is easier to blend CG characters with live action backgrounds if part of the scenery is CG too. So even if they shoot real plates, part of them will be recreated (or augmented) with CG just to make the CG animals blend in better. Definitely all the foliage the CG animal interacts with will also be CG </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-25 08:55:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This is the first time I realized he was in his forties in the height of his career  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-25 08:52:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I guess she did not want the hose again </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-24 22:32:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Serious questions: how often do these nudist gatherings involve men with erections and how are erections viewed in your community? Do first time nudists get hard and is that something to be embarrassed about or is it accepted by the other participants (female or male)? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> These are most of my books (hardbacks are on a different shelf) and yes, I am a fan of Nesbo </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-24 19:39:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-24 16:17:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> funny how yo-yo master and Yo-Yo Ma are so vastly different </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-24 15:38:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Slovakia - the first time we became an independent state, our first ever president Tiso collaborated with the nazis and we deported Jews. As if that wasn't bad enough, nowadays we have a growing number of ultra-right fascist groups who hail Tiso as a hero (a political party linked to these people is currently in our parliament, a shameful thing in and of its self) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-24 15:36:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I don't think "I'm so sorry" is meant to be an apology. It also has a second meaning that is meant to convey regret. As in "I regret that this happened" which is the same as "I am sorry that this happened" which then gets shortened to "I'm sorry." </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-24 15:31:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Any cheap 10-12 year old car. You can learn to really drive with an older car without all the modern electronic amenities that practically do all the work for you and you don't have to worry about the occasional minor scratch or bump. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-24 14:34:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> My grandfather died at home, in his favorite armchair, listening to his most favorite song. Not a bad way to go, I think. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-24 14:30:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm not sure if you're looking for an answer that names a specific person (a celebrity?) but I'm gonna tell you about my friend who is currently on the road to becoming socially normal.

For a long time my friend was reclusive and introverted to the point where I worried about him. This is a guy that used to be the life of the party in high school, but during college he developed something which I can only describe as a combination of depression and an inferiority complex. In addition to that, he did not feel at ease in social situations, he turned into a loner and he would not hang out with his friends if more than 4-5 people were going to be present (he would ask in advance what the expected attendance was and would leave if more people showed up). He became generally disillusioned with his life, owing to an inability to find a fulfilling job (he graduated environmental studies), an inability to find a girlfriend (he is still a virgin at 28 and tbh he is hopeless with women), his inability to break through with his band (he is singer/songwriter/lead guitarist of a rather unsuccessful but badass rock band), his self image of being unattractive (he is very skinny and has no muscles) and his growing dependence on weed and alcohol. However, thanks to some professional help and gradual baby steps in self-improvement, he is becoming socially normal again. He is now much happier than I remember him in at least 5 years and and it looks like he might even have a potential girlfriend lined up. He also gave up the substance abuse, which is the best news. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-24 13:07:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> umbrella repair shops used to be quite big in my country </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-24 11:09:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  I actually own the library.

pics check out </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-24 11:08:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I feel like you could save a lot of space if you stacked those books differently on the shelves </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-24 09:15:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If only they had this in that pig fucking episode of Black Mirror </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-22 23:48:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I wonder if they will make any mention of temp scores and how those affect the final score </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Is there any way for a pregnant female to sense her unborn offspring's gender or even to influence it during conception? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-22 20:58:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-22 20:49:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I will probably switch jobs at least two times, get married and have a kid by the time this series ends. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-22 14:59:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [The ending of Take Shelter](https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=ukh04BviEC8) (spoilers, obviously)

It is already a great movie full of intrigue, atmosphere and good drama and it features the always great Micheal Shannon and Jessica Chastain. But that ending. Holy shit. Not only does it simultaneously turn the whole movie on its head and leaves room for interpretation, but the score in those final moments is incredibly effective.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> ELI5: why am I able to use my phone's touchscreen with a bandaid but not with a glove? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-21 22:46:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-21 22:44:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Oh man(n), I would love to see this on the big screen

Everything about this movie is so well done, it's like leafing through a filmmaking textbook. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
