<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject2165</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-09 01:00:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> First, the phrase is "utmost". Second, the drivers are *also* the regulars. Maybe they should be treated as members of the communities they work in. Not some mindless drones. Sure, there are good and bad drivers. You can't punish everyone for the actions of some poor employees, whether their conversations factor into any missed stops or not. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-09 00:53:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I agree with you that everyone should not be punished for other people doing their jobs properly. There are always good and bad employees. God help us if there is a "no talking" policy implemented. I would enjoy seeing drivers and other employees keep to the letter of the rule and speak to no one at all in protest. And the fact that they won't let drivers in the tunnels wear masks seems arbitrary.

I would disagree with you on the "beer after work" part, however. I think the new policy (which I don't agree with on principle) is aimed at those having a couple beers before work. Or, allegedly, that and other things during. I think the worker's union should have been involved in the process of creating the rules, rather than railing against them. Possibly they could have used the implementation of random testing as a bargaining chip at contract time. Just one union man's opinion to another. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-08 11:56:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> **All the Birds in the Sky, Charlie Jane Anders** Really not digging it, 86 pages to go.

Planning to jump back into **China Mieville's Three Moments of an Explosion** next.

Also picked up a copys of **Warren Ellis' James Bond: VARGR** for a change of pace. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-08 11:53:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I feel the same about the subject matter. I keep thinking I should like this book more. Maybe a stronger editorial voice would have helped. I think it is Anders' first long book. I've read other writers who don't translate well from short fiction right away. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> All The Birds In The Sky - Does it get better? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-08 07:37:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> (this turned i to kind of a negative-sounding rant, when I really just want to know if the book is worth finishing)

I'm having a hard time with this book in a way I haven't in quite a while. As in, I want to throw it out a window, but it is a library book. I probably wouldn't have jumped into it, but I'm reading it for the Hugo awards, although it was on my radar.

The content is interesting enough I want to know what happens. The biggest problem is the style, I suppose.

Locations will change but you won't notice because it isn't mentioned at all for a page or two, then you go back and realize the characters have been somewhere else for quite a while. No break in text or anything.

There's a lot of telling, and no showing (as much as you can in a novel). For example, there is a major time jump at one point and events in the intervening years are heavily referenced with Capital Letters, but not explained. I understand drawing out the mystery, but how many times can you do it without following up? 

Secondly: A lot of exposition that could have been done better in dialogue. "This character felt this way and the other one also felt like this but didn't say so". Pretty good summary of most of the central relationship, as well.

The inside references to clubs and bars and restaurants in SF are annoying. Describe the place, maybe. I just get the sense that I'm meant to be jealous the author knows all these cool places and I don't. (Actually a bit of a leap to assume their real, I guess, but that is the vibe I get from the name-dropping)

As if a knife was being pressed into my eyes, I keep reading "like". Am I reading texts from a tween girl, or a book. "Laurence was like, "You should sneak her up here..." Ugh. This happens no less than three times by page 179. If it was in character for someone in the book, okay, but it isn't.

I haven't quit a book since the third Riverworls installment (ugh), but this will be a near-run thing.

Sorry for the rant. I welcome disagreement and corrections.




 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-08 07:16:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It sounds similar to Steinbeck's retelling of Arthurian legends. From what I recall, he loved them, and wanted to makw them accesible to a wider audience. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-07 14:49:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Are you able to visit breweries for tasting purposes now? We were in Winnipeg a year and a half ago, and made a hike to a brewery only to be told the weren't allowed to sample anything. Made for a very frustrating trip on the bus. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-07 12:49:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> "Trappist" is a very specific definition and does not apply to Stella in any way. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-07 10:47:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What is that? Like, 20, 30 dudes? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-05 06:53:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Please! Even Chicago has a better Ray Touch Tank than Tampa, and they're represented by a bear and some laundry.

(shoutout to the Shedd Aquarium) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-04 15:17:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> A winning lottery ticket. Seems foolproof. No regrets. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-02 22:19:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I always find myself thinking about how their statements are affected by the Bottom Line. "...the left side of the infield will be ready for the next home stand (because fuck we need to sell more jerseys and we aren't paying these guys to stretch)" </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-02 04:55:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> These long-haired super-nerds will be the doom of the Republican Empire! ARROOOOOOO!!! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-01 19:49:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I hate this mentality. Rushing your star players off the DL for some perceived boost in ticket revenue. I see a similar trend on our end, with Donaldson and more recently Sanchez coming back only to go right back out again. Let the guys rest and heal, christ. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-01 00:26:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Welcome to Kitchen Stadium. Pick up your baseballs and stand mixers on the way in. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-29 19:53:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Didn't they used to have street addresses for each station under the name? Or am I misremembering? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-28 13:33:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> He talks about his book deal on [his blog](http://whatever.scalzi.com/2015/05/25/about-that-deal/). 
 A new epic space opera series (two books planned at the moment, lets see where it goes from there) in an entirely new universe

Which I'm guessing refers to The Collapsing Empire. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-28 12:42:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I think the questions OP is asking is: Is it an article, or is it advertising? If the site is owned wholly by a company and promoting products by that company, it is the latter, and should at least be labelled. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-27 05:07:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The system (edit: the stations) is actually constantly powerwashed. There are several crews (couldn't tell you how many) working nightly.

The operators wear earplugs due to constant exposure to sound that doesn't affect riders over the the short term. Masks can be seen in the same light. If the exposure limit is low enough it can affect the operator's health. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-27 05:02:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If it's asbestos people are worried about, wetting it is the best thing to do. It's the subsequent cleanup that needs to be done.

Problem is, we need to know what is in the dust, what the concentration is and what thr exposure limit is. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-26 23:18:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Somewhere there is a guy whose job it is to clean the undercarriage with a pressure washer. I'd hate to be him on those days. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-26 22:23:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Don't worry, no one is judging you...... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-26 22:20:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Between the necessary cleanup of track and train, additional delays, compassionate leave for train operator and other witnesses, and the plain fact he saved a life, even if you're being as cynical as possible, this guy saved time and money already. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-26 22:13:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I feel like the superhero team from the most recent season (feels like ten years ago) of VB was copy-pasted from the Tick's canon. And it felt so good. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-26 22:11:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Wait, is this the moment I've been waiting for all these years?

KEEN! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-26 22:10:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I read the comics in Townsend Coleman's voice. It's perfect. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-26 12:15:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That picture is making my palms sweat. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-26 12:10:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This won't affect breweries' retail stores or the Wine Rack. I'm guessing it won't affect grocery stores selling booze either?

So strike. The province won't go dry. If anything, maybe people will learn how well they can get on without the LCBO.

I'm as pro-union as you can be, but the LCBO is a terrible place. A near monopoly and the still need radio/tv/print ads. I'm noticing uninformed, clueless employees are the exception now, not the rule. Even so, the crapshoot of product info and stock consistency frustrates me to no end. 

Feels like another business model refusing to adapt to the times, and blaming everyone but themselves. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-26 08:09:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Out of curiosity, how do you "count" shorter books? This is my first year with a reading goal (52), and I feel like I'm cheating with shorter books, say ~150 pages. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-25 21:12:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> A Wes Anderson, Gulliver's Travels-style film starring Bryan Cranston where each island is stranger and quirkier than the last? All in. Forever. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-25 12:00:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Charles Stross' Laundry Files books have some interesting combat scenes. If you haven't read them, they look at summoning demons and a whole host of paranormal creatures through the lens of computer programming as a ritual (I'm oversimplifying, and missing the mark a bit I am sure). So you get gadgets that Q could have come up with (ie. basilisk camera, a reverse camera that uses a basilisk's glare to explosovely turn flesh to stone) for demon hunting, plus classic arcane weapons like Hands of Glory and amulets and charms.

The series itself can get dense, and it helps if your maths/comp sci part of your brain works well.

I think I got off topic and this just became a recommendation for the series. Enjoy! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-25 11:05:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> "It is a transitionalecoregion..."

Literally what you asked for, but not close enough? More explanation, less condescension, maybe. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-25 00:13:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Shan boxes changed my life. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-25 00:09:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I am a bulk-buyer of Shan dal and tikka masala packages. Is there anything they can't do!

Do you have a preferred cut of beef you use? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-25 00:07:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Wow. Gf will love the chicken option, thanks! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-24 17:45:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> My glassware collection is getting extensive, and I pay for them all nowadays. Ten years ago, however, my young, drunk, idiot self would wake up with a new one once or twice a month. I think it's just one of those things that comes with age. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Recipe recommendations - Haleem Beef </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-24 17:02:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I usually just lurk and try to learn in this sub, but I'm hoping some more experienced members can kindly offer some guidance. 

This weekend was capped by another trip to one of our [favourite Toronto restaurants](http://lahoretikkahouse.com/). In the market for something new, we ordered the haleem beef (and Hara chicken, and saag paneer and...there is no bad dish there!), and it instantly became a new favourite of mine.  

Initial research online has yielded many many recipes for haleem, and I was wondering if anyone here was familiar with making the dish, or could steer me in the direction of an authentic recipe out of the hundreds online. I know the style spreads over many areas, and has many iterations. The one we had was definitely made with shredded beef (not ground, as the menu indicates) and was almost like a thick stew.

I look forward to any advice, and to sharing hopefully successful results in the future, thank you! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-24 15:51:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> **No One Writes to the Colonel, Gabriel Garca Mrquez**, the titular story was very good, and I'm off on the shorter ones. I've never read Mrquez, and this is meant to be an introduction/test the waters. Finding his writing very approachable and detailed, with colourful characters. Reminds me a bit of Steinbeck in that regard.

I also have bookmarks jabbed into the very early pages of **The Long Utopia, by Pratchett and Baxter**, and **The Last Continent, Terry Pratchett**. Not sure which one will take off first.

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-24 15:36:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I hear ya. From theatre aspirations, to reading how much that would cost me, to joining a trade. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-24 15:33:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> In this country, we grudgingly read the Beaverton, and we like it that way </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-21 03:04:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Over the track, you mean? Probably just slap signage overtop. Much like St George's and new signage. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-21 00:24:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Canada Day game is always fun. I'll be there. Plus free hat. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-20 23:05:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> And aren't baseball fans now. They've all got a transfer to the Leafs' bandwagon. Good news for everyone who likes cheap tickets on stubhub. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-20 23:03:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Not for long :-/ </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-19 21:47:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I've always assumed it is for families who don't want drunk assholes falling all over them. Maybe people working the program too?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-18 08:39:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> My cat destroyed my armchair. Now I have to read books and drink on my sectional like a commoner. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-13 17:38:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I think gf beers would more likely be bottled, however. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-07 12:59:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I got into a trade because I couldn't afford to fork out for Uni. The pay difference in my trade for unionized v. non-unionized work is huge, anywhere from $10-15. 

Large, bloated unions that pad their own pockets and keep poor workers from being fired are bad, but in many cases they're the only way for workers to get a fair sake. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-06 22:50:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> One might expect a home opener to be on a weekend. Not a Tuesday evening.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [guest] Just got asked to have my ID verified for the first time, curious about AirBnB's usage of my info </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-06 13:08:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I have no issue providing verification for hosts, but reading their privacy policy, there is a lot of dense text about providing my info to third parties if they choose to. Has anyone got insight into other ways they use your provided info? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-05 15:10:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> In the specific case of Robohop, the 650ml bottles are listed for 8.95. $5 for a 473ml can seems like a better price either way. Don't know what people would be up in arms about.

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-03 22:42:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This is it. This is my heart attack season. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-03 22:33:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> How about that eyeball! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-03 22:30:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Looks like they just unpacked him from a shipping crate filled with dirt from his homeland </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-03 22:13:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I wonder if Jays tickets on stubhub rise and fall in price with every run for/against </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-03 22:08:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Can you not do pitch-by-pitch on mlb? Auto refresh.
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-01 19:11:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Makes sense, if your a fast reader. You might like Alan Moore's From Hell, since the artwork, while good, often takes a backseat to Moore's writing. But I won't try to convert you :) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-01 12:21:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Girlfriend just finished this one, and she had much the same opinion. Gunslinger was a hard sell (outside her reading comfort zone), but II and III locked her in. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-01 12:04:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Why not? Just curious. As someone with a thick stack of graphic novels in my library, I'm always interested in why people *don't* like them.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-31 22:03:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I like to think I deserved both </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-31 18:56:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Over-BOO-led!

/laugh track </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-31 18:53:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> "Players are safe under cover. Grounds crew, get out there!" </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-31 18:50:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> "And so you see, your honour, my clients have, without a doubt, proven the existence of a discorporeal afterlife. Ghosts are real, and there is a very real chance neither you, nor I, nor anyone in this courtroom will gain access to a heavenly afterlife. Instead we will be relegated to walk this mortal plane *ad inifinitum*, never again knowing the touch of a loved one....

Shit..." </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-31 18:18:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Wouldn't call it fast food. Went to the Danforth location when it opened up. I would say it is better than Swiss Chalet, in terms of flavour (if spicy barbecue chicken is your thing). The wings were large and grilled, sides were great, not just bland veg + potato. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-29 21:09:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Luxury is definitely the category I put train travel in Canada under. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-29 21:06:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Last time I took a long-distance train, I handed my bag to the porter, who put in the the car. Same process, in reverse, upon arrival. Hard to fuck that up.

(ninjaedit: there was a carousel in winnipeg, now I recall) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-29 21:04:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Future advertising space for our corporate overlords.

(but really, [sound baffles](http://www.soundproofcow.com/product-category/sound-absorption-materials/hanging-baffles/)) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-29 20:49:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> As someone who has used presto to go UP - TTC at Dundas West, it couldn't be more confusing. Unless they've changed it recently. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-29 20:46:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Carpooling really kills any discount. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-29 02:11:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Definitely makes a difference in those communities. I never thought of Via being that integral until I took the Winnipeg-Churchill train. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-29 02:10:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Via Rail: Second biggest beneficiary of CPP after OLG </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-28 23:56:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> We have a conversation about taking Via to Ottawa/Montreal/Quebec whenever we travel there. The other options being to drive or fly. Always ends with me paraphrasing [Sterling Archer](https://youtu.be/Kq-N3_plNq8?t=6s). Let me explain:

As a quick experiment, looked up pricing vs. travel time for our Civic holiday weekend trip to Quebec City.

Via - $659 round trip, 26 hours total travel

Porter - $680 round trip, 3 hours total travel

Maybe this trip, or ourselves as travellers, aren't Via's target demographic. But let me ask you: Who is? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-27 05:01:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Usually when the author goes completely round the bend and inserts themselves into the book. Clive Cussler, Stephen King, and Philip Jose Farmer spring to mind. Speaking of Farmer:

The only book I've fully abandoned in recent memory was the third Riverworld book. Character had the same initials and background as Farmer, as I recall. Couldn't stand it after a while. Took all three books to donate the next day.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-26 16:17:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I can appreciate that. Untying laces at the end of twelve hours is the bane of my existence some days.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-26 14:53:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Never seen pull-on work boots before (Canadian, hi). Do those things have a steel toe in them? Honestly, they look like the kind of thing I would be sent home for wearing.
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-26 00:42:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Lucky you. Quite a few line tonight. Glad I tried the sours earlier. Wristbands are the future. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-25 22:03:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> But what about the wine and spirits bar? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Heading to Winter Brewfest this evening, any suggestions? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-25 18:01:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Going fairly early in the evening. Anyone go last night and have recommendations for what to check out? How much of a gong show are the lines?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-25 17:56:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What an strange sentence this would have been a couple years ago </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-24 00:33:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I personally enjoy taking the guesswork out of drunkenly choosing a platform and getting it wrong... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-24 00:33:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> One would hope they at least filled the bug holes and coated it with something that will let them pressure wash it easily. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> trioKAIT -- Don't Speak (cover) [jazz/fusion/instrumental](2016) </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-23 15:32:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-22 18:00:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> (This originally began as a reply to another "I'm watching Iron Fist" comment, and got lengthy...)

As I write, watching Iron Fist, Episode 12.

I think my biggest problem with Iron Fist is the lack of fighting. Or the lack of *quality* fighting. It's like the showrunners have never seen a kung fu movie. Wires and epic setting for battles would be wonderful. The fights are so boring, with so many cuts, nothing looks impressive. And it isn't like they couldn't have upped the ante a *little bit* from faceless goons. It isn't as thought they are trying to hide that Danny's powers are real (but he's *angsty* so he can't always use it, guys) so why not fire some powered up enemies at him. In *The Immortal Iron Fist*, magical warriors are a dime a dozen. More interesting than cannon fodder, at least.

[update](#s Oh god, Danny and Colleen are centering their *chi* together to hip hop. What the hell.) 

The biggest problem, in my mind, is the show's policy of "Tell, Don't Show". No one is pretending Danny doesn't actually have powers after the first reveal, throw some flashbacks in there! Not like *Arrow* levels of flashbacks, but shit. Danny talks ad nauseum about his training and K'un L'un. And Shou Lao the Undying! Hey guys! Know what's really popular on a competing network right now? Dragons! Unless they're planning a reveal where the Dragon was really inside Danny all along...Please don't let this be true.

[update, episode 13](#s Colleen and Danny are wearing matching shoes, can't unsee)

This show seems to lean more towards a CW superhero drama more than Netflix's previous forays. And it had (has?) such potential.

[update](#s By the way, in the comics, Danny's mom died defending him from a pack of wolves. Is that not better than "sucked out an airplane?") </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-22 15:28:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I thought this sounded familiar.

Michael Crichton's [Airframe](https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Airframe_\(novel\)#References_to_reality) used elements of this tragedy for the main storyline. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-22 15:22:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Huh. I always thought it was "le mot d'escalier". Thanks for saving me from future embarassment. TIL. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-21 18:42:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> We did High Dump from the Crane Lake Rd. parking lot last year. Trails were well maintained and easy to follow. Haven't done the Stormhaven hike, but from what I read, the shore trail can be difficult if you are coming from the east.

Can't recommend enough trying to get a site on Flowerpot Island for a night. waking up for a swim with the flowerpots and no tourists is well worth it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-21 01:23:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I can see a marketing company torpedoing putting something like "Ask us about our yeast" on a sign.

Then again, in the world of craft beer, it might not be a terrible idea.... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-19 23:21:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If you were ever going to make an exception, Sandman should really be it.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-17 12:59:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I've heard Comerica is a lot more fun than the SkyDome, though. From both sides of the fence. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-16 04:25:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Like the condos at Woodbine and Danforth. I dont mind the size or style of the building. The commercial options leave a little to be desired (personal opinion). We got a Firkin, a cigar shop and an empty storefront. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-16 04:22:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> How dare you give us numbers to draw our own conclusions from! I demand bias! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-16 03:39:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm the same, sometimes. The stakes are so low in any argument I have online, I'm not going to google things for you.

However, f I'm coming out of left field with a "little-known" fact or something, I'll usually source it because people will be interested. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-13 23:58:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I misquoted a half-remembered [bit of Orwell](http://www.george-orwell.org/The_Road_to_Wigan_Pier/7.html) which, upon re-reading this afternoon, doesn't mean what I thought I remembered. Fun read about class conflict in England, however. Some stuff still partially applicable today. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-13 14:17:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> "...cold beer, warm p_ssy, and someplace to take a sh_t with a door on it."

-Mr. Ford, Frisky Dingo </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-13 14:15:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Practice your stuffy indignation in the meantime. Start with "Well, I never!" and work your way up to "Ra-ther!" </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-13 14:13:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Upper lower middle class, as they say </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-13 14:09:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Is this how it works? I believe in my own elitism and the money starts rolling in? Here goes nothing! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-13 03:49:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Having been forcefed a considerable amount of Dickens in high school, I've developed a superpower where I subconsciously gloss over intense descriptions. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-07 21:13:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Reminds me of the Australian politician who said that young people would be able to afford a house if they stopped going out for brunch every weekend. Porridge and landlines for everyone! That will fix the world... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-03 12:47:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Do these guys have beer out already? The website is just a placeholder.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-28 00:36:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> *Indiana Jones and the Last Crusade* I must have seen at least once a year for every year of my life (even more as a kid).


 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-24 22:40:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's very fetch. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-24 22:33:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [Let me help you](https://youtu.be/h1WJqKWqUHQ) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-24 20:57:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I had a friend fail his first driving test because of a rolling stop (he was warned, and did it again, unthinking). In no way is it considered a stop. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-24 03:29:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> As a Canadian who made the trip to Belgium for Westvleteren (amonst other things) I vote you book a train/plane and get down there. Well worth it. And there's less of an ocean in your way! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-24 00:02:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Definitely. Just re-read a couple years ago. Great story, characters and humour. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-23 22:58:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Well, if the shoe fits...

/s

/ON </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
