<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject5054</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Analysis predicts extremely disruptive, total transition to EV / autonomous vehicles in 13 years </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-09 21:43:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-09 19:58:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Study: [Trajectories toward the 1.5C Paris target: Modulation by the Interdecadal Pacific Oscillation](http://onlinelibrary.wiley.com/doi/10.1002/2017GL073480/full)
___

**Abstract**

Global temperature is rapidly approaching the 1.5C Paris target. In the absence of external cooling influences, such as volcanic eruptions, temperature projections are centered on a breaching of the 1.5C target, relative to 18501900, before 2029. The phase of the Interdecadal Pacific Oscillation (IPO) will regulate the rate at which mean temperature approaches the 1.5C level. A transition to the positive phase of the IPO would lead to a projected exceedance of the target centered around 2026. If the Pacific Ocean remains in its negative decadal phase, the target will be reached around 5 years later, in 2031. Given the temporary slowdown in global warming between 2000 and 2014, and recent initialized decadal predictions suggestive of a turnaround in the IPO, a sustained period of rapid temperature rise might be underway. In that case, the world will reach the 1.5C level of warming several years sooner than if the negative IPO phase persists.

**Plain Language Summary**

Global temperature is rapidly approaching the 1.5C Paris target. In this study, we find that in the absence of external cooling influences, such as volcanic eruptions, the midpoint of the spread of temperature projections exceeds the 1.5C target before 2029, based on temperatures relative to 18501900. We find that the phase of the Interdecadal Pacific Oscillation (IPO), a slow-moving natural oscillation in the climate system, will regulate the rate at which global temperature approaches the 1.5C level. A transition to the positive phase of the IPO would lead to a projected exceedance of the target centered around 2026. If the Pacific Ocean remains in its negative phase, however, the projections are centered on reaching the target around 5 years later, in 2031. Given the temporary slowdown in global warming between 2000 and 2014, and recent climate model predictions suggestive of a turnaround in the IPO, a sustained period of rapid temperature rise might be underway. In that case, the world will reach the 1.5C level of warming several years sooner than if the negative IPO phase persists.

Related Material(s):

- Study (open access): [Initialized decadal prediction for transition to positive phase of the Interdecadal Pacific Oscillation](https://www.nature.com/articles/ncomms11718) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Global temperatures could break through the 1.5C barrier negotiated at the Paris conference as early as 2026 if a slow-moving, natural climate driver known as the Interdecadal Pacific Oscillation (IPO) has, as suspected, moved into a positive phase. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-09 19:57:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Study (open access) | Actively evolving subglacial conduits and eskers initiate ice shelf channels at an Antarctic grounding line </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-09 18:35:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-09 09:25:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Pretty sure the example had nothing to do with drinking anything, but everything to do with demonstrating the contribution of sea ice to sea level rise. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Report | Rethinking Transportation 2020-2030: The Disruption of Transportation and the Collapse of the ICE Vehicle and Oil Industries </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-09 08:51:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Forecast Podcast | Climate economics with Sol Hsiang </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-09 08:19:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Warm Regards Podcast | Talking mammoths, timescales, and rewilding with "Welcome to Pleistocene Park" </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-09 08:15:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-09 07:32:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's only true if you use ice and a glass of fresh water. It's not true if you use ice (fresh water) and salt water (different densities). That being said, the resulting increase in sea level rise from melting sea ice is effectively negligible. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-09 07:30:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Minor technicality. Sea ice *does* contribute to sea level rise (different density between fresh water and salt water resulting from brine rejection during formation of the sea ice), it's just that the contribution is so minuscule it's effectively negligible. As the sea ice melts (fresh water) it lowers the salinity, which lowers the density and therefore increases the volume. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-09 07:21:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The terrestrial biosphere can only take up so much CO2, it has a finite size. (1) We are not only outpacing its ability to take up emissions by not reducing our emissions but (2) the carbon sink that is the terrestrial biosphere is rapidly saturating. That leaves the oceans, and as they continue to warm (becoming more acidic in the process) their ability to uptake CO2 emissions also slows with time. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-09 06:01:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Study: [Trajectories toward the 1.5C Paris target: Modulation by the Interdecadal Pacific Oscillation](http://onlinelibrary.wiley.com/doi/10.1002/2017GL073480/full)
___

**Abstract**

Global temperature is rapidly approaching the 1.5C Paris target. In the absence of external cooling influences, such as volcanic eruptions, temperature projections are centered on a breaching of the 1.5C target, relative to 18501900, before 2029. The phase of the Interdecadal Pacific Oscillation (IPO) will regulate the rate at which mean temperature approaches the 1.5C level. A transition to the positive phase of the IPO would lead to a projected exceedance of the target centered around 2026. If the Pacific Ocean remains in its negative decadal phase, the target will be reached around 5 years later, in 2031. Given the temporary slowdown in global warming between 2000 and 2014, and recent initialized decadal predictions suggestive of a turnaround in the IPO, a sustained period of rapid temperature rise might be underway. In that case, the world will reach the 1.5C level of warming several years sooner than if the negative IPO phase persists.

**Plain Language Summary**

Global temperature is rapidly approaching the 1.5C Paris target. In this study, we find that in the absence of external cooling influences, such as volcanic eruptions, the midpoint of the spread of temperature projections exceeds the 1.5C target before 2029, based on temperatures relative to 18501900. We find that the phase of the Interdecadal Pacific Oscillation (IPO), a slow-moving natural oscillation in the climate system, will regulate the rate at which global temperature approaches the 1.5C level. A transition to the positive phase of the IPO would lead to a projected exceedance of the target centered around 2026. If the Pacific Ocean remains in its negative phase, however, the projections are centered on reaching the target around 5 years later, in 2031. Given the temporary slowdown in global warming between 2000 and 2014, and recent climate model predictions suggestive of a turnaround in the IPO, a sustained period of rapid temperature rise might be underway. In that case, the world will reach the 1.5C level of warming several years sooner than if the negative IPO phase persists. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Global temperature is rapidly approaching the 1.5C Paris target. A new study finds a transition to the positive phase of the Interdecadal Pacific Oscillation (IPO), a slow-moving natural oscillation in the climate system, would lead to a projected exceedance of the target 1.5C Paris target by 2026 </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-09 05:59:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-09 02:58:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm sharing this to point out that in 1975, 32 years prior to the IPCC's 4^(th) assessment report (published in 2007 - which also finds an [ECS of 3C](https://www.ipcc.ch/publications_and_data/ar4/wg1/en/tssts-6-4-2.html)) Manabe and Wetherald had arrived at a climate sensitivity of +2.93C in their GCM ([table 1](http://journals.ametsoc.org/doi/pdf/10.1175/1520-0469%281975%29032%3C0003%3ATEODTC%3E2.0.CO%3B2))(pdf). Ten years on from the IPCC's AR4, another recent study still finds [ECS to be 2.9C](https://www.nature.com/nclimate/journal/v7/n5/full/nclimate3278.html).

I'd be interested in hearing why 'lukewarmers' have opted for lower end values, and why 'alarmists' have opted for higher end values. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Study (open access) | The Effects of Doubling the CO2 Concentration on the climate of a General Circulation Model - published in 1975 </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-09 02:44:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-09 01:39:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Indeed, and this trend in terrestrial sinks turning from sinks to sources has long since been predicted^[1](http://i.imgur.com/Tj9iJg0.jpg) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-08 21:38:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Study: [Carbon dioxide sources from Alaska driven by increasing early winter respiration from Arctic tundra](http://www.pnas.org/content/early/2017/05/02/1618567114)
___

**Significance**

Rising arctic temperatures could mobilize reservoirs of soil organic carbon trapped in permafrost. We present the first quantitative evidence for large, regional-scale early winter respiration flux, which more than offsets carbon uptake in summer in the Arctic. Data from the National Oceanic and Atmospheric Administrations Barrow station indicate that October through December emissions of CO2 from surrounding tundra increased by 73% since 1975, supporting the view that rising temperatures have made Arctic ecosystems a net source of CO2. It has been known for over 50 y that tundra soils remain unfrozen and biologically active in early winter, yet many Earth System Models do not correctly represent this phenomenon or the associated CO2 emissions, and hence they underestimate current, and likely future, CO2 emissions under climate change.

**Abstract**

High-latitude ecosystems have the capacity to release large amounts of carbon dioxide (CO2) to the atmosphere in response to increasing temperatures, representing a potentially significant positive feedback within the climate system. Here, we combine aircraft and tower observations of atmospheric CO2 with remote sensing data and meteorological products to derive temporally and spatially resolved year-round CO2 fluxes across Alaska during 20122014. We find that tundra ecosystems were a net source of CO2 to the atmosphere annually, with especially high rates of respiration during early winter (October through December). Long-term records at Barrow, AK, suggest that CO2 emission rates from North Slope tundra have increased during the October through December period by 73%  11% since 1975, and are correlated with rising summer temperatures. Together, these results imply increasing early winter respiration and net annual emission of CO2 in Alaska, in response to climate warming. Our results provide evidence that the decadal-scale increase in the amplitude of the CO2 seasonal cycle may be linked with increasing biogenic emissions in the Arctic, following the growing season. Early winter respiration was not well simulated by the Earth System Models used to forecast future carbon fluxes in recent climate assessments. Therefore, these assessments may underestimate the carbon release from Arctic soils in response to a warming climate.

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Tundra May Be Shifting Alaska to Put Out More Carbon Than It Stores, Study Says </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-08 21:37:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Study (pre-print)| Re-calibration of Arctic sea ice extent datasets using Arctic surface air temperature records (pdf) </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-08 19:03:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-08 18:54:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Study (open access): [Neutralizing misinformation through inoculation: Exposing misleading argumentation techniques reduces their influence](http://journals.plos.org/plosone/article?id=10.1371/journal.pone.0175799)
___

**Abstract**

Misinformation can undermine a well-functioning democracy. For example, public misconceptions about climate change can lead to lowered acceptance of the reality of climate change and lowered support for mitigation policies. This study experimentally explored the impact of misinformation about climate change and tested several pre-emptive interventions designed to reduce the influence of misinformation. We found that false-balance media coverage (giving contrarian views equal voice with climate scientists) lowered perceived consensus overall, although the effect was greater among free-market supporters. Likewise, misinformation that confuses people about the level of scientific agreement regarding anthropogenic global warming (AGW) had a polarizing effect, with free-market supporters reducing their acceptance of AGW and those with low free-market support increasing their acceptance of AGW. However, we found that inoculating messages that (1) explain the flawed argumentation technique used in the misinformation or that (2) highlight the scientific consensus on climate change were effective in neutralizing those adverse effects of misinformation. We recommend that climate communication messages should take into account ways in which scientific content can be distorted, and include pre-emptive inoculation messages.

Related Material(s):

- Study (open access): [Inoculating the Public against Misinformation about Climate Change](http://onlinelibrary.wiley.com/doi/10.1002/gch2.201600008/full) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> To beat science denial, inoculate against misinformers' tricks: A new study finds that explaining the techniques of science denial makes people resistant to their effects </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-08 18:53:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-08 18:48:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I think you're being misleading in your comment, as the 97% consensus claim has been effectively verified by multiple studies over the decades, see: [Consensus on consensus: a synthesis of consensus estimates on human-caused global warming](http://iopscience.iop.org/article/10.1088/1748-9326/11/4/048002)

Furthermore, there is no consensus among so-called 'skeptics.' Their position has morphed over time from outright denying that warming is occurring, to accepting warming is occurring but stating humans aren't contributing to the warming, to accepting human caused climate change but denying the amount of warming, to accepting the amount of warming but denying its potential impacts.

The problem is that there is no debate among scientists, but having a debate in media gives the illusions that the science *is* debated. This doesn't result from the scientific literature, it results from misinformation campaigns funding climate science denial, see for example: [Institutionalizing delay](http://drexel.edu/now/archive/2013/December/Climate-Change/).  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The New York Times should not have hired climate change bullshitter Bret Stephens </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-08 08:33:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> E.P.A. Dismisses Members of Major Scientific Review Board </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-08 04:07:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-07 19:13:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Study: [Upper Ocean O2 trends: 1958-2015](http://onlinelibrary.wiley.com/doi/10.1002/2017GL073613/abstract)
___

**Abstract**

Historic observations of dissolved oxygen (O2) in the ocean are analyzed to quantify multi-decadal trends and variability from 1958 to 2015. Additional quality control is applied and the resultant oxygen anomaly field is used to quantify upper ocean O2 trends at global and hemispheric scales. A widespread negative O2 trend is beginning to emerge from the envelope of interannual variability. Ocean reanalysis data is used to evaluate relationships with changes in ocean heat content (OHC) and oxygen solubility (O2,sat). Global O2 decline is evident after the 1980s, accompanied by an increase in global OHC. The global upper ocean O2 inventory (0-1,000m) changed at the rate of -243124TmolO2 per decade. Further, the O2 inventory is negatively correlated with the OHC (r=-0.86; 0-1,000m) and the regression coefficient of O2 to OHC is approximately 8.20.66 nmol O2 J^1 , on the same order of magnitude as the simulated O2-heat relationship typically found in ocean climate models. Variability and trends in the observed upper ocean O2 concentration are dominated by the Apparent Oxygen Utilization (AOU) component with relatively small contributions from O2,sat. This indicates that changing ocean circulation, mixing and/or biochemical processes, rather than the direct thermally-induced solubility effects, are the primary drivers for the observed O2 changes. The spatial patterns of the multi-decadal trend include regions of enhanced ocean deoxygenation including the subpolar North Pacific, eastern boundary upwelling systems and tropical oxygen minimum zones. Further studies are warranted to understand and attribute the global O2 trends and their regional expressions. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> A new analysis of decades of data on oceans across the globe has revealed that the amount of dissolved oxygen contained in the water  an important measure of ocean health  has been declining for more than 20 years </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-07 19:12:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-07 19:06:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Study (open access): [The million-year evolution of the glacial trimline in the southernmost Ellsworth Mountains, Antarctica](http://www.sciencedirect.com/science/article/pii/S0012821X17301851)
___

**Abstract**

An elevated erosional trimline in the heart of West Antarctica in the Ellsworth Mountains tells of thicker ice in the past and represents an important yet ambiguous stage in the evolution of the Antarctic Ice Sheet. Here we analyse the geomorphology of massifs in the southernmost Heritage Range where the surfaces associated with the trimline are overlain by surficial deposits that have the potential to be dated through cosmogenic nuclide analysis. Analysis of 100 rock samples reveals that some clasts have been exposed on glacially moulded surfaces for 1.4 Ma and perhaps more than 3.5 Ma, while others reflect fluctuations in thickness during Quaternary glacial cycles. Modelling the age of the glacially moulded bedrock surface based on cosmogenic 10Be, 26Al and 21Ne concentrations from a depth-profile indicates a minimum exposure age of 2.12.6 Ma. We conclude that the glacially eroded surfaces adjacent to the trimline predate the Last Glacial Maximum and indeed the Quaternary. Since erosion was by warm-based ice near an ice-sheet upper margin, we suggest it first occurred during the early glaciations of Antarctica before the stepped cooling of the mid-Miocene at 14 Ma. This was a time when the interior Antarctic continent had summers warm enough for tundra vegetation to grow and for mountain glaciers to consist of ice at the pressure melting point. During these milder conditions, and subsequently, erosion of glacial troughs is likely to have lowered the ice-sheet surface in relation to the mountains. This means that the range of orbitally induced cyclic fluctuations in ice thickness have progressively been confined to lower elevations. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Antarctic study sheds light on central ice sheet: Central parts of Antarcticas ice sheet have been stable for millions of years, from a time when conditions were considerably warmer than now, research suggests. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-07 19:05:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-07 19:02:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Study: [Upper Ocean O2 trends: 1958-2015](http://onlinelibrary.wiley.com/doi/10.1002/2017GL073613/abstract)
___

**Abstract**

Historic observations of dissolved oxygen (O2) in the ocean are analyzed to quantify multi-decadal trends and variability from 1958 to 2015. Additional quality control is applied and the resultant oxygen anomaly field is used to quantify upper ocean O2 trends at global and hemispheric scales. A widespread negative O2 trend is beginning to emerge from the envelope of interannual variability. Ocean reanalysis data is used to evaluate relationships with changes in ocean heat content (OHC) and oxygen solubility (O2,sat). Global O2 decline is evident after the 1980s, accompanied by an increase in global OHC. The global upper ocean O2 inventory (0-1,000m) changed at the rate of -243124TmolO2 per decade. Further, the O2 inventory is negatively correlated with the OHC (r=-0.86; 0-1,000m) and the regression coefficient of O2 to OHC is approximately 8.20.66 nmol O2 J^1 , on the same order of magnitude as the simulated O2-heat relationship typically found in ocean climate models. Variability and trends in the observed upper ocean O2 concentration are dominated by the Apparent Oxygen Utilization (AOU) component with relatively small contributions from O2,sat. This indicates that changing ocean circulation, mixing and/or biochemical processes, rather than the direct thermally-induced solubility effects, are the primary drivers for the observed O2 changes. The spatial patterns of the multi-decadal trend include regions of enhanced ocean deoxygenation including the subpolar North Pacific, eastern boundary upwelling systems and tropical oxygen minimum zones. Further studies are warranted to understand and attribute the global O2 trends and their regional expressions. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> A new analysis of decades of data on oceans across the globe has revealed that the amount of dissolved oxygen contained in the water  an important measure of ocean health  has been declining for more than 20 years </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-07 19:00:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-07 09:10:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Geological Society, London, Memoirs Vol. 46, 2016: [Atlas of Submarine Glacial Landforms: Modern, Quaternary and Ancient](http://mem.lyellcollection.org/content/46/1.toc) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> New atlas provides highest resolution imagery of the Polar Regions seafloor </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-07 09:08:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Methane Mystery Gets More Muddled </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-07 03:55:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-07 03:51:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> From the article itself:

"Prior to this [the Mid Ordovician] the Earth was exposed to a prolonged super-greenhouse with sea surface temperatures estimated above 40 degree Celsius. Thus, seriously affecting the ability of life to evolve and diversify. The researchers therefore speculate that the sudden emergence of icehouse conditions brought about fundamental changes in ocean circulation, instigating thermohaline circulation in the oceans.

Today this thermohaline 'pump' has a fundamental importance with respect to bioproductivity in the oceans. Thus, back in the Ordovician, an initiation of this pump which circulates warm surface waters with cold bottom waters could have sparked a massive increase in bioproductivity thereby facilitating the Great Ordovician Biodiversification Event." </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-07 01:06:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Study (open access): [Onset of main Phanerozoic marine radiation sparked by emerging Mid Ordovician icehouse](https://www.nature.com/articles/srep18884)
___

**Abstract**

The Great Ordovician Biodiversification Event (GOBE) was the most rapid and sustained increase in marine Phanerozoic biodiversity. What generated this biotic response across Palaeozoic seascapes is a matter of debate; several intrinsic and extrinsic drivers have been suggested. One is Ordovician climate, which in recent years has undergone a paradigm shift from a text-book example of an extended greenhouse to an interval with transient cooling intervals  at least during the Late Ordovician. Here, we show the first unambiguous evidence for a sudden Mid Ordovician icehouse, comparable in magnitude to the Quaternary glaciations. We further demonstrate the initiation of this icehouse to coincide with the onset of the GOBE. This finding is based on both abiotic and biotic proxies obtained from the most comprehensive geochemical and palaeobiological dataset yet collected through this interval. We argue that the icehouse conditions increased latitudinal and bathymetrical temperature and oxygen gradients initiating an Early Palaeozoic Great Ocean Conveyor Belt. This fuelled the GOBE, as upwelling zones created new ecospace for the primary producers. A subsequent rise in 13C ratios known as the Middle Darriwilian Isotopic Carbon Excursion (MDICE) may reflect a global response to increased bioproductivity encouraged by the onset of the GOBE. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> A new study finds the first unambiguous evidence for a sudden Mid Ordovician icehouse, comparable in magnitude to the Quaternary glaciations, fueled the Great Ordovician Biodiversification Event - the most rapid and sustained increase in marine Phanerozoic biodiversity </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-07 01:06:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-07 00:58:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Study (open access): [Onset of main Phanerozoic marine radiation sparked by emerging Mid Ordovician icehouse](https://www.nature.com/articles/srep18884)
___

**Abstract**

The Great Ordovician Biodiversification Event (GOBE) was the most rapid and sustained increase in marine Phanerozoic biodiversity. What generated this biotic response across Palaeozoic seascapes is a matter of debate; several intrinsic and extrinsic drivers have been suggested. One is Ordovician climate, which in recent years has undergone a paradigm shift from a text-book example of an extended greenhouse to an interval with transient cooling intervals  at least during the Late Ordovician. Here, we show the first unambiguous evidence for a sudden Mid Ordovician icehouse, comparable in magnitude to the Quaternary glaciations. We further demonstrate the initiation of this icehouse to coincide with the onset of the GOBE. This finding is based on both abiotic and biotic proxies obtained from the most comprehensive geochemical and palaeobiological dataset yet collected through this interval. We argue that the icehouse conditions increased latitudinal and bathymetrical temperature and oxygen gradients initiating an Early Palaeozoic Great Ocean Conveyor Belt. This fuelled the GOBE, as upwelling zones created new ecospace for the primary producers. A subsequent rise in 13C ratios known as the Middle Darriwilian Isotopic Carbon Excursion (MDICE) may reflect a global response to increased bioproductivity encouraged by the onset of the GOBE. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> A new study finds the first unambiguous evidence for a sudden Mid Ordovician icehouse, comparable in magnitude to the Quaternary glaciations, fueled the Great Ordovician Biodiversification Event - the most rapid and sustained increase in marine Phanerozoic biodiversity </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-07 00:57:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Average surface air temperatures for April 2017 </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-06 00:33:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> 15 years of NASA satellite cloud measurements finds that clouds worldwide show no definitive trend during this period toward decreasing or increasing in height. The new study updates an earlier analysis of the first 10 years of the same data that suggested cloud heights might be getting lower </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-05 20:27:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-05 09:30:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Study (open access): [Monitoring and Projecting Snow on Hawaii Island](http://onlinelibrary.wiley.com/doi/10.1002/2016EF000478/full)
___

**Abstract**

The highest mountain peaks on Hawaii Island are snow covered for part of almost every year. This snow has esthetic and recreational value as well as cultural significance for residents and visitors. Thus far there have been almost no systematic observations of snowfall, snow cover or snow depth in Hawaii. Here we use satellite observations to construct a daily index of Hawaii Island snow cover starting from 2000. The seasonal mean of our index displays large interannual variations that are correlated with the seasonal mean freezing level and frequency of trade wind inversions as determined from nearby balloon soundings. Our snow cover index provides a diagnostic for monitoring climate variability and trends within the extensive area of the globe dominated by the North Pacific trade wind meteorological regime.

We have also conducted simulations of the Hawaii climate with a regional atmospheric model. Retrospective simulations for 1990-2015 were run with boundary conditions prescribed from gridded observational analyses. Simulations for the end of 21st century employed boundary conditions based on global climate model projections that included standard scenarios for anticipated anthropogenic climate forcing. The future projections indicate that snowfall will nearly disappear by the end of the current century. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Hawaiian mountains could lose snow cover by 2100 </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-05 09:29:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-05 09:27:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Relevant tweet with 'gif' via [R Iestyn Woolway](https://twitter.com/riwoolway/status/853646420741586945) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Study (open access) | Warming of Central European lakes and their response to the 1980s climate regime shift </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-05 09:25:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> De Beers Says It Could Operate Carbon-Neutral Mine Within Half a Decade </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-05 04:50:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-05 03:55:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Study (open access): [Measurement of the 13C isotopic signature of methane emissions from northern European wetlands](http://onlinelibrary.wiley.com/doi/10.1002/2016GB005504/full)
___

**Abstract**

Isotopic data provide powerful constraints on regional and global methane emissions and their source profiles. However, inverse modeling of spatially resolved methane flux is currently constrained by a lack of information on the variability of source isotopic signatures. In this study, isotopic signatures of emissions in the Fennoscandian Arctic have been determined in chambers over wetland, in the air 0.3 to 3m above the wetland surface and by aircraft sampling from 100m above wetlands up to the stratosphere. Overall, the methane flux to atmosphere has a coherent 13C isotopic signature of 711, measured in situ on the ground in wetlands. This is in close agreement with 13C isotopic signatures of local and regional methane increments measured by aircraft campaigns flying through air masses containing elevated methane mole fractions. In contrast, results from wetlands in Canadian boreal forest farther south gave isotopic signatures of 671. Wetland emissions dominate the local methane source measured over the European Arctic in summer. Chamber measurements demonstrate a highly variable methane flux and isotopic signature, but the results from air sampling within wetland areas show that emissions mix rapidly immediately above the wetland surface and methane emissions reaching the wider atmosphere do indeed have strongly coherent C isotope signatures. The study suggests that for boreal wetlands (60N) global and regional modeling can use an isotopic signature of 71 to apportion sources more accurately, but there is much need for further measurements over other wetlands regions to verify this. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Aircraft measurements confirm that methane emissions from northern European wetlands exhibit a uniform regional carbon isotopic signature, despite considerable ground-level heterogeneity </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-05 03:53:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Bret Stephens Takes On Climate Change. Readers Unleash Their Fury. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-05 02:48:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-04 04:52:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Study: [Does It Matter if the Consensus on Anthropogenic Global Warming Is 97% or 99.99%?](http://journals.sagepub.com/doi/abs/10.1177/0270467617702781?journalCode=bsta )
___

**Abstract**

Cook et al. reported a 97% scientific consensus on anthropogenic global warming (AGW), based on a study of 11,944 abstracts in peer-reviewed science journals. Powell claims that the Cook et al. methodology was flawed and that the true consensus is virtually unanimous at 99.99%. Powells method underestimates the level of disagreement because it relies on finding explicit rejection statements as well as the assumption that abstracts without a stated position endorse the consensus. Cook et al.s survey of the papers authors revealed that papers may express disagreement with AGW despite the absence of a rejection statement in the abstract. Surveys reveal a large gap between the public perception of the degree of scientific consensus on AGW and reality. We argue that it is the size of this gap, rather than the small difference between 97% and 99.99%, that matters in communicating the true state of scientific opinion to the public. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Is the climate consensus 97%, 99.9%, or is plate tectonics a hoax? A new study argues the 97% climate consensus estimate is too low, while deniers claim its too high </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-04 04:51:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-04 03:13:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Study: [Reconciling controversies about the global warming hiatus](https://www.nature.com/nature/journal/v545/n7652/full/nature22315.html)
___

**Abstract**

Between about 1998 and 2012, a time that coincided with political negotiations for preventing climate change, the surface of Earth seemed hardly to warm. This phenomenon, often termed the global warming hiatus, caused doubt in the public mind about how well anthropogenic climate change and natural variability are understood. Here we show that apparently contradictory conclusions stem from different definitions of hiatus and from different datasets. A combination of changes in forcing, uptake of heat by the oceans, natural variability and incomplete observational coverage reconciles models and data. Combined with stronger recent warming trends in newer datasets, we are now more confident than ever that human influence is dominant in long-term warming. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Detailed look at the global warming hiatus again confirms that humans are changing the climate </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-04 03:12:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-04 03:06:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Study (access token): [Reconciling controversies about the global warming hiatus](https://www.nature.com/articles/nature22315.epdf?referrer_access_token=hympehHIyVLDFKYScpDhZdRgN0jAjWel9jnR3ZoTv0NuFtYPLl1PUnqxUYbpB1uVru_rIjRyseUxK8YNRXQS46Tpa21x-vwjLraHJV2WWDOd7rzP-5_uGJHWoKN87dtIDyBdNky75pFNm3b1kPsZxFgLQCm1UFW4NOEQe9y-d0LIIFM51eerv_KMOolbXA-_zYlLSGtwkRvxvaAL_iZ_ahmkqUVIQ9DKmzi7uZMfF0E_AB4nI0NGR9ysvX-gKcKiacdVJnGlupBJgpzyxunH5fNJrXpPbKMXCsMEWMZb5KQ%3D tracking_referrer=www.spiegel.de utm_content=buffer2df61 utm_medium=social utm_source=twitter.com utm_campaign=buffer)
___

**Abstract**

Between about 1998 and 2012, a time that coincided with political negotiations for preventing climate change, the surface of Earth seemed hardly to warm. This phenomenon, often termed the global warming hiatus, caused doubt in the public mind about how well anthropogenic climate change and natural variability are understood. Here we show that apparently contradictory conclusions stem from different definitions of hiatus and from different datasets. A combination of changes in forcing, uptake of heat by the oceans, natural variability and incomplete observational coverage reconciles models and data. Combined with stronger recent warming trends in newer datasets, we are now more confident than ever that human influence is dominant in long-term warming. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Detailed look at the global warming hiatus again confirms that humans are changing the climate </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-04 03:05:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-02 18:01:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Study (open access): [Quantifying the trade-off between carbon sequestration and albedo in midlatitude and high-latitude North American forests](http://onlinelibrary.wiley.com/doi/10.1002/2016GL071459/full)
___

**Abstract**

Afforestation is a viable and widely practiced method of sequestering carbon dioxide from the atmosphere. However, because of a change in surface albedo, placement of less reflective forests can cause an increase in net-absorbed radiation and localized surface warming. This effect is enhanced in northern high latitudes where the presence of snow cover exacerbates the albedo difference. Regions where afforestation could provide a climate benefit are determined by comparing net ecosystem production and net radiation differences from afforestation in midlatitude and high latitude of North America. Using the dynamic vegetation model Integrated Biosphere Simulator, agricultural version (Agro-IBIS), we find a boundary through North America where afforestation results in a positive equivalent carbon balance (cooling) to the south, and a negative equivalent carbon balance (warming) to the north. Including the effects of stand age and fraction cover affect whether a site contributes to mitigating global warming. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Although it might be beneficial to plant trees in low-latitude (near the equator) regions, planting trees elsewhere could actually produce more warming. A new study quantifies the trade-off between carbon sequestration and albedo in midlatitude and high-latitude North American forests </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-02 18:00:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-02 17:59:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Study (open access): [Quantifying the trade-off between carbon sequestration and albedo in midlatitude and high-latitude North American forests](http://onlinelibrary.wiley.com/doi/10.1002/2016GL071459/full)
___

**Abstract**

Afforestation is a viable and widely practiced method of sequestering carbon dioxide from the atmosphere. However, because of a change in surface albedo, placement of less reflective forests can cause an increase in net-absorbed radiation and localized surface warming. This effect is enhanced in northern high latitudes where the presence of snow cover exacerbates the albedo difference. Regions where afforestation could provide a climate benefit are determined by comparing net ecosystem production and net radiation differences from afforestation in midlatitude and high latitude of North America. Using the dynamic vegetation model Integrated Biosphere Simulator, agricultural version (Agro-IBIS), we find a boundary through North America where afforestation results in a positive equivalent carbon balance (cooling) to the south, and a negative equivalent carbon balance (warming) to the north. Including the effects of stand age and fraction cover affect whether a site contributes to mitigating global warming. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Although it might be beneficial to plant trees in low-latitude (near the equator) regions, planting trees elsewhere could actually produce more warming. A new study quantifies the trade-off between carbon sequestration and albedo in midlatitude and high-latitude North American forests </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-02 17:58:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> David Roberts on Twitter: "My piece on NYT hiring Stephens is punishingly long, and yet ... there's a point I feel I didn't emphasize sufficiently. Ergo: tweetstorm!" </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-02 17:48:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Arctic Knowledge of the U.S. Public </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-02 17:45:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Opinion | Answering Bret Stephens on Climate Science </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-02 01:57:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Study (open access) | Anatomy of Heinrich Layer 1 and its role in the last deglaciation </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-30 17:10:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-30 06:00:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Study (open access): [Temperature and rainfall interact to control carbon cycling in tropical forests](http://onlinelibrary.wiley.com/doi/10.1111/ele.12765/full)
___

**Abstract**

Tropical forests dominate global terrestrial carbon (C) exchange, and recent droughts in the Amazon Basin have contributed to short-term declines in terrestrial carbon dioxide uptake and storage. However, the effects of longer-term climate variability on tropical forest carbon dynamics are still not well understood. We synthesised field data from more than 150 tropical forest sites to explore how climate regulates tropical forest aboveground net primary productivity (ANPP) and organic matter decomposition, and combined those data with two existing databases to explore climate  C relationships globally. While previous analyses have focused on the effects of either temperature or rainfall on ANPP, our results highlight the importance of interactions between temperature and rainfall on the C cycle. In cool forests ( 20 C), high rainfall slowed rates of C cycling, but in warm tropical forests ( 20 C) it consistently enhanced both ANPP and decomposition. At the global scale, our analysis showed an increase in ANPP with rainfall in relatively warm sites, inconsistent with declines in ANPP with rainfall reported previously. Overall, our results alter our understanding of climate  C cycle relationships, with high precipitation accelerating rates of C exchange with the atmosphere in the most productive biome on earth. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Conventional wisdom has held that forest growth will dramatically slow with high levels of rainfall. But CU Boulder researchers this month turned that assumption on its head with an unprecedented review of data from 150 forests that concluded just the opposite. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-30 05:55:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-30 05:47:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Study (open access): [Holocene winter climate variability in Central and Eastern Europe](https://www.nature.com/articles/s41598-017-01397-w)
___

**Abstract**

Among abundant reconstructions of Holocene climate in Europe, only a handful has addressed winter conditions, and most of these are restricted in length and/or resolution. Here we present a record of late autumn through early winter air temperature and moisture source changes in East-Central Europe for the Holocene, based on stable isotopic analysis of an ice core recovered from a cave in the Romanian Carpathian Mountains. During the past 10,000 years, reconstructed temperature changes followed insolation, with a minimum in the early Holocene, followed by gradual and continuous increase towards the mid-to-late-Holocene peak (between 4-2kcal BP), and finally by a decrease after 0.8kcal BP towards a minimum during the Little Ice Age (AD 13001850). Reconstructed early Holocene atmospheric circulation patterns were similar to those characteristics of the negative phase of the North Atlantic Oscillation (NAO), while in the late Holocene they resembled those prevailing in the positive NAO phase. The transition between the two regimes occurred abruptly at around 4.7kcal BP. Remarkably, the widespread cooling at 8.2kcal BP is not seen very well as a temperature change, but as a shift in moisture source, suggesting weaker westerlies and increased Mediterranean cyclones penetrating northward at this time. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Ice cores drilled from a glacier in a cave in Transylvania offer new evidence of how Europe's winter weather and climate patterns fluctuated during the last 10,000 years </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-30 05:47:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Huge Arctic report ups estimates of sea-level rise: Report prompts warnings that the polar region is 'unravelling'. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-30 02:58:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Study (open access) | Rapid decline in river icings detected in Arctic Alaska: Implications for a changing hydrologic cycle and river ecosystems </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-28 08:58:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-28 08:58:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Study: [The extreme El Nio of 20152016 and the end of global warming hiatus](http://onlinelibrary.wiley.com/doi/10.1002/2017GL072908/abstract)
___

**Abstract**

Slower rates of increase in global mean surface temperature (GMST) after 2000, dubbed global warming hiatus, recently gave way to a rapid temperature rise. This rise coincided with persistent warm conditions in the equatorial Pacific between March 2014 and May 2016, which peaked as the 2015 extreme El Nio. Here we show that the El NioSouthern Oscillation (ENSO) tightly controls interannual variations in atmospheric heating rate in the tropics (r  0.9), allowing us to construct a simple, physically based model of GMST variations that incorporates greenhouse gas emissions, ENSO forcing, and stratospheric sulfate aerosols produced by volcanoes. The model closely reproduces GMST changes since 1880, including the global warming hiatus and the subsequent temperature rise. Our results confirm that weak El Nio activity, rather than volcanic eruptions, was the cause of the hiatus, while the rapid temperature rise is due to atmospheric heat release during 20142016 El Nio conditions concurrent with the continuing global warming trend. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Weak El Nio activity, rather than volcanic eruptions, linked to slower rates of increase in global mean surface temperature (GMST) after 2000, while the rapid temperature rise is due to atmospheric heat release during 20142016 El Nio conditions concurrent with the continuing global warming trend </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-28 08:56:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-28 02:25:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Peer-reviewed papers in scientifically credible journals have contributed far more than any ad hominem ever did. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-27 08:23:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Study (open access): [Mobile measurement of methane emissions from natural gas developments in Northeastern British Columbia, Canada](http://www.atmos-chem-phys-discuss.net/acp-2017-109/)
___

**Abstract**

North American leaders recently committed to reducing methane emissions from the oil and gas sector, but information on current emissions from Canadian unconventional developments is lacking. This study examined the incidence of methane in an area of unconventional natural gas development in northwestern Canada. In August to September 2015 we completed almost 8000 km of vehicle-based survey campaigns on public roads dissecting developments that mainly access the Montney formation in northeastern British Columbia. Six survey routes were repeated 36 times and brought us past over 1600 unique well pads and facilities developed by more than 50 different operators. To attribute on-road plumes to infrastructural sources we used gas signatures of residual excess concentrations (anomalies above background) less than 500 m downwind from infrastructural sources. All results represent emissions greater than our minimum detection limit of 0.59 g/s at our average detection distance (319 m). Unlike many other developments in the US for which methane measurements have been reported recently, the methane concentrations we measured at surface were close to normal atmospheric levels, except inside natural gas plumes. Roughly 47 % of active wells emitted methane-rich plumes above our minimum detection limit. Abandoned and under-development well sites also emitted methane-rich plumes, but the incidence rate was below that of producing wells. Multiple sites that pre-date the recent unconventional Montney development were found to be emitting, and in general we observed that older infrastructure tended to emit more often (per unit) with comparable severity in terms of measured excess concentrations on-road. We also observed emissions from facilities of various types that were highly repeatable. Emission patterns in this area were best explained by infrastructure age and type. Extrapolating our results across the Montney development, we estimate that the emission sources we located (emitting at a rate  0.59 g/s) contribute more than 111,800 tonnes of methane annually to the atmosphere. This value exceeds reported bottom-up estimates of 78,000 tonnes for all oil and gas sector sources in British Columbia, of which the Montney represents about 55 % of production. The results also demonstrate that mobile surveys could be used to exhaustively screen developments for super-emitters, because without our intensive 6-fold replication we could have used single-pass sampling to screen 80 % of Montney-related infrastructure. This is the first bottom-up study of fugitive emissions in the Canadian energy sector, and these results can be used to inform policy development in an era of methane emission reduction efforts. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Methane pollution from B.C.s oil, gas industry higher than provincial estimates </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-27 08:22:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-27 08:21:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Study (open access): [Mobile measurement of methane emissions from natural gas developments in Northeastern British Columbia, Canada](http://www.atmos-chem-phys-discuss.net/acp-2017-109/)
___

**Abstract**

North American leaders recently committed to reducing methane emissions from the oil and gas sector, but information on current emissions from Canadian unconventional developments is lacking. This study examined the incidence of methane in an area of unconventional natural gas development in northwestern Canada. In August to September 2015 we completed almost 8000 km of vehicle-based survey campaigns on public roads dissecting developments that mainly access the Montney formation in northeastern British Columbia. Six survey routes were repeated 36 times and brought us past over 1600 unique well pads and facilities developed by more than 50 different operators. To attribute on-road plumes to infrastructural sources we used gas signatures of residual excess concentrations (anomalies above background) less than 500m downwind from infrastructural sources. All results represent emissions greater than our minimum detection limit of 0.59g/s at our average detection distance (319m). Unlike many other developments in the US for which methane measurements have been reported recently, the methane concentrations we measured at surface were close to normal atmospheric levels, except inside natural gas plumes. Roughly 47% of active wells emitted methane-rich plumes above our minimum detection limit. Abandoned and under-development well sites also emitted methane-rich plumes, but the incidence rate was below that of producing wells. Multiple sites that pre-date the recent unconventional Montney development were found to be emitting, and in general we observed that older infrastructure tended to emit more often (per unit) with comparable severity in terms of measured excess concentrations on-road. We also observed emissions from facilities of various types that were highly repeatable. Emission patterns in this area were best explained by infrastructure age and type. Extrapolating our results across the Montney development, we estimate that the emission sources we located (emitting at a rate 0.59g/s) contribute more than 111,800 tonnes of methane annually to the atmosphere. This value exceeds reported bottom-up estimates of 78,000 tonnes for all oil and gas sector sources in British Columbia, of which the Montney represents about 55% of production. The results also demonstrate that mobile surveys could be used to exhaustively screen developments for super-emitters, because without our intensive 6-fold replication we could have used single-pass sampling to screen 80% of Montney-related infrastructure. This is the first bottom-up study of fugitive emissions in the Canadian energy sector, and these results can be used to inform policy development in an era of methane emission reduction efforts. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Methane pollution from B.C.s oil, gas industry higher than provincial estimates </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-27 08:20:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Study (open access) | Constraining the mass balance of East Antarctica </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-27 03:44:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-27 03:42:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Study: [New estimate of the current rate of sea level rise from a sea level budget approach](http://onlinelibrary.wiley.com/doi/10.1002/2017GL073308/abstract)
___

**Abstract**

We revisit the global mean sea level (GMSL) budget during the whole altimetry era (January 1993 to December 2015) using a large number of data sets. The budget approach allows quantifying the TOPEX A altimeter drift (amounting 1.5  0.5 mm/yr over 19931998). Accounting for this correction and using ensemble means for the GMSL and components lead to closure of the sea level budget (trend of the residual time series being 0.0  0.22 mm/yr). The new GMSL rate over January 1993 to December 2015 is now close to 3.0 mm/yr. An important increase of the GMSL rate, of 0.8 mm/yr, is found during the second half of the altimetry era (20042015) compared to the 19932004 time span, mostly due to Greenland mass loss increase and also to slight increase of all other components of the budget. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Sea level rising faster now than during 1990s, new study shows </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-27 03:41:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-27 03:40:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Study: [New estimate of the current rate of sea level rise from a sea level budget approach](http://onlinelibrary.wiley.com/doi/10.1002/2017GL073308/abstract)
___

**Abstract**

We revisit the global mean sea level (GMSL) budget during the whole altimetry era (January 1993 to December 2015) using a large number of data sets. The budget approach allows quantifying the TOPEX A altimeter drift (amounting 1.5  0.5 mm/yr over 19931998). Accounting for this correction and using ensemble means for the GMSL and components lead to closure of the sea level budget (trend of the residual time series being 0.0  0.22 mm/yr). The new GMSL rate over January 1993 to December 2015 is now close to 3.0 mm/yr. An important increase of the GMSL rate, of 0.8 mm/yr, is found during the second half of the altimetry era (20042015) compared to the 19932004 time span, mostly due to Greenland mass loss increase and also to slight increase of all other components of the budget. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Sea level rising faster now than during 1990s, new study shows </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-27 03:40:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Iceberg 'doodles' trace climate history </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-26 02:54:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-25 15:59:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Arctic Monitoring and Assessment Programme (AMAP) Report(s): http://www.amap.no/ </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The Arctic's quickening thaw is melting the permafrost under buildings and roads from Siberia to Alaska, raising world sea levels and disrupting temperature patterns further south. Arctic warming could have cumulative net costs from 2010-2100 of between $7 trillion and $90 trillion, report finds </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-25 15:56:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> A new and improved surface mass balance data product has just been launched on the Polar Portal. This upgrade to the existing model not only improves the way the snow pack is handled in the model used to calculate surface mass balance, it also extends the data series back to 1980. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-25 15:49:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-25 07:03:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Study (open access): [An englacial hydrologic system of brine within a cold glacier: Blood Falls, McMurdo Dry Valleys, Antarctica](https://www.cambridge.org/core/journals/journal-of-glaciology/article/an-englacial-hydrologic-system-of-brine-within-a-cold-glacier-blood-falls-mcmurdo-dry-valleys-antarctica/B5C197906AD54619AEA26068AD92989A/core-reader)
___

**Abstract**

Taylor Glacier hosts an active englacial hydrologic system that feeds Blood Falls, a supraglacial outflow of iron-rich subglacial brine at the terminus, despite mean annual air temperatures of 17C and limited surface melt. Taylor Glacier is an outlet glacier of the East Antarctic ice sheet that terminates in Lake Bonney, McMurdo Dry Valleys. To image and map the brine feeding Blood Falls, we used radio echo sounding to delineate a subhorizontal zone of englacial brine upstream from Blood Falls and elongated in the ice flow direction. We estimate volumetric brine content in excess of 13% within 2 m of the central axis of this zone, and likely much higher at its center. Brine content decreases, but remains detectable, up to 45 m away along some transects. Hence, we infer a network of subparallel basal crevasses allowing injection of pressurized subglacial brine into the ice. Subglacial brine is routed towards Blood Falls by hydraulic potential gradients associated with deeply incised supraglacial valleys. The brine remains liquid within the subglacial and englacial environments through latent heat of freezing coupled with elevated salt content. Our findings suggest that cold glaciers could support freshwater hydrologic systems through localized warming by latent heat alone. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Researchers solve the century-old mystery of Blood Falls </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-25 07:03:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-25 07:02:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Study (open access): [An englacial hydrologic system of brine within a cold glacier: Blood Falls, McMurdo Dry Valleys, Antarctica](https://www.cambridge.org/core/journals/journal-of-glaciology/article/an-englacial-hydrologic-system-of-brine-within-a-cold-glacier-blood-falls-mcmurdo-dry-valleys-antarctica/B5C197906AD54619AEA26068AD92989A/core-reader)
___

**Abstract**

Taylor Glacier hosts an active englacial hydrologic system that feeds Blood Falls, a supraglacial outflow of iron-rich subglacial brine at the terminus, despite mean annual air temperatures of 17C and limited surface melt. Taylor Glacier is an outlet glacier of the East Antarctic ice sheet that terminates in Lake Bonney, McMurdo Dry Valleys. To image and map the brine feeding Blood Falls, we used radio echo sounding to delineate a subhorizontal zone of englacial brine upstream from Blood Falls and elongated in the ice flow direction. We estimate volumetric brine content in excess of 13% within 2 m of the central axis of this zone, and likely much higher at its center. Brine content decreases, but remains detectable, up to 45 m away along some transects. Hence, we infer a network of subparallel basal crevasses allowing injection of pressurized subglacial brine into the ice. Subglacial brine is routed towards Blood Falls by hydraulic potential gradients associated with deeply incised supraglacial valleys. The brine remains liquid within the subglacial and englacial environments through latent heat of freezing coupled with elevated salt content. Our findings suggest that cold glaciers could support freshwater hydrologic systems through localized warming by latent heat alone. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Researchers solve the century-old mystery of Blood Falls </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-25 07:00:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Climate sensitivity in models consistent with energy budget constraints </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-25 06:57:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Denier vs Scientist on CO2 versus O3 </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-25 06:53:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-24 05:03:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Study (open access): [Large near-term projected snowpack loss over the western United States](https://www.nature.com/articles/ncomms14996)
___

**Abstract**

Peak runoff in streams and rivers of the western United States is strongly influenced by melting of accumulated mountain snowpack. A significant decline in this resource has a direct connection to streamflow, with substantial economic and societal impacts. Observations and reanalyses indicate that between the 1980s and 2000s, there was a 1020% loss in the annual maximum amount of water contained in the regions snowpack. Here we show that this loss is consistent with results from a large ensemble of climate simulations forced with natural and anthropogenic changes, but is inconsistent with simulations forced by natural changes alone. A further loss of up to 60% is projected within the next 30 years. Uncertainties in loss estimates depend on the size and the rate of response to continued anthropogenic forcing and the magnitude and phasing of internal decadal variability. The projected losses have serious implications for the hydropower, municipal and agricultural sectors in the region. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> An international team of scientists has found that up to 20% loss in the annual maximum amount of water contained in the Western United States' mountain snowpack in the last three decades is due to human influences </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-24 05:02:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-24 05:00:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Study (open access): [Large near-term projected snowpack loss over the western United States](https://www.nature.com/articles/ncomms14996)
___

**Abstract**

Peak runoff in streams and rivers of the western United States is strongly influenced by melting of accumulated mountain snowpack. A significant decline in this resource has a direct connection to streamflow, with substantial economic and societal impacts. Observations and reanalyses indicate that between the 1980s and 2000s, there was a 1020% loss in the annual maximum amount of water contained in the regions snowpack. Here we show that this loss is consistent with results from a large ensemble of climate simulations forced with natural and anthropogenic changes, but is inconsistent with simulations forced by natural changes alone. A further loss of up to 60% is projected within the next 30 years. Uncertainties in loss estimates depend on the size and the rate of response to continued anthropogenic forcing and the magnitude and phasing of internal decadal variability. The projected losses have serious implications for the hydropower, municipal and agricultural sectors in the region. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> An international team of scientists, has found that up to 20% loss in the annual maximum amount of water contained in the Western United States' mountain snowpack in the last three decades is due to human influences. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-24 04:59:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> BREAKING @EPA announced it will shut down its #opendata site with US #pollution data @altUSEPA #EndangeredData </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-24 02:56:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-24 02:42:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Study (open access): [Designing better methane mitigation policies: the challenge of distributed small sources in the natural gas sector](http://iopscience.iop.org/article/10.1088/1748-9326/aa6791)
___

**Abstract**

Methanea short-lived and potent greenhouse gaspresents a unique challenge: it is emitted from a large number of highly distributed and diffuse sources. In this regard, the United States' Environmental Protection Agency (EPA) has recommended periodic leak detection and repair surveys at oil and gas facilities using optical gas imaging technology. This regulation requires an operator to fix all detected leaks within a set time period. Whether such 'find-all-fix-all' policies are effective depends on significant uncertainties in the character of emissions. In this work, we systematically analyze the effect of facility-related and mitigation-related uncertainties on regulation effectiveness. Drawing from multiple publicly-available datasets, we find that: (1) highly-skewed leak-size distributions strongly influence emissions reduction potential; (2) variations in emissions estimates across facilities leads to large variability in mitigation effectiveness; (3) emissions reductions from optical gas imaging-based leak detection programs can range from 15% to over 70%; and (4) while implementation costs are uniformly lower than EPA estimates, benefits from saved gas are highly variable. Combining empirical evidence with model results, we propose four policy options for effective methane mitigation: performance-oriented targets for accelerated emission reductions, flexible policy mechanisms to account for regional variation, technology-agnostic regulations to encourage adoption of the most cost-effective measures, and coordination with other greenhouse gas mitigation policies to reduce unintended spillover effects.

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Stanford research shows plugging methane leaks will cost about a third less than the EPA estimates, further underscoring the cost-effectiveness of emissions mitigation  but the agency will also likely fall short of its 2025 reduction targets. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-24 02:41:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-24 02:38:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Study (open access): [Dominant 100,000-year precipitation cyclicity in a late Miocene lake from northeast Tibet](http://advances.sciencemag.org/content/3/3/e1600762.full)
___

**Abstract**

East Asian summer monsoon (EASM) precipitation received by northern China over the past 800 thousand years (ky) is characterized by dominant 100-ky periodicity, mainly attributed to CO2 and Northern Hemisphere insolationdriven ice sheet forcing. We established an EASM record in the Late Miocene from lacustrine sediments in the Qaidam Basin, northern China, which appears to exhibit a dominant 100-ky periodicity similar to the EASM records during the Late Quaternary. Because evidence suggests that partial or ephemeral ice existed in the Northern Hemisphere during the Late Miocene, we attribute the 100-ky cycles to CO2 and Southern Hemisphere insolationdriven Antarctic ice sheet forcing. This indicates a 6million year earlier onset of the dominant 100-ky Asian monsoon and, likely, glacial and CO2 cycles and may indicate dominant forcing of Northern Hemisphere climate by CO2 and Southern Hemisphere ice sheets in a warm world. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Tibet sediments reveal climate patterns from millions of years ago. The new study establishes an East Asian summer monsoon (EASM) record in the Late Miocene from lacustrine sediments, which appear to exhibit a dominant 100-ky periodicity similar to the EASM records during the Late Quaternary. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-24 02:37:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-24 02:27:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Study: [Temperature Decouples Ammonium and Nitrite Oxidation in Coastal Waters](http://pubs.acs.org/doi/abs/10.1021/acs.est.6b03483)
___

**Abstract**

Nitrification is a two-step process linking the reduced and oxidized sides of the nitrogen cycle. These steps are typically tightly coupled with the primary intermediate, nitrite, rarely accumulating in coastal environments. Nitrite concentrations can exceed 10 M during summer in estuarine waters adjacent to Sapelo Island, Georgia, U.S.A. Similar peaks at other locations have been attributed to decoupling of the two steps of nitrification by hypoxia; however, the waters around Sapelo Island are aerobic and well-mixed. Experiments examining the response to temperature shifts of a nitrifying assemblage composed of the same organisms found in the field indicate that ammonia- and nitrite-oxidation become uncoupled between 20 and 30 C, leading to nitrite accumulation. This suggests that nitrite peaks in coastal waters might be explained by differences in the responses of ammonia- and nitrite-oxidizers to increased summer temperatures. Analysis of field data from 270 stations in 29 temperate and subtropical estuaries and lagoons show transient accumulation of nitrite driven primarily by water temperatures, rather than by hypoxia. Increased climate variability and warming coastal waters may therefore increase the frequency of these nitrite peaks, with potential ecosystem consequences that include increased N2O production, NO2^ toxicity, and shifts in phytoplankton community composition. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Rising water temperatures endanger health of coastal ecosystems, study finds </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-24 02:26:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-24 01:46:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Such mass graves aren't created *during* the flood, or even from a single event, but rather result from tens of thousands of years of accumulating sediments that provide favorable conditions for the preservation of, geologically speaking, young organic material.

For example, a brief summary of the SnowMastadon site your refer to is as follows:

~130,000ka (?) the [Bull Lake glaciation](https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Bull_Lake_glaciation) was coming to an end. As conditions warmed (leading into the Sangamonian Stage), local glaciers receded, leaving a terminal moraine which impeded drainage of the glacial meltwater. This step generates a proglacial lake, filling with glacial outwash and fine wind blown sediments (loess) as the glaciers continue to recede. Moraines are relatively steep sided and unstable, and repeated slumps, and slides occurred over tens of thousands of years carrying with them organic rich material (ie. the local fauna). This process would repeat itself with the Pinedale Glaciation and subsequent warming, eventually filling with sediments, becoming a peat bog and meadow and its present condition. 

The mass grave at SnowMastadon contains a succession of unique fossil rich beds deposited over tens of thousands of years primarily from slope collapses into a lake environment that was favorable for the preservation of organic material. So while you are certainly correct in one sense, providing a mechanism of transport into the lake bottom through 'mud slides/rock slides' you were incorrect in another sense - the sense of scale. Glacial outburst floods resulting in Mwp 1a   b are nearly unfathomable, catastrophic events, while the events that occurred to give us such sites as the SnowMastadon site were far less spectacular, local (rather than regional) and were on much, much smaller scales. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-23 11:10:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Absolutely not. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-23 11:10:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Countless flood myths from around the globe are a result of naturally occurring catastrophic events centered around sea level rise, glacial outburst floods, and other events as the transition from glacial to interglacial periods occurred, there's no need to invoke religious  doctrines. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Perspective: Its Not a War on Science </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-22 22:22:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-22 19:53:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Meltwater ~~spike~~ 'pulses'^[1](http://i.imgur.com/wb63ykW.jpg) 

Which mass animal graves are you referring to? Glacial outburst floods were catastrophic events for which there would be little evidence of anything left behind as they scoured the bedrock and moved massive amounts of debris. I would be skeptical of any claim that these events lead to the formation of mass animal graves of well preserved fauna. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> How the Disappearing Arctic Ice is Already Changing Your Weather </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-22 19:09:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-22 10:23:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Study: [Megafaunal isotopes reveal role of increased moisture on rangeland during late Pleistocene extinctions](https://www.nature.com/articles/s41559-017-0125)
___

**Abstract**

The role of environmental change in the late Pleistocene megafaunal extinctions remains a key question, owing in part to uncertainty about landscape changes at continental scales. We investigated the influence of environmental changes on megaherbivores using bone collagen nitrogen isotopes (n = 684, 63 new) as a proxy for moisture levels in the rangelands that sustained late Pleistocene grazers. An increase in landscape moisture in Europe, Siberia and the Americas during the Last GlacialInterglacial Transition (LGIT; ~2510 kyr bp) directly affected megaherbivore ecology on four continents, and was associated with a key period of population decline and extinction. In all regions, the period of greatest moisture coincided with regional deglaciation and preceded the widespread formation of wetland environments. Moisture-driven environmental changes appear to have played an important part in the late Quaternary megafaunal extinctions through alteration of environments such as rangelands, which supported a large biomass of specialist grazers. On a continental scale, LGIT moisture changes manifested differently according to regional climate and geography, and the stable presence of grasslands surrounding the central forested belt of Africa during this period helps to explain why proportionally fewer African megafauna became extinct during the late Pleistocene. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Mammoths, sabre-tooth tigers, giant sloths and other megafauna died out across most of the world at the end of the last Ice Age because the changing climate became too wet, according to a new study </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-22 10:22:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-22 10:21:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Study: [Megafaunal isotopes reveal role of increased moisture on rangeland during late Pleistocene extinctions](https://www.nature.com/articles/s41559-017-0125)
___

**Abstract**

The role of environmental change in the late Pleistocene megafaunal extinctions remains a key question, owing in part to uncertainty about landscape changes at continental scales. We investigated the influence of environmental changes on megaherbivores using bone collagen nitrogen isotopes (n = 684, 63 new) as a proxy for moisture levels in the rangelands that sustained late Pleistocene grazers. An increase in landscape moisture in Europe, Siberia and the Americas during the Last GlacialInterglacial Transition (LGIT; ~2510 kyr bp) directly affected megaherbivore ecology on four continents, and was associated with a key period of population decline and extinction. In all regions, the period of greatest moisture coincided with regional deglaciation and preceded the widespread formation of wetland environments. Moisture-driven environmental changes appear to have played an important part in the late Quaternary megafaunal extinctions through alteration of environments such as rangelands, which supported a large biomass of specialist grazers. On a continental scale, LGIT moisture changes manifested differently according to regional climate and geography, and the stable presence of grasslands surrounding the central forested belt of Africa during this period helps to explain why proportionally fewer African megafauna became extinct during the late Pleistocene. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Mammoths, sabre-tooth tigers, giant sloths and other megafauna died out across most of the world at the end of the last Ice Age because the changing climate became too wet, according to a new study </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-22 10:20:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Open-Source Calving Model  St Andrews Glaciology </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-22 10:15:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-21 17:43:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Study (open access): [Pathways for balancing CO2 emissions and sinks](https://www.nature.com/articles/ncomms14856)
___

**Abstract**

In December 2015 in Paris, leaders committed to achieve global, net decarbonization of human activities before 2100. This achievement would halt and even reverse anthropogenic climate change through the net removal of carbon from the atmosphere. However, the Paris documents contain few specific prescriptions for emissions mitigation, leaving various countries to pursue their own agendas. In this analysis, we project energy and land-use emissions mitigation pathways through 2100, subject to best-available parameterization of carbon-climate feedbacks and interdependencies. We find that, barring unforeseen and transformative technological advancement, anthropogenic emissions need to peak within the next 10 years, to maintain realistic pathways to meeting the COP21 emissions and warming targets. Fossil fuel consumption will probably need to be reduced below a quarter of primary energy supply by 2100 and the allowable consumption rate drops even further if negative emissions technologies remain technologically or economically unfeasible at the global scale. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Barring unforeseen and transformative technological advancement, anthropogenic emissions need to peak within the next 10 years, to maintain realistic pathways to meeting the COP21 emissions and warming targets. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-21 17:43:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-21 17:42:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Study (open access): [Pathways for balancing CO2 emissions and sinks](https://www.nature.com/articles/ncomms14856)
___

**Abstract**

In December 2015 in Paris, leaders committed to achieve global, net decarbonization of human activities before 2100. This achievement would halt and even reverse anthropogenic climate change through the net removal of carbon from the atmosphere. However, the Paris documents contain few specific prescriptions for emissions mitigation, leaving various countries to pursue their own agendas. In this analysis, we project energy and land-use emissions mitigation pathways through 2100, subject to best-available parameterization of carbon-climate feedbacks and interdependencies. We find that, barring unforeseen and transformative technological advancement, anthropogenic emissions need to peak within the next 10 years, to maintain realistic pathways to meeting the COP21 emissions and warming targets. Fossil fuel consumption will probably need to be reduced below a quarter of primary energy supply by 2100 and the allowable consumption rate drops even further if negative emissions technologies remain technologically or economically unfeasible at the global scale. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Barring unforeseen and transformative technological advancement, anthropogenic emissions need to peak within the next 10 years, to maintain realistic pathways to meeting the COP21 emissions and warming targets. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-21 17:41:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> March 2017, global temperature update </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-21 17:38:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Emissions growth slowdown: Can we now keep global warming under 2C? We have had three years with virtually no growth in carbon dioxide emissions from fossil fuels and industry. What has caused the slowdown and does this put us on a path below 2C? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-21 17:35:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Fake news threatens a climate literate world </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-21 08:51:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> New study reveals elevated levels of mercury in women of child bearing age in Pacific Island countries. The study found 96% of the women sampled from the Pacific Islands contained significantly elevated hair mercury levels. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-21 08:07:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Is It O.K. to Tinker With the Environment to Fight Climate Change? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-21 08:03:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Changing minds on a changing climate </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-21 05:20:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Judy Currys attribution non-argument </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-20 05:28:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-20 05:03:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Study: [Widespread movement of meltwater onto and across Antarctic ice shelves](https://www.nature.com/nature/journal/v544/n7650/full/nature22049.html)
___

**Abstract**

Surface meltwater drains across ice sheets, forming melt ponds that can trigger ice-shelf collapse, acceleration of grounded ice flow and increased sea-level rise. Numerical models of the Antarctic Ice Sheet that incorporate meltwaters impact on ice shelves, but ignore the movement of water across the ice surface, predict a metre of global sea-level rise this century in response to atmospheric warming. To understand the impact of water moving across the ice surface a broad quantification of surface meltwater and its drainage is needed. Yet, despite extensive research in Greenland and observations of individual drainage systems in Antarctica, we have little understanding of Antarctic-wide surface hydrology or how it will evolve. Here we show widespread drainage of meltwater across the surface of the ice sheet through surface streams and ponds (hereafter surface drainage) as far south as 85 S and as high as 1,300 metres above sea level. Our findings are based on satellite imagery from 1973 onwards and aerial photography from 1947 onwards. Surface drainage has persisted for decades, transporting water up to 120 kilometres from grounded ice onto and across ice shelves, feeding vast melt ponds up to 80 kilometres long. Large-scale surface drainage could deliver water to areas of ice shelves vulnerable to collapse, as melt rates increase this century. While Antarctic surface melt ponds are relatively well documented on some ice shelves, we have discovered that ponds often form part of widespread, large-scale surface drainage systems. In a warming climate, enhanced surface drainage could accelerate future ice-mass loss from Antarctic, potentially via positive feedbacks between the extent of exposed rock, melting and thinning of the ice sheet.


Study: [Antarctic ice shelf potentially stabilized by export of meltwater in surface river](https://www.nature.com/nature/journal/v544/n7650/full/nature22048.html)
___

**Abstract**

Meltwater stored in ponds and crevasses can weaken and fracture ice shelves, triggering their rapid disintegration. This ice-shelf collapse results in an increased flux of ice from adjacent glaciers and ice streams, thereby raising sea level globally. However, surface rivers forming on ice shelves could potentially export stored meltwater and prevent its destructive effects. Here we present evidence for persistent active drainage networksinterconnected streams, ponds and riverson the Nansen Ice Shelf in Antarctica that export a large fraction of the ice shelfs meltwater into the ocean. We find that active drainage has exported water off the ice surface through waterfalls and dolines for more than a century. The surface river terminates in a 130-metre-wide waterfall that can export the entire annual surface melt over the course of seven days. During warmer melt seasons, these drainage networks adapt to changing environmental conditions by remaining active for longer and exporting more water. Similar networks are present on the ice shelf in front of Petermann Glacier, Greenland, but other systems, such as on the Larsen C and Amery Ice Shelves, retain surface water at present. The underlying reasons for export versus retention remain unclear. Nonetheless our results suggest that, in a future warming climate, surface rivers could export melt off the large ice shelves surrounding Antarcticacontrary to present Antarctic ice-sheet models, which assume that meltwater is stored on the ice surface where it triggers ice-shelf disintegration. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Water is streaming across Antarctica: New survey finds liquid flow more widespread than thought </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-20 05:02:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-20 05:00:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Study: [Widespread movement of meltwater onto and across Antarctic ice shelves](https://www.nature.com/nature/journal/v544/n7650/full/nature22049.html)
___

**Abstract**

Surface meltwater drains across ice sheets, forming melt ponds that can trigger ice-shelf collapse, acceleration of grounded ice flow and increased sea-level rise. Numerical models of the Antarctic Ice Sheet that incorporate meltwaters impact on ice shelves, but ignore the movement of water across the ice surface, predict a metre of global sea-level rise this century in response to atmospheric warming. To understand the impact of water moving across the ice surface a broad quantification of surface meltwater and its drainage is needed. Yet, despite extensive research in Greenland and observations of individual drainage systems in Antarctica, we have little understanding of Antarctic-wide surface hydrology or how it will evolve. Here we show widespread drainage of meltwater across the surface of the ice sheet through surface streams and ponds (hereafter surface drainage) as far south as 85 S and as high as 1,300 metres above sea level. Our findings are based on satellite imagery from 1973 onwards and aerial photography from 1947 onwards. Surface drainage has persisted for decades, transporting water up to 120 kilometres from grounded ice onto and across ice shelves, feeding vast melt ponds up to 80 kilometres long. Large-scale surface drainage could deliver water to areas of ice shelves vulnerable to collapse, as melt rates increase this century. While Antarctic surface melt ponds are relatively well documented on some ice shelves, we have discovered that ponds often form part of widespread, large-scale surface drainage systems. In a warming climate, enhanced surface drainage could accelerate future ice-mass loss from Antarctic, potentially via positive feedbacks between the extent of exposed rock, melting and thinning of the ice sheet.
___

Study: [Antarctic ice shelf potentially stabilized by export of meltwater in surface river](https://www.nature.com/nature/journal/v544/n7650/full/nature22048.html)
___

**Abstract**

Meltwater stored in ponds and crevasses can weaken and fracture ice shelves, triggering their rapid disintegration. This ice-shelf collapse results in an increased flux of ice from adjacent glaciers and ice streams, thereby raising sea level globally. However, surface rivers forming on ice shelves could potentially export stored meltwater and prevent its destructive effects. Here we present evidence for persistent active drainage networksinterconnected streams, ponds and riverson the Nansen Ice Shelf in Antarctica that export a large fraction of the ice shelfs meltwater into the ocean. We find that active drainage has exported water off the ice surface through waterfalls and dolines for more than a century. The surface river terminates in a 130-metre-wide waterfall that can export the entire annual surface melt over the course of seven days. During warmer melt seasons, these drainage networks adapt to changing environmental conditions by remaining active for longer and exporting more water. Similar networks are present on the ice shelf in front of Petermann Glacier, Greenland, but other systems, such as on the Larsen C and Amery Ice Shelves, retain surface water at present. The underlying reasons for export versus retention remain unclear. Nonetheless our results suggest that, in a future warming climate, surface rivers could export melt off the large ice shelves surrounding Antarcticacontrary to present Antarctic ice-sheet models, which assume that meltwater is stored on the ice surface where it triggers ice-shelf disintegration. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Water is streaming across Antarctica: New survey finds liquid flow more widespread than thought </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-20 04:57:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Bloomberg just launched a site dedicated to climate coverage: Climate Changed </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-20 04:41:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-19 18:19:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> For the Western Hemisphere Warm Pool:

...the monthly residuals of the warm pool area index, **defined as the area inside the 28.5C isotherm at the sea surface** -[NOAA/AOML](http://sunburn.aoml.noaa.gov/phod/regsatprod/whwp/sst_anm.php) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Reconciling ECS estimates  again </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-19 09:15:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Will Earth's Climate Get More Sensitive to CO2? Only Better Satellites Can Say </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-19 09:05:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-19 06:10:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Source: [ Randall Gates](https://twitter.com/rgatess/status/854474271128670208) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The Indo-Pacific Warm Pool is Earth's largest storage of climate system energy. It's been adding huge amounts since 2012. (circled in green) </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-19 06:10:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-18 09:32:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> And predicted in a 2006 paper by co-author John Clague:

Continued retreat of Kaskawulsh Glacier may result in piracy of
Slims River meltwater by Kaskawulsh River due to the much
steeper gradient of the latter. 

\- [Rapid changes in the level of Kluane Lake in Yukon Territory over the last millennium](http://www.sfu.ca/cnhr/papers/Kluane%20Lake.pdf) (pdf) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-18 09:11:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> There actually *is* another term, and if you read the article you'll learn it as well. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-18 08:23:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Study: [Migration induced by sea-level rise could reshape the US population landscape](https://www.nature.com/nclimate/journal/vaop/ncurrent/full/nclimate3271.html)
___

**Abstract**

Many sea-level rise (SLR) assessments focus on populations presently inhabiting vulnerable coastal communities, but to date no studies have attempted to model the destinations of these potentially displaced persons. With millions of potential future migrants in heavily populated coastal communities, SLR scholarship focusing solely on coastal communities characterizes SLR as primarily a coastal issue, obscuring the potential impacts in landlocked communities created by SLR-induced displacement. Here I address this issue by merging projected populations at risk of SLR with migration systems simulations to project future destinations of SLR migrants in the United States. I find that unmitigated SLR is expected to reshape the US population distribution, potentially stressing landlocked areas unprepared to accommodate this wave of coastal migrantseven after accounting for potential adaptation. These results provide the first glimpse of how climate change will reshape future population distributions and establish a new foundation for modelling potential migration destinations from climate stressors in an era of global environmental change. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Migration induced by sea-level rise could reshape the US population landscape with approximately 13.1 million people displaced by rising ocean waters, with Atlanta, Houston and Phoenix as top destinations for those forced to relocate. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-18 08:21:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-18 08:04:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Study (open access): [Ambiguity in the causes for decadal trends in atmospheric methane and hydroxyl](http://www.pnas.org/content/early/2017/04/11/1616020114.full)
___

**Significance**

Recent trends in atmospheric methane are not well understood as evidenced by multiple hypotheses proposed to explain the stabilization of methane concentrations in the early 2000s and the renewed growth since 2007. Here we use a multispecies inversion to determine the cause of these decadal trends. The most likely explanation for the renewed growth in atmospheric methane involves a decrease in hydroxyl (OH), the main sink for atmospheric methane, that is partially offset by a decrease in methane emissions. However, we also demonstrate that the problem of attributing methane trends from the current surface observation network, including isotopes, is underdetermined and does not allow unambiguous attribution of decadal trends.
 
**Abstract**

Methane is the second strongest anthropogenic greenhouse gas and its atmospheric burden has more than doubled since 1850. Methane concentrations stabilized in the early 2000s and began increasing again in 2007. Neither the stabilization nor the recent growth are well understood, as evidenced by multiple competing hypotheses in recent literature. Here we use a multispecies two-box model inversion to jointly constrain 36 y of methane sources and sinks, using ground-based measurements of methane, methyl chloroform, and the C13/C12 ratio in atmospheric methane (13CH4) from 1983 through 2015. We find that the problem, as currently formulated, is underdetermined and solutions obtained in previous work are strongly dependent on prior assumptions. Based on our analysis, the mathematically most likely explanation for the renewed growth in atmospheric methane, counterintuitively, involves a 25-Tg/y decrease in methane emissions from 2003 to 2016 that is offset by a 7% decrease in global mean hydroxyl (OH) concentrations, the primary sink for atmospheric methane, over the same period. However, we are still able to fit the observations if we assume that OH concentrations are time invariant (as much of the previous work has assumed) and we then find solutions that are largely consistent with other proposed hypotheses for the renewed growth of atmospheric methane since 2007. We conclude that the current surface observing system does not allow unambiguous attribution of the decadal trends in methane without robust constraints on OH variability, which currently rely purely on methyl chloroform data and its uncertain emissions estimates. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> 'Detergent' Molecules May Be Driving Fluctuations in Atmospheric Methane Concentrations: New study suggests hydroxyl radicals may be behind unexplained recent increase in methane levels </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-18 08:03:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-18 08:02:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Study (open access): [Ambiguity in the causes for decadal trends in atmospheric methane and hydroxyl](http://www.pnas.org/content/early/2017/04/11/1616020114.full)
___

**Significance**

Recent trends in atmospheric methane are not well understood as evidenced by multiple hypotheses proposed to explain the stabilization of methane concentrations in the early 2000s and the renewed growth since 2007. Here we use a multispecies inversion to determine the cause of these decadal trends. The most likely explanation for the renewed growth in atmospheric methane involves a decrease in hydroxyl (OH), the main sink for atmospheric methane, that is partially offset by a decrease in methane emissions. However, we also demonstrate that the problem of attributing methane trends from the current surface observation network, including isotopes, is underdetermined and does not allow unambiguous attribution of decadal trends.
 
**Abstract**

Methane is the second strongest anthropogenic greenhouse gas and its atmospheric burden has more than doubled since 1850. Methane concentrations stabilized in the early 2000s and began increasing again in 2007. Neither the stabilization nor the recent growth are well understood, as evidenced by multiple competing hypotheses in recent literature. Here we use a multispecies two-box model inversion to jointly constrain 36 y of methane sources and sinks, using ground-based measurements of methane, methyl chloroform, and the C13/C12 ratio in atmospheric methane (13CH4) from 1983 through 2015. We find that the problem, as currently formulated, is underdetermined and solutions obtained in previous work are strongly dependent on prior assumptions. Based on our analysis, the mathematically most likely explanation for the renewed growth in atmospheric methane, counterintuitively, involves a 25-Tg/y decrease in methane emissions from 2003 to 2016 that is offset by a 7% decrease in global mean hydroxyl (OH) concentrations, the primary sink for atmospheric methane, over the same period. However, we are still able to fit the observations if we assume that OH concentrations are time invariant (as much of the previous work has assumed) and we then find solutions that are largely consistent with other proposed hypotheses for the renewed growth of atmospheric methane since 2007. We conclude that the current surface observing system does not allow unambiguous attribution of the decadal trends in methane without robust constraints on OH variability, which currently rely purely on methyl chloroform data and its uncertain emissions estimates. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> 'Detergent' Molecules May Be Driving Fluctuations in Atmospheric Methane Concentrations: New study suggests hydroxyl radicals may be behind unexplained recent increase in methane levels </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-18 08:01:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-18 01:43:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Study (open access): [Windscapes and olfactory foraging in a large carnivore](https://www.nature.com/articles/srep46332)
___

**Abstract**

The theoretical optimal olfactory search strategy is to move cross-wind. Empirical evidence supporting wind-associated directionality among carnivores, however, is sparse. We examined satellite-linked telemetry movement data of adult female polar bears (Ursus maritimus) from Hudson Bay, Canada, in relation to modelled winds, in an effort to understand olfactory search for prey. In our results, the predicted cross-wind movement occurred most frequently at night during winter, the time when most hunting occurs, while downwind movement dominated during fast winds, which impede olfaction. Migration during sea ice freeze-up and break-up was also correlated with wind. A lack of orientation during summer, a period with few food resources, likely reflected reduced cross-wind search. Our findings represent the first quantitative description of anemotaxis, orientation to wind, for cross-wind search in a large carnivore. The methods are widely applicable to olfactory predators and their prey. We suggest windscapes be included as a habitat feature in habitat selection models for olfactory animals when evaluating what is considered available habitat. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> How polar bears find their prey using wind and sense of smell: Arctic wind speeds are projected to increase due to climate change and could impede polar bear hunting success </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-18 01:42:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-17 23:13:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Figure 1 in the paper (available ITT) has a better illustration. However, an article by 'The Guardian' provides perhaps the most clear illustration: [here](http://i.imgur.com/Cc5mNv4.jpg) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-17 22:19:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Study (author access token): [Energy budget constraints on climate sensitivity in light of inconstant climate feedbacks](https://www.nature.com/articles/nclimate3278.epdf?author_access_token=iTHNUTjTl9ad1re2zIjHE9RgN0jAjWel9jnR3ZoTv0Oro9uT6LjYQd4TJtmay3BEfj_tdH1KtMjucqsMwNwevJCaGWvAt_zQ4HHn-g2-IPRowtTA5CQr3Mly8AGp0ITl)
___

**Abstract**

Global energy budget constraints suggest an equilibrium climate sensitivity around 2 C, which is lower than estimates from palaeoclimate reconstructions, process-based observational analyses, and global climate model simulations. A key assumption is that the climate sensitivity inferred today also applies to the distant future. Yet, global climate models robustly show that feedbacks vary over time, with a strong tendency for climate sensitivity to increase as equilibrium is approached. Here I consider the implications of inconstant climate feedbacks for energy budget constraints on climate sensitivity. I find that the long-term value of climate sensitivity is, on average, 26% above that inferred during transient warming within global climate models, with a larger discrepancy when climate sensitivity is high. Moreover, model values of climate sensitivity inferred during transient warming are found to be consistent with energy budget observations indicating that the models are not overly sensitive. Using model-based estimates of how climate feedbacks will change in the future, in conjunction with recent energy budget constraints produces a current best estimate of equilibrium climate sensitivity of 2.9 C (1.77.1 C, 90% confidence). These findings suggest that climate sensitivity estimated from global energy budget constraints is in agreement with values derived from other methods and simulated by global climate models. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Models, observations not so far apart on planets response to greenhouse gas emissions: recent observations support a climate sensitivity of 2.9 degrees Celsius. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-17 22:19:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-17 22:15:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Study (author access token): [Energy budget constraints on climate sensitivity in light of inconstant climate feedbacks](https://www.nature.com/articles/nclimate3278.epdf?author_access_token=iTHNUTjTl9ad1re2zIjHE9RgN0jAjWel9jnR3ZoTv0Oro9uT6LjYQd4TJtmay3BEfj_tdH1KtMjucqsMwNwevJCaGWvAt_zQ4HHn-g2-IPRowtTA5CQr3Mly8AGp0ITl)
___

**Abstract**

Global energy budget constraints suggest an equilibrium climate sensitivity around 2C, which is lower than estimates from palaeoclimate reconstructions, process-based observational analyses, and global climate model simulations. A key assumption is that the climate sensitivity inferred today also applies to the distant future. Yet, global climate models robustly show that feedbacks vary over time, with a strong tendency for climate sensitivity to increase as equilibrium is approached. Here I consider the implications of inconstant climate feedbacks for energy budget constraints on climate sensitivity. I find that the long-term value of climate sensitivity is, on average, 26% above that inferred during transient warming within global climate models, with a larger discrepancy when climate sensitivity is high. Moreover, model values of climate sensitivity inferred during transient warming are found to be consistent with energy budget observations indicating that the models are not overly sensitive. Using model-based estimates of how climate feedbacks will change in the future, in conjunction with recent energy budget constraints produces a current best estimate of equilibrium climate sensitivity of 2.9C (1.77.1C, 90% confidence). These findings suggest that climate sensitivity estimated from global energy budget constraints is in agreement with values derived from other methods and simulated by global climate models. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Models, observations not so far apart on planets response to greenhouse gas emissions: recent observations support a climate sensitivity of 2.9 degrees Celsius. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-17 22:12:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-17 21:47:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This particular scenario refers to the retreat of a glacial body such that the melt water is now able to find a new drainage path. Similar scenarios would have occurred during transitional periods from glacial to interglacial periods. Potentially similar scenarios may have therefore occurred during any number of regionally sufficient warm episodes^[1](http://www.nature.com/nature/journal/v397/n6719/full/397515a0.html) . Large landslides, and the collapse of natural dams also contribute to the process. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-17 19:52:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Study (shared access): [River piracy and drainage basin reorganization led by climate-driven glacier retreat](https://www.nature.com/articles/ngeo2932.epdf?shared_access_token=wBJcymOXmHDu0B8QtFJO39RgN0jAjWel9jnR3ZoTv0MpG3T_FPz_DYjXaSQxu9ve9DB9zW87KArNSr-S0xAlhYVWccc1_wqtxKPsbAd7ldVHihgh2pFNXWh_tev99kdinXB9CRI80Xz2wKVQFSXWlA%3D%3D)
___

**Abstract**

River piracythe diversion of the headwaters of one stream into another onecan dramatically change the routing of water and sediment, with a profound effect on landscape evolution. Stream piracy has been investigated in glacial environments, but so far it has mainly been studied over Quaternary or longer timescales. Here we document how retreat of Kaskawulsh Glacierone of Canadas largest glaciersabruptly and radically altered the regional drainage pattern in spring 2016. We use a combination of hydrological measurements and drone-generated digital elevation models to show that in late May 2016, meltwater from the glacier was re-routed from discharge in a northward direction into the Bering Sea, to southward into the Pacific Ocean. Based on satellite image analysis and a signal-to-noise ratio as a metric of glacier retreat, we conclude that this instance of river piracy was due to post-industrial climate change. Rapid regional drainage reorganizations of this type can have profound downstream impacts on ecosystems, sediment and carbon budgets, and downstream communities that rely on a stable and sustained discharge. We suggest that the planforms of Slims and Kaskawulsh rivers will adjust in response to altered flows, and the future Kaskawulsh watershed will extend into the now-abandoned headwaters of Slims River and eventually capture the Kluane Lake drainage. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Climate change has caused the massive Kaskawulsh Glacier, one of Canadas largest glaciers, to retreat so much that its meltwater abruptly switched direction, in the first documented case of "river piracy" in modern times. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-17 19:52:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-17 19:45:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Study (open access): [Future climate forcing potentially without precedent in the last 420 million years](https://www.nature.com/articles/ncomms14845)
___

**Abstract**

The evolution of Earths climate on geological timescales is largely driven by variations in the magnitude of total solar irradiance (TSI) and changes in the greenhouse gas content of the atmosphere. Here we show that the slow 50Wm2 increase in TSI over the last 420 million years (an increase of 9Wm2 of radiative forcing) was almost completely negated by a long-term decline in atmospheric CO2. This was likely due to the silicate weathering-negative feedback and the expansion of land plants that together ensured Earths long-term habitability. Humanitys fossil-fuel use, if unabated, risks taking us, by the middle of the twenty-first century, to values of CO2 not seen since the early Eocene (50 million years ago). If CO2 continues to rise further into the twenty-third century, then the associated large increase in radiative forcing, and how the Earth system would respond, would likely be without geological precedent in the last half a billion years. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Future climate forcing potentially without precedent in the last 420 million years. Humanitys fossil-fuel use, if unabated, risks taking us, by the middle of the twenty-first century, to values of CO2 not seen since the early Eocene (50 million years ago). </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-17 19:44:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-17 19:38:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Study (shared access): [River piracy and drainage basin reorganization led by climate-driven glacier retreat](https://www.nature.com/articles/ngeo2932.epdf?shared_access_token=wBJcymOXmHDu0B8QtFJO39RgN0jAjWel9jnR3ZoTv0MpG3T_FPz_DYjXaSQxu9ve9DB9zW87KArNSr-S0xAlhYVWccc1_wqtxKPsbAd7ldVHihgh2pFNXWh_tev99kdinXB9CRI80Xz2wKVQFSXWlA%3D%3D)
___

**Abstract**

River piracythe diversion of the headwaters of one stream into another onecan dramatically change the routing of water and sediment, with a profound effect on landscape evolution. Stream piracy has been investigated in glacial environments, but so far it has mainly been studied over Quaternary or longer timescales. Here we document how retreat of Kaskawulsh Glacierone of Canadas largest glaciersabruptly and radically altered the regional drainage pattern in spring 2016. We use a combination of hydrological measurements and drone-generated digital elevation models to show that in late May 2016, meltwater from the glacier was re-routed from discharge in a northward direction into the Bering Sea, to southward into the Pacific Ocean. Based on satellite image analysis and a signal-to-noise ratio as a metric of glacier retreat, we conclude that this instance of river piracy was due to post-industrial climate change. Rapid regional drainage reorganizations of this type can have profound downstream impacts on ecosystems, sediment and carbon budgets, and downstream communities that rely on a stable and sustained discharge. We suggest that the planforms of Slims and Kaskawulsh rivers will adjust in response to altered flows, and the future Kaskawulsh watershed will extend into the now-abandoned headwaters of Slims River and eventually capture the Kluane Lake drainage. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Climate change has caused the massive Kaskawulsh Glacier, one of Canadas largest glaciers, to retreat so much that its meltwater abruptly switched direction, in the first documented case of "river piracy" in modern times. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-17 19:37:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-17 19:29:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Study (shared access): [River piracy and drainage basin reorganization led by climate-driven glacier retreat](https://www.nature.com/articles/ngeo2932.epdf?shared_access_token=wBJcymOXmHDu0B8QtFJO39RgN0jAjWel9jnR3ZoTv0MpG3T_FPz_DYjXaSQxu9ve9DB9zW87KArNSr-S0xAlhYVWccc1_wqtxKPsbAd7ldVHihgh2pFNXWh_tev99kdinXB9CRI80Xz2wKVQFSXWlA%3D%3D)
___

**Abstract**

River piracythe diversion of the headwaters of one stream into another onecan dramatically change the routing of water and sediment, with a profound effect on landscape evolution. Stream piracy has been investigated in glacial environments, but so far it has mainly been studied over Quaternary or longer timescales. Here we document how retreat of Kaskawulsh Glacierone of Canadas largest glaciersabruptly and radically altered the regional drainage pattern in spring 2016. We use a combination of hydrological measurements and drone-generated digital elevation models to show that in late May 2016, meltwater from the glacier was re-routed from discharge in a northward direction into the Bering Sea, to southward into the Pacific Ocean. Based on satellite image analysis and a signal-to-noise ratio as a metric of glacier retreat, we conclude that this instance of river piracy was due to post-industrial climate change. Rapid regional drainage reorganizations of this type can have profound downstream impacts on ecosystems, sediment and carbon budgets, and downstream communities that rely on a stable and sustained discharge. We suggest that the planforms of Slims and Kaskawulsh rivers will adjust in response to altered flows, and the future Kaskawulsh watershed will extend into the now-abandoned headwaters of Slims River and eventually capture the Kluane Lake drainage. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Climate change has caused the massive Kaskawulsh Glacier, one of Canadas largest glaciers, to retreat so much that its meltwater abruptly switched direction, in the first documented case of "river piracy" in modern times. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-17 19:28:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Beyer Enlists Scientific Experts for Fact-Check Project to Correct the Record On Misstatements Made During House Science Committee Hearings : Congressman Don Beyer </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-17 02:42:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Setting up Processing and the Keeling Curve  Kevin Pluck </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-17 02:31:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> April 2017 ENSO update: Conflicting signals from the tropical Pacific Ocean </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-16 18:31:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-15 18:07:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Source: [Larry Hamilton](https://twitter.com/ichiloe/status/852917178659635204) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Graphing the *warmest and coolest* months each year highlights fact that warming involves both highs and lows. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-15 18:07:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Scientists just found a strange and worrying crack in one of Greenlands biggest glaciers </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-14 16:31:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-14 16:28:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Study (open access): [Sea surface pCO2 and O2 dynamics in the partially ice-covered Arctic Ocean](http://onlinelibrary.wiley.com/doi/10.1002/2016JC012162/full)
___

**Abstract**

Understanding the physical and biogeochemical processes that control CO2 and dissolved oxygen (DO) dynamics in the Arctic Ocean (AO) is crucial for predicting future air-sea CO2 fluxes and ocean acidification. Past studies have primarily been conducted on the AO continental shelves during low-ice periods and we lack information on gas dynamics in the deep AO basins where ice typically inhibits contact with the atmosphere. To study these gas dynamics, in situ time-series data have been collected in the Canada Basin during late summer to autumn of 2012. Partial pressure of CO2 (pCO2), DO concentration, temperature, salinity, and chlorophyll-a fluorescence (Chl-a) were measured in the upper ocean in a range of sea ice states by two drifting instrument systems. Although the two systems were on average only 222 km apart, they experienced considerably different ice cover and external forcings during the 4050 day periods when data were collected. The pCO2 levels at both locations were well below atmospheric saturation whereas DO was almost always slightly supersaturated. Modeling results suggest that air-sea gas exchange, net community production (NCP), and horizontal gradients were the main sources of pCO2 and DO variability in the sparsely ice-covered AO. In areas more densely covered by sea ice, horizontal gradients were the dominant source of variability, with no significant NCP in the surface mixed layer. If the AO reaches equilibrium with atmospheric CO2 as ice cover continues to decrease, aragonite saturation will drop from a present mean of 1.000.02 to 0.860.01. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> How Arctic Ice Affects Gas Exchange Between Air and Sea </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-14 16:27:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Could Subsea Methane Hydrates Be a Warming "Tipping Point"? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-14 16:24:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-14 16:19:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Study (open access): [Direct observations of ice seasonality reveal changes in climate over the past 320570 years](https://www.nature.com/articles/srep25061)
___

**Abstract**

Lake and river ice seasonality (dates of ice freeze and breakup) responds sensitively to climatic change and variability. We analyzed climate-related changes using direct human observations of ice freeze dates (14432014) for Lake Suwa, Japan, and of ice breakup dates (16932013) for Torne River, Finland. We found a rich array of changes in ice seasonality of two inland waters from geographically distant regions: namely a shift towards later ice formation for Suwa and earlier spring melt for Torne, increasing frequencies of years with warm extremes, changing inter-annual variability, waning of dominant inter-decadal quasi-periodic dynamics, and stronger correlations of ice seasonality with atmospheric CO2 concentration and air temperature after the start of the Industrial Revolution. Although local factors, including human population growth, land use change, and water management influence Suwa and Torne, the general patterns of ice seasonality are similar for both systems, suggesting that global processes including climate change and variability are driving the long-term changes in ice seasonality. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Nearly 600 years of historic records from citizen scientists in Japan and Finland give researchers centuries of direct observational data on ice conditions </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-14 16:18:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-14 07:39:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Before the inevitable fear mongering citing the catastrophic 'Clathrate Gun hypothesis' makes its appearance in the comment section, I'd like to state that while thawing permafrost, and warming oceans are certainly of concern when considering our carbon budget and warming, such a scenario is (a) not *strongly* supported in the scientific literature^[5](http://onlinelibrary.wiley.com/doi/10.1002/2016GL069676/abstract) and (b) recent studies simply find such a scenario to be unlikely^[1](http://onlinelibrary.wiley.com/doi/10.1002/2016RG000534/full), ^[2](http://onlinelibrary.wiley.com/doi/10.1002/2016GL068999/abstract), ^[3](http://onlinelibrary.wiley.com/doi/10.1002/2016GL069292/full), ^[4](http://onlinelibrary.wiley.com/doi/10.1002/2016GL068999/full) . </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-14 07:38:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Study: [Extensive Early Cretaceous (Albian) methane seepage on Ellef Ringnes Island, Canadian High Arctic](http://gsabulletin.gsapubs.org/content/early/2017/04/07/B31601.1.abstract)
___

**Abstract**

During field mapping of Ellef Ringnes Island, Canadian Arctic Archipelago, 139 isolated Early Cretaceous methane seep deposits were found from 75 field sites. Stable isotopes of the carbonates have values of 13C = 47 to 35 and 18O = 4.0 to +0.7. Isoprenoids in organics from one of the seeps are significantly depleted in 13C, with the most negative 13C value of 118 and 113 for 2,6,10,15,19-pentamethylicosane (PMI) and phytane/crocetane, respectively. These values indicate an origin through methane oxidation, consistent with biomarkers that are characteristic for anaerobic methanotrophic archaea within the seep deposits, accompanied by terminally branched fatty acids showing similar 13C values (92) sourced from sulfate-reducing bacteria. The seep deposits contain a moderate-diversity macrofaunal assemblage comprising ammonites, bivalves, gastropods, scaphopods, vestimentiferan worm tubes, and brachiopods. The assemblage is dominated numerically by species that probably had chemosymbionts. The seep deposits formed in the subsurface within strong redox zones, in an otherwise normal marine setting, characterized by oxic waters at high paleolatitudes.

While geographically widespread over an area of 10,000 km^2 , seep deposits on Ellef Ringnes Island occur in a narrow stratigraphic horizon, suggesting a large release of biogenic methane occurred over a brief period of time. This gas release was coincident with a transition from a cold to warm climate during the latest early Albian, and we hypothesize that this may have been related to gas hydrate release. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Extensive Early Cretaceous (Albian) methane seep deposits discovered in the Canadian High Arctic suggest a large release of biogenic methane occurred over a brief period of time, coincident with a transition from a cold to warm climate, and are hypothesized to be related to gas hydrate release </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-14 07:36:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-13 08:36:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Should you decide to watch the hearing it can be viewed on the House Committee on Science, Space, and Technology youtube channel: [Hearing- Climate Science: Assumptions, Policy Implications, and the Scientific Method (Version 2)](https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=mN0qWRI7Rpc) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Scientists reactions to the US House Science Committee hearing on climate science </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-13 08:32:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-13 03:31:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> A fellow Quaternary geologist, nice to see. As a Quaternary Geochronologist do you focus primarily on cosmogenic nuclide dating? 

The following is copy and paste from a previous comment of mine:

Before the inevitable fear mongering citing the catastrophic 'Clathrate Gun hypothesis' makes its appearance in the comment section, I'd like to state that while thawing permafrost is certainly of concern when considering our carbon budget and warming, such a scenario is (a) not *strongly* supported in the scientific literature^[5](http://onlinelibrary.wiley.com/doi/10.1002/2016GL069676/abstract) and (b) recent studies simply find such a scenario to be unlikely^[1](http://onlinelibrary.wiley.com/doi/10.1002/2016RG000534/full), ^[2](http://onlinelibrary.wiley.com/doi/10.1002/2016GL068999/abstract), ^[3](http://onlinelibrary.wiley.com/doi/10.1002/2016GL069292/full), ^[4](http://onlinelibrary.wiley.com/doi/10.1002/2016GL068999/full) . </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-13 03:14:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Before the inevitable fear mongering citing the catastrophic 'Clathrate Gun hypothesis' makes its appearance in the comment section, I'd like to state that while thawing permafrost is certainly of concern when considering our carbon budget and warming, such a scenario is (a) not *strongly* supported in the scientific literature^[5](http://onlinelibrary.wiley.com/doi/10.1002/2016GL069676/abstract) and (b) recent studies simply find such a scenario to be unlikely^[1](http://onlinelibrary.wiley.com/doi/10.1002/2016RG000534/full), ^[2](http://onlinelibrary.wiley.com/doi/10.1002/2016GL068999/abstract), ^[3](http://onlinelibrary.wiley.com/doi/10.1002/2016GL069292/full), ^[4](http://onlinelibrary.wiley.com/doi/10.1002/2016GL068999/full) . </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-13 03:06:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Study: [An observation-based constraint on permafrost loss as a function of global warming](http://www.nature.com/nclimate/journal/vaop/ncurrent/full/nclimate3262.html)
___

**Abstract**

Permafrost, which covers 15 million km2 of the land surface, is one of the components of the Earth system that is most sensitive to warming. Loss of permafrost would radically change high-latitude hydrology and biogeochemical cycling, and could therefore provide very significant feedbacks on climate change. The latest climate models all predict warming of high-latitude soils and thus thawing of permafrost under future climate change, but with widely varying magnitudes of permafrost thaw. Here we show that in each of the models, their present-day spatial distribution of permafrost and air temperature can be used to infer the sensitivity of permafrost to future global warming. Using the same approach for the observed permafrost distribution and air temperature, we estimate a sensitivity of permafrost area loss to global mean warming at stabilization of 4.0 (+1.0, -1.1) million km^2  C^1 (1 confidence), which is around 20% higher than previous studies. Our method facilitates an assessment for COP21 climate change targets: if the climate is stabilized at 2 C above pre-industrial levels, we estimate that the permafrost area would eventually be reduced by over 40%. Stabilizing at 1.5 C rather than 2 C would save approximately 2 million km^2 of permafrost. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> More than 40% of the world's permafrost is at risk of thawing even if the world succeeds in limiting global warming to the international goal of 2C. The new estimate is around 20% higher than previous studies </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-13 03:05:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-13 03:03:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Study: [An observation-based constraint on permafrost loss as a function of global warming](http://www.nature.com/nclimate/journal/vaop/ncurrent/full/nclimate3262.html)
___

**Abstract**

Permafrost, which covers 15 million km2 of the land surface, is one of the components of the Earth system that is most sensitive to warming. Loss of permafrost would radically change high-latitude hydrology and biogeochemical cycling, and could therefore provide very significant feedbacks on climate change. The latest climate models all predict warming of high-latitude soils and thus thawing of permafrost under future climate change, but with widely varying magnitudes of permafrost thaw. Here we show that in each of the models, their present-day spatial distribution of permafrost and air temperature can be used to infer the sensitivity of permafrost to future global warming. Using the same approach for the observed permafrost distribution and air temperature, we estimate a sensitivity of permafrost area loss to global mean warming at stabilization of 4.0 (+1.0, -1.1) million km^2 C^1 (1 confidence), which is around 20% higher than previous studies. Our method facilitates an assessment for COP21 climate change targets: if the climate is stabilized at 2C above pre-industrial levels, we estimate that the permafrost area would eventually be reduced by over 40%. Stabilizing at 1.5C rather than 2C would save approximately 2 million km^2 of permafrost. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> More than 40% of the world's permafrost is at risk of thawing even if the world succeeds in limiting global warming to the international goal of 2C. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-13 02:59:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Trump eyes climate 'skeptic' for key White House environmental post </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-13 02:55:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Sea-level rise in California will be bad to catastrophic, study says </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-13 02:39:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Public Participation in EPA's Regulatory Reform: In accordance with Executive Order 13777, Enforcing the Regulatory Reform Agenda, EPA is seeking input on regulations that may be appropriate for repeal, replacement, or modification. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-12 16:12:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-12 16:06:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Study: [The transitional climate of the late Miocene Arctic: Winter-dominated precipitation with high seasonal variability](http://geology.gsapubs.org/content/early/2017/03/16/G38746.1.abstract)
___

**Abstract**

The late Miocene (11.65.3 Ma) was an important transitional period following the greenhouse conditions of the Eocene. In order to gain insight into the Arctic paleoclimate of the time, we performed high-resolution intraring 13C analyses on fossil wood collected from the late Miocene Khapchansky sediments of northeastern Siberia (69N). From these data we quantified the ratio of summer to winter precipitation (Ps/Pw) and compared it to current values for the region determined from modern wood samples and instrumental records. We observed much greater frequency of winter-dominated precipitation (Ps/Pw  1) and much greater variability in Ps/Pw during the Miocene than today. Specifically, years with Ps/Pw  1 occurred three times more often, and years with at least three times as much precipitation in summer or winter (0.33  Ps/Pw  3.0) occurred approximately twice as often during the Miocene than today. We attribute the high interannual variability in precipitation to an inconsistent moisture source associated with the relatively unstable and incomplete ice cover in the Arctic Ocean during the late Miocene. Our result highlights the potential for enhanced variability in Arctic precipitation in response to Arctic sea ice decline caused by anthropogenic, CO2-induced warming.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Researchers conclude less Arctic sea ice means more rain </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-12 16:05:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Does the carbon budget mean the end of fossil fuels? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-12 06:25:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Climate model projections compared to observations </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-12 06:22:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Savor the Cryosphere: This article provides concise documentation of the ongoing retreat of glaciers, along with the implications that the ice loss presents, as well as suggestions for geoscience educators to better convey this story to both students and citizens. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-12 06:18:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-11 07:43:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The article discusses your question should you opt to actually take a minute and read the paragraph. The study is also open access should you seek a more detailed answer. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Study (open access) | Reconstructing El Nio Southern Oscillation using data from ships logbooks, 18151854. Part I: methodology and evaluation </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-11 07:24:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-11 07:21:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Study (open access): [Processing political misinformation: comprehending the Trump phenomenon](http://rsos.royalsocietypublishing.org/content/4/3/160802)
___

**Abstract**

This study investigated the cognitive processing of true and false political information. Specifically, it examined the impact of source credibility on the assessment of veracity when information comes from a polarizing source (Experiment 1), and effectiveness of explanations when they come from one's own political party or an opposition party (Experiment 2). These experiments were conducted prior to the 2016 Presidential election. Participants rated their belief in factual and incorrect statements that President Trump made on the campaign trail; facts were subsequently affirmed and misinformation retracted. Participants then re-rated their belief immediately or after a delay. Experiment 1 found that (i) if information was attributed to Trump, Republican supporters of Trump believed it more than if it was presented without attribution, whereas the opposite was true for Democrats and (ii) although Trump supporters reduced their belief in misinformation items following a correction, they did not change their voting preferences. Experiment 2 revealed that the explanation's source had relatively little impact, and belief updating was more influenced by perceived credibility of the individual initially purporting the information. These findings suggest that people use political figures as a heuristic to guide evaluation of what is true or false, yet do not necessarily insist on veracity as a prerequisite for supporting political candidates. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Psychology of a Trump victory: Donald Trump's supporters believed what he said - and didn't change their vote even if they knew he lied. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-11 07:20:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-11 07:03:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Study (open access): [River logjams cause frequent large-scale forest die-off events in Southwestern Amazonia](http://www.earth-syst-dynam-discuss.net/esd-2017-19/)
___

**Abstract**

This paper investigates the dynamics of logjam-induced floods and alluvium deposition in the Bolivian Amazon and the effects these have on forest disturbance/recovery cycles. It expands on previous work by Gullison et al (1996) who reported a case of catastrophic floods triggered by logjams in the Chimane Forest on the Bolivian Amazon. No further studies have followed up on this observation and no research has been published on the effects of large wood in tropical lowland rivers. The study is based on the analysis of a time series of Landsat imagery (19842016) and field evidence. Results show that logjam-induced floods are a major driver of forest disturbance along the Andean piedmont in the Bolivian Amazon. Logjams form on an almost yearly basis and migrate upriver until an avulsion takes place. Logjam-induced floods are here characterized by a sudden deposition of a thick sand layer and the death of forest in a V-shaped area. The Bolivian Amazon offers a unique opportunity to further research on how large wood affects river behavior in lowland tropical settings and how large and frequent forest disturbance events resulting from river logjams affect forest biodiversity and community successions. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Using more than 30 years of satellite images a new study shows that flooding caused by naturally occurring logjams in the Bolivian Amazon kill off almost as much rainforest as human activity </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-11 07:02:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Study (open access) | Climate change and sea ice: Shipping accessibility on the marine transportation corridor through Hudson Bay and Hudson Strait (19802014) </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-11 06:46:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Study (open access) | Mitigating the risks of rapid event attribution in the gray literature </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-10 03:20:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-10 02:58:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Excellent, thank you. Though the description touches on it I would note the following:

Scientists have hypothesized that, just prior to the Younger Dryas, meltwater fluxes were rerouted from the Mississippi River to the St. Lawrence River... although other possible routings such as to the Mackenzie River cannot be ruled out presently.

Indeed, in '06 Broecker had suggested the Mackenzie River route, though, at the the time lacked evidence to support the theory^[1](http://science.sciencemag.org/content/312/5777/1146) Further examination would lead to confirmation of Broecker's theory years later^[2](http://www.nature.com/nature/journal/v464/n7289/abs/nature08954.html), ^[3](http://www.nature.com/nature/journal/v464/n7289/fig_tab/nature08954_F1.html)

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Study (open access) | Freshening of the Labrador Sea as a trigger for Little Ice Age development </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-09 09:08:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Energy Dept. Scrubs Paris Agreement From Climate Page </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-09 09:06:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Complacency threatens climate change action </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-09 09:03:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
