<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject2274</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-09 19:36:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> And call them [Uterbraten](https://m.youtube.com/watch?t=2m20s v=35Ulwur8brY) . </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-09 19:32:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That's up to you. It apparently wasn't up to you up until that point, according to the slogan order. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-09 19:29:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> But now you have defined what the actual state depends on. Whether you can actually know it is a different question. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-09 16:14:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Right, not as words on a page, but I usually remember them as "a story", which is different from how I remember real events. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-09 16:01:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I first read it the way it was recommended on the prologue, but skipping some of the optional chapters and wandering around to read some random ones.
When re-reading, I just read random chapters, one will remind me of another, and I go find that one.
I still find connected chapters that I hadn't realized. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-09 15:51:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If the materials are worth more than the coin, what would prevent someone from getting a lot of those coins, melt them, and sell them for the material?

The cost of *making* it and the cost of the material are very different. You can offset the cost of making it because of the utility of using it multiple times. You can't prevent people from melting them if the metal is worth more. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-09 15:44:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It was also probably more expensive to make, in relative terms. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> I love the way in which Hopscotch seems like a lived memory rather than a read one. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-09 15:34:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> In the book, you can read the chapters in any order you like.
I recently discussed this with a friend. Hopscotch (by Cortazar) is stored in my memory almost as a lived memory. I think it's because you have to read the story out of order and put together the chronology in your head. Similar to how in real life we remember things related to each other thematically, and then have to think harder to see what happened first. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
