<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject3863</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> U.S. regulator's 'throttling' lawsuit against AT T to be reheard: court </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-10 07:25:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> AP Analysis: Trump thrusts US presidency into perilous area </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-10 07:15:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-10 07:09:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> RT is more or less one of the main links in this entire story. You have no fucking idea what is going on here, so with that said at least read the fucking article and inform your self about topic at hand before you start sharing your wisdom.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Trump thrusts US presidency into perilous area </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-10 07:04:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-10 06:43:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I see that Breitbart and RT are working just as intended.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-10 06:34:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Surprise, surprise, guy that is approximately same size as entire boy band dies from suspected heart attack! You don't say! How did that happened?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-10 06:30:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Wait, you do understand that Republicans control all 4 branches of government plus they have majority of governors. 

I'm sorry but are just not making any sense.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-10 06:19:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> But why? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-10 06:15:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I think that developing treason case against President of United States is pretty big fucking deal.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-10 06:13:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> ... For now, building treason case against President of United States is not as easy as you might think.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-10 06:11:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Only thing is that he didn't lie to President and VP. They knew about it all along, and that is why we have this shit show. Further more Trump is control freak. Chances of him not being directly involved are slim to none.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-10 06:08:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> No need to take day off. I'm sure that we will have national holiday  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-10 06:04:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Which is? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-10 02:27:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> O dear, but why?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-09 21:17:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> No wonder he wanted out. Team tried to trade him numerous times.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-09 20:46:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Link is dead. What happened?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-09 20:20:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Ok, fair enough, next order of business pass bill that requires state officials to call religion brainwashing cult in all public statements. 

Seriously though, what is the penalty if state officials rightfully ignore this bill?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-09 17:59:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah, trough their Facebook page  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-09 17:58:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> One of the reporters said so today live on the air.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-09 17:03:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Majority of B H sales comes form online sales. Work environment at B H is abusive and religiously bias. If you truly want to support independent walk in store than spend your money at Adorama. 

They treat workers as well as costumers with actual respect. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Gubernatorial Primary Debate Update: News12 TV and news12.com will broadcast it live at 6pm for Republicans and 8pm for Democrats </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-09 15:50:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I know that many people don't have access to News 12 so maybe one of you glorious bastards with access and know how could live stream it on youtube.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-09 05:40:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Well, look at it this way. 

First our three letter agencies had problem with Flynn, than Obama told him not to deal with Flynn and he still didn't listen. What makes you think that he would even consider as relevant what she had to say. He knew well everything about Flynn's involvement before she even mentioned it.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-09 05:37:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Obama deported more people than any other president. Get your shit together you brainwashed puppet. 

http://abcnews.go.com/Politics/obamas-deportation-policy-numbers/story?id=41715661 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-09 02:36:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm not questioning that she learned from media or that she didn't even see the order before it was signed. 

What I'm saying is that this particular article is nothing more than load of shit and that people are buying in to it.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-09 02:30:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Wait a second, we knew the day he was scheduled to sign Muslim Ban because it was reported by all media outlets? If nothing else her office was expecting it to happen, even though those idiots didn't officially informed her.

As the matter of fact I remember reading about her statement to the media that she won't enforce the ban and only later that night it was announced that she was fired. 

Don't get me wrong I'm not arguing pro-Trump here I hate the fucker as much as everyone else. I'm just trying to set record straight. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-09 02:19:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> As far as I remember he fired her the day she said she wont enforce Muslim Ban Executive Order. 

Seriously people we all complain about fake and bias news, while we collectively we have a memory of a fucking gold fish. No wonder they can serve us loads of shit on daily bases.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-09 02:14:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> O, I don't know about dentist. That was about 15 years ago ... 

I thought you were asking about article it self :) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-09 02:08:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> According to their website they are still accepting new patients 

https://lifestylesmedical.com </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-09 00:52:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Do prisoners in British prisons commit suicide by stabbing them selfs 63 times with four different Shanks?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-09 00:47:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> O yes they can ... all they have to do is mention Sharia Law and people will lose their minds.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-09 00:46:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Churches have been doing it privately for a long, long time. I have New Jersey priest on tape endorsing Trump inside the church right before the wedding ceremony.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-09 00:43:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Point is no oversight even though the laws are on the books. IRS is already running on skeleton crew, and now he is telling them not in enforce the law.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-08 23:57:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Did article mentioned Hillary?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-08 23:57:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If this is all known why is no one prosecuting them? I get that POTUS gets immunity in some cases, but staffers should be fair game. 

Seriously, can someone rationally explain this without turning it in to political shit show.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-08 23:37:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Why? Were Soviets anti-zoo maybe?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-08 23:31:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If I remember correctly George Harrison financed Life of Brian. He specifically opened production company with the sole purpose to make this movie.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-08 23:23:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Arguably the greatest movie of all time!  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-08 21:49:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Great idea! He can serve as THE WALL it self. Added bonus is all that body odor baking in the hot sun ... Entire border would turn in to lifeless wasteland in no time.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-08 21:44:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Making shirts in parachute factory is not easy or cheap. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-08 21:15:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> www.craigslist.com </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-08 21:07:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Where can we get tickets for Newark debates?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-08 19:50:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah I know ... I was young and naive :)  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-08 19:48:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I think the market would quickly be flooded by people with actual education, training and experience who for one reason or another simply can't get the state to give them their license, e.g. tax issues or child support problems.

Or you know "minor issues" such as medical malpractice, pill pushing, sexual abuse, mental problems, etc ... just to name a few. 

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-08 19:43:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Well, at the time price and pain was my main concern, so I wanted to take care of it as soon and as cheap as possible. 

At the time I never even thought that someone would have balls to illegally practice dentistry in the middle of Manhattan.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-08 19:08:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Not necessarily, some prices are artificially inflated. Several gas stations in my area charge as much as $2.49 for gallon of regular even though as you said price is about $2.20 ... 

For the record these gas stations always had slightly higher prices, but difference was never more than few pennies.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-08 17:34:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I too don't use Facebook ... Maybe someone here is willing to link the stream on Youtube or something ...  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-08 17:25:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Page I linked supposedly should have a live stream or at least provide a link for it. 

... Maybe I should have made that clear in the title :)  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-08 17:19:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> My point it that what happened 2000 years ago is completely irrelevant. 

Just like when people say 2000 years ago we circumcised newborns to prevent infections and deceases, now we do it because of "tradition" ...  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-08 17:15:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yep, it worked for me too!  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-08 17:12:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This could easily be the case of Doctor actually moving to US and than failing to pass exams required to practice medicine America. 

Years ago I actually saw dentist in East Village in Manhattan that was charging cash only and charged me only fraction of what would cost me to do same procedure at legit dental office. 

Interestingly enough he even had waiting room and receptionist. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-08 17:04:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  If anyone has evidence to prove that kosher slaughter was in fact not among the most painless way to kill animals thousands of years ago, please share a link.


Here is the thing, we live in 21st century, and not **thousands of years ago**.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-08 16:56:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I just tried and it is dead.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-08 16:56:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  gofccyourself.com

Unfortunately it is dead now.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-08 16:55:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Maybe it is time to post many, many videos on this matter to r/videos  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Tomorrow, May 9 at 6:30pm and 8pm - Don't forget to watch New Jersey Gubernatorial Primary Debates </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-08 16:47:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-08 16:42:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> There is a lot of articles on this matter yet, not a single source is listing all apps that are using Silverpush. 

Does anyone have this list?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Man posed as doctor for nearly 30 years. New Jersey prosecutor is asking for 6 month prison sentence even though fake doctor already has 3 prior convictions for illegally practicing medicine. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-08 15:44:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-08 15:43:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> New Jersey prosecutor is asking for 6 month prison sentence even though fake doctor already has 3 prior convictions for illegally practicing medicine.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Man posed as doctor for nearly 30 years, state officials charge </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-08 15:36:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-08 04:37:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah ... MURICA ... my ass ...

Maybe you should respect people who truly deserve credit. Some 25 million Russians and few million dead Europeans ...  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-06 04:40:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Those little things are fucking evil! I tried to save one and she bit me. Had to spend 6 fucking hours in ER waiting to get tetanus shot. 

Every single staff member was laughing at me, and no one understood where the fuck did I find squirrel in the middle of Manhattan.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Uber Faces Federal Inquiry Over Use of Greyball Tool to Evade Authorities </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-05 23:51:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-05 17:10:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Well, paint is definitely safer method because you can throw it from a far, but I think that it can easily wiped off with wipers before it dries. 

As far as tips if you guys have any specific questions I'll be glad to answer them if I can. For the record it is not my intention to put anyone in to harms way. It goes without saying that everyone should be careful. No politician is worth your life. 

You should look in to ways to prevent armored vehicles reaching demonstrators in the first place. Our organizers would commander large vehicles (mainly city busses, heavy construction equipment and in some cases disabled police vehicles ) and put them as a road block. 

Additionally you can target tires and engine compartments ( if there is any openings ) ... Fire burning on top of the armored vehicle won't do much, however if tires or engine compartment is on fire it will eventually immobilize vehicle unless they come out to put out the fire. 

To put this all pin prospective we were protesting for about 7 years before following events took place.

Beginning of the end for Milosevic was when construction worker took his bulldozer and symbolically "attacked" building of national television ( dictators propaganda machine ) As soon as that happened people rushed the building as well as both buildings of national parliament and there was no stopping them. 

Here is unedited video of events form that day: https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=fCAdPBZLqTA </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-05 14:55:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I took my mom to Costanera Restaurant in Montclair for her B-day. Food was amazing and prices are fairly reasonable ( about $20-$30 per plate ) best part is that restaurant is BYOB ... For the record I had to make reservation.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> To all protestors. You should start carrying blankets, and here is why. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-05 14:46:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This news inspired me to make this post: http://globalnews.ca/news/3428049/venezuelan-tanks-plow-through-crowds-as-2-month-protest-continues/

So if I'm braking any rules mods please take my post down.

For the record I'm from Yugoslavia and during 90s I was involved in demonstrations agains oppressive regime of Slobodan Milosevic. He too was sending tanks and armored vehicles on civilians so I know for fact this will work. For the record you should all be aware that it is extremely dangerous.


Use blanket to throw it over drivers window or camera they may have on the vehicle. Once their view is obstructed they will be forced to stop and or exit the vehicle in order to remove obstruction.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> NC House Just Passed HB 330  Allowing Drivers To Legally Hit Protesters Who Block Roads </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-05 05:52:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-05 05:44:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Common mods, now we are doing obvious advertising on this sub? 

Seriously OP at least you can be honest and offer Reddit discount or something.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-05 05:41:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Christie is exempt form it. Our beloved leaders exempt them selfs form magnificent healthcare bill they created for us. 

When you will learn that we are fucking peasants and they are royalty.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-05 05:39:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This is not about politics. If this healthcare bill was any good lawmakers ( people creating and voting on it ) would not exempt them selfs from it. 

How fucking hard is it for you to understand that Republicans are fucking us with no lube.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-05 04:41:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hopefully this is beginning of the end for them. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-05 04:35:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That can't be real, can it? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-05 04:33:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Brilliant!  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-05 04:15:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Fucking Wizards are Ghetto Kings  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-05 03:55:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> O wow, IT got a foul </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-05 03:53:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-05 03:49:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I don't know ... They have 16 more championships than Garbage State Warriors? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-05 03:47:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Relax Boston is having shitty game, that is all.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-05 03:42:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> We can't buy a fucking basket or defensive rebound. Wiz deserve to win this one.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-05 03:41:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> We can't buy fucking basket </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-05 03:34:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If you have someone in Serbia they could place legal bet on virtually anything for you.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-05 03:33:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I like your enthusiasm, just stay away form sharp objects when reality sinks in.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-05 03:18:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Fuck Gargamel he will foul out anyway </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-05 03:17:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Gargamel is giving it his all tonight </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-05 03:14:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Why the fuck are they allowing all these offensive rebounds.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-05 03:13:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> W61 B37 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-05 03:11:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> By the end of 3rd you will be crying  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-05 03:07:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I am since I typed that Boston is on 9-2 run :)
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-05 03:07:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Did your fishing trip end early? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-05 03:06:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Ha! Sad.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-05 03:04:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> O yeah, team effort!!!! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-05 03:04:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Wiz can't shoot over 60% entire game  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-05 02:54:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Kelly is playing ball, all you bitches need to grow a fucking pair.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-05 02:52:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Wiz are losing it. I'm expecting full meltdown by the end of 3rd  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-05 02:48:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Out with that little punk ... Why even waste time on him?
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-05 02:41:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Bogdan translates to Godgiven 

Edit: My bad this is Bojan ... His name is not even remotely related to god.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-05 02:36:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Not the same, not even the same ballpark  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-05 02:33:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Agree, one could spend the lifetime trying to get image like this.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-05 02:07:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Can someone please explain how can parasite rationally determine what will eat fish? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-05 01:34:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I hate that loud mouth motherfucker with passion! Now I have one more reason. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-05 01:28:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  yeezys

WTF is yeezy? Why are they so fucking ugly? Most importantly why in the world they cost so fucking much? 

Honestly only uglier shoes that I can think of are those Sketchers that were supposed to help you lose weight. 

No seriously, who is buying in to this shit? 

Edit: Adidas website is even selling those fucking things on credit!!!  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-05 01:20:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Damn ... If idiots are willing to spend that on pair of gym shoes who is he to deny them.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-05 01:13:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Soo, few hundred dollars for pair of Jordans is not overcharging? Got it!!!

Just out of curiosity how much are they charging for shoes in question.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-05 01:10:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> There might be something there, but you need to work on delivery ;) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Former Nba Player 'Fly' Williams Among 13 Charged In Major Brooklyn Heroin Bust </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-04 22:42:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Meet 7 NY House Representatives that voted YES to repeal and replace Affordable Care Act </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-04 22:40:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Meet Congressman Tom MacArthur and Rodney Frelinghuysen. These two representatives voted today to repeal and replace Affordable Care Act. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-04 22:32:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Here is now to contact them and let them know what you think about it: 

[Tom MacArthur](https://macarthur.house.gov)

[Rodney Frelinghuysen](https://frelinghuysen.house.gov) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-04 22:24:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Would it be possible to see NJ votes?

Edit: never mind I found it ... https://www.nytimes.com/interactive/2017/05/04/us/politics/house-vote-republican-health-care-bill.html </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-04 22:18:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> No, not one bit. However I'm concerned for the sport it self and judging by what happened in other major sports chances of top level athletes not taking PEDs in this league are slim to none.

We are talking about the league that only follows basic minimum standards by occasionally slapping on the wrist mediocre players. Heck they didn't even test for PEDs until two or three seasons ago. 

For the record I'm not saying that LeBron is alone in this, many players do shit that human bodies are not designed to handle, I don't care how much work you put in to it.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-04 20:29:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Ok great, can we start testing/talking about PED's now?

 No? 

Who cares about FairPlay when we have all these magnificent stats to circle jerk over, right?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-04 20:20:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If nothing else people living there should have rights as tenants, right? Landlords can't evict someone just because they were in hospital or they were away for any other reason. Even if that tenant is on section A for example.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-04 18:49:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> ... And that is why he supported Hillary to begin with ... Fuck Bill Maher and everyone like him. We don't need fucking hypocrites.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-04 18:42:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> My close relative is Vegan Celiac ... I fucking hate eating out with him. Thankfully we live few hours apart so we don't go to restaurants often :)  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-04 18:39:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Medical conditions and made up religious bullshit is not the same, so don't mix those two together please.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-04 18:36:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  ... Flight attendant proceeds to activate ejection seat </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-04 18:34:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I have no food restrictions, and I still don't trust airline to provide decent meal in economy class ... Always bring extra food and water with you.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-04 17:42:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I feel bad for poor bastard editing that ceremony </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-04 17:35:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So by that reasoning Spanish, Chinese, French and Tagalog should all be official languages in United States, right? 

Also I know form personal experience that Albanians are not teaching children language of the home country ( I'm talking about kids in their early teens ) and I'm not talking about some random villages. I'm talking about kids living in cities that can't communicate with their neighbors. 

That in my opinion is outrageous and unacceptable and most importantly clearly shows intent of divide and separation.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-04 17:33:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That is fucking horrifying ... Why is no one challenging it in court?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Remember "Death Panels"? Maybe we should ask politicians about preexisting condition? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-04 17:00:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-04 16:46:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Dude why are you ignoring entire situation leading up to him taking the office? What you are comparing is apples and oranges? You are either not familiar whit what has been going on in Macedonia since it's independence or you are trying to downplay Albanian nationalism for whatever reason.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-04 16:27:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Kosovo is independent for now. Uniting Kosovo with Albania is already underway. Unofficially they are already united on so many levels. 

As far as flag, in this context that is clearly provocation. Nothing more nothing less. Talat Xhaferi is first and foremost Macedonian who was born and raised there as well as his parents, grandparents, etc ... He did not immigrated to Macedonia. Further more he served in Yugoslav and well as Macedonian army as officer for close to 20 years. 

Flying foreign flag is acceptable during official visits. Flying it next to Macedonian flag on the desk in one of the most important offices in the country is disrespectful to all Macedonians to say the least. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-04 15:31:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Albanians are trying to create ["Greater Albania"](https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Greater_Albania) and take over parts of Montenegro, Serbia ( they already annexed Kosovo ), Macedonia and Greece.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-04 05:08:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Trump is a fan. Big fan. Just ask anyone. That I can tell you! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-04 05:07:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> They were talking about LeBron James and not about Isaiah Thomas.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-04 05:03:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Kelly? But why Kelly? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> U.S. firm in Iraq ignores smuggling, security risks for F-16s </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-04 04:06:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> U.S. firm in Iraq ignores smuggling, security risks for F-16s </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-04 04:03:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-04 03:08:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So what you are saying is that I should be happy about innocent dying over someones personal interest that is wrapped in nationalism? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-04 03:03:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Actually, I'm part Albanian. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-04 02:50:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You are an idiot. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-04 02:44:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> They are working on creating "Big Albania" ... Mark my words. Albanians will start another civil war, just like they did in Kosovo and US will back them 100%.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-04 02:39:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Received two emails yesterday on my private account. Didn't have to even think about it, body of the email looked really shady. I just reported them as spam without even thinking.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-04 02:12:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Good for them, US judges should do it to, along with presidents. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-04 02:09:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That is because everyone drops the ball and holds their hands over their junk since they know that league is letting him get away with murder </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> New Macedonian speaker brings Albanian flags to his office </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-04 02:01:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-04 01:56:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Protestors should dance their way in to his compound and give him the same treatment that Rumanians give to Nicolae Ceauescu. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-04 01:52:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> True plenty, but thankfully not majority that is precisely why HRC could not beat weakest fucking candidate in history  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-04 00:53:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Problem is Trump didn't steal anything, he won fair and square ( probably with the help of Putin, but nothing is proven yet ) 

Democratic Party Leadership is the one to blame. Plain and simple. They are the ones who fucked up royally and as long as they don't own up to it and fucking leave we will have this farce of governing.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-04 00:48:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Problem is that people how made mistake don't see it that way ... I'm talking about current Democratic Party leadership and people who voted for Trump. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-04 00:47:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I heard he likes Cavs </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-04 00:44:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Why? He stepped waist deep in to a pond while doing his job ... 

It just goes to show how fucked up our society is that mundane "incident" such as this one gets all this attention. Heck I'm willing to bet that 100 out of 100 rational adults would do same exact thing without thinking twice.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-04 00:39:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You mean to tell me that any other rational adult would not step in to waste deep pond to pull out a fucking kid? 

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-04 00:33:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> All these years I thought of Kobe as selfish prick ... as it turns out I was wrong all along.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-04 00:29:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Flair up of shut up  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-04 00:28:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Respek!!! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-04 00:26:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Suns GM is true MVP! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-04 00:25:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Good job Kings front office and special thanks to Suns GM! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-03 23:48:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> O, I too can remember about half dozen numbers from my past, problem is "newer" numbers ... 

Just like driving directions, ever since I started using GPS 15+ years ago I'm fucking lost without it. On the other hand if you would ask me how to get to my grandparents village in the middle of Serbian mountains I could probably give you turn by turn directions without any problems even though I didn't go there since mid 90s ... lol  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-03 22:55:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This! I can barely remember my home landline number ... Didn't use that number in years. We just keep it around for various forms, applications, intrusive companies, etc ...  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-03 22:52:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Businesses will, when I opened my office few years ago clients were telling me that initially they were on the fence to contact us because we had 862 area code, so I ended up changing all numbers to 973 ... Thankfully I paid only $20 or so dollars per line so that wasn't bad at all.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-03 21:49:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Only right answer </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-03 21:46:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This is true, virtually all dealerships on east coast have at leasts sticker. Fancy ones even have metal badges such as [this one](http://www.ebay.com/itm/VINTAGE-DEALER-BADGE-CAR-DEALERSHIP-RAY-CATENA-UNION-MERCEDES-BENZ-NEW-JERSEY-/131723793604) and by the looks of it they are even collectible and people pay good money for them.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-03 19:29:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Entire article and most of the comments acknowledge that.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-03 06:37:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This is beyond pathetic  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-03 06:28:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Those complaining about German police should stop by USA </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-03 06:24:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Their salty comments make every victory so much sweeter!  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-03 06:21:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> No gold for ugly flairs  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-03 06:20:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> ... And that is how you get gaming console and truck load of ice cream  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-03 06:14:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Toothless Fucking Royalty!!! Gotta love IT! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-03 06:11:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Who said Boston will let him walk? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-03 06:06:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> No one in their right mind is vacationing in Cleveland  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-03 05:12:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What do you mean for no reason? They have to create some sort of paper trail in an attempt to protect killer. 

What is wrong with these fake news reporters? They should get with the program. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-03 05:05:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So in the words of great IT where are Wizards going on vacation? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-03 05:04:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> O dear! ... Lolol </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-03 05:02:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Best fucking game of the season </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-03 05:02:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What did he say? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-03 05:00:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> **PURE FUCKING MADNES** </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-03 04:56:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> 2pt, foul and Morris out! What else can you ask for? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-03 04:52:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> AB MOFO!!!! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-03 04:50:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Twin is next </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-03 04:47:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Alright boys, no more fucking around unleash The Swede  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-03 04:44:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Uhhh </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-03 04:43:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This is by far best game I saw this season! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-03 04:33:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Can this game get any better? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-03 04:27:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> fucking wizards </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-03 04:25:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> They know excellence when they see it.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-03 03:14:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What makes you say that? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-03 03:13:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Your comment shows how much Cavs fans know about basketball </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-03 02:18:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> No, it is not. Hidden gems are beautiful for reason, you don't have to go around broadcasting shit to everyone.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-02 20:06:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Coke is expensive now days  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-02 19:46:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> To be fair most of us don't want Fat Bastard as governor ... It seems like what majority want is irrelevant.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-02 19:43:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> 202 is a fucking mess anyway, just imagine how bad it will be if they close it unexpectedly.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-02 17:29:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm talking about NYC Tri-State area.

* First and foremost brand spanking new wardrobe head to toe usually accompanied by DSLR ( you have to look good for pictures ) 

* Walking side by side 4 people wide and everyone is looking up causing everyone around them to rip their hair out. 

* Not tipping waiting staff

   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-02 16:50:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> No  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-02 16:47:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Fuck off. 

You can't ban people just because they comment on some sub no matter what that sub is.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-02 16:44:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Naturalized American here, it is perfectly normal everywhere except here ... I remember Chicago couple ( originally form Serbia ) getting in trouble few years ago for sharing pictures of their newborn baby taking a bath on Facebook. They made huge fucking deal out of it and even some local media outlets covered the story. 

Paranoid people with fake morals are really fucking loud in America.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-02 16:36:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Since Trump is planning to cutting funding and allow drilling we should talk about National Parks. In my opinion it is extremely important to preserve them.

So with that said vote for **National Parks**. Do it! Do it now!! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-02 16:23:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> OP you found Pennsylvania driver in Europe!  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-02 15:40:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I knew it! I fucking knew it! It was a land whale.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-02 06:59:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Lol. You are so full of shit it is actually amusing  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-02 06:58:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This was 4 months ago, we have attacks in public places ( many of them deadly ) on weekly if not daily basses, yet best you can do it pull up 4 month old article. Sad. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-02 06:56:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Really? Why are you than fallowing my comments and reply to everything I write no matter if I was talking to you or not? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-02 06:52:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What about it? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-02 06:49:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Maybe you could shed a light on this matter. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-02 06:42:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> NRA bots are working overtime on this one  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-02 06:37:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Civilians?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
