<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject2868</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-09 17:28:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm genuinely glad you and others were able to experience that for a while. 

I guess I should be doing my research on Asia and South America... maybe somewhere super far out in Queens. I've heard Berlin is the closest thing in Europe. 

I'm fortunate in that I make enough money to live pretty much anywhere, so I guess it's more about finding the right people.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-09 17:08:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thanks for the reply. I agree with your examples and have lived in places like that - this will sound elitist but I found the art/writing scenes to be more amateurish than I expected. Maybe the problem is that I didn't find the right people - so maybe a better question is, **are there any collectives out there that are wildly talented but not necessarily that famous yet?** It's more about the network of people, they could be living in Nowheresville.

Maybe there are examples in Asia, Africa, and South America that I'm just not aware of. 

And finally, to your point, I think a big part of the change is the internet/telecom - people aren't necessarily forced to congregate to exchange ideas, so movements become more diffuse and harder to recognize. It's a lonelier world in some ways.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Where is Hemingway's Paris today? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-09 16:49:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> My question is: where can you find a place in the world today that is similar to Paris as described in A Moveable Feast? 

I.e., where lots of artists and intellectuals from diverse backgrounds converge in once place because they know they will find like-minded people there.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-07 01:50:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Serious question on the rules: how is this not a verbal tap? Theoretically it could have happened because of some unseen sub attempt from Dillon. I don't get how this turns into a time out. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-29 16:58:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This is the answer. The point of drilling is to learn a movement. Going HAM in drills is asinine - that's not drilling, it's sparring (positional sparring I guess). 

Next time just say "Hey man, I'm trying to practice this movement. I don't think I've got it down well enough to go live. Can you let up a bit? Maybe go 20%?"  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-29 16:51:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Judging by the number of downvotes you got, I guess a lot of people are mad cuz they believed those vids were real </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-28 22:24:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thanks for your wisdom on the zeitgeist, but like I said elsewhere, calling somebody a "street thug" to boost views is a shitty thing to do and deserves to be called out.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-28 20:24:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> IIRC these were before Henatch existed. Sorry, I mean, before his first of 27 World Championships - obviously he is the GOAT. But yeah Rhaasan was in at least one pretending to be a Thug Fu guy.  

Anyway, they now claim it was just to troll their own students and IIRC changed the public youtube titles to make it more obvious that it was just a prank, bro </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-28 20:20:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Sure, but publicly labeling somebody a "street thug" to get more youtube views is a shitty thing to do.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-28 16:52:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yup. The way they frame this video is extremely shitty. 

1. I see no evidence that he's doing anything thuggish. If anything he seemed pretty funny and chill.

2. 10p has a history of staging fights/challenges as a "joke" (aka to make themselves look cool)

In the absence of additional context I'm calling this typical 10p marketing bullshit.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-26 20:27:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> 100% this. Grappling clubs in college can be straight-up bonkers. All the variation in styles and backgrounds coming together along with relatively young ages and less oversight, it can be a wild environment. 

I think starting out in that type of club made me a much more well-rounded grappler. I'm comfortable dealing with spazzes because I've seen just about EVERY type of bad behavior. You quickly develop a very safe and protected game that translates well to tournaments and self-defense.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-26 17:41:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Happened to me twice - both times when I was a white belt rolling against visiting purples. Though I sucked in certain areas (still do) I had been working hard on my A-game and just caught them. 

Ryan Hall says in a DVD that if a white belt does a technique perfectly, it's no different than a black belt doing it perfectly - it's gonna work. 

I also happen to have a very old-school style and simply dont relinquish an advantage after I get it. Build up enough little advantages and you're going to submit them even if they're good and you suck (overall on average)

This is overkill but to be extra nice, maybe for a while try to match people's pace vs. setting the tempo and see how that goes. I got tapped more when I started doing this but it also allowed me to explore more areas of my game (escapes, guard retention, etc.) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-01 03:10:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> heel hook in retaliation for a strike? you must be doing some wack local tournaments if you've seen matches turn into real fights more than once. did you compete in 90s Rio or something? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-21 16:15:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Me too (   ) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-21 04:04:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Actually not correct. Sudden mechanical pressure on the carotid artery activates baroreceptors that usually monitor your blood pressure. They interpret the choking pressure as a sudden rise of blood pressure and this triggers a reflex that causes blood vessels to dilate to reduce it, even though your overall blood pressure has not actually risen. This reflex is actually what causes syncope (unconsciousness) at least initially. That's why BJJ chokes cause unconsciousness so quickly - in fact there's plenty of blood still in the brain to otherwise maintain consciousness  (at least for longer than you might expect.)

Source: Have choked hundreds of people </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-15 19:44:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> happy cakeday to the ground </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-12 00:47:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's understandable that you're posting this in a BJJ forum, but you're actually mistaken. Seph Smith teaches **Ground Karate**, not BJJ. The two are commonly confused. For reference: https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=x-I401NweC8 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-20 15:02:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> so you're that guy everyone has to spot when you go to cash-only places? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-09 01:57:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> no. his own actions say it. as in: i am judging him purely based his own self-professed actions, and also based on straightforward facts (comp video of him as a blue belt, promo video to "brown belt," etc.) 

you clearly have some stake in this and are interpreting the facts differently. i cant blame you for that. but you can't tell me these are not facts. 

like i said, there's a sucker born every minute, but nobody wants to admit they're one of them. 

there's a simple thing you could do to convince all of us, and that is post a video of ari rolling where he shows technical proficiency (asking his permission of course). he would have done this by now to clear his name if he could. 

hell i'd love to even hear a written account from you on what it's like to roll with him. i would 100% keep an open mind for this.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-08 22:11:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> i think you mean completely justified, evidence-based, and well-cited judgements. 

people like ari make a living because there's a sucker born every minute. 

the sad thing is if he trained half as much as he self-promotes, he would be at least a solid amateur black belt by now. but he wouldnt have all that money from scamming people into attending seminars and buying ersatz instructional dvds  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-08 21:23:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> "brown belt"

FTFY. His brown belt promotion video is one of the funniest bjj-related vids ive ever seen. Absolute joke. 

You could very generously say that him misrepresenting his rank was all just a big misunderstanding and youthful error. But the fact that he owned his own gym while getting wrecked by white belts in competition is hilarious. 

Im sure he is perfectly nice in person, but he's also a narcissist hack fraud pathological liar with delusions of grandeur.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-15 20:14:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Classic rookie mistake showcased here. Of course the mistake I'm referring to is calling the MANSITION a technique. Obviously it's not a technique at all. It's a way of life. It's not about moves, it's about moveMENT. Or should I say moveMANt. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-06 06:10:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> OK, I know this is not one word, but it is a classic:

"That is not only not right, it is **not even wrong**."

https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Not_even_wrong

Pauli said this one. Basically he's saying their argument is not even coherent enough to evaluate the rightness or wrongness of it. For insultees who know and/or care what this means, that's about as brutal as it gets.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-30 14:11:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I get what you're trying to do, playing the heel and everything.


But you should ask someone clever/funny to write it for you, because you are not those things. 

Also your hair looks stupid. Good luck! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-09 17:32:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I love Eddie, but you really gotta take his stories with a grain of salt. He gives some kind of elaborate explanation like this for nearly every match he has lost. 

This story for example is hyperbole at best. One of my first instructors was a spectator at this event and he tells the same story, but the crowd's reaction was nowhere near what was described here. And the sub wasn't as close as he made it sound.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-04 20:58:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> +1 to this. i think the typical signals for who is good can be deceptive, but this one is almost always true. 

take top position for example. 

people who think they're real good will sort of lean back, lazily look around for a submission, maybe talk to someone on the sidelines if they're really clowning you. when bottom guy moves, they surf them to the other side, etc.  

people who are actually real good have their head glued down the whole time, they already know what sub they're going for and are constantly inching toward it from the beginning. there is absolutely no space. they dont have to surf on you because you cant move without breaking your own neck on the crossface. the soul is being sucked out of you. a feeling of pure futility takes over. you had no chance. they were glued to the position they wanted from the beginning split second.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-23 21:02:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You'll get a lot of mileage out of Ryan Hall's Deep Half Guard dvd if you like the Electric Chair. 

The Electric Chair used to be my #1 highest percentage move, and is still one of them, but I don't use Eddie's setups anymore. I find his setups really expose your neck for the crossface and other very bad things because of how far you have to reach, even in the best of circumstances. 

I personally think you'll have an easier time and take less damage if you go for it using some of Ryan's dogfight-like setups rather than Eddie's usual setups. Especially if you dont have super long arms.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-22 21:00:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Geo and Denny I get, but I am curious to see how Orchard develops. There are some serious, serious holes in his game that are not obvious when you've got two guys going balls-to-the-wall (e.g., him vs. Baret) but are really obvious when his opponent is being patient and strategic (e.g., him vs. Denny... and [him vs. the no-name blue belt that beat him recently](https://www.facebook.com/video.php?v=730750193669345 set=vb.100002031140578 type=2 theater))

I really like the 32-man idea. Moar EBI! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-22 20:50:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Happy to help! 

Your MMA coach sounds pretty good. If you're interested in self defense, honestly I would just casually ask him for tips once in a while - focused on what types of moves should be your go-to for self-defense situations. This will be things like simple/safe takedowns (e.g., basic single-leg, or double underhooks to trip from the back), how to protect your face with your hands, and how to be disciplined in your base and footwork. EDIT: And breakfalls. Seriously breakfalls are the MOST important thing in my experience, second only to having a good base/sprawl so you don't just get bum-rushed over. 

That's all the average person needs for self-defense. I'm concerned that the HJJ would be a waste of your time at best, or at worst it will dilute your focus for what's actually useful when you end up in a self-defense situation. Self defense is more about a mindset (e.g., run away from guns and knives) than it is about a specific set of moves.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-22 19:58:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That's a great question and I'm sorry to see that your original post has been down-voted. This is a BJJ forum, so no question you will get a bias in favor of BJJ. But the thing to realize is that you'll also get a bias in favor of wrestling and catch (CACC). The reason being that they are proven to work. So that's probably why the HJJ question didn't go over too well. 

To your question about knowing if it's legit MMA, it's pretty hard to answer without more info. What's the background of the folks teaching it? Huge red flag if it's the same people who teach everything else. 

If the MMA instructor teaches grappling, do you know their background or lineage? If it has never once come up casually, that's not a great sign. Not that people should be bragging about it, but generally you know if someone started as a D1 wrestler or something becuase it's just naturally part of their bio. 

EDIT: Adding more helpful advice - from what you've told us, I think you'd be better off looking for one of the following:

* A cheap Judo club

* A boxing gym

* A cheap wrestling club

* A serious muay thai gym

You're generally going to get more mileage out of a place that only does one thing because they typically have more and more consistent classes. 
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-22 19:38:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Let me start by saying I fucking love EBI and what it is doing for the sport. 

But I feel that Eddie is really limiting its potential by using it to put a spotlight on his fighters, some of whom are way overrated. I have nothing against Nate Orchard, seems like a good guy and promising fighter, but he is astoundingly over-hyped. 

I know it's not realistic to expect that he wouldnt include his own fighters, but I would love to see Eddie make more room for higher-level grapplers and not focus so much on promoting the affiliation.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-22 19:26:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What kind of qualifications does the MMA coach have?

I say this with all respect, but it sounds like you're not really training MMA either, to be honest. Sounds like theyre doing MMA as a typical McDojo add-on. 

I would honestly suggest switching gyms - find a place that does legit muay thai, for example.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-19 07:55:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I apply heavy crossface pressure (shoulder of justice) from side control, then with my other hand, I mess with their far wrist as if going for a kimura. 

Generally folks will fight hard to keep that elbow tight to their side, because doing so blocks the kimura. However, it also tends to leave their neck wide open. So while they're thinking about the kimura, I just switch my crossface into the N/S choke position and circle-step to N/S from side control. 

People walk themselves into this sub constantly, because them defending the kimura properly is actually what gives you the opportunity to snatch the N/S choke.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-14 18:52:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I am trying to understand what's getting in the way of better match-ups. For example, and I ask this with all respect, is Nathan Orchard overrated? 

Seems like he is often hyped, his name constantly comes up, and yet he consistently fails to perform. 

Honest question: where does the hype come from - what has he done in the past to justify it? Maybe I'm missing something.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [Spoilers] What Dana White actually said about the TUF finale </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-12 17:16:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-09-22 21:16:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> sweet, even better. 

also, you can turn it into a "hip lock" too, depending on the position. e.g., when guard passing against the knee shield, I'll do a kind of "omoplata" motion against their top leg while still remaining upright.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-09-22 21:02:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> that is literally exactly my favorite move down to the position of every limb and grip. from seated position: reap knee, kick out other leg, heel hook. I don't think I've ever seen someone else do it, much less in competition (for obvious reasons). 

sick video, thank you </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The beautiful dying art of Neon sign manufacturing in Kowloon (2014) 11m (X-post: /r/documentaries) </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-30 00:40:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-14 22:53:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I partially agree. Awesome that she can handle it and  awesome that he (presumably) didn't go easy on her because of her gender. 

But he spazzed a lot (e.g. the armbar escape attempt kick near the end). Spazzing is always bad regardless of who you're training with. Bad technique and people (any person) could get hurt. If some of that spazzing comes from ego, then it's especially bad. 

Look at the spazzy headlock and uncontrolled forearms in face at the beginning. Anybody would get called out for that at my gym for being unsafe, regardless of their training partner.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-12 07:21:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> please try to do better </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-07 15:58:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> top guy has absolutely no pressure and is reaching way too much with his arms (I guess trying to block those rabbit punches). cool to see RG work as intended but I'd rather see it against somebody using fundamentally sound posture while in guard. sitting way back and reaching is not how good grapplers or MMA fighters pass any guard, including RG.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-27 20:10:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> i can understand why you would think this, except you're thinking about ryan circa 2011 fighting in a pure sport context. the rules dictate the style. ryan is one of the most adamant "takedown - mount/HG - GNP" guys out there

EDIT: FYI I didn't downvote you. I think your comment is pretty understandable based on the prevailing info out there.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-27 19:09:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> yeah, in terms of work ethic he deserves it. he is one dedicated motherfucker. if he wants to get good at something, he will, or die trying. my buddies who train with him say he's shadowboxing around the academy all day.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-27 19:05:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> off-topic: it makes me happy to see white belts battling right behind murilo santana. for some reason, the inclusiveness of that makes me love bjj even more.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-27 19:02:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> yes, these days he spends like 90% of his time (exaggeration) training mma.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-27 19:01:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> yup, confirmed by his wife Jen Hall on facebook. 

answering some questions in this thread:

**why?** his goal is to do MMA

**will he get it?** personality-wise, ryan is absolutely the antithesis of reality show people. so it's up to the producers

**should he do it?** selfishly I hope he doesnt get it. i want him to be successful but i dont like change. EDIT: To clarify, I also fucking hate TUF personally, but it makes perfect sense as a career move for him breaking into big-time MMA </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [Serious] What beers do they most often drink? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-09 00:44:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I've spotted the New Glarus Brewery's Spotted Cow (label here: http://img1.findthebest.com/sites/default/files/675/media/images/Spotted_Cow_840668.png)

What else do they drink, you fucks?

SERIOUS REPLIES ONLY PLEASE

EDIT: Just kidding about the serious replies. Seriously.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-06 19:22:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I interpreted this vid more as demonstrating a fundamental concept than a specific move you want to drill. Floating on your opponent is key to high-level guard passing, and this is a nice demonstration of the float in action. 

I do most of my passing like this, and in my experience, the float helps because if the bottom guy moves toward my back, it's easier to feel this coming and react if I'm floated vs. trying to hang back like most people do. It's making him carry your weight and falling through the cracks vs. trying to find a way around. 

I recommend the following for a better explanation of what you see in this video:

* Jeff Glover is a master of this - check out his neat stability ball vids

* Ryan Hall guard passing DVD

* Marcelo has a nice DLR pass that involves floating in the opposite direction (backstepping) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-02 22:28:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I don't agree with the operational definitions of their numbering scheme. By this list I guess I'm 2-3. 

By my own estimation I roll at about 30% of max on average, maybe 50% in tournaments. The only time I would even approach 70-80% is when I have to finish - specifically: in a tournament, with a sub locked in, down on points, with only a few seconds left. 

It's a marathon, not a sprint, including (especially?) in tournaments.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
