<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject7026</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-09 19:41:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hah, I just looked, it's still messed up. You would think Amazon would anticipate things like this..  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-09 17:31:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Me too thanks  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-09 17:30:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Great article. Glad to hear he started writing again after all those years. Inspiring!  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-09 16:47:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> For many of us it is new. It was released in the United States today.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-09 16:44:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Found this in an article from the New Yorker.

"Scheherazade was included in a collection of stories you recently published in Japan, titled Men Without Women, all of which involve men who are withoutor who losewomen. What inspired you to write this series?"

"What I wish to convey in this collection is, in a word, isolation, and what it means emotionally. Men Without Women is a concrete example of that. The title grabbed me first (of course, Hemingways short-story collection of the same title figured in), and the stories followed. Each story came from the vibrations produced by the title. Why Men Without Women? I dont know. Somehow or other, that title put down roots in my mind, in the same way that a wind-blown seed settles and grows in some field."

Source: http://www.newyorker.com/books/page-turner/fiction-this-week-haruki-murakami-2014-10-13 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-09 15:08:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Nice! How's it looking? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-09 13:40:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> GOOD point </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Haruki Murakami's new short story collection "Men Without Women" out today. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-09 13:37:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-08 19:49:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> OP here. Sorry guys. Didn't know this was from a movie, saw it on Facebook where it was posted by someone as being an actual event. My bad.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-08 16:48:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Those are rookie numbers man. You gotta pump up those numbers. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Haitian woman with a machete </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-08 16:34:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-07 04:04:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> My man, that goes without saying. Eeww-readers don't even smell like books.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Interesting new study finds that male readers tend to have bigger cocks than non-readers. Also women readers reportedly have more awesome titties than non-reading women on average. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-06 23:51:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Not really too surprised though, as I myself read many many books and happened to be blessed with a very big dick, not to brag or anything.. Anyway, anyone one else heard about this gem the handmaids tale? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-04 18:26:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That's a funny way to spell Flowers for Algernon. I'm just so moved and destroyed by this story I can't even jerk it right now...  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-04 04:28:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Jesus Christ.. Every day it's the same shit. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-26 16:54:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Have you read tortilla flat? I thought it was even funnier than Cannery.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Jeff VanderMeer's New Novel, Borne, Released Today </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-25 21:30:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> In a world of shit sandwiches.. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-25 20:26:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> In a world of shit sandwiches there was a dream. There was a building. There was an underground building. In a world of shit sandwiches there was an underground building. There was a building of hallways and tables. Table after table placed inside hallway after hallway as far as the eye could see. Thousands of shit sandwiches on these tables. A drunken Minotaur stumbles and is confused by the sheer amount of these goddamn intoxicating sandwiches. Why so many sandwiches? One was nice. Two was not too bad. But this was just too much. Too many shit sandwiches. One can just never eat ALL the shit sandwiches. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-13 19:20:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> http://youtu.be/FaWgRw78Y1M </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-12 23:20:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I would have enjoyed it more if there was less piss. Literally in like every scene someone is pissing on someone.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-28 23:32:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Exactly. This is a great summary.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-28 22:53:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Except the letters don't prove the White House blocked her. I feel like no one here actually bothered to read them. 

Here they are:
https://apps.washingtonpost.com/g/documents/national/read-the-letters-detailing-how-sally-yates-was-blocked-from-testifying-on-russia/2390/

I hate trump as much as anyone else here but this is a wildly misleading headline from WAPO. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-28 22:32:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Did no one here actually read the letters? I did. Spicy is unfortunately correct on this one. I hate trump as much as the next guy but there is nothing in those letters showing White House blocked Yates. 

Obviously the White House could have just told nunes on the low down to shut down the whole thing if they were worried about yates, but that's just speculation at this point. 

Edit: here are the letters https://apps.washingtonpost.com/g/documents/national/read-the-letters-detailing-how-sally-yates-was-blocked-from-testifying-on-russia/2390/ </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-28 21:06:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I actually read the letters. What spicy says here is correct, and the headlines for that story from wapo are definitely misleading. However the White House could have just told nunes to shut it down if they were worried about Yates.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-24 13:04:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Boone  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-16 23:21:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> At the mountains of madness is much better enjoyed after reading his short stories. It's not a good starting point for lovecraft in my opinion.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-13 13:25:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Exactly. I look at it like this. If an adult is sitting around all day and watching the Disney channel it would be weird (or should be at least) but because these people are consuming media for kids via a book they feel like it's totally normal. It's literally an immature thing to do. But like everyone says if that's what their into so be it. I'm not going to call them out on it in public or anything. But yeah, I'll silently judge them. Maybe I'm just an asshole though. 

Edit: I feel like I should also say that reading kids books probably isn't any worse than watching reality TV or playing call of duty all the time though. Our culture has become pretty stupid in general.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
