<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject2122</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-09 04:31:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Marketing was smart enough to release a trailer that showed some of the action scenes, which always sell regardless of country. The cast is also pretty popular at the moment. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-08 21:15:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> $60 million OW

$175 Domestic

Hopefully it does very well, because this looks like it cost a fortune. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-08 17:05:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I groaned every time I saw "The Lawrence Welk Show" title card. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-07 21:19:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> *Sighs* 

We're not going to re-sign him are we? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-07 06:38:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Okay </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-07 06:20:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Oscar Isaac after Episode 8.

Jessica Chastain also seems to have a sense of humor. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-06 05:24:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Is Vanessa leaving for sure? Because I know Bobby leaving is likely due to him having offers for pilots. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-06 00:32:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> But if we were to trade D'Armand one day, he'd be an iron man at the catching position for his new team... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-05 23:31:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> M'comrade. Or whatever the female version of "comrade" is. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-05 22:14:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> https://twitter.com/dril/status/685870817528442881

This tweet is begging to be framed. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-05 05:44:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> SEND THE CHECK!! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> I guess Pepsi pulled out their sponsorship </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-05 01:44:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-04 23:43:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Well, SNL did do an ad last year where they called Trump supporters Nazis so maybe this could actually happen. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-04 23:42:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> His scene in Smokin' Aces where he "talks" to Ben Afflecks character is both hilarious and sad. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-04 08:26:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Damn she's good

-Daniel Day-Lewis watching those promos </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-03 09:14:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Side note: Can anyone help me find the track that plays over the montage at the end where the, uh, "cooking" gets out of control? It has some heavy guitar in it. Thanks! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-03 04:13:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I've always thought it sounded like a scientific institution. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Perhaps one of the most complicated and fascinating relationships of the 21st century: wint and the trolls. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-03 02:25:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-01 19:37:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> How Woke Are You?

A game show sketch where Kyle plays a high schooler who want to take down seemingly dumb jock (Chris Pine) by asking him tough questions about what's going on in the world today. The plan backfires when it turns out he answers every question in a perfect, concise manner. Melissa and Pete play the other participants who also have beef with the jock. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-30 06:07:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I think Ben Wheatley would actually be a great choice for directing a Suicide Squad sequel. Oh well. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-29 11:32:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> *Scraeming </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-27 19:53:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> http://screenrant.com/blade-runner-2049-cinemacon-footage-jared-leto/

Here ya go </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-26 21:29:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Quick question: why are there so many Chicagoans in Phoenix? Just curious. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-26 18:02:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Two good men are dead, and you guys are fighting over who's going to be the next big hotshot, huh? Is that what's happening?! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-23 20:30:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Unfortunately, this is going to get like a 30% on Rotten Tomatoes and the consensus will say something like "movie does not take full advantage of its premise." </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Chris Pine played a psychotic, Neo-Nazi hitman in Smokin' Aces, while Ryan Reynolds was a leading-man-like FBI agent in the same movie. Both would later be best known for their performances as Captain Kirk and Deadpool. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-22 09:31:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-22 00:43:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> La La Land- This is where I spent most of my time imagining a better movie!

Hidden Figures- I hope they stay there! (Hidden.) (This is where the audience would hiss probably.

Hacksaw Ridge- I liked it better when it was just called "Saw"!

Fences- Please make it bigger, Trump! (Audience hisses again)

Manchester by the Sea- Casey Affleck living in the shadow of an older brother. Original much?!

Hell or High Water- One-way ticket to the former, please!

Arrival- Where's the "Departure" sign?!

Lion- I'd rather get eaten by one than watch this movie!

Moonlight- Boyhood but with a gay, black male? (Eye roll). I'd make an actual joke but the audience members are being sissys after that Trump joke!  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-20 18:28:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Genuinely surprised it's Leslie. If someone from SNL would've made this list, I'd figure it'd be McKinnon or maybe Baldwin. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-19 22:15:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Trainwreck also lasted way longer than it needed to. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-19 22:01:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Big fan of both of you! Which directors would each of you like to work with in the future, given the chance? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-19 01:14:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hanks- (Not a bad one in the episode, though the one where Hanks played Sully was kind of forgettable. Any questions? ;)

Chappelle- (Not a fan of Sheila Sovage, but everything else was great.)

Johannson- (Also not a fan of Shanice Goodwin. Solid all-around though.)

Baldwin- (Actually glad this wasn't a Trump-a-thon, as Baldwin proved why he's a good host. I'd watch the whole episode again, but I'd skip the fart sketch,)

Stewart- (Surprisingly a very good episode. They played well to Stewart's strengths.)

Louis CK- (The only thing I didn't like in this one was the O'Reilly/Trump sketch. I love me some Louis CK, so I may be a bit biased.)

Ansari- (I actually think the dirty talk sketch was overrated, but I can't wait to see Ansari host again. He was made for this.)

Robbie- (She did a better job than fellow summer movie breakout Chris Pratt did back in 2014. Not a bad sketch in this episode, though not a lot of highlights tbh.)

Fallon- (I'm glad that he didn't rely on Timberlake to cameo, since I feel that he uses him as a crutch. Solid episode.)

Affleck- (He wasn't too shabby, though Ben is a better fit for SNL than he is. He was very funny in the last sketch. New York Now was a drag, but I fully expect Chance the Rapper to host one day.)

Stone- (A bit disappointed since I'm a huge fan of hers, though not bad. Just ok. I only really remember "Posters" and the Nativity sketch.)

Miranda- (He's a very capable host, and I think we will see him again one day. His monologue was a blast and I usually hate singing ones. I have trouble remembering much else though besides that and the Poetry teacher sketch.)

Wiig- (Her second hosting stint on the show was better than her first, but I don't remember much besides the CNN and QVC sketches.)

Jones- (Not as bad as everyone says, though it is kind of forgettable.)

Blunt- (She deserved much better than this, as she was very game. Maybe she'll get a second chance when the Mary Poppins sequel comes out?)

Cumberbatch- (He does have comedy chops, but they really only worked in the sketch where Beck questions why everyone thinks he's hot. Disappointing episode since it was the last one before the election.)

Spencer- (The second half was abysmal, and this would've ranked higher if said half was only ok.)

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Dril's take on the illusion of free will and freedom </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-18 18:17:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-17 19:45:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That's a good comparison. He also seems good at impressions so maybe he's a Hader/Meyers combo. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-17 09:09:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> @dril You are an idiot and your family will die due to your grandfather clock fetish. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-16 21:08:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I see Kate leaving in two seasons while this is truly Bobbys last season. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-16 08:02:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I knew Beck was going to callback last week and I still laughed. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-16 07:48:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Nah, we're gonna pass!

- Bernie Sanders...or was it Larry David? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-16 06:44:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Correct </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-16 06:40:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This must've been written by Streeter Seidell or Julio Torres. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-15 20:53:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Compared to The Dark Knight Rises, where Gotham just feels like "generic American city." </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-15 20:34:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> At least Liam Neeson didn't even bother with one haha. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-15 05:18:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I hope they do get it resolved. I really want to see how Chris Pine fares on SNL. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-15 03:58:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Wassup with these Marlins always giving the Mets a hard time?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-14 20:39:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Maybe she could team up with McKinnon as a straight woman/larger-than-life comedic duo. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-14 20:37:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> But to be fair, the trailers didn't sell her character very well.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-14 19:11:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> *the minute </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-14 19:09:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Step 1: Rename every month on every calendar in Coors Field to April.

Step 2: Profit. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-13 02:35:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Wait, my feed is behind haha </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-13 02:34:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Finish him! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-13 02:30:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Even the Mets players know to run like hell when Ray Ramirez comes a lurkin'. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-13 02:11:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'd honestly rather have Lagares and/or Nimmo in center next year with Yoenis and Conforto in the corners. We need someone out there who is a great defender. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-13 01:57:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> We'll be fine if Bruce and/or Granderson walk after the season. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-10 23:42:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> https://twitter.com/dril/status/748279131612262401 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-10 03:28:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Ctrl + f "Suicide Squad"

I rest my case. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-09 20:41:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I would've liked to see Alex Moffat plays Bill O'Reilly last night instead of Alec tbh. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-09 19:57:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Really looking forward to Chris Pine'a episode. He's hilarious in Smokin' Aces and Stretch. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-09 07:30:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> My ranking of his monologues:

1. March 2014

2. November 2012

3. This one

5. May 2015 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-09 07:02:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> He's said that he mainly focuses on the monologue whenever he hosts and that he just let everything else fall into place. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-09 06:39:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Good thing we got one more Bobby/Louis CK sketch after the Hotel one they did the first time he hosted. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-09 06:04:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Here it is folks! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-09 05:40:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> My mans Louis CK wears suits now! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-09 05:28:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Louie, Louie, Louie, Louaaa... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-09 05:27:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What was the episode for SNL Vintage btw? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-07 18:59:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'll use some comps.

Beck- Really brings the same Midwestern charm as Sudeikis yet is also capable at the weirdos Chris Parnell used to play. 

Kyle- Absurdist humor like Armisen but in a more millennial way

McKinnon- Can completely disappear into a character like Bill Hader

Strong- Maybe the best pure actress of the cast rn, like Kristen Wiig

Kenan- Can do it all, like Phil Hartman.

Bayer- Effective straight woman, more or less similar to Jane Curtin

Aidy- Can go over-the-top but remain grounded at the same time. Kind of like Will Ferrell.

Mikey- Solid utility guy. I actually see a bit of Chris Kattan and Seth Meyers in him when he was starting out.

Alex- Very good at impressions like Bill Hader yet his "Just bought a boat" character is Sudeikis-like

Pete- Good at carving out his identity like Chris Rock and Adam Sandler did (or any other standup on the show).

Melissa- Impressionist. 

Sasheer- Deadpan humor but I also think the show still doesn't know how to use her

Leslie- Big broad personality like Tracy Morgan

Bobby- Brings the most out of his appearances.





 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-06 23:58:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Emma Stone also had one where she had trouble with the elevator. It should still be on Youtube. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-05 22:19:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If Blade Runner: 2049 is a hit, he'll have almost complete creative control. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-05 06:59:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Exactly. I don't think Casey and Todd really care about high production values. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-05 00:54:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I love me some Inside Socal! Alex and Melissa would also do great in one of these. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-04 16:15:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I feel like he hasn't made that big of an impression this season so maybe he could decide to just leave to focus on his standup. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-04 06:46:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Bobby's out, especially if his pilot is picked up for a series order.

I think Vanessa stays for another season. 

Pete is on the fence.

Mikey will be promoted, while Melissa really needs to make these next 5 episodes count. Alex will stay, but I'm not sure if he will get promoted. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-01 05:56:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The Master. Sorry guys, this one just didn't do it for me. And I love PTA's movies. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-31 01:04:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> *Daniel Day-Lewis drinks my milkshake*

Hey what the heck man?

*Daniel Day-Lewis sews my dress*

Thanks man! I was struggling with that. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-29 05:19:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> "I shot him. I shot the Joker."

"...Good. Great. Is he dead?"

"Um no he's in a coma." </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-26 05:35:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> And he's ERIC! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-26 04:45:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> My take:

I've always considered Cecily Strong more of an actress rather than a comedian, as in a Phil Hartman way, and I believe that it's the other way around for McKinnon, which is why she overshadows Cecily a bit at times.

Kate will have some of the best comedy roles offered when she leaves, while I picture Cecily having the type of career Kristen Wiig has now (supporting roles in blockbusters, indie drama leads, etc.)
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-25 20:15:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> "Dave Chappelle/A Tribe Called Quest"

An SNL Vintage episode when the show celebrates its 50th season. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-25 04:39:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's her 40th birthday today as well! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-23 23:06:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I think that's one of the reasons why Louis C.K. is already set to host for the fourth time. He mainly stays in NYC when he's not touring. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-23 22:17:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> He was directing an action-comedy starring Ahnuld during the summer and it would've interfered with the first few weeks of Season 42. There's a couple of other reasons but I'm not totally sure what they are. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-23 22:15:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Brad Pitt showed up once but I doubt he'll ever host. He's actually pretty good at comedy. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-23 22:12:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> He cameo'd in Jonah Hills monologue once. He was at SNL 40, though as a guest. Only a matter of time.... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-23 07:50:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Maybe 3 years as it originally was. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-22 07:08:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I thought Silence would do reasonably well... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-21 06:05:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I was expecting someone from Guardians of the Galaxy, Donald Glover (though hes pretty busy rn), Emma Watson, and Jason Sudeikis for the finale  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-21 06:04:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> They're going live across the nation for those four episodes, so they want to make sure they get hosts who know  the show inside and out, excluding Pine. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-19 03:32:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I bet he makes his conquests dress up as the American flag before sex. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-19 03:23:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Ah, you think Justin Smoak hate is your ally? etc. etc. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-19 03:18:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Anne Hathaway's monologues about love in Interstellar

"You came back to die for your city?"

"No I came to stop you!"  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-19 03:16:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> "Peanut branding" actually sounds like a great idea for a parody of a panel. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-19 02:02:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I say 3 more, during Fallon's, Pine's, and Johnson's episodes. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-16 23:31:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I want to see what Oscar Isaac would bring to the table as a host. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-16 23:30:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I think they announced it early so the affiliates could have time to organize their programming on those Saturday nights. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-16 22:47:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Don't sleep on Chris Pine. In a way, he's like Brad Pitt: a bit bland in leading man roles but delivers when you throw them a good character. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-15 23:17:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I was about to comment Ben Affleck until I read your post haha. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-13 08:25:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The Girl With The Dragon Tattoo cost $90 million. Fincher is pretty expensive though and acquiring the rights must've cost a fortune. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-13 08:20:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That scene proved that Marvel may still have a couple of tricks up their sleeve. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-13 08:16:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I actually thought that Emily Blunt was a pretty committed and game host. I just wish she had been given better material to work with. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Now that 3/4ths of the season is now in the books, how would you rank the episodes? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-13 01:08:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Here's my ranking:

1. Hanks

2. Chappelle

3. Ansari

4. Baldwin

5. Robbie

6. Stewart

7. Stone

8. Johansson

9. Miranda

10. Wiig

11. Affleck

12. Cena

13. Jones

14. Blunt

15. Cumberbatch

16. Spencer </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-12 23:53:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I still think she was a bit miscast in Silver Linings Playbook but she was quite good in that. And she was the only thing I liked about Winters Bone. Besides that, she's been serviceable. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-12 23:51:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I could see him carving out a John Cusack type of career. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-12 23:49:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You could write a book about the last twenty years in film without mentioning any of her movies and nothing of note would be lost. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-12 06:47:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I like how he always gets paired up with the hottest pop musical guests at the moment (f.u.n., Sam Smith blew up after his appearance, Rihanna, The Chainsmokers).

Anyway, get his Five-Timers key up and running soon, boys!  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-11 07:29:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I presume only rich people get to fuck the flag in this novel? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-09 21:37:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> "What do you believe in?!" </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-07 00:59:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Nolan

1. The Dark Knight

2. Inception

3. The Prestige

4. Batman Begins

5. Memento

6. The Dark Knight Rises

7. Following

8. Interstellar

9. Insomnia </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-07 00:55:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Christopher Nolan's debut film The Following. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-06 18:32:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Honestly...I was confused as shit. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-05 07:04:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Looks like he'll have to wait a long time to get into the five-timers club. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-05 07:00:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Jim Parsons 2014

Jonah Hill 2016 

Octavia Spencer 2017

Why is the first episode of March a dud every year?

For 2015, Dakota Johnson's episode aired on February 28th. Chris Hemsworth's first stint was surprisingly good if you want to consider that one the first true March episode of that year. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-05 06:44:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> However, the flip side is coming off looking like a dick when you say no to a lot of sketches. Tough to find that balance of being game for anything while not being a yes man. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-05 06:42:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Moffat and Villasenor bought themselves some time to make a case for Season #2 for both of them.

Leslie on the other hand... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-05 06:35:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That sketch seemed straight out of the Hader-Sudeikis-Wiig-Samberg-Forte-Armisen era. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-05 06:19:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Its ERIC! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-05 06:09:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Looks like Aldo Raine decided to pick up the guitar  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-05 05:42:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Funny comment TBD </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-05 05:34:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I saw it coming! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-05 00:46:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Lorne seems to really like him. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-04 18:11:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> But that election tho... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-04 18:10:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The first half of Season 41 had nine episodes, which is why the second half had three episodes in April (Dinklage, Crowe, Louis-Dreyfus) instead of the usual two.

March of 2014 also had three episodes since February only had one of that episode that season. They always try to balance them out.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-27 06:10:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Michael Keaton and Emma Stone have been in 2 of the last 3 Best Picture winners. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-27 06:03:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Calling Trump out gets you a lot of brownie points apparently in Hollywood. Who knew? /s </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-27 05:53:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Haha yes I doubled down on Casey! :D </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-27 05:44:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Wait, Brie Larson isn't presenting?

Oh right... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
