<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject7881</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-10 14:59:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> They seem to be.  They're a startup by Politco's founders with Mike Allen being Politico's former White House correspondent. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-10 14:55:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I can see them trying if they get desperate.

But with what's already known, Flynn carrying the bag for this would raise too many questions about who knew what and when.  Do they burn Sessions as well?  Pence?  Why the delay?  Why were Flynn's ring-ins kept on even after the firing?  What if he sings?

If Flynn lands in the shit for this he's going to spray it over most of the executive whether he wants to or not. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-10 14:44:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> No man is an island.

If they thought they could burn him with the bridges they would have likely done so by now.  That we still see the administration spending capital defending the man suggests those connections are either too hard to hide or already known. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-10 14:41:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'd argue that a White House and an Attorney General being this incompetently transparent in aim and so apparently tone deaf to consequence would remain baffling.

You'd at least expect competent corruption. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> GOP baffled by timing; WH braces for independent probe </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-10 14:36:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Trump's explanation for Comey's firing is literally unbelievable </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-10 14:10:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Nauru loses US financial support </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-10 13:57:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-10 13:41:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> A rather fun bit of trolling from King. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Independent senator: Comey could lead Senate investigation on Trump-Russia ties </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-10 13:40:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Federal budget 2017: Centrelink accused of plan to 'profile' vulnerable drug users in welfare crackdown </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-10 13:22:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Michael Flynn targeted by grand jury subpoenas, sources confirm </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-10 12:31:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-10 06:05:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Joyce just stated in a press conference that he will be pressing charges. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Dems ask Justice Dept, FBI to 'preserve any and all files' on Comey firing </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-10 05:40:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-10 02:25:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This was done without a replacement lined up showing a level of impulsive

Or showing a desire to stall investigations for the longest period possible.

With the NYT on Sessions being instructed to find a reason to fire Comey I doubt there was much impulse in this, just opportunity. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-09 19:18:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Read the URL.  AP updated it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> US watched Russia penetrate French systems during election </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-09 17:34:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> US watched Russia penetrate French systems during election </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-09 17:25:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> S. Korea's next leader will engage North, reconsider THAAD </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-09 17:23:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-09 17:13:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm now seeing averages of *24 days* for documents between Geneva and Sydney and NYC and Sydney.

And that's airport to airport, it often takes 5+ days to make it to my office in Melbourne from there.

It is fucking absurd. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-09 17:03:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's a bit grim when this...

How we can expect to see a thorough, nonpartisan investigation and definitive answers from Republicans running the hearings?

...is coming from...

Jennifer Rubin writes the Right Turn blog for The Post, offering reported opinion from a conservative perspective.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Unanswered questions from Yatess testimony </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-09 17:02:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Why Did the White House Ignore Sally Yatess Warning About Michael Flynn? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-09 16:51:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Donald Trumps former campaign adviser Carter Page said he had a brief interaction with a suspected Russian spy </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-09 16:40:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-09 12:41:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Treatment of drug addiction and use as a medical issue rather than bludgeon to a subset of Australians the Coalition reliably makes political mileage out of scapegoating.

The connection drawn by this budget between these issues has no utility save for polling. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-09 12:25:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Guess you'd better be ready to live with the consequences of such an asinine ultimatum. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-09 12:05:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Drug testing is going to lead to massive problems.  You're going to drive people with addictions out of the welfare system with obvious consequences for both them and their families. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-09 07:01:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If you willingly choose to align yourself with an organisation whose leadership structure consists of nazis, you're a nazi.

You might be there because you're a dickhead, not because you're deeply ingrained in the tenets of national socialism.  You're still carrying the banner and I will identify you as you choose to identify yourself without hesitation or reservation. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> NT royal commission: Investigator thought guard hitting detainee with a torch was a game </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-09 06:56:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-09 06:48:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yes.

It's Shermon Burgess' splinter because Reclaim was too moderate for his liking.

You've got Neil Erikson and Blair Cottrell involved as well.  Erikson was done a few years back for harassing the local Rabbinate amongst other things.  Cottrell's known for such gems as a campaign to have Mein Kampf on the school curriculum and a little light arson.

Add to that Phillip Galea who's currently on remand over bomb making materials along with assorted thugs and you've got a throughly awful bunch of nazi cunts. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-09 06:36:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I will gladly describe actual, bonafide, be-swastika'd, charged and convicted nazis as nazis.

If you have a problem with this, I don't give a flying fuck about your opinion. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Fairfax boss Greg Hywood was paid as much as $7.2m in 2016 </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-09 06:04:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-09 04:57:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Haha.  Get fucked nazi scum. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Red Pill Boss: All Feminists Want to Be Raped </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-09 02:48:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-08 19:40:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Advisers.  Most of them?   All of them? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-08 19:36:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Knock, knock

Who's there?

Your close adviser is a grave threat to national security </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-08 17:25:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Depends whether Australia's, and /r/Australia's, cadre of racists can find a new target to hate.

With Yassmin being a useful tool in Coalition internal moves against Bishop and her basically being the perfect storm of qualities for our alt-right hystericals to whine about, I sadly doubt we've heard the end of it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-08 17:22:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What happens to these positions in the event of an impeachment? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Kentucky Is Home to the Greatest Declines in Life Expectancy </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-08 17:09:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-08 15:20:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Well you clearly have no respect for the rule of law either.  When are you leaving? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-08 11:46:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> As did 10s of 1000s of others.  A day of national memorial is political by its very nature.  She called for an act of remembrance and consideration on the impact of war, like 10s of 1000s of other Australians did.

The reason we're here, two weeks later, with people like you sniping at her rather than, for example, our PM's rather cynical use of the day is that we do a very fine job in this country of policing who is and isn't Australian enough to speak for us all.

Yassmin does not make the bar for many it would seem.  Frankly, I'd far rather her than the bigots whose wailing we've had to put up with for a fortnight. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-08 11:37:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I think people are pissed off that someone they'd comfortably cast as the "other" dared to speak as one of "us". </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-08 11:31:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Unlikely unfortunately.

A large part of the reason this has been kept dragging on is that, aside from playing well with the Coalition's racists, it's been a useful proxy war issue against Bishop. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-08 10:45:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Someone in caucus asked whether there was a process to remove photos of billy hughes and latham. Shorten: ''They are there as a reminder''.

https://twitter.com/michellegrattan/status/861498965375594496 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-08 08:46:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Said it before, I'll say it again.  No one owes your hatred a platform.

If you don't like that, I don't care.

As for the article, editorialised, previously discussed and out of date. Reported. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-08 08:22:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> There'd be some schadenfreude to be had by my sense of humour around racist fuckwit thugs in parliament has been worn thin enough already. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-08 08:21:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Bought and paid.  The whole organisation needs to be put under a a very public microscope and the cancer excised. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-08 08:09:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hateful cunts of a feather flock together.

My money was on Ross Cameron but I'm sure he won't be far behind. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-08 08:07:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Naturally.  The AFP are bought and paid for at this point.

A formal, independent and public review followed by major restructuring is well past due. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-08 04:38:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This went down an absolute clanger long before any of the press latched on to it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-08 04:37:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It'd be much less of an issue if their advertising team had thought for a minute.

I doubt there's been any attempt at a dog whistle here, it's far, far too hamfisted for that.  But when you've got a community that's getting really fucking tired of hearing that tone loud and clear from the Coalition, try not to stand on the squeeky toy when you're stumbling around with no idea.  People will notice. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-08 04:33:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The pure unadulterated religious, and frequently racial, hatred is getting more than tiresome.  The harassment of the few users who have dared to out themselves as Muslim has been even more disgusting.

And yet, it's let fester on and on and on. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> As some Republicans rush to defend House health bill, Senate GOP warily pauses </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-07 20:43:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-07 20:17:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I quite liked /r/France's adoption of /r/Le_Canard for that subreddit.  I think it should perhaps be kept as a momento. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> On eve of fired Justice official's testimony, Trump tweets about Russia probe </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-07 16:07:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-07 04:41:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Interesting on several fronts, not least of which being the publication.

Of note is the US connection. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> There Are No Macron Leaks in France. Politically Motivated Hacking Is Not Whistleblowing. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-07 04:40:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-06 13:29:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's absurd that we have a coordinated nationalist international but we have one none the less.

The rejection of it needs to be just as coordinated and just as international. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-06 13:13:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Only an idiot fights a war on two fronts. Only the heir to the throne of the kingdom of idiots would fight a war on twelve fronts. 

Or in this case, twenty-seven. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-06 06:19:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> A cockholster, to use the parlance of our times. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-06 06:18:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's a good read on what's important to Trump but I bet Turnbull is praying that soundbite doesn't get much of a run domestically. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Texas police chiefs: Do not burden local officers with federal immigration enforcement </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-05 18:50:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> White House fires its chief usher - the first woman in that job </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-05 16:30:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-05 16:12:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> jester actual </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-05 15:24:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'd take "better than unquestioning subservience to anyone" at this point. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Jose Ramos-Horta warns gas dispute with Australia risks pushing East Timor closer to China </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-05 14:44:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-05 07:46:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'd urge you to read the article. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-05 07:37:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> They can not be refouled. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-05 07:29:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> They can't change it.  They can however seek to evade it, an urge that goes to the very root of this whole mess of abuses. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-05 07:24:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I didn't catch it but Michelle Grattan's saying he agreed that the phone call reporting was "fake news" as well.

https://twitter.com/michellegrattan/status/860360270358630400

Who needs reality when you've got an arsehole to tongue I guess. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-05 07:16:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Is it really that hard to comprehend that even a criminal has rights? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-05 07:16:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Meant to be.  It's sometimes a long way from the reality though, particularly with DIBP over the last 20 years. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-05 05:40:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah, it's been pretty disappointing to watch a community that lives and breathes the Australian media largely ignore this aspect.  Doubly so for all the complaining here about clickbait and media standards.

We seem pretty happy to consume quality press.  We're rather less inclined to put ourselves out to support it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-05 05:33:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Abbott.  McMahon. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-05 05:15:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> There's been dissent in the ranks since the merger with many taking issue with the paramilitarisation of the agency and the particular class of recruit it subsequently attracted.

It's long past due that people started speaking out over this though.  At this point if you're not actively resisting, you're collaborating. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-05 05:12:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Indeed.  But it was a massive improvement over what came before it, and a massive improvement over what Trump and the GOP intend to have replace it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Justice Department opens criminal probe into Uber </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-05 04:57:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Justice Department opens criminal probe into Uber </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-05 04:57:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-05 04:56:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Nice URL Mark. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The Australian Prime Minister Just Said Trump's Repeal Of Obamacare Is "Great" </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-05 04:56:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-05 04:55:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> North wrote that had Dutton properly understood the consequence of his refusal, protection may have been granted to avoid the consequence that the applicant would be returned to Syria in contravention of Australias non-refoulement obligations.

"Had Dutton properly understood the consequence" seems a phrase we could oft repeat in this whole saga.

Important ruling because of the Federal Court's recognition of non-refoulement requirements in relation to Section 501.  Will be interesting to see whether the government braves an appeal or moving it to the High Court. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Peter Dutton ordered by court to revisit Syrian man's refugee application </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-05 04:52:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-05 04:40:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Don't worry Donald.  The Liberal party is working on fixing that. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Amid scrutiny, Corey Lewandowski quits his new lobbying firm </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-05 04:00:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-05 03:23:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> General oversupply does not imply an oversupply of affordable and appropriate housing for all sectors.

https://www.anglicare.org.au/media-releases/rental-stress-worsens-greater-sydney-and-illawarra </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-05 02:38:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> And yet that arrangement had worked amicably for 15 years. The owner certainly took on a risk but there's a clear reduction in utility here, both for the owner and his customers.

I would say that it should have been fairly obvious that the new scheme reduces the ability for welfare recipients to plan necessary but non-urgent spending and thus severely limits the degree of even trivial debt that can be taken on safely.  That however is a statement far better directed at those who designed the scheme than any shop owner. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-04 18:00:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Remember the name of every person who votes for this vandalism.

Do everything in your power to ensure they never hold office again. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-04 17:59:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Vowing to fight what he called discrimination against religious people and institutions, Trump said,  "We will not allow people of faith to be bullied, targeted, or silenced any more." 

Unless you're a Muslim of course. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> ObamaCare repeal plan could remove protections for people on employer health plans: report </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-04 14:46:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-04 08:42:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Now that's a handy docker image. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-04 06:39:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Very unlikely it was planned given the hour in the UK.  I guess we'll know for sure in about 3.5 hours. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-04 06:32:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Perhaps not.

http://www.nzherald.co.nz/world/news/article.cfm?c_id=2 objectid=11850144

You could safely assume the Queen and Prince Philip are not dead," a palace press officer told a TVNZ reporter this afternoon. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Peter Dutton's claims about Manus violence unsupported on the ground, Greens senator says </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-04 05:48:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Fairfax boss Greg Hywood the target of striking journalists' anger as cuts backlash continues </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-04 05:40:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Russian election hacking 'wildly successful' in creating discord: former U.S. lawmaker </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-03 15:17:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-03 06:40:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'd like to think it would be the latter but in Fairfax's instance I'd expect it to be the former. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-03 06:37:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Actually, Bourke and Massola being given the boot would be a boon if it didn't come with the 1/4 of the rest of the newsroom.

Both have been producing drivel, frequently overtly contrived to fit an editorial line, and I'd imagine costing Fairfax a pretty penny to do so. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-03 06:35:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> As a shorter summation then, our bastardry isn't removing asylum seekers from mixed migration pathways nor deterring people from entering them.

In the absence of alternatives and in view of what's being fled it's not particularly surprising but it has been oft denied by our governments nonetheless. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-03 06:29:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> People have a right to seek asylum via any means save violence and we have a basic legal obligation and have made explicit international undertakings to uphold those rights.  We flout both.

Mixed migration is however very adept at operating on paths of least resistance.  We had an effective, if what would now be considered very, very dated system in place during the Indochina refugee crisis that managed to both shorten the journeys of asylum seekers and mostly defused the domestic political concerns.  A return to a modernised, regionally cooperative system would likely be the best outcome for all sides of this debate and it's something the Greens have been running as part of their policy platform for some time.  Unfortunately, we've done much to hamper those relationships in recent years.  It's not something that could be put in place quickly and we've actively exacerbated that timeline. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-03 06:24:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> They're looking at the context of humanitarian outcomes for the people involved, not onshore politicking.

The report that's linked goes into substantially more detail. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Another Fox News Employee Accuses the Network of Gender Discrimination </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-03 04:51:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-03 04:19:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> "Top 10 reasons why you'll love the Liberal party"

by Latika M Bourke </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-03 04:08:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The startling submission about the conditions on Nauru as recently as September provides a description that would otherwise be outlawed under the Border Force Acts disclosure provisions. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Nauru self-immolation led to 'up to 50' similar threats and attempts </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-03 04:07:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-03 03:54:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Unfortunately the same can be said of much of the country.  The shortsightedness of this policy matches the parochial concerns of the electorate depressingly well.

Push the problem just a touch over the horizon and it's quite literally out of sight, out of mind.

How much coverage did the Andaman Sea Crisis receive locally? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Nauru MP Matthew Batsiua accuses Justice Minister of interfering with judicial system </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-03 03:43:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-03 03:37:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> There's also a companion piece to this by Dr Violeta Moreno-Lax at: http://www.theage.com.au/comment/stopping-the-boats-is-a-futile-cynical-exercise-20170502-gvx2y9.html </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Asylum seeker boat turnbacks illegal and don't deter people, report finds </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-03 03:29:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-03 03:26:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> por qu no los dos? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Mike Pence: Lying or incompetent on Flynn </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-03 03:16:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Fairfax to cut 125 FTE jobs from the SMH, Age and AFR - more than a quarter of the newsroom. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-03 02:21:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Victoria's budget tackles family violence with unprecedented $1.9bn </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-02 09:30:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-02 06:31:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So fucking cynical.  And fuck me Gonski must be a glutton for punishment.

The one thing of note is that, like Labor should have done, they've indicated they're prepare to cut funding to some of the east coast private schools.  I'll congratulate them for that if it's ever actually done. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Trump refers to Face the Nation as Deface the Nation  while on the show </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-01 17:07:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Trump starts dismantling his shadow Cabinet </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-01 16:57:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-30 18:45:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> She's certainly a competent operator but it currently seems as if the whole UN team is operating without direction from the rest of the administration.  It'll be fascinating to see how long that's allowed to continue.  With State's current progress on staffing/funding it may be some time.

Whilst she's very competent, and that really does make her a notable standout presently, I'd suggest there's perhaps rather less to celebrate about positions she's likely to take from a progressive standpoint.  And that goes regardless of whether she's taking orders or freestyling. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-30 18:15:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm not sure that this much impotent flailing constitutes enough wielding of power to qualify him. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Trump's first 100 days: ignorant, thuggish, insecure - a president as would-be oligarch </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-30 17:56:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> People's Climate March: thousands rally to denounce Trump's environmental agenda </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-30 16:13:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Government's budget deficit for 2016-17 likely to be $38.3bn, report says </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-30 16:09:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-30 11:09:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Most of it seemingly lifted from the pages of this subreddit. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-30 08:53:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> He's punching down rather than punching up. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-30 07:48:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It happened about the time it came to be used as a shield in defence of unthinking, unquestioning nationalism rather than a day of reflection on war and its impact.  Of late it's being wielded as truncheon in defence of the same.

Your reaction is a symptom of the disease. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-30 07:25:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Ms White said her own party was focused on ensuring candidates did not present these sorts of issues.

One thing you can definitely say about Labor candidates of late, they sure do lack convictions. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-30 07:25:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> They were given passwords.  So no.

http://www.theage.com.au/national/journalists-for-the-age-apologise-for-unauthorised-access-to-alp-database-20130805-2raib.html </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Queensland Galaxy: 52-48 to Labor as One Nation slumps </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-30 05:47:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Federal Labor backtracks on support of Adani's planned Carmichael coal mine </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-30 05:02:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Metadata fiasco shows need for parliamentary inquiry  Paul Farrell </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-30 05:01:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-30 04:50:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> And unfortunately this is nothing new, though it's become more blantant in recent years, and nor is it a particularly unreasonable comment.

There's been significant issues with investigative bias since the late 90s that started to be put in stark relief under Mick Keelty's tenure and the events of 2001.

Where it really accelerated though IMO was with the remerger of the APS for anti-terrorism purposes, which was ultimately done despite the Stewart Royal Commission's initial reasoning.  In that light, it's hardly surprising that we're where we are.

The AFP needs inquiry and remaking on a scale I fear neither party is willing to entertain. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-29 10:13:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Likewise.  Who could have predicted that mindless obedience the moment any Lib whispered "national security" could lead us here?

It's pathetic but I'd rather a hypocritical song and dance rather than silence and that's the most likely alternative from Labor. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> AFP data breach: six cases of alleged police misconduct investigated </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-29 10:00:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Mark Dreyfus demands answers on Australian police metadata breach </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-29 09:59:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Trump team did vet Flynn, hired him anyway: NBC News </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-29 05:11:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-29 04:55:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> She's Australian. You really do struggle with the concept, don't you? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-28 15:37:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Sorry should clarify, I specifically mean crossposts of this article.  Not the story in general. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-28 15:33:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Interesting indeed.  Wonder if it's the subreddit or site wide because Reddit corporate seems to be finding the meta discussion about this site's harbouring of hate groups pretty uncomfortable.

I note with interest that this story has no other discussions on the site. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> More Americans say race relations deteriorating: Reuters poll </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-28 15:12:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-28 10:01:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If it's the NBN investigation at the centre of this, this needs a major independent inquiry. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-28 10:00:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hasn't that Japanese pepper stuff had hemp seed in it forever? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-28 05:31:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Greed, avarice, jealousy, resentment, spite, malevolence... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-28 04:12:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Canavan's telling all the Queenslanders they should boycott them. XD </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-28 03:47:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You get the feeling Donald sees a lot of himself in Kim. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-27 19:24:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Cocos Islands  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-27 17:23:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's because his nose is located above his mouth. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Defense Deptartment opens investigation into ex-Trump adviser Flynn </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-27 16:13:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Trump met with Matt Drudge in Oval Office: report </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-27 14:33:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Treasury secretary can't guarantee middle class wouldn't pay more under tax plan </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-27 14:03:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Locking up children shouldn't be last resort, NT minister suggested  despite not believing it </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-27 10:48:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-27 09:53:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Simple; they are cowards. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-27 09:38:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Debate her?  They might lose.

Worse, they might have to consider her position. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-27 09:22:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> And if you believe that, I've got this new suburb of McMansions to sell you. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Developers tell CCC they expect nothing in return for political donations </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-27 09:22:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-27 09:15:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> We killed off our FB account about a year back and by then it had just gotten insane.  We'd already rolled it back to being an "impersonal" face of the organisation where previously we actually had a staffer acting as the face of it.

Its cost us for sure, both financially and socially, but in our line of work with refugees it had gotten to the point where *any* interaction wasn't just resulting in trolling but outright threats.

Think the cops give a fuck about today's chosen UPF racist with his name, address, phone number, ugly mug and next of kin splattered all over his public page threatening to rape your employees?  Nah, of course not.  Think Facebook give a fuck?  Ahahahahahahaha. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Justices Alarmed by Government's Hard-Line Stance in Citizenship Case </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-27 05:33:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> US launches probe into aluminium imports, citing security concerns </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-27 05:14:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> That time the Government adopted Greens Economic Policy </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-27 05:12:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Manus refugees who fed child lodge complaint about Duttons false allegations </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-27 05:09:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-27 04:48:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Forgetting the whole Don Dale thing I take it?

Not saying it's justified, but it definitely happens. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-27 04:42:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> And far too many media outlets are happy to repeat the soundbite without dedicating the column inches to explaining the landscape in which it sits. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-27 04:30:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Isn't he running Border Force? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-27 03:52:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I meant anyone who wishes to draw attention to it.  UN Watch actually have special consultative status with ECOSOC so they're attached, if not directly.

To be absolutely clear, Saudi Arabia's human rights record is a fucking disgrace and absolutely deserving of critique and scrutiny at the highest levels.  I just grow weary of the word games played with the UN's structure, and the assumption that the structure would be so navely constructed. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-27 03:41:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This article's a pretty good example of it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-27 01:32:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Except of course, they aren't.

This is a committee under ECOSOC and is thus under the General Assembly's structure.  It can discuss and make statements only.  If anything, a smart operator would use Saudi Arabia's presence on the group as a mechanism to highlight issues in the country over the course of this session's sittings.

Actual implementation of rights programs, monitoring and enforcement are roles of bodies under the Secretariat, an entirely separate division of the UN System.

The UN System is complex and you'll get similar sounding groups under the different wings but it's worth looking at precisely what is being talked about.  It's that confusion, and the associated conflation of statehood with citizenship, that is used to push agendas. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-26 17:51:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It just needs an antenna behind the seat that wags when it sees you.

...Or some good twisties. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Trump's proposed tax plan could cost the Government $6 trillion </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-26 16:49:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Judge cites Trump's comment in "sanctuary city" ruling </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-26 15:14:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-26 07:12:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Personally, I'm looking forward to Dutton and Reclaim Australia getting thrown in prison under the whistleblower laws. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-26 06:42:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> May it open the floodgates. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-26 06:38:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You do know what a lot of those refugees are fleeing, right?

Then again, that doesn't concern your ever obvious agenda. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-26 06:34:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Brandis:  "Sorry, you can't go.  There's drunk dickheads firing guns at people, it wouldn't be safe." </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> One Nation rebuffs invitation to join Cory Bernardi's Conservatives party </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-26 05:32:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-26 04:55:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Where was the judgement?

LEST. WE. FORGET.

(Manus, Nauru, Syria, Palestine...)

That's all it said.  Does that bother you?  Does it judge you?

If that lands so close to home as to make you feel judged, I'd suggest you were feeling conflicted long before yesterday. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-26 04:51:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Perhaps but it seems a pretty accurate summation of the attitude on display. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-26 04:50:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> LEST.  WE. FORGET.

(Manus, Nauru, Syria, Palestine...)

That's it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-26 04:47:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The Australian part.

Looks like /u/fuckoffnazis was on the money with the wrong colour bit. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-26 04:33:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah, you of all people would never do that. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-26 04:29:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I always considered it to include what those people fought to defend, in fact or in inspiration.

As for making you sad, I really don't care.  For what it's worth, and I'm sure you don't care either, your attempt to dictate such a narrow scope is depressing to me as well. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-26 04:28:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yet the vast machinery of the Australian right makes a fuss about one and one alone. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-26 04:21:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Pretty much.

There's few greater sins for Australian conservatism than the "other" having the presumption to think that they're "us". </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-26 04:18:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm sure you were howling with outrage about Turnbull and Bishop's exploitation of this sacred day as well.  I'm sure all of those decrying Adbel-Magied's comments were. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-26 03:53:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm not sure it would have made a difference even if the party had fallen apart before it.  I *think* that her name being on the ticket and the ticket having received votes would stand.

Might be one for Antony Green. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-26 03:48:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> As well they should.

Remind me again, who gets to say what we can and can't reflect upon on a day of reflection?

That Adbel-Magied's comments were so incendiary, regardless of timing, with a rather predictable slice of Australia reflects far more on their sensitivities than any lack of them from her.  All she asked was for people to think.

**Edit:**  I'd like to draw particular attention to /u/fuckoffnazis' [reply below](https://np.reddit.com/r/australia/comments/67kyk8/abc_stands_by_yassmin_abdelmagied_after_facebook/dgr9emw/), they hit the nail on the head beautifully and were inevitably downvoted to hell for it.  Read it anyway. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-26 02:21:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I wonder what McKim's secret squirrel name will be with the Wilson Rent-a-thugs?  The Raven is hard to beat. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-26 02:19:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yes, absolutely.  The protocol is normally that one should resign, particularly in the Senate, but there's absolutely no legal mechanism and plenty of precedent to say otherwise. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Greens senator Nick McKim to investigate detention centre shooting during Manus Island visit </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-26 01:45:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-26 01:29:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah we do.  Give us a shout when they get an equitable and critical voice in this discussion. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-26 01:06:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> For those who've come across the seas

We've boundless plains to share;

With courage let us all combine

To Advance Australia Fair.

?

Yeah, on second thoughts that's got nothing to do with Australia's values any more.  Certainly not our government's.

How do you rhyme "Fuck off Muslims, we're full" with the current tune though? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-26 00:57:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> By "classified information" he of course means Reclaim Australia's FB.

http://www.4zzzfm.org.au/news/audio/2017/04/25/duttons-claims-first-came-far-right-group </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-25 19:15:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Having your name attached to the processes that ended a Republican presidency will do that for a Republican. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-25 18:48:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Worst case, it's an embarrassment and Chaffetz is threatening to take his bat and ball and go home if the party won't let him play chairman.

Best case, he realises he's just been put in a position where he can no longer protect the WH from its own stupidity and may be about to have the committee he chairs throw Flynn, and likely at *least* Pence along with him, under the bus.  Thus rendering him persona non grata both with the WH and within the GOP more generally. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-25 18:34:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Chaffetz, a relatively young rep in a reasonably safe seat and prominent position as House Oversight Committee chairman announced on the 19th that he won't be standing for relelection for any public office and may not even see out his term.

At the time everyone assumed he was trying to pre-empt some scandal and now we find out that a major request from the committee he chairs was turned down on the same day.

Hell of a coincidence. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-25 18:02:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Personal faith wise certainly but politically they're still a good match and it's a political relationship that I don't see dissolving. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-25 17:50:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You'll need to be more specific about which nutjob Senator Graham. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-25 17:32:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Blame Canada! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-25 17:28:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> April 19th

Same day Chaffetz announced he wasn't running again

http://edition.cnn.com/2017/04/19/politics/jason-chaffetz-not-seeking-re-election </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-25 17:22:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I think we're starting to see why Chaffetz is making a run for the exit.

Edit: House Oversight rejection came the same day, April 19th

2nd Edit: The dated letter https://twitter.com/AmandaWills/status/856879541620527105 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> 66 percent of Americans under 30 disapprove of President Trump, poll finds </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-25 17:05:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-25 15:25:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> He is.  But he's far more aligned with the Hillsong style prosperity gospel than your average church goer.

FFP's success in South Australia had quite a bit to do with its ability to draw votes from outside of the pentecostal/AOG circles that funded it.

I wouldn't be surprised to see that bridge burn when it comes to Cory's Tories.  I guess we'll see how much it impacts them at the next election. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-25 14:55:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> He's religious enough in magnitude but he may prove very much the wrong flavour for the average SA Christian FF voter.  We'll see in time no doubt.

On Xenophon, one wonders whether he'll court Gichuhi. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-25 14:48:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The political alliance makes sense, but it'll be interesting to see whether the electoral one does.  Particularly in SA.

I'd wager that their voters might prove substantially incompatible. The SA MLCs likewise. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
