<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject2331</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-10 00:17:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It was awesome. They had music playing, kids playing at the park and every kind of food truck you could want! Cousin's Maine Lobster was amazing! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-09 19:57:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> No Problem! It was freakin' awesome! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Food Trucks in Lancaster (x-post r/Palmdale) </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-09 19:47:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hiya there! Not sure if this has been posted before, but either way, thought I would share.

Every Monday, from 5pm-10pm at Lancaster City Park, there is a large collection of food trucks! Yesterday was my first time going and it was absolutely amazing!

You can go to the website to see the trucks for the week and any other pertinent information!

https://www.thefoodtruckcollective.com/monday-bitez-in-lancaster  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Food Trucks in Lancaster! </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-09 19:36:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hiya there! Not sure if this has been posted before, but either way, thought I would share.

Every Monday, from 5pm-10pm at Lancaster City Park, there is a large collection of food trucks! Yesterday was my first time going and it was absolutely amazing!

You can go to the website to see the trucks for the week and any other pertinent information!

https://www.thefoodtruckcollective.com/monday-bitez-in-lancaster  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-09 19:32:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Pets R Us in Lancaster. They are very affordable for the yearly stuff.. haven't had to get any other stuff done thought  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-01 21:08:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Well, her family is also in Florida, so it'd be quite an ass pain to get her over there. I've been looking at rentals and sending them to her lmao
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-01 15:07:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Actually, the only one who pays rant is her boyfriend. She hasn't paid rent the whole time she's lived there. She ended up getting foodstamps, so groceries are her psuedo way of contributing, but I haven't seen her buy groceries yet.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-01 15:04:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I agree, but in some cases, it comes from a lifetime of poor eating habits, so it's perfectly fine to be proud of it. Some people are dicks about it, which isn't okay. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-01 06:15:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Most people get fat by having horrible eating habits, so when they can overcome that, it's pretty impressive. But I feel ya. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Get the fuck out of my house </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-01 05:48:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So, a little backstory first. My sister in law and her son moved into my house last July, because her husband decided he didn't want to be married. I offered her to move in because living with her parents would be incredibly toxic for her and her son. Her new boyfriend recently moved in because he was going to rent a room from someone and they want to move out together. (There's more to it, but doesn't really matter)he's already here all the time, so I figured "meh, just move in here". We can at least make some money off of his presence. He works swing shift (3pm-1230am) so he's not ever really home when I am anyway. 

This rant is mostly about my sister in law. I'll start off by saying she is my best friend, but a huge pain in my ass. First off, I was gone for 6 months on deployment. The whole time I hear nothing but how my husband is a slob, he's lazy..blah blah. It's not entirely false, but she also tried to blame everything wrong with the house on him. I get home a few weeks ago and my house is outwardly clean. 

I open the fridge, and take absolutely covered in all kinds of random shit. My microwave is filthy. I have the refold and reorganize my linen closet because she "doesn't like to fold blankets". There's stains all over my carpet from her kid. There's a pile of dryer lint next to the dryer that she was too lazy to walk 5 feet to the trash can. The washer was covered in dirt and laundry detergent. My dog no longer eats any of her dog food because she's so accustomed to getting fed by my 2 1/2 year old nephew. 

My expensive knives and pots and pans were put in the dishwasher, even though I specifically asked for them to be hand washed. The motor in my carpet cleaner burned out because she hasn't figured out that you're supposed to vacuum before you use it. (I posted a pic on /r/wtf if you wanna see just how bad it was). 

Basically the only thing she gives her kid is milk. Constantly. He asks for milk and he gets it. He gets milk when he goes to bed, chugs it, screams for more, and gets it. This goes on several times throughout the night. I bought three gallons of milk last week and they didn't even last 5 days. She's moderately good at disciplining him, but doesn't do it over things I really think she should. I can't tell her how to raise her kid, so that's kind of a moot point. She always asks my husband or me to watch her son when she goes to the store because "he'll see a toy and then scream until he gets it". Hmm, maybe if you didn't give in so often it wouldn't be an issue. There are so many things that she complains her kid does when a majority of it is because she never put a stop to it. 

Her boyfriends shit takes up half my garage, but that's basically it. He does sometimes notice that my husband isn't doing something right( project wise) but runs to one of us to tell us instead of telling him directly. "It's a man thing"

She is so terrible at keeping house. Maybe I'm a clean freak and a control freak, but Jesus Christ. I've been back for 2 weeks after being gone for 6 months and I've hardly sat down since I've been home! I do not want them to rush into finding a place (they're looking, just not much in their price range. Yay California) but they need to get the fuck out. My husband and I want to start a family and that's definitely not possible while they're here. Get out and ruin your own things. 

Also, don't fucking complain about getting fat if you're going to eat fast food 3 times a day. Don't fucking tell me my method of dieting (keto) doesn't work when I lost 20lbs. 

Rant over
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-01 04:42:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Ugh, I had a co worker say that I wear yoga pants to the gym because I want people to look. Uh, no, I wear them because there comfortable.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Took the carpet cleaner apart because it wasn't doing a good job..think I found out why </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-30 22:37:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Got my stitch hat!! My favorite hat that they sell </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-30 06:16:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Ready for Takeoff!! </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-25 05:34:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-24 04:12:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I enjoyed doing first dates at the movies. I like comedies because then you can see the other persons sense of humor. Went with a group of friends to see bad grandpa years ago and one of the guys loved how I just let loose and laughed my ass off, so he called me and asked me on an actual date lol </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Rats in a pineapple, part 2 </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-05 06:25:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-04 00:16:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It absolutely drove me nuts. I'm only 24 and I don't remember anyone having anything close to that many tattoos. I feel like almost everyone in the show looked older than they should have. Especially Bryce </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-31 06:19:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Oh my... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-31 06:19:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> maybe give it a round in a salad spinner </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-31 06:17:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This is their second one. I'm pretty surprised its still in tact lol. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-31 05:50:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I bought my wedding dress from Burlington Coat Factory for $25 lol. I would have bought used if I had more time to shop around. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> How many rats fit in a pineapple? The answer is 4! </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-31 02:15:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-29 07:58:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> and I believed this until just now -_- </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-27 23:47:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm 5'5 174 lbs. (pretty overweight). In order to lose 2lbs per week, I would need 1118 cals per day. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-27 03:41:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> My calorie limit for the day is ~1200 calories a day... 2300 is a lot for some people  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-25 22:48:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Ugh, I had a friend invite me over, saying she was having a small get together. I love meeting new people and going to social events, so I was like "okay!" Imagine my surprise when one of the guys starts a presentation on cheap vacations and shit. I was fucking pissed. Don't bamboozle people,bitch.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-25 22:23:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I am deployed. Just as a contractor lol :D </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-25 08:41:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Man, we can't leave food out for my cat because he's a total glutton. He's the only cat I've ever seen that manages his diet so poorly. We feed him once in the evening and once in the morning...I think he's just a big cat, because he's not noticeably fat, minus his little jiggle pooch. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Everything had to have a background and some text for it to be cool </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-25 04:15:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-25 04:07:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm a civilian contractor :)  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-24 23:37:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Alright, thanks!  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The mysterious disappearing lip ring... </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-24 23:07:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hey there! 

I've had my lip pierced for just under a year. Just about an hour ago, after I finished eating, my lip ring fell out. I managed the find the ball between my legs in my chair, but the post is no where to be found. I'm pretty sure I swallowed it...so I guess I could TECHNICALLY get it back..but ya know...gross.

Anyway, I'm currently in the Middle East on deployment and will be home in the states in about 2 weeks. I'm more than positive shipping a lip ring out here would not get here before I leave. I do not have anything that I can place in as a retainer. 

What are the possibilities of this closing in 2 weeks? Can I slow the process by sticking a clean earring/nose ring in it every couple hours? If it does close, are there any issues with repiercing the same spot? Not really freaking out, just love my lip piercing :/ 

Thanks in advance for the answers :D </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-23 09:49:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I met my first one a few months ago. He doesn't vaccinate his kids. Not because they might get autism. No, he thinks the government is poisoning us and vaccines are their way of slowly eradicating us. I'm not kidding, and I fucking wish I was. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-22 07:01:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Oh sweet! Thanks :) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Farmer's Market </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-22 05:23:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hello Valley people!

I've been living in the AV for about 2 years and I have yet to find a Farmer's Market! Anyone have any intel on this? I've heard of one in Lancaster, but don't know where. Also heard of one in Wrightwood, but don't know where, lol. 

If ya'll could give me some info, that'd be great :) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-21 23:22:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I asked my husband one day if I fell into the category of "fat" or "curvy". He said "is definitely consider you curvy, because whenever I look up "curvy girl" porn, I get behemoth whales" lol </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-19 22:11:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This is what I was expecting. I emailed Disney to get a straight answer. I'll post when I get a response.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-19 06:38:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I feel like the website does not provide enough insight on this. I think it should say "each ticket holder must have an ID" or something like that.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-19 06:29:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I bought my tickets online and it only asked for my info for billing and such, which would prove I'm a SoCal Resident. I'm just curious why it would allow me to buy multiple tickets without providing proof for the rest of the tickets.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> SoCal Discount ID question </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-19 04:49:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hi there!

I recently purchased 4 SoCal $149 3-day one park per day tickets. My friend will be purchasing 2, one for his sister, one for himself.

According to the Disneyland Website, a person May purchase up to 5 tickets per person per day with valid ID. I am curious if my ID will be good enough for the 4 tickets I purchased, and my friend's ID will be good for his 2 tickets. 3 of the 4 people in my group have SoCal ID's, but one does not (even though we all live there, so she could bring a bill or something). My friend is a SoCal Resident, but his sister is coming in from out of state. 

I would really appreciate some insight here. Just in case it wasn't clear, I used my credit card and address for the 4 tickets. My friend will be using his as well for his 2.

Thanks in advance!

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-03 08:11:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This give me another reason to like Marriott.. most of their hotels of been in have white comforters. If that thing was "dirty" I would know. I'm not so grossed out about it not getting changed between guests, but more the idea that it has to be visibly dirty to do it.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-02 08:36:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> holy fuck, me too. I had Naruto dog tags I always wore. The fingerless gloves and wristbands. I did then ninja run, tried to learn the incantations (SHADOW CLONE JUTSU! Huhayayahab) I only watched the subbed version of the anime so I didn't lose any authenticity. I managed to watch 200 episodes of Naruto in a week (spring break).

Jesus, those were dark times. Great show tho.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-24 21:12:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> No, it was coke </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-20 06:32:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hahaha, oddly enough, I myself, did not notice the relevance hahaha </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-20 05:10:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I love baking things for work and parties, I don't really NEED one of these, but it's been a long time want. There's so many things I can do with my hands being free! Hhaha </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-20 05:09:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thanks! It was actually my husband who found it! I'm  working overseas right now, so I won't get to use it until April. He was wise enough to message me that there was one there haha  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Kitchenaid Classic mixer for $80 at Goodwill! Dreams DO come true! </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-19 08:04:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-17 07:59:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I was pretty shocked when I had to add a stamp to my ballot...of all mail that should be marked official, I'd say a ballot is one of those lol </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-10 20:21:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Ugh, I felt like I was looking at one of my family members' Facebook accounts  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Almost 2 month plateau </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-09 01:18:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hey There~

I'll start out with my stats: 23 F SW:190 CW:178 GW:160. I have been consistently working out for 4 months, 6 days a week. I stick to a Keto-ish diet (I do like potatoes every once in a while, ha!). I do not track my food any more, because I'm deployed and I have no clue what is in my food, at all. (i.e meatloaf in sauce that's probably made of nothing but sugar). I do my best to have small portions (successfully), and avoid carbs. I may be +/- on my calories, but I'm definitely burning a good bit in the gym. I don't touch soda, even when I'm not dieting, and I typically don't like sugar anyway. Because of my work shift and the available meal times, I eat at 1130pm and 730am. So I've got quite a bit of fasting going on in there.

Having worked out for 4 months (lifting and cardio), I have only lost 12 pounds. I lost those 12 pounds in the first 2 months, and I have been stalled since then. I have of course been increasing my weights for my lifting, as much as I can. This in itself is a struggle because I do not have a wide variety of dumbbells available. They start at 5kg, then move to 10kg so on and so forth. It makes it difficult to actually change my weight since the next step up is often too heavy. I typically do more reps with the light weight, or do as many reps as I can with the heavy weight, then finish the set with the other weight. 

I don't know if this helps any, but I carry almost all my weight in my stomach. Throughout my work out program, my legs and arms have toned up significantly. My problem area is the belly! My weight trends in the past few years have stayed pretty consistent. I usually hang out between 175-185. 190 is my highest. I have been on the birth control pill for many of those years. Is it possible my birth control is hindering my weight loss? What can I do? HALP ! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-09 00:27:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> My dog and cat do this all the time... it's quite hilarious  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-08 00:38:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I lived in the bible belt from grade 8-11. We had our "sex ed" class in 8th grade. it was called "Life Choices". Imagine my surprise when it was a decent class. That being said, a majority of my would have been senior class now have children. (I'm 23) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-07 22:19:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> At my company, we do a 9/80 schedule. We get every other Friday off, and it's fucking glorious. On working fridays, we work 8 hours. The rest of the days are 9hours, but having a 3 day weekend every other week definitely makes up for that </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-06 03:34:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I thought this as soon as I heard it. It was definitely a subtle way to send a message without pissing people off  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-04 21:38:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Having a male rat crawl on me was an odd experience haha  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-02 18:35:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> My old school district in Georgia did this. Elementary, middle, and high school started at he same time. The town was small enough that we had enough busses to accommodate, without causing an issue. It was definitely convenient for those with siblings.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-01 04:40:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> They sell a premade one... I think its from Peppridge Farm. 4-cheese Garlic bread. Shit is delicious </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-01 04:19:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I had Implanon as well. I bled for 6 of 9 months. I DEMANDED they take it out. I was moody, gaining weight, acne...the shit was horrific. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-31 04:40:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Holy shit. I have been wanting to play this game again!  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-30 22:57:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I've been working out and dieting for 3 months now. The first 2 months, I lost 12lbs. I've been stuck at 178 for the past month. Sooo frustrating. I blame my birth control lol </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-30 22:39:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I think Daniel Radcliffe wore the same style of clothing for months to prevent the paparazzi from getting "new" candids. Might have been a different celebrity, but funny nonetheless  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-30 07:29:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Wasn't some of this the premise of "shutter island"? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-28 03:04:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Another quote that I really like is "and everything was as good as it could be"
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-27 10:51:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Remember Me.

I know it seems silly, but I feel down for a day or so after watching it. Not even because of the "plot twist" at the ending, but the amount of emotion conveyed throughout the whole movie. Definitely a chick flick, but so goood!

Plus Robert Pattinson is a total babe with great acting chops!  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-27 10:49:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The book is really good too. It's definitely something I want to give to my future teenage kids  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-27 10:42:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Ooh, sounds interesting. I'll have to give it a read.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-27 10:40:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This terrifies me. Whenever I watch any kind of disease movie, I get chills. I feel it is the most likely thing to take us all out </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-27 10:37:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I absolutely REFUSE to get into a tanning bed. I've never wanted to prior to that movie, but it basically sealed the deal for me  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-27 10:16:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I really hope I never have to get on meds. I would probably lose my job...aviation woes :/ </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-26 07:00:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Just did this in the office...laughter ensued  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-25 10:05:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Ugh, the horrors of community showers... I haven't taken a shower barefoot in 3 months  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-25 09:56:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm a woman and I have a serious question. Having already known about having the separate holes, why does my tampon get soaked if I pee with it in?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-24 21:12:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This actually makes me feel much better about my inability to do a pull-up lol </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-21 00:04:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> One of my coworkers said "wait until your child is sick, and you will find god" 

Like... really?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-18 09:26:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Maybe they meant embarrassment OVER dying </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-17 09:43:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Oh yeah! That's right! I just reread all the books and watched all the movies and I can't remember at all </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-17 07:11:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It was a reference to someone's dark mark. I want to say it was Karkoff to someone else, but I might be complete wrong </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-17 07:09:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I actually found it kind of funny. Mostly because it caused sooo much controversy with fans lol </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-15 10:01:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Holy fuck. I'm dying.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-14 21:22:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Bass clarinet here. Yup. Low brass </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-12 23:38:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I always call it wish-shish-er lol </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-07 03:27:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I did a little bit of research and I think I could claim her if her and her husband file separately, but I don't forsee that happening. It's frustrating that supporting someone else doesn't even get me tax benefits, ha. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Can I claim my sister in law on my taxes? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-07 03:13:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hello, PF!

I'm getting a jump start on my taxes with Turbo-Tax. It is asking if I have a child or support someone else. In it's help window, it defines support:

"Whether it's a child, a friend or a relative you support, the term 'support' is generally defined as what you spend on a person to provide the basic necessities of life. While the specifics may be debatable in certain circles, here's what the IRS considers typical for the purposes of a tax return. 

Support includes:
 *  Food 
 *  Lodging (even if your mortgage is paid off)  
 *  Clothing
 *  Education (including the GI bill)
 *  Medical and dental care (including insurance and supplementary Medicare premiums)
 *  Recreation
 *  Transportation and similar necessities"

I am technically doing almost all of this for my husband's sister and her son. While the simple answer should probably be yes, I've hit a bit of a wall. She is still married to her husband (soon to be ex, if he ever files). Can I still add her as someone I support if she's married? I'm curious if I do add her, if it will cause some issues with their taxes. She didn't start her job until Nov. 1 which is kind of irrelevant, since she only makes about $1000 a month.

Could really appreciate some insight here!
thanks :)
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-02 07:57:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> But they're comfy!  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-08 02:51:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm not her. She is a friend from high school. When this all happened originally, she posted this same tweet on her Facebook to let everyone know that someone is using her photos. As I said in my above comment, she wouldn't say something along those lines. And it is embarrassing. She is being misrepresented. Would a good friend not be upset about that? 
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-08 01:17:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> For the record, the girl in the picture isn't the one who posted this. Her photos were stolen and used to troll. I went to high school with her and she would never say anything like that. She's aware that this happened, many months ago. She was pretty pissed off </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-05 20:51:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That one time when UPS left my $1200 laptop on the doorstep without even ringing the door bell...  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-05 00:58:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Straws help me drink more. I love lemon water. La Croix waters are strangely addictive as well </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-03 23:38:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Ooh! A place I've actually visited! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-27 01:10:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Bleu... cos you're feeling blue  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-24 21:57:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Ha, I joined the military, got out, became on contractor, currently on deployment, making 100k a year and I'm still lazy _ </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-23 23:18:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I've been doing keto for almost 5 weeks. I'm struggling a lot. Not so much with not eating particular things, but with the options I have. I'm deployed overseas to a relatively new location, so we don't get a lot of options for chow. I grab what I assume doesn't have a lot of carbs, and then find out it has waaaaay more than I'd like. I can barely meet my calorie goals because of so few choices. 

I'm working out 6 days a week. I've lost 5lbs since I started all this. I'm going to assume I'm not losing because I'm gaining muscle in the process. I'm feeling very discouraged, like I should stop keto until I get home and can actually choose my food. I've felt so great since I stopped eating so many carbs, but I know as soon as I just "watch" my carbs, I'll be eating the whole dessert table. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-23 23:13:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Just scrape the filling out hehe  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-15 04:23:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> We played a lot of Robert W. Smith music. There is almost always a French horn solo (his wife was a French horn player) and a bass clarinet solo. Check out Into the Storm. There's a great bass clarinet/ piccolo duet thingy. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-12 05:30:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Unfortunately, I have no way to cook :( </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-11 22:00:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I think the main reason I struggle with hydration is because I can't always get up and go to the bathroom with my job. Also, the bathroom is like 1/2 mile walk lol. I try to do a bottle an hour, but it doesn't always work out.

I don't have access to coconut oil, and ordering it would probably get it here by the time I leave,lol. We done have actual butter here, just shitty margarine, I think, haven't actually looked. No avacados. We have nuts that are unbearably salty, but I could rinse them, I guess. I think just adding an oz of nuts would get my cal count up </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Keto thus far </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-11 21:03:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hello!

I've been doing keto for about 3 weeks now. I think I've lost 2lbs. I'm working out (lifting) a little as well, so maybe that's why I'm not losing.  My husband says my stomach looks smaller(pics). I'm currently deployed, so keto is actually pretty easy with the limited choices. I've stopped tracking my food, since I'm typically eating the same things everyday.

I find that I'm not hungry nearly as often as i used to be. I also find that when I do eat, it makes me kind of nauseous. It quickly goes away, but it's odd. I am coming concerned that I'm not eating enough. When I last tracked my food, it had me at only 900cals. I should be eating 1200 to lose. My issue is that I'm just not hungry! 

I've also noticed that when I have to pee, there isn't much warning, I just realize "shit, I need to pee". I definitely have the keto pee stank. It's harder and harder for me to stay hydrated. Keto also managed to start my period. Which totally sucks, because I'm on BC and just had my period a week and a half ago. 

Overall, I feel alright, a little discouraged due to almost no weight loss, not even the large amount of water weight most people lose. I plan to stick with it a little longer, but shit, I want a waffle. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-25 08:04:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm trying to figure out how I didn't even know these existed until recently... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-18 05:59:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Sometimes thrift stores will have Levi's in great shape. You can probably find some at Ross/Tj Maxx/ Burlington coat factory  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-14 18:32:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> A terrible habit :( </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-14 18:32:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> We've always wanted koala tats. I suggested doing this and he didn't disagree lol.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Husband and I got koala "ring" tattoos. [Psycho City, Palmdale, CA] </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-14 03:56:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-12 19:00:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This is more what I was heading for. Apparently this doesn't exist though, lol </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-12 18:43:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I don't give a fuck if I get salmonella. I just want my DIPPY EGGS!~ </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-12 18:38:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Sunny side up! Gotta have some toast with strawberry jelly on it to dip into that sweet,sweet, yolk </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-12 18:29:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> My husband and I dated for 9months during our senior year. After I joined the Air Force, we broke up for 3 years. We reconnected and got married 2 months later. We have been married for 2 1/2 years and it's pretty damn fantastic. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-12 18:26:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Don't shelter your kids. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-12 18:25:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I have no filter. If I think you're stupid, I'm going to let you know. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-12 18:24:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The cello. Watching people play the cello is so relaxing to me. The amount of passion put into playing is just amazing. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-12 18:22:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Milk. My nephew goes through milk like it's going out of style. It's way cheaper to buy 2 gallons at Costco than anywhere else.

Also, cheese. You can get a 3lb block of mozzerella for like, $5 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-12 18:20:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I forgot to got to the cafeteria for breakfast :/ </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-12 18:19:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Maybe, but it's happened. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-12 18:04:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's happened a few times. I'll describe someone as a tall black guy or light-skinned black guy, and I get funny looks or accused of being racist. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-12 18:00:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Choosing to join the Air Force. Had I not, I have no clue where I'd be. Thanks to the Air Force, I work for a company doing the same exact job as when I was in, but for more money. I bought my house with the VA loan. Having Veteran status has done a lot for me. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-12 17:59:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Heather Sinclair from Degrassi. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-12 17:59:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> He accepted me, flaws and all. He loves me for who I am, not what I've done.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
