<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject2851</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> I Heard My Neighbour Talking </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-10 02:12:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I know what you're all thinking "whoopie doodle, I hear my neighbours talking all the time"
but are there other people around when you hear them talking?    if there aren't, do you hear the other party responding?

I was home alone, it was a quiet tuesday evening.  I was killing time by playing stupid cell phone games.  Y'know, just a normal night.  But I was startled by a voice in the hallway, it was my neighbor across the hall talking to someone.

Now, my first thought was 'well, at least it's not me'.  Don't get me wrong, he's a nice guy, friendly, but oh my god can he talk your ear off!    being the anti-social introvert that I am, I tend to just keep to myself   try to avoid human contact whenever possible

But the more I thought about it, the weirder it got.  Cuntzilla upstairs was away on vacation,   the lady who lived above him worked until midnight.  I knew for a fact that we were the only 2 people currently in the building (it's a small, high security building)

I thought maybe the landlord was here, but a glance into the apartment told me that no, we really were the only people in this building.

Curiosity got the better of me, so I ninja'd my way to the door, a move I've perfected whenever I hear him   Cuntzilla talking (no, I'm not one of those old busybodies who has their nose in everyone's business - first off, I'm only 36.  Secondly, I just want to keep on top of what rumours she's spreading about me.  But that's not important right now)

Through my peephole, I have a perfect view of the foyer I share with him.  I saw him, facing one of the 2 exit doors,   talking to someone.  But the door was closed   no one was on this side of it.
Then I heard another voice, another male voice, reply to him.  The only men who live in this apartment building are my neighbour   my husband, so I KNOW it wasn't either of them.  

'They' continued to chat for another 5ish minutes about nothing overly important; weather, cars, the sort of thing you chat with an acquaintance with, before my neighbour says goodbye   heads out the other exit door.  I stand at my door, listening.  I hear my neighbour go up the stairs   leave, but I never hear anything from the other side of the door that he was talking to. 

I decide to grow some balls   investigate under the guise of doing laundry.  I grab my ever-present laundry basket full of dirty clothes   walk out the door, through the closed door,   into....
nothing.  Just the stairwell   laundry room.  I look under the stairs, glance into corners,   even go into the laundry room, but there is no one anywhere to be seen.  If he had left, I would have heard him.

I know this isn't that scary, but I'm pretty high strung   can usually tell just by sound alone what's going on in my building (it's not that there's thin walls, just that I'm hyper-aware of sounds   what they mean, annoyingly so) so as it gets darker   I'm home alone, I'm left wondering: who was that man?    where did he go? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-07 16:34:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> "Hey guys, meet my mom" </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-06 06:36:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I was really enjoying this series, looking forward to the next part...

I hate this ending.  I am dissapoint. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-02 10:42:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This actually happened to me.  I still have the ring,   I wore it in the beginning,  long enough to have a reason to complain about something other than the appearance - it was a wide ring   I have sensitive skin, it was trapping sweat   other moisture   irritating my skin.

Luckily it was cheap (my husband knows not to buy me expensive things)   one day while we were browsing a pawn shop, a ring caught my eye   I told him that was the one I wanted.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-01 05:41:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'd be happy with 10 or so tickets.  Just spend them on people who hated me   made my life miserable,  Just so my memory can keep making them miserable  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-30 07:33:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hey everyone, let's say we send this music back to Dullsville   we can start a rousing round of Kum-bye-ah! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Terrible profession/name combinations </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-30 00:55:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-27 21:31:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Skirts get put on like pants, dresses like shirts
That's what works for me, but if it doesn't feel right, try different ways </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-27 18:12:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> "When you tickle me,   I will be tickled, it will be a great tickle,   I will laugh, it will be a great laugh,   it will happen" </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-25 19:53:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> "Listen up you fucking wee bitches, it's nap time"

"I'm not tired teacher!"

*Gordon rolls child up in blanket* "What are You?"

"An idiot burrito"  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-25 07:25:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's neat seeing the place I live  mentioned in a story :D  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-25 07:22:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Actually it was just a random YouTube video,  but it's still weird that I went from never hearing about it to twice within 6 hours in completely different areas of the internet  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
