<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject6464</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Eating For Free on My Birthday </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-09 18:08:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yesterday was my birthday. Before going to the restaurant to eat for free, I went to tutoring. We completed a chapter from the accounting class before the lecture in my class. The tutor won't be available on Wednesday because he will be going to an internship.

The restaurant have five locations: two in Manhattan, one in Queens, one in Brooklyn, and one in New Jersey. I went to the one at East Village by bus because it's just two train stops to the restaurant. The place wasn't still in renovation, so I took the bus to Chinatown.

The buses that go to Chinatown is frequented by seniors, as younger people prefer the subway. I would go to Chinatown from my college via subway as it is 4 stops away and 2 or 3 dozen bus stops away.

When I entered, the restaurant wasn't that buzy. I got a seat right away and showed my ID for my free meal. I ordered their curry soup base hot pot with mountain yam, fried tofu, special pork, lamb, fish fillet, Fuzhou fish balls, fried dough, rice, fish roe balls, fried tofu skin, and crab sticks. The crab sticks are served with plastic wrap. I removed the wrap after putting the crab sticks into the pot.

When I went to the sauce counter, I mix sesame sauce, peanut sauce, peanut oil, welsh onion, cilantro, soy sauce, hoisin sauce and wasabi. Some of the labels are misplaced. When I came back the second time, I found chili oil, so I took the bowl of sauce and added the chili sauce. I mix the sauce up and end up with a red, pungent, and savory concoction.

I couldn't finish the rice and went got tong sui for dessert. I chose to have grass jelly with coconut milk to neutralize the acidity from the hot pot. I left $2 as tips. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> No Birthday Cake on My Birthday </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-09 17:39:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This past Sunday, my dad preordered the birthday cake for me. He told me that he will pick it up Monday night.

However, on Monday, he forgot to pick up the birthday cake because he was busy and when he tried to pick it up the bakery closed.

Today, he told me that he will pick it up when he goes to work and put it in the fridge and I have to remind him to get it from the fridge at 10pm. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Types of Ramen Broths </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-08 02:06:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> There are various kinds of ramen soup bases you may not have heard of or never tasted before.

The simplest and oldest type of soup base is salt. It is just chicken stock flavored with salt. The Hakodate ramen uses this kind of soup base.

The second type of soup base is soy sauce. It is chicken stock flavored with soy sauce. The Tokyo ramen uses this soup base.

The third type of soup base is tonkotsu. Tontoksu is pork bone stock. Kyushu uses this kind of soup base. The Ajisen and Ichiran chains are based in Kyushu and have three stores and one store in NYC respectively.

The fourth type of soup base is miso. Miso is fermented soy bean paste. This is a newcomer and is originated in Hokkaido.

The fifth type of soup base is curry. This is also a newcomer and is originated in Muroran, Hokkaido. In Hokkaido, there is soup curry, a watery curry dish.

The sixth type of soup base is paitan, or white soup. It is usually made by boiling bones before crushing it. It results in a milky-while soup base.

The seventh type of soup base is chintan, or clear soup. It is made from boiling chicken bones or bonito flakes. The soup is transparent. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-07 20:45:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This will piss off Trump and Germany will revert to Merkel. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Hotpot Restaurants vs. Asian Barbecue Restaurants </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-07 04:16:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> There are various versions of hotpot: Japanese hotpot, i.e. shabu shabu and sukiyaki, Chinese hot pot, i.e. doulao and huowuo, and Korean hotpot, i.e. jjigae and sinseollo.

There are Chinese and Taiwanese hotpot restaurants where you ask the waiter items you want to eat or get it yourself at the counters and dump it in your pot of broth before taking it our before eating. Restaurants usually use electric burners to heat your pot.

There are some restaurants that use gas burners. I don't like using gas burners because the fire is inconsistent, can leak carcinogenic poisons, and needs to be replaced from time to time. Electric burners are consistent and is easy to control.

In these restaurants, you have to make your sauce at the sauce counter. I like mixing sesame oil, peanut sauce, sesame sauce, shacha BBQ sauce, wasabi, chili oil, soy sauce, ponzu or lemon, oyster sauce, welsh onions, and cilantro. I whisk up my sauce and end up with a red concoction that is spicy and acidic. Some restaurant charge extra for drinks but there is only one that includes drinks in NYC. I drink a bottle of Yakult to coat my stomach.

I like to order pork, beef, lamb, offal, fish, squid, clams, potato, yams, taro, fish balls, tofu, and noodles. For thick items like seafood and vegetables, I just let them sit in the broth and fetch them up later. I swish the thinly slices of meat at they cook easily. Letting them sit on the broth will make them hard to eat.

I always end the hotpot meal with dessert. I eat ice cream as it's a dairy. Some do include tong sui water dessert.

There is only one restaurant that lets you eat for free on your birthday and there is one that gives a discount for showing your student ID.

The Japanese shabu-shabu is a hot pot dish where you swish the meats in the water before dipping in sauce. You only have ponzu and sesame sauce. From time to time, you would have to remove floating scum to keep the broth consistent. There is only one restaurant that serves buffet shabu-shabu in NYC and in New Jersey with a sauce counter.

The Koreans don't have Chinese or Japanese-like hotpot restaurants but have the sinseollo and the jjigae. Jjigae are stews cooked in ceramic pots. One well-known jjigae is budae-jjigae that was developed during the Korean war that uses instant ramen and American ingredients. The sinseollo used to be eaten by the royalty. It consists of 22 ingredients and is considered nutritious.

There are three types of barbecue restaurants: Korean barbecue, Japanese yakiniku, and Chinese chuan skewers and shaomi Cantonese BBQ.

In Korean barbecue, the waiter cooks the food for you. The portion sizes is suitable to be shared with friends. At the end of the meal, any uneaten pieces of kimchi and meats will be used to make fried rice to end the meal. You are also served complementary banchan and samchu to wrap your meats on. Waiters usually bring the food to your table to be cooked. However, there is a restaurant where you go to the counter to pick up. Usually, the grills are flat or slanted for the fat to be collected with an flame hood hanging from the ceiling. Smokeless grills are not that common as it's not authentic to Korean style.

The last time I ate Korean BBQ was in Summer 2014. The restaurant serves it buffet style. I ordered too much. In top of meats, they have cooked food of fried chicken, pajeon, and japchae.

In Japanese yakiniku, the portions are usually bite-sized unless stated, which is ideal for one person. Restaurants usually have waiters bring the food to you, but there are few that require you to pick up from the counter. In Japan, there are restaurants that uses shichirin bucket grills filled with charcoal with a flame hood hanging from the ceiling. However, in NYC, there are no charcoal yakiniku, but uses smokeless grills that uses electric or ceramic charcoal possibly due to regulations. You cook the food yourself unless stated. In addition to yakiniku, there are yakitori skewers. Some yakiniku restaurants do also have yakitori as part of the buffet, but are not that common. In Hokkaido, there is the jingisukan, a dish consists of grilled lamb on a pan, instead of a net in yakiniku.

In NYC, there are the chains Yakiniku Gen, Yakiniku Futago, Gyukaku, and Yakiniku West, and the independent restaurant Takeshi. One time, I invited my friend to eat at Gen and ordered all of their assorted items and paid $130. At Futago, I ordered two orders of offals, samgeopsal, appetizers, cold noodles, and kakigori shaved ice and paid $93. At Takashi, I ordered to orders of beef and paid $30. Gyukaku have the cheapest prices as they have happy hour, lunch special, and group sets. They have buffet but is only limited-time.

The Chinese don't eat barbecue similar to the Korean or Japanese style. However, there are chuan skewers and siu mei Cantonese barbecue. In NYC, there are these street venders that sell skewers by item and grill the food before you. I don't eat that often. There are restaurant in NYC that sell skewers where you cook on your own, but charge by item, instead of buffet. The siu mei Cantonese barbecue is cooked in rotisserie. I am not a fan of chicken, but like to eat duck, char siu, and roast pork. The Mongolian barbecue is not Mongolian but is a modern barbecue originated from Taiwan. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The Passing of AHCA </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-06 19:41:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hi David. After AHCA 3.0 was passed in the House, I don't see it passing in the Senate, but rather have it revised. If it passed to the White House, I would see blue state implementing their form of healthcare, or what California is doing right now is attempting to pass their own universal health care. I think it will pass due to the it being popular by Bernie Sanders. Other states will follow suit. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> YouTube Adpocalypse Will Only Cause YouTube to Fail </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-06 18:27:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> For more than a month since the start of YouTube Adpocalyse, many content creators are being affected. Every alternative news networks I subscribe to saw a decrease on revenue. However, they are making up the lost revenue by asking for donations from viewers and selling merchandise.

Some YouTubers have accounts on Twitch and Musical.ly for an alternative way to make money or have side jobs to earn alternative revenue. Lately, GradeAUnderA hasn't been uploading on YouTube for more than 4 weeks. Maybe he is buzy with Twitch or delay uploading the next video.

If the YouTube adpocalyse doesn't go away, content creators will leave and look for YouTube 2.0 as their new home. I myself would have a Twitch account and start an independent entertainment studio and create pay-per-view animation on iTunes or Netflix and have an account on YouTube until YouTube 2.0 is released. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Why the AHCA Will Be Unpopular With Blue States </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-06 00:48:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Now the House passed the AHCA, we will see what the Senate will do. I asked a psychic about it and she said that the Senate will revise it and be pushed back to the House.

The new healthcare will affect the red states more than the blue states. The red states are poor while the blue states are richer. The blue states can reject the AHCA and raise their own taxes and implant their own healthcare. California is proposing a universal health care. It is likely that it will pass as it's popular due to Sanders. When that happens, other states will follow suit.

Red states, on the other hand, will have to drop healthcare for some people. This will cause poorer people and people with pre-existing conditions to go bankrupt and die from preventable diseases. That will cause an exodus into the blue states. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Being a Left-Wing Conspiracy Theorist </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-03 16:46:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I have lived in NYC for the past 17 years. I myself can be considered a left-wing conspiracy theorist as NYC is a predominately liberal city.

My first post on Reddit is about Gravity Falls being a metaphor of the 2012 and 2016 presidential elections. The show was created by a liberal producer Alex Hirsch. I found a lot of parallels between the show and the respective presidential elections. However, season 2 only reflects the result if Hillary becomes president. The show is likely influenced by the Illuminati due to the fact that Bill Cipher is a triangle-shaped creature.

The Children's Anime Shin-chan is what I considered is a metaphor for globalism. Shin-chan's attires fits the colors of the Chinese flag. Kazama's attires fits the colors of the NYC flag. He also speaks English.

Anpanman is a metaphor for a salad bowl. In the show, you will see various cultures in the late creator's world. If I were to create an adult spin-off of it, I would include politically incorrect and vulgar content. I think that the late creator Takashi Yanase was influenced by the Illuminati due to the fact that one of his characters Niyandar Kamen is an anthropomorphic cat superhero. Cats have pointed ears that can resemble a triangle, the symbol of the Illuminati.

Any animator who have created any animation that contains cats or foxes are influenced by the Illuminati. These animals have pointy ears resembling triangles, the symbol of the Illuminati. Popular examples include, but not related to, the late Doraemon creator Fujiko F. Fujio, The Amazing World of Gumball creator Ben Bocquelet, failed pilot Kitty Bobo creators Kevin Kaliher and Meaghan Dunn, and the Cyborg Kuro-chan creator Naoki Yokouchi.

Prime Minister Winston Churchill was a racist, self-centered leader during the WWII. If he was a full-blown clone of Hitler, he would have enhance and glorify colonialism.

NYC is a predominately liberal city. Conservatives usually get marginalized here. Staten Island is a predominately conservative borough except for the northern neighborhoods. Due to Brexit, Staten Island may have its own Stanexit and become its own independent entity. If that happens, it will be stopped by the city.

Bakumatsu marks the end of the samurai era in Japan. During those final years, the East is pitted against the West. The East represents liberalism while the West represents conservation, with the emperor backing the West. After the last shogun abdicated, conservatism takes over Japan, even to this day.

The GOP is currently attempting to achieve political supremacy. However, it won't stick like the Liberal Democratic Party in Japan. After Trump leaves and another hard-line conservative is elected, we will see the demise of the GOP to the point of rebranding or dissolution.

The remilitarization of Japan can be viewed as a reignition of a Sino-Japanese cold war. I see that as a lose-lose situation. It can go nuclear.

The only way for Japan to turn politically left is by having a Bernie Sanders-like politican and have him as the prime minister. If Bernie Sanders himself was elected president, we would be better off than Trump.

Some police use stop-and-frisk tactics. This is a way to suppress minorities. NYC chose to discontinue the practice.

Using condoms is an effective way to prevent rape and child abuse. It forms a barrier between a penis and a vagina.

C-section-based abortions, or hysterotomy abortion, are acceptable. This is an alternative to ripping a fetus apart with a speculum. It is often done by Japanese soldiers during WWII. If I were to show a pregnant minor getting an abortion on Collegehumor, the surgeon will perform it by chaining the minor up. He then uses a dagger to cut open her womb and cut the umbilical cord with a regular scissors before stitching up the womb. This is all done without anesthesia.

Tanukis are raccoon-dogs that are viewed as good luck in Japanese culture. The reason why it is so is that the kanji for taunki refers a medium-sized animals resembling cats. As stated above, cats are part of the Illuminati.

I think the 8th Tokugawa shogunate Yoshimune from Kii, or modern-day Wakayama, is Japan's first Bernie Sanders before the 21st century. He is known as the unruly shogun, or ararenbo shogun. He mingles with the commoners and set up a box for commoners to make requests, thus making him a populist.

Every person gets killed by police in the US is one step closer to becoming a police state to racial suppression.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Trump-Kim Rivalry=Lose-Lose Situation </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-02 04:38:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> We are see growing tensions betweens the US and North Korea to the point of nuclear war. I sense that both sides will face defeat should they fight.

Nuclear war will destroy humanity and is expensive to finance. This will not fix any existing problems. The nuclear war will turn into a world war. That is when full humanity will be annihilated.

Both Trump and Kim are narcissists and have a cult of personality. They are both equally dangerously incompetent. People in North Korea is living in misery. Only the ones in Pyongyang like in prosperity. Trump will fund military but will make people poor from social cuts.

However, there is a chance of North Korea unify with South Korea and Trump's approval rating will tank to 25% or lower.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Types of Grades Schools Give to Students </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-01 16:16:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> There are various types of grading systems schools use to grade a student's performance.

During my elementary school years, the grades are based on a number system, with 1 for below target, 2 for approaching target, 3 for meeting target, and 4 for exceeding target. I got a lot of 2's as I didn't care about my classes then.

During my intermediate and high school years, the grades are based on number grades, with 55 as fail and increasing in 5-point increments, where from 90 points increase in 1-point increments. I never got a 55 in any classes but did got 65's and 75's. However, in high school, I had to change classes due to the fact that I was put into a class that I already took and on the report card it was N/A meaning that I was recently placed with limited class assignments completed.

In college, the grades are letter-based, the letters are based on the range of your performance in the classes a student take. Some classes are quite hard but there is tutoring. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> May 7 French Presidential Elections </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-01 02:50:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hi David. Who do you see becoming the next president in France? I am seeing some parallels between the 2016 Clinton-Trump election and this upcoming election. In February, Wilders lost to Geert in second place. If Wilders won, Le Pen would have won easily. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Moritomo Controversy=Trump's New Executive Order </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-01 02:48:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Earlier this year, we have seen Japanese PM Shinzo Abe after selling public land to the Japanese nationalist private Moritomo schools. This has caused high disapproval among the Liberal Democratic Party. The offer was later got turned down.

This is similar to Trump new executive order of using national monuments for oil drilling purposes. The president has been trying to enrich himself from this, this considering this unconstitutional. This will end up polluting the environment. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Macron-Le Pen Runoff=Clinton-Trump Runoff </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-01 02:39:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> On May 7, there will be an election to see who will be France's next president. Similar to the November 4 election, we see a runoff between an establishment left candidate and an anti-establishment right candidate. It was a lose-lose situation that if either one was elected, it doesn't help the US. Now that we have seen Trump's first 100 days, it was full of unconstitutional executive orders.

The same will follow in the French runoff. We may see the same situation. However, earlier this year, Wilders lost to Rutte in the Netherlands. If Wilders had won, Le Pen could have won easily. However, France might expect from the same old-same old campaigns.

If Le Pen won, the marginalized, the poor, and the minority will support Melenchon, similar to what Sanders is currently doing. If Melenchon was the top two in the first round, he could have won easily.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Taking the Bee Line </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-30 06:55:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> 100 Days of Fail </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-30 04:31:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The first 100 days are considered the honeymoon period. Presidents usually have high approval ratings. However, 45 is currently at 40% approval.

45 isn't that popular due to his unconstitutional policies. These policies only made people miserable. He reached 50% unpopular rating in just 8 days.

All he did in the first 100 days was promoting his own brand. All of his world leaders visited him at Mar-a-Lago in Florida. He is already made US the laughingstock and turned it upside-down, similar to Berlusconi's tenure in Italy.

I don't see him getting a second term as by then his approval rating will be 25% or lower. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The Second Attempt to Repeal the ACA </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-30 03:27:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hi David. The congress is attempting a second attempt to real the ACA. Do you see it passing? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-29 23:35:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> To make education free, we need taxes and cut military spending. To make edication affordable, college should charge students 100 per class they apply and additional classes are free for full time </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-29 23:24:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Why are the swords in the game don't have sheaths to hold the sword with </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Eating Salt-Fermented Fish and Eggs </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-29 22:17:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> From time to time, my grandma makes salt-fermented fish and eggs. She fills a jar with water and add salt into it before adding fish or eggs.

We sometimes eat steamed eggs. Sometimes, the eggs do crack, causing the egg to be very salty. I like to scoop the yolk. The fermentation takes more than a week before eaten.

At the supermarket, there are dried salted fish that are sold. She would use salt brine to fermentate supermarket-brought fish. Today, when she opened the jar, the stench was unbearable. By the time I had lunch, it wasn't that salty and is served with minced meat.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-28 20:36:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Here's one:

http://www.nbcnews.com/news/us-news/calls-about-space-aliens-flood-new-ice-hotline-after-twitter-n752006 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Why the VOICE Hotline is Useless </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-28 03:59:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Trump has announced the creating VOICE for victims of immigrants. I don't see it meaningful as immigrants don't commit a lot of crimes. If anyone became a victim of any crime, they can just report it to their local police departments.

People use the hotline to troll the Department of Homeland Security. The department didn't receive any calls regarding to any crimes committed by immigrants. Instead, they received calls of martial alien and UFO citing and cow abductions. This has cause the department to be unhappy. People stated to proclaim Alien Day to stop the VOICE hotline. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> My Aunt's New Job </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-28 02:58:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Earlier this year, my aunt quit her old job where to makes clothes. The factory plans to move to the Queens-Nassau border. She got a raise, instead of giving transportation compensation. She was fed up with the miscommunication and left the company.

After leaving the factory, she took a break from working. She tries to apply for unemployment. My dad said that she shouldn't leave the old job but rather find another factory.

Currently, she works as a freelance babysitter. She uses an app to look for potential people to work for. She is still waiting to see if she is eligible for unemployment benefits. She would change from family to family base on her current situation. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Chifa </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-28 02:47:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The Current Situation of Right-Wing Populism </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-25 05:46:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Justice Department After Assange </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-24 20:18:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hi David. The justice department is currently going after Juillian Assange. I find this meaningless as Assange is not a US citizen. Do you see this backfire? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Why Right-Wing Populism Will Be Short-Lived </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-24 15:41:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> In March, there was the Dutch general election. Wilders lost to Geert in second place. He is a right-wring populism but people realized what happened if he was prime minister due to Trump becoming president and the Brexit.

In France, Macron and Le Pen are the top two nominees for the next president. If Wilders won, Le Pen would have won easily. However, she is in a deeper hole. People also have known what will happen Le Pen becomes president due to Trump and Brexit.

Sanders is quite popular. People who voted for Trump are turning to him because he is a socialist democrat, who believes that there should be a balance between socialism and capitalism. Currently, the US has a capitalistic government, that causes recessions from time to time. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-24 06:14:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Looks like sublimial messaging to me </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-24 05:59:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Crabs can regrow limbs back </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-24 05:56:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I agred. The oliguarphs are ruining the country. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Why I Watch News From Independent Media </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-23 04:54:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Ever since 2015, I have been watching more independent news than corporate news. Independent news covers topics corporate news tend to avoid.

The first news network I watched was Infowars. I do not watch him anymore as this source is conspiracy theory-based. The reporter Alex Jones just makes up likes that cannot be confirmed. Recently, he apologized for the Pizzagate conspiracy he made up.

Currently, I get my news from The Young Turks, Ring of Fire, Jimmy Dore Show, The Davis Packman Show, The Humanist Report, and Secular Talk. These news networks have channels on YouTube. They report what mainstream news doesn't cover.

However, many large companies pulled their advertisements from the website due to a fake news report from the WSJ about videos showing up on right-wing channels. These reporters are making up their lost revenue with donations.

Recently, The Young Turks, Secular Talk and Sanders supporters teamed up together and created the Justice Democrats PAC to pick progressives to replace corporate and establishment Democrats. Donations rose quickly the few days after launching. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
