<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject8993</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-10 06:19:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Wow thanks!  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-10 06:17:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thanks man. I love my sous vide but you can't beat a perfectly grilled steak.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-10 04:44:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> At certain indirect stores yes. OP specifically asked about corporate so I assume the post is from a corporate rep.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-10 04:34:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You're not gonna get $400 for that phone in all likelihood... It's $576 brand new right now. It also is a LG and it is used, I'd be happy to get $300 tbh.

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-10 04:32:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You traded in at 50% which means you didn't pay the other $350ish you owed on your phone  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-10 04:31:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> There are two forms. One is a promo adjustment form, one is a trade-in adjustment form. Make sure the person is doing the latter.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-10 04:26:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That person is FOS, even if they are making $35k in commission they don't have a $80k salary. 

Also to make $7k in commission this person would have to "cap" their quota and do nearly 3x their sales bucket. If he is doing this this year he must be in the best situation/store in the country.  And literally be top 10 in the country as a rep.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-10 04:25:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You can try a store and ask them to do the form to make sure it's done. I have both promos on my line. Though I got it added by calling.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-10 03:45:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Much appreciated!  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-10 03:45:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yes - sriracha is money on Mac. Never tried pesto will have to try it! Thanks :)  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-10 03:00:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Ok don't see that you said that anywhere..... But anyway. 

Go online, call, or go to a store and do an actual device change on your tablet line. Then once it's a tablet, and not a phone line, you can move to the $65 UDP. 

It'll be $65 UDP + $20 phone + $20 tablet  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-10 02:35:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Right that's what I'm saying. If the account is closed (which if it's $1500, sounds like it could be since DPP buyouts would get sent to bill), then they can't port. Because the number is gone.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-10 02:33:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Have you read anything everyone posted so far? Why don't you just tell us if your second phone is a basic phone or not instead of going in circles  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-10 02:25:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Because it's awful in comparison and apparently not working for you anymore?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-10 02:24:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I don't understand your question. I said it would cost more to have two separate things going unless one phone is a basic phone. If you have 2 smartphones you're better off just doing multi - line unlimited. 

The 65 option has been around since UDP came out.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-10 02:23:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> No im saying if the Verizon account is disconnected for non-payment  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-10 02:22:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> They look great. Nice camera too.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-10 02:16:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Actually yeah. Especially when it is busy. They understand that I took some of my time to help them, and either solved some of their problems/questions or gave it an honest attempt. I just say "sir, I honestly can't help you with these kind of questions right now there are other customers waiting and I am a sales person. I would be happy to get you on the phone with tech support to further assist you because they are the experts on these things, or I can give you the direct number and have you call from home where you're comfortable. But it is too busy right now to try to figure out this app I don't know how to use. You're also welcome to come back and if it isn't busy, I can try to help you further but I don't want to waste your time."

Now that's referring to 3rd party apps, password resets etc. If it's a Verizon related issue, like a bill question, or service issue then I will spend more time and get it fixed or get to the point where I can't do anything else. 

I also gauge the customer in those first minutes. They come in with an email issue and I will just ask if they check a lot of email on their phone if they have ever considered owning a tablet and try to transition the password reset to a sales opportunity. If they are clearly not buying anything then they get a more curtailed service.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-10 02:04:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Why can't you just email/Google hangouts/etc </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-10 02:02:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Will that work if the Verizon account is already disconnected though?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-10 02:00:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's $10/more a month than Tmobile. I think Tmobile got rid of their free HD promo too? So that means for HD Tmobile is $75 and Verizon is $80. Assuming Verizon is better in your area and/or you travel a lot it's a no brainer.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-10 01:55:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It will almost certainly cost you more unless one phone is a basic phone  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-10 01:49:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> How big are they? They look like silver dollars?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [HOMEMADE] Blackened and grilled ribeye with Mac and Cheese </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-10 01:38:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-10 01:21:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Basically be honest with them. Say I can't afford to give up anymore of my time, or that I can't figure out whatever issue it is that their having and suggest they they call tech support. And then offer to call in the store or I can give them the number and they can call from the comfort of their home.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-09 23:49:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I've been looking </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-09 13:30:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Must be nice... My quota is 65N this month  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-09 13:25:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So pay for more, use less, or stop complaining  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-09 04:09:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Well if all you do on your phone is call, text, email, and web browse (which is what these non-technical savvy people say) then no, you don't *need* a 128gb iPhone 7 plus. A $400 phone will do you just fine.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-09 04:05:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Nice goalpost shift  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-09 03:07:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> They haven had an iPhone deal for awhile. Doubt there is anything upcoming. If there is, it will likely require a trade in and new UDP.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-09 02:48:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's a good thing the Verizon reps in your store gave you good advice and read reddit :)  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-09 02:41:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> How many services have you had for 7 years where the price doesn't change? 

And if you were getting kicked off, I'd be willing to bet you were circumventing some rules of some kind to tether a ton of data.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-09 02:09:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> And mine is over 90% for my career. I can count the detractors I've had on 2 hands, and most of those were "great service but [issue that has nothing to do with me]". Venting and having a person in front of you is different. 

However, now the most you will get out of me is 10 minutes if you aren't buying anything. I cannot afford to help you with easily Googled questions when you aren't buying anything. 

NPS isn't paying anymore, RSS are fired, it's clear the goal of the company.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-09 02:06:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah its shame they added $20 for the first time to that 10yr old plan, lol  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-08 23:51:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Probably means you applied successfully  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-08 23:43:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah, nobody is saying we aren't starting an icloud restore after a sale.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-08 19:34:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Showing how to use the basics and trying to help you with your Facebook/yahoo account/bank app are not the same 


Also, it's your money. Nobody is telling you how to spend it. But buying a fully capable device for a premium and not using it is akin to buying a ferrari and only driving it around the block. But it's your money, so nobody is gonna care how you wanna spend it.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-08 19:10:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You'll get the same deal everywhere. I would go to a store because you can trade in your phones for a discount on the S8. It's worth it to pay off.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-08 18:36:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Well since you used an off brand charger you're not Gonna get anywhere  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-08 15:56:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> But half the time that human that we value doesn't value us. There can be a line of 10 people and someone comes up with an inane question so you help them. And you think you're done with their quick question but it becomes another question. And another. And another. And then all of a sudden you're stuck with this person who you were nice to help even though their problem had nothing to do with Verizon and then what. Do you eventually just tell them to leave? Then they look at you like you're a dick for not continuing to answer every question and low and behold you spent 30 minutes helping someone, with no gain, and they STILL are mad you couldn't give them more time. 


There is a tech support department and a this thing called the Internet that exists.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-08 15:52:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Call customer service  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-08 15:36:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Just so you know, what you just posted has nothing to do with tech support. Helping someone get set up and showing them a couple things about products is not resetting an email password or helping with some 3rd party app I've never used  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-08 15:35:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Itt OP takes a thread venting about customers and assumes nobody does tech support 


I've spent countless hours of my time helping people because I've felt bad. Spent an hour with them solving their problem. Once in awhile you can get them to buy something. 95% they won't. And 0% of the time have I ever got a referral that isn't more tech support. And now I have a weekly customer that can't figure out anything on their own because, Google doesn't exist apparently coming in and asking for me and wasting my time. 

Edit: not to mention the "job description" that the quoted has nothing to do with tech support  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-08 15:32:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> No </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-08 05:45:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I have a pixel. And in basically 0 situations has my Tmobile phone been better.. I dont even have signal in most buildings and I can't even watch my free MLB.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-08 05:43:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Lol. Your read couldn't be further off. But good try! Somehow you jumped to the conclusion that because people are stupid I don't help them. Thought this was a thread to vent. Of course from you're posting history we all know you are a dick already.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-08 05:31:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Most games have a login or connect to your Gmail/itunes/Facebook  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-08 05:26:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That's quite a leap you made there. Not sure how you made that jump but carry on.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-08 05:25:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Lol ok buddy. Keep spending 30 minutes resetting email passwords on the off chance you can convince someone to get a tablet or hum.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-08 05:23:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I mean, no. But I'm done discussing how adults need to be babied apparently since they have no ability to say no or ask questions if something isn't clear.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-08 05:20:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I don't give a crap what they buy. That doesn't mean they aren't stupid for doing so. They have no problem bitching that their bill is $100 even though $36 of it is a phone. 


The crossover of people who "aren't tech savvy", yet buy 800 dollar phones without blinking but are appalled at spending $25 on a case is huge. The logic makes no sense.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-08 05:18:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> And what does copying game data have anything to do with Verizon? 

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-08 05:16:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> $1000 purchases aren't considered large for you? That must be nice. 

What makes you think the account was "stuffed"? There is 0 indication of that. In fact, the customer in this story sound like she was even able to talk about some of the features of hum to the OP. 

If the customer thinks they are gonna use the device (hence, they are sold), and they are fine with the monthly cost, and you still see a problem, idk what to tell you.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-08 05:04:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That was a waste of :40 seconds  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-08 04:59:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Well, as an adult about to make a large purchase I would do 5-10 minutes of research to figure out how shit works before signing a contract (or phone agreement). 

I would also say "ok what is covered in that $400" or some clarifying question if I wasn't sure. 


Ignorance is not an excuse.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-08 04:57:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The people who have stupid questions don't buy anything. They are not the reason sales people have a job.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-08 04:55:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The problem is they think because they spent $800 on it it will work perfectly. Well it was built by a 14 yr old in a factory in china using cheap parts. And the first time it freezes/stops working/etc they come to the store and we soft reboot the phone and wow it's a miracle your phone works again. I'm shocked it got frozen since you havent turned it off in 10 months or closed out a single app since you bought it.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-08 04:52:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> A car is a luxury item. You don't need to be car savvy to drive a vehicle. The differences in a Mercedes and Honda have nothing to do with whether you can change your own oil. 

People who use less than 10% of their device capabilities don't benefit from having a $800 phone any more than a $400 phone.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-08 04:49:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> They did until Verizon laid off everyone who isn't a sales person a few weeks ago </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-08 04:48:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yes, obviously  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-08 04:47:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You weren't there. If the customer says something like "what if I don't want [item]?" "Or, does [item] cost anything?" then of course. 

If the rep says "you can get all this and still pay less" and the customer says "ok", idk how you can you say that's unethical. The rep told the customer exactly how much their bill is. The customer is an adult, not a child. They can make their own decisions.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-08 03:53:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You can't get texts while you're on airplane mode

You can also just remove your sim it you're that nervous about it, or call as the other poster mentioned to have them put a block.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-08 03:46:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> "I'm not tech savvy"

"I don't know any of my passwords" 

"what do you mean you can't transfer my apps and emails and texts? And pictures and videos and contacts will take 45 minutes? This is ridiculous"


Sigh. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-08 03:44:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Who's gonna teach the class?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-08 02:45:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Well that's odd. You might get it charged back at some point you might not.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-08 02:43:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Are you for real? If you're an adult and you do zero research or have any idea how wireless works that's not my fault. 

If you're paying $100 and I say you can pay $100 with this and this and this and the customer agrees what's the issue exactly?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-08 00:39:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> And what happens when you try to use the gift card on your bill?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-07 23:04:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Not really </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-07 22:22:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Oh got it so you were there listening, cool 


Sounds like OP's friend had an old plan. And a rep said, you can get a hum and a tablet and a discount. None of which were untrue. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-07 22:21:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Did you read the next post? I don't have binge on.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-07 22:16:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You have a bill credit for each device traded in? Or it shows a trade in credit amount?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-07 22:15:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What was shitty and/or awful?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-07 22:14:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Oh nice. A box from a company that will take no liability for, that has users use torrents and illegal streams.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-07 22:11:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Verizon bills in advance. So you're being charged $110 for this month. You paid for this month on last month's bill. You're also being refunded whatever your old plan was, which you have provided 0 details on. 

Imagine you rent a house. They charge you $50/person and you have 4 people. So at the beginning of the month you paid $200. Then, 22 days into the month, you decided to have 6 new people come in. The landlord also decides to change the rate, to $60/person, retroactively. So, since you've already paid for this current month ($200) next month you'll have to pay :

- $40 (for the difference in the rate for the first 4 people) 
- $96 (for 8 days of each new resident for the past month, at $2/day or $60/mo)
- $600 (full month for 10 people) 
- total: $736



If you want help you need to tell us the details of your old plan, how many contracts and device payments you have, etc. I'm not sure what "important numbers" you think you've posted, but so far we have 0 information about your old plan, and only limited info on what you're now paying.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-07 19:30:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This is how your bill has worked since you joined Verizon, nothing is different. 

If you want an actual breakdown, then how about posting any details of your plan at all. Otherwise you will get general answers.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-07 19:27:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> No idea what the hell you're talking about OP. It's right in the app.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-07 19:23:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What do you mean you "see the account credit on the account but also got gift cards" 

Please provide more details of your transaction  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-07 19:22:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I don't have binge on. I have one+ international. So yes I am aware of the idiotic nuances of a Tmobile plan and I have what I need to have enabled. I used to have to enable my HD pass daily.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-07 19:19:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Not unlimited plan, no

No you can't use a prepaid sim in a postpaid device </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-07 16:23:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Well, I also can't stream ESPN, MLB, or watch tnt. So I'm gonna say yeah, it is Tmobile. 

I can also fire up the same youtube video on Verizon and have it work in 1080p with no issue.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-07 15:00:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Because otherwise shit gets pro-rated and then you have a customer who has mad because they "had 50 minutes left" but got charged an overage because when you current date everything is reduced. 

I'd be surprised if the new plan isnt less expensive that whatever OP had anyway. But we don't know because OP gave no details. Just because a line is $20 instead of $10 doesn't mean anything since each line also had its own data package.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-07 14:01:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I have a Tmobile phone. Verizon blows it out of the water. Half the time I can't even use my Tmobile data at all. I'll do a speed test and it'll say 70 mbps down and then I try to stream YouTube and it can t load anything past 360p lol (on tmo).  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-07 13:57:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> We have 1 floating manager </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-07 13:56:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You have to backdate when coming from an old plan like that.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-07 03:45:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yep. I decided not to get the S8 this year and stick with my Z Force, personally.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-07 03:39:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Can you get a dd214 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-07 03:38:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Never heard of that </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-07 03:36:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I've lived in dc/va suburbs my whole life and never had an issue anywhere  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-07 03:35:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hot Fire  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-06 16:01:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You say you need to buy out but you say you have a contract/early upgrade, so which is it?


For Phones, the consensus rating would probably be:

S8  G6  pixel  z force 

My personal preference would be the Z force. I'm sick of Samsung's shitty battery and lag, I don't trust LG. And the pixel is boring to me. 

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-06 06:23:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> No DPP  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-06 04:48:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> OP, your cycle end date and the bill due date are not the same. The bill that is due is for the cycle that ends 4 days later.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-06 04:47:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> When your bill is due has nothing to do with your bill cycle, and you are confusing the two.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-06 04:46:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The ellipsis 8 was fine for what it was. It's 2 or 3 years old now and the 8 HD is actually pretty solid. As is the ellipsis 10.

I don't have a wear 24 but I played with one for a couple minutes. Seemed like your standard android wear to me but I haven't thoroughly tested it. I don't like how it looks.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-06 03:26:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That's what I'm assuming was the case as well </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-06 02:54:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Well what you're describing makes no sense. Either post some screenshots or call 611 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-06 02:22:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So do you qualify for 0 down payment? Or do you have to put down 40% due to your credit?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-06 01:56:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You had less available than you thought? Idk what you want anyone hear to tell you we can't see your account. Contact customer service again or try to order in a store.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-05 15:12:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Someone else's semen?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-05 14:09:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I was gonna say Wrong Turn but I don't think anyone got impregnated in that movie  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-05 00:48:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Probably because there is no problem to xfer phone credits. The rep probably never realized you were getting a promotional credit. 

They don't transfer. That is gone now unless you're very lucky  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-04 15:39:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The dream </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-04 15:39:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Contact customer service  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-04 05:13:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah, wish I wasn't emotionally drained after every shift so I could have taken advantage of the school.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-04 05:03:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Well at least you provided 0 details about your device or plan so we can help out 

/s </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-04 05:02:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Go ask us cellular? What does this have to do with Verizon  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-04 04:59:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I mean literally our entire store is hoping to get laid off for a severance. That's a good sign.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-04 04:56:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Lol yeah. 

March our quota was 60/17/12k or something. I was 6th in the zone in new lines but still got SMP! since i "only" got 47.

So then I'm on counseling. Quota last month is a reasonable 38. I made 2.6k like the old days! Hooray it's back to normal! All I had to do was sell 18 tabs, 6 Hotspot and 1 hum. $135 ARD and 70% TMP. That got my bucket to 13k or so. 

65/80/13k this month. Annnnnnd I'm not even gonna try. It's not possible. Oh did I mention I'm a B store and we are short reps and usually have 3 sales reps all day? Fun. We don't even have time to make calls and we have no RSS to help anything.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
