<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject4170</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> A bot is flooding the FCC's website with fake anti-net neutrality comments </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-10 16:39:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-09 17:12:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> According to support they randomly pick times and the user who clicks the "play now" button closest to that wins something.  My wife has won a gift card or two in the middle of the day. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Developer buys shuttered 1930s Grand Rapids theater to restore </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-08 02:23:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-06 21:55:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'll be very surprised if he's actually lost them.  Were this the comics it'd be the sort of thing to get a neon sign saying "WE GOT A CHEKOV'S GUN HERE" every few issues until it paid off. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Welp, Amash made The Onion. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-05 22:05:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-05 16:35:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Optics are how something looks in public. So in this case, a news cycle saying they finally won. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-04 22:38:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thank you for doing this. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-30 01:21:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I wasn't completely moved in before the meth head downstairs started hounding me trying to bum cash. Neighbors were always screaming at each other. Loud ass parties until 4-5 in the morning on the weekends. Management was less than responsive about the first one, never complained about the others. This was in 2009. Things may have changed. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-14 17:16:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Gamrat was expelled, Courser resigned.  

...And then they both had the cojones to try a run for their seats again.

It really says something about our state lately that I came here checking to see if anyone had mentioned Kwame Kilpatrick yet, and  your comment made me go, "Wait...yeah, never mind Kwame." </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-14 17:00:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Republican presidential candidate Donald Trump told reporters Thursday that he attends a church in Manhattan, but the church released a statement saying the real estate developer is not an "active member."

Source:
http://www.cnn.com/2015/08/28/politics/donald-trump-church-member/index.html

References to this were about all I could find.

Edit: also this Quora post:
https://www.quora.com/How-often-does-Trump-go-to-church
Says Obama stopped going to keep from being disruptive but unlike Obama, there's not much evidence Trump went before the election. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-09 02:33:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I hate to say it, but Charter is basically the only option Up North, unless of course even they aren't around. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-09 00:58:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I am and know a few people who could have been registered Republicans in the 90s but now will never, ever vote for a Republican again after the past few years and especially the past few months.  If there are as many of us as I think there are, that could affect the first poll a bit.  

I'm not comfortable calling myself a Democrat because I'm not thrilled with them either, but centrists have lost a place at the table, and it increasingly feels like a choice between the old-style frustrating, corrupt and ineffectual politicians and the pants-on-headers.

I was never really comfortable with the dichotomy in the first place, if I'm being honest.  Especially now.  It punishes critical thought to actively participate in either group.  It feels like one has to believe all of the same things for all of the same reasons now in either group.  Screw that.
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-09 00:28:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Frankfort or Beulah/Benzonia might be right up your alley, and are far enough from / still not terribly far from Traverse so you could still do Costco (they're getting one) or Target from time to time while largely avoiding the (trendier at least) tourist crowd.  My parents retired to Ludington and I can't believe how well they took to it, but their social circle is/was church-based, so I don't know if that would be a plus or minus for you, and it helps that my sister and her kids live there. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-03 01:58:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I still have no idea why I went there yesterday but Alpine Wal Mart also had four of them around 1 PM. I think maybe the stock shortage is waning. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-30 00:52:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Alas, I'm pretty sure the Michigan Democratic Party couldn't find Grand Rapids on a map of Kent County.  They're notorious for not showing up on behalf of candidates here. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-29 20:00:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Afterwards the islanders were told they had to swear an oath of allegiance to the UK or...leave within a month.  Most just took the oath. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-29 19:49:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> FWIW it's [the Blue Bridge](https://www.google.com/maps/place/Blue+Bridge,+Grand+Rapids,+MI/@42.9645803,-85.6769362,17z/data=!3m1!4b1!4m5!3m4!1s0x8819addb0236cc3b:0xed8896c8fbb6ceea!8m2!3d42.9645803!4d-85.6747475) on Google, in case anyone was wondering. If it has a more official name I've never heard it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-29 19:33:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I feel ya, I really do, but it would help to know *what part* of this very large state you are in.

If near Grand Rapids, I highly recommend checking with [Psychology Associates](http://pagr.net/).  I have no idea if they take BCBS, though. I believe it's on a provider-by-provider basis. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-29 19:23:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> FWIW the Sears at Woodland Mall in GR was quietly "disinvited" from renewing their lease so the mall could put an expansion in.  Von Maur has already confirmed they're the new anchor.

Just saying, upheaval !=downturn. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-29 15:44:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Delphi's Magneride suspension isn't exactly this, but it does use a magnetic field to control the viscosity of a ferromagnetic fluid inside the shock absorber, allowing it to adjust based on road conditions. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-28 17:28:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's been forever since I played it but I seem to remember there's a crazy difficulty spike near the end where if you haven't been grinding, you might as well stop playing. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-28 15:01:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Federal poverty line for 2017 is $12,060, so actually no. It's closer to the poverty level for a family of two ($16,240). I can't believe it either, and I work with people who meet it each week. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-25 15:24:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You're right. We were in Sheboygan last summer and heard an ad for a nearby dealership with the same script as the one playing on GR radio when we left. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-20 00:10:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  SR-71B

K-Zoo Air Zoo?

(Edit: [source for the curious](http://www.airzoo.org/page.php?page_id=192). All my kid wants to do there is ride the rides.) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-15 16:48:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  Xoloitzcuintli

Which were sacrificed with their owners to serve as a guide to the underworld.  Nice catch. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-15 16:17:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah, it feels like it goes straight from the character-longs-through-the-screen setup from Wall-E, Up and Ratatouille into a Spirited Away situation.

* Kid wanders into spirit realm
* Other characters suddenly ignore him
* See-through people
* Village of colorful lights with the main colors being black/blue and orange.

Considering Pixar's massive respect for Ghibli it wouldn't surprise me if they cited it as a primary inspiration. Now you've got me hoping for an in-movie nod to it like when Totoro showed up in Toy Story 3. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-11 00:18:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Sorry, I didn't mean to delete this. I'm awkward.  Posting it again from memory, not that it probably matters at this point.

Since DeVos came up nationally there's been a huge amount of shoddy reporting about my hometown seeing as her last name is all over the place here.  From some of the stuff I've read you'd think everyone here was a mindless robot with Amway stamped on our asses.  

I'm not sure why I'm defending them here, but Spectrum Health is the second or third largest hospital system in Michigan.  It's certainly *not* a "DeVos family business." DeVos isn't even in control over Spectrum. He's got an emeritus position on the board, that's it.  He's not the chairman like the article says.  I think he might've been at one point, but name a major hospital chain that doesn't have at least one local philanthro-fatcat on its board.

I'm not saying nothing's here, just that it's not a slam dunk like the article implies.

I want Trump gone yesterday along with everyone involved in this putrescent boil of an administration.  I really do.  But I think this one warrants caution.  Let's not forget that mischaracterizing things to make them more dramatic is one of the things that sent the other guys so far down the rabbit hole.

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-10 23:59:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Sorry, somehow I deleted this comment :( I reposted it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-08 03:27:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Shot in the dark, but the parks have all been undergoing minor to major upgrades since last year.  They might just be up for replacement later? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-05 20:56:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yes it does. Went in this summer. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-05 03:58:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> West-central lower peninsula Michigan here.  I'd say it's been more of a luxury than a necessity, but our summers are getting hotter, so it's becoming more common.  I didn't have it growing up, but I live in a 'nicer' part of town now and have it.  I have family about 100 miles north and basically no one has it up there. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-05 03:22:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> *sigh*
Yeah, we do.  [It's pretty...existent.]  (http://www.mlive.com/news/grand-rapids/index.ssf/2015/09/is_this_grand_rapids_flag_one.html) We actually have two, but no one cares about the official one.

Urban Renewal, man.  Some might not know about this dark period in American history where dozens of US cities razed their downtowns in favor of "forward thinking" brutalist monstrosities and fields of useless concrete.  

During this time our city demolished [this](https://www.google.com/search?q=old+grand+rapids+city+hall source=lnms tbm=isch sa=X ved=0ahUKEwiL4sSL9vfRAhWk24MKHUTTBZ4Q_AUICCgB biw=1366 bih=672), replaced it with a steel box and commissioned Alexander Calder to build [this](https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/La_Grande_Vitesse) to liven up the "plaza" in front of it.  

The Powers That Be were mighty proud of this purchase, and pretty soon our official city emblem was just the image of the Calder (we literally just call it the Calder now) in front of the Grand River, shown flowing free instead of blocked off behind walls of more concrete, with a big yellow circle ("the sun rising," because of course) behind it.

These days it's mostly referred to in some variation of Pac Man, as In "Bloody Sabertooth Pac Man" or "Walk of Shame Ms. Pac Man."   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-22 14:18:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'd say "he" or "she" is used pretty much any time the gender of the animal is known.  And no, this isn't a new thing.

I had the same thing happen to me with Spanish teachers here in the US.  There had to be a dozen things my collection of teachers over the years INSISTED that native Spanish speakers never did while trying to wean us from American habits of speech, and all of it had to be thrown out the window the moment I actually landed in Honduras. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-19 05:12:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> She "has" [a Twitter account](https://twitter.com/SUEtheTrex).  The interns over at the Field seem to have a lot of fun with it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-08 02:34:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Battle Creek and Portage still have Schlotsky's.  I can't remember if I liked them or not--they left GR in the late 90s.  So I guess *we can* forget them.  Obviously not worth the drive (well, Kzoo has Bell's and an Alamo Drafthouse...), but there it is.

For some bizarre reason we have a [Freddy's](https://freddysusa.com/menu/).  I am weirded out by them choosing GR first instead of starting out by you like literally everyone else does. They'd be between Steak n Shake and Culver's on my list (very similar), but Culver's comes first by a country mile.  What other first-rate burger place serves a decent Reuben if you're so inclined? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-06 19:19:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I thought Cutlerville closed already? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-06 15:20:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm still laughing at the Freep headline from a few days ago:

["Study: Michigan has the 49th most enjoyable winters in America."](http://www.freep.com/story/news/local/michigan/2017/01/04/michigan-winters/96148284/) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-06 12:59:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I encourage you to visit Wisconsin cheese country and even *find* Kraft cheese out there. 

You wouldn't like it either if we judged British beer by the version of Guinness (edit: yes, British. The juxtaposition was intentional) they send us. I've heard the real thing is great but the stuff we get here can't hold a vomity candle to the ambrosia made right here in town.

Every country has multinationals selling shit. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-03 18:27:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I found [this interesting perspective](http://archive.boston.com/news/nation/articles/2004/08/29/cities_dust_off_air_raid_sirens/) from ~~Boston~~ Baltimore.  Apparently their writer thought no one used them anymore.  IIRC almost everywhere got one back in the days of fallout shelters and duck-n-cover.

Here in Grand Rapids (Midwest, of course) I grew up knowing the first Friday of every month from May to September would involve a noon test of the old neighborhood siren, and only heard them otherwise during a tornado warning.  The wife is from Northwestern Michigan, and she always associated them with the volunteer fire department. It didn't occur to her that a city with a full-time department would have any other use for them until we discussed it a few years ago. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-30 14:23:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Futureworld is the sequel to the original Westworld. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-26 21:17:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Desktop Chrome and Edge are both doing this with the RES expando too. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-27 05:42:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> "Masha and the Bear" and 'Masha's Tales" </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Trump picks Betsy DeVos for education secretary </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-23 19:33:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-12 04:47:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I live where most of the Americans of Dutch descent live (West Michigan).  The hypermart down the street from me sells at least three different kinds of stroopwafel.  Then again, the place *is* named Meijer.  

I've never heard of the second one, but a lot of family recipes got Americanized names sometime in the last two generations.  People stare at me when I mention Banket sometimes, but it's all over the place (you might be amused to hear it's a Thanksgiving tradition in our family). </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-03 04:43:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> "This commercial-free break is brought to you by T-mobile"

...wait. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-31 00:22:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> TBF three characters is a a super insecure answer for a security question.  This is probably a database limitation and it's better still to lie altogether, but yeah. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-29 04:17:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I don't know if the Englesma's sold at FH Foods is UV or Pasteurized, but they have it.  Hill Bros, which in addition to their orchard and (as already pointed out) at Kens, is also sold at Kingma's.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> MLive Endorses Hillary Clinton </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-28 16:01:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-28 00:14:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Not saying they are, just that they exist right here in Michigan. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-27 04:02:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yes.  There are a few farms in Michigan, too.  Newaygo springs to mind.  It's just not as cost effective as cows. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-25 19:16:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> For some reason there was a flash sale the week before last, so possibly not. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-24 04:10:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> He's pretty clearly putting politics ahead of his employees' wellbeing, intentionally or not.  That's not an attitude I can personally support.  Words do things. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-14 18:59:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> And it's gone.  Thanks though. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-03 02:38:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I've spent quite a bit of time thinking about how people used to live their lives here, how GR developed along with and fits into US history, and the hidden histories of different places.  [HistoryGrandRapids.org](http://www.historygrandrapids.org/) has been a great resource for this stuff.  They have [an old redline map of town](http://www.historygrandrapids.org/tilemap/2596/the-holc-map), for instance, and it shows the presence of **Dutch** people as a possible detriment to the Grandville Avenue / Roosevelt Park area.  It's hard to think of a time where that was the case. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-03 01:28:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> **If you're from the east side: Grand Rapids**

I'm going to see pushback for this, so I'll be a bit long-winded.

GR is a typical second city in that, if people in the larger metro think of it at all, they tend to think of it as backwards.  It's underrepresented in statewide media and it has a reputation for being exactly the wrong sort of Christian.  

We came by the reputation for conservatism honestly.  GR's main two cultural forces have both been white but insular--the Dutch Calvinists and Polish Catholics--who were still treating themselves as immigrant minorities decades after they eclipsed everything else.  It's not a good look, especially considering both groups were deeply religious.  

Things have become much more open and pluralistic around here.  Irrespective of whether that's a factor or *the* factor, there's a certain sense of momentum around here. Some are now calling it *overrated* because the locals are so outspoken about the positive change we've been experiencing.

I'm not going to go into the beer scene or whatnot, TL;DR: my entire life I wanted to leave GR for someplace bigger and more cosmopolitan, but the past 5-10 have made me rethink that.  Grand Rapids is, in fact, growing up.
___
**If you're from anywhere else in Michigan, and you aren't an ignorant idiot about Detroit: Kalamazoo**

Similarly to above, If Kazoo is on anyone's radar at all, it either seems to be typecast as another failed industrial town or as a place where wild college parties happen.

Ehh...yeah, both are still true to a degree, but it's also making huge inroads, and it's an awesome town steeped in history with a good local culture and some of the best beer (the artistic kind, not the beer pong kind) you'll find anywhere.  It's the only smaller-than-GR town that I'm familiar with in the entire US that I'd move to without hesitation.

_______
**If you're from out-of-state: Detroit**

You've probably heard both sides of this one *ad nauseam* by now.  Suffice it to say that you won't truly understand Detroit, or why it's so worth fighting for, until you spend some real quality time there. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-23 06:30:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> My favorite part of this is scrolling past an ad for an app ON THE WAY TO SELECTING THAT SAME APP which is already installed but is for some reason on the bottom. Three of my apps are this way. Get your shit together, Sony.
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-11 18:02:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> There's a "Star Trek Summit" on one of the movie Blu-Ray sets which is Shatner, Nimoy, Stewart and Frakes being interviewed at length by Whoopi Goldberg.  Shatner is asked this question directly, and starts by saying they never actually called him to do it.  A bit later he admits to not having seen any TNG, at which point Stewart invites him over to see a few eps and Nimoy calls him out gently on feeling sore that TNG existed in the first place while it was running, something he apparently got over since. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-11 02:22:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I mean, to be fair, it's the New Mexico desert. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-10 16:06:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Michigan is a state where you can drive from Hell to Paradise (or Christmas, if that's your thing) through Climax. We have a very nice and fairly large metro area that goes by the nickname Kazoo and they pick Freesoil, so named because of the Homestead act. Okay. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-07 23:54:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> * No, it'll autodetect the TV's capabilities.

* You'll need an HDR capable TV to see any difference. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-07 14:38:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm waiting on a holiday bundle to go Xbox.  Is the MCC OK if you never intend to play it online, or is that still broken, too?  Should I look into a 360 instead? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-07 00:28:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I *wish* the nineties were fuzzier.  Ugh, the clothes.

You're right; Playstation was absolutely abbreviated as PSX before the PS2 came out, just like the Nintendo 64 was the N64. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-03 18:31:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's Word of God, so it's canon if you count that. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-02 20:19:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> They used to tell you to swim across Lake Michigan if you weren't close enough to the Ludington or Muskegon ferry services. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-02 18:57:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That's USDA and state government turf. Sort of. The regulations determine some crazy things, like shelled eggs are FDA and liquid ones are USDA. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-02 03:31:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Do you actually live in Alger? I know people who swear by JB's.
If you're further away, I grew up near Andrea's on Boston near Breton.  I just had a slice from there a few days ago and it's only gotten better.

My favorite crust in town is Big O.  Come at me. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-02 03:24:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Take it from someone who lives in NE GR near Plainfield and 4 mile.  Save for Taco Boy the NE quadrant is the only part of GR that *doesn't* have good Mexican or Tex-Mex from anything other than a six dollar burrito chain.

That said, speaking as someone with a Spanish degree who lived in Latin America for a spell....Cheese sauce?!  You wouldn't be talking about queso asadero or real-honest-to-gosh sour cream, would you?  Or do you mean that travesty that Qdoba dares call their "3 cheese queso?" </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-01 21:11:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [Same thread](https://www.reddit.com/r/AskAnAmerican/comments/50kmib/why_do_americans_seem_to_be_fixated_on_canadian/d74tiob).
\*shrug\* </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-01 20:53:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Was referring to this earlier comment:

But you don't know what it is that we have. It's not a socialized system like the NHS in the U.K - it's single payer. I think what some of you actually want is an NHS system that covers everything.
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-01 16:14:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I mean, I'm not joining in the downvotes, but s/he *was* being pretty presumptuous about what we do and don't know.  I'm a regular commenter here and healthcare policy is part of *my friggin' job.*  People are being sensitive about foreigners calling us dumb, I guess. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-01 16:08:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Just commenting to point out that a full NHS program is still political plutonium here.  Some people might think the idea's great, but it's not likely to go anywhere without a massive change in public perception of social programs.  No, as it's already been pointed out, a system like yours or Australia's is *exactly* what we've been taking a serious look at. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-01 15:58:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> A lot of people make the mistake of looking at healthcare policy (well, any policy) as a question of how it's going to affect them directly, as if they were not only one data point in (in our case) 320 million.  In your case, you're comparing your own costs with those of another middle class person in the US.  This doesn't work, because our system is way more expensive, before or after insurance, and everyone pays for things differently.  It's a classic question of forest vs trees.

The main point of comparison is actually how much money each potential patient is able to contribute to the system vs what they are able to take out.  Under our system, even after the ACA which was supposed to address this, healthcare costs are being inflated by poor people's inability to contribute to their healthcare costs, even as they are being bankrupted by it, which has an additional effect on our economy.  You don't have that problem (as much) in Canada.  

I'm not going to get into the vagaries of adapting your system to fit ours, but the above is one of the main drivers for looking at the positive points of a system like yours when looking to improve ours.

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-01 15:41:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> ^ This is your answer in a nutshell.  As a Michigander I hear a lot of people talking about Canadian policy in general as a source of ideas for improvement of American policy, mostly owing to the cultural and economic similarities between us (many Michiganders view Ontario practically as if it were another neighboring state, to give you an idea of what I'm talking about).

I work in the healthcare administration field, and the three systems I most often hear people saying we should emulate are Canada by a country mile, then Australia, then Germany. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-01 15:31:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The second two are not even likely to come up.  Don't believe everything you read on the Internet.  

The first one is more complicated, but that's why there's traveler's insurance, which should honestly be a consideration when traveling to *any* foreign country.  [Here's your own government's page](https://www.gov.uk/foreign-travel-advice/usa/health) of recommendations for travel in the US.

OP, "where are you planning on staying?" really does matter as a question as it will help us tell you a bit about the area.  I know you said you don't know, but the States are a relatively diverse place. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-01 15:22:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> And Christmas.  And Pigeon.  And Climax... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-01 14:33:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Oh, god, there are so many.

In general, former frontier areas will have more weird names, and older areas will have more names from people or other places.   Sandwich, MA was named for Sandwich, Kent, but no one was thinking of their birthplace when they named Meat Mountain in Alaska (well, as far as we know).

* A personal favorite is [Lake Chaubunagungamaug](https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Lake_Chaubunagungamaug) in Massachusetts, sometimes stylized as Chargoggagoggmanchauggagoggchaubunagungamaugg.

* Someone already mentioned Hell, Michigan.  It's about 300 mi (483 km) from Paradise, Michigan, which itself is about 100 (161 km) from Christmas, MI, making Hell about 400 mi (644 km) from Christmas via Paradise (yes, things actually get that far apart in Michigan)

* I keep hearing people say Kalamazoo is a weird name.  I grew up too close to it to have an opinion.

* Walla Walla, WA is another funny-sounding one where enough people actually live that people might forget it's a bit off.

* Normal, Illinois, yet another of these, is aptly named for the most part, but still...

* I've heard there's a town in Washington named Humptulips.  I don't want to know.

* Canuck bonus (they also have many): Saint-Louis-du-Ha! Ha!, Quebec.

(Editing to add some and remove a few I saw others covered already)


 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-01 13:55:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I can think of one example of the above off the top of my head, but that was Kate Smith, and you haven't heard of her because the ballgame in question was in the thirties.

It's also worth pointing out that this is a baseball tradition first (i.e. that's where it started), an American sports tradition second. The Canadian teams have someone sing "O Canada" before their major league games, too, and I think Japan may be the only country with a league who doesn't do it regularly. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-29 17:10:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> A lot of people are using it as a parody of the outrage surrounding shootings of black people.  Casting Harambe as the black person.


Please note I don't have a position on this, I'm just repeating the criticism I've heard. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-29 05:14:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I have both.  My original/main machine is the slim and the super is in our bedroom.  There's a good reason for this.  The slot load on the slim is WAY better than the flimsy slider door on the super.  The design and build quality are much better, too.  Also, the super is louder, which is saying something.  This is a problem if I want to play it when my wife's asleep.

Now, I admit these are pretty tiny things, especially considering there's basically no difference between the two in actual function.  I just really prefer my original. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-26 07:23:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> No kidding. My wife was dropping hints so hard in the end I began regretting the decision to get a custom ring because it wasn't finished yet. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-24 15:58:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Pre-coffee me thanks you. Edited to be more factual (still a bit off) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-24 14:50:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I've seen this line of thinking around a lot, and I'm interested in something.  Does the verbal imagery of "Milwaukee is burning" in the first sentence of the article not cover this for you? Are precise semantics that important?

I'm not trying to argue, I'm genuinely wondering. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-24 14:45:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Not sure if I'm supposed to be the dipshit or if the author is (affirmative on the former, no idea on the latter), but:

I kinda felt like the gist (this is only my take, mind) of the author's point was a bit more nuanced than that.  Anyone is going to have preconceived notions.  Anyone is going to let their own personal standpoint/worldview/bias/banana preference influence their thinking.  This is a human thing.  I get that the whole coastal-elite-vs-"real murican" thing is a sore spot for a lot of people, but I do think there's a discussion to be had around the fact that we're allowing our media to consolidate to six or seven coastal cities where people don't have the in-the-trenches perspective that a local journalist would.  

It's not really Washington or New York's fault.  I live in the secondary region of my state, and I'm damned sick of statewide media completely forgetting my 1.5-million-person metro exists just because there's a 4-million-person metro a hundred miles away.  There are people in this very thread from KC complaining that this is a St. Louisan's perspective.  I see what the author is highlighting here as being a sign of the same thing writ large.

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-24 14:29:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I get where you're going with this, but I can't help but point out that half of anything tends to have below average anything. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-24 06:09:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I also, cynical as it sounds, think the situation surrounding the Milwaukee incident just didn't have the optics to keep it on the media's mind.

That said, there are stories to be told about the context that led to the riot after the incident, and the question I have is, if it's necessary, who will report on it?

Take [this article](http://www.citylab.com/crime/2016/08/half-of-wisconsins-black-neighborhoods-are-jails/495152/), for instance.  Sure, we're reading about it in The Atlanic, but it's based in an observation from a fricking high school student who was playing around with a nonprofit's mapping tool. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-24 04:27:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I feel like you're missing that this is part of the point of the article.

It's not about complaining that X is not getting coverage (and by the way, I'm not a member of any of these communities, so I'm confused as to why you're directing your argument at me to begin with), and it isn't about local media needing to step up. Local media is *disappearing*, so there's no one left with the resources to report but the big guys, and she's exploring the fallout of those big guys swooping in and getting the story of X all tangled up in their preconceived notions. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-24 04:03:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I don't know that the argument, though, is that there isn't enough coverage.  The question would be whether that coverage is equipped to tell the whole story.

Edit: apparently phrasing it "no one's arguing there wasn't coverage" was downvote-worthy.  eep. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
