<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject4227</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-09 22:35:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I think its 100% from apologists. Back in the Obama days we thought Bush was the worst it could get. Then Trump comes along and fucks everything up so bad that you now have Democrats wishing for Bush back. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-09 22:17:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  Bush realized halfway through that there would be video of him saying "shame on me" which would be run in election commercials. So, mid-thought he tried to switch gears, and kind of fell on his face.

You sure about that? I mean Bush fooled us once making us think he was competent and well.... you know that old saying. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-09 18:18:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Eh I think it will be gone soon. A large portion of the right wing fringe movement are baby boomers and they should be out of the political scene in the next decade. Millennials and Gen X are much less radical and often fall into a mixed bag of moderate Conservatives or moderate liberals with a generous sect of people gravitating more toward liberal "socialism".  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-05 20:09:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> They already broke that pledge back in 2013. That means nothing to them now. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-05 19:59:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yes it was voted that it applies to them but i believe they still have the option to opt out and go with congress funded healthcare which iirc is basically military level healthcare with a few options removed. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-05 05:49:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Wow. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-04 22:30:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The US has constantly been falling behind every other major nation. Hell we even still use the stupid ass imperial system for measurements. The only reason we still think were the best is sensational nationalism. We're basically North Korea with much more freedoms. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-03 22:41:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's simple when you dont pay attention to anything they pass. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-25 22:04:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> No one ever wins a trade war. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-25 21:46:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> And whens the last time you've seen any of them interview a serious Democrat. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-25 20:31:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Good for him. This is how a U.S president is supposed to make money. You profit off of speeches AFTER your presidency not weekend getaways during your presidency. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-25 01:22:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> those who can't get visas because of criminal ties, are the ones who come over the fence, those are the ones that the wall target and I'm okay with that. It will reduce crime.

Not all these people are criminals. It's not like crime lords are hopping the fence to get into America. Crime lords want to stay in Mexico where there's much less law enforcement. The people that are "hopping the fence" (Much more likely traveling through tunnels, on boats, and smuggled in cars) are the lowest income families in Mexico/central america/south america (Mostly CA) that dont have access to amenities such as the internet to apply for visas and are only interested in running from the crime lords of their town.
Source: https://www.forbes.com/sites/kenrapoza/2016/01/28/immigrants-fleeing-increasingly-violent-latin-america-study-suggests/#496e995c2972

https://www.wola.org/analysis/people-leaving-central-americas-northern-triangle/
 
The amount of actual criminals that are coming across the border is tiny compared to the amount of people. Even if they do have a record Legal and illegal immigrants are both less likely to commit crimes than native born citizens. Why would they immigrate to a place with harsher penalties to try to commit more crime.

Source : https://www.nytimes.com/2017/01/26/us/trump-illegal-immigrants-crime.html?_r=0 

What is happening is that people are fleeing to the United States to get away from tragedies and a crime spree that is running rampant through poorer countries. And instead of helping these people and countries were turning away the people and trying to steal oil from the middle east. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-25 01:00:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  This argument seems to rely on Trump taking no action to change legislation around visa issuance or deportation enforcement.

Trump has hinted at expanding the H1B visa program to look for higher skilled work but i haven't seen him hint toward changes for low skill work. Especially since trump uses these visas to hire people for his own resorts.
Source: http://money.cnn.com/2016/07/28/news/donald-trump-foreign-workers/ 

On deportation he does have ICE deporting people but i dont see it ever greatly reducing the amount of Illegal Immigrants.

Not to mention a 33-50% decrease in illegal immigration is still huge...

Just because you build a wall instead of a fence doesn't mean that 33-50% goes away. A good percentage of those people are definitely not hopping fences. There's still tunnels, boats, and people being smuggled in cars. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-24 22:24:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> My sources:
http://www.nbcnews.com/news/latino/visa-overstays-outnumber-illegal-border-crossings-trend-expected-continue-n730216

http://www.nationalreview.com/article/424879/visa-overstays-todays-immigration-crisis-mark-krikorian

https://mic.com/articles/170500/more-people-have-overstayed-their-visas-than-have-illegally-crossed-the-border-since-2007#.4mMAEcfdJ


None of your sources even state how many immigrants are entering through work visas so how can your sources disagree with my original statement? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-24 21:51:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Using your logic you're telling me Prisons should drop their fences and walls because they dont work..

Walls are great at keeping people in... not so great at keeping people out.

272+ MILES is small? What?

Yes very small when compared to the 1,989 miles of the U.S-Mexico border.

Are you really suggesting the Berlin Wall and the Great Wall didn't work? The Great Wall helped secured China for many many years, allowed ease of troop movements, long distance communication and still stands to this day. The Berlin wall did hell of a job dividing Germany.

Yes all rose and fell. They did do a great job while they were up but that was during war when they had constant patrolls and they were still toppled. This wall that Trump is proposing is going to cost billions to put up. Hundreds of millions to maintain. And is going to serve what purpose? Keep out hard working mexicans that we inevitably fly over anyway with temporary work visas? or Keep out drugs which are obviously in high demand if they are being smuggled in? Its a ridiculous proposition that if built would only serve to display the racist and prejudice underbelly of America.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-24 21:33:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Where are you getting the 40% number? I have seen most numbers regarding this topic to be 50% - 66%. 

Sources:
http://www.nbcnews.com/news/latino/visa-overstays-outnumber-illegal-border-crossings-trend-expected-continue-n730216

http://www.nationalreview.com/article/424879/visa-overstays-todays-immigration-crisis-mark-krikorian

https://mic.com/articles/170500/more-people-have-overstayed-their-visas-than-have-illegally-crossed-the-border-since-2007#.4mMAEcfdJ

Either way 40%, 50%, 60% - a wall will not change any of those numbers. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-24 20:39:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> illegal immigration from the southern border is at a 25 year LOW. 

Idk about a 25 year low but illegal Immigration from the southern border has been declining since 2007. This has nothing to do with the wall.

Source: http://www.pewresearch.org/fact-tank/2017/03/02/what-we-know-about-illegal-immigration-from-mexico/

Israel disagrees. Hell. Bel-Air and almost every upscale neighborhood in the country, disagrees.

I'm guessing that this is you saying that you think walls work?? Maybe for small areas like Israel and "Bel-Air" (No clue what you're referring to) but if you want an example of large scale walls failing to enact their intended purpose look no further than China and Berlin. 

Source for more info on success rate of walls: http://www.newsweek.com/what-history-tells-us-about-building-wall-solve-problem-381875 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-24 20:23:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Eh the numbers on that are kinda sketchy. Ive seen numbers from 50% up to 66%. But either way if that many people are being brought in on visas there is obviously a larger problem that no wall will fix.

Sorce: http://www.nbcnews.com/news/latino/visa-overstays-outnumber-illegal-border-crossings-trend-expected-continue-n730216 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-24 19:46:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Most of them do not enter the country through jumping over any border fence. Most illegal immigrants are people who were brought into the country on a temporary work visa and just never left. 

The issue is a population of our country does not understand this and now wants to build a wall to keep illegal immigrants out. Unfortunately this wall will do almost nothing. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-24 19:37:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If there's a tariff, then we all pay the increased cost for those imported goods or no one does.

That's not really how it works. The tariff ends up increasing the price of the good. Say for instance Avocados once priced at $1 under a 20% tariff go to $1.20. You can either choose to continue to buy Avocados or not....  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-24 18:24:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The republican party doesnt care how they got power as as long as they got the power. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-24 18:07:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> While some of Trump's policies do seem inherently racist I think his policies are actually better defined as classism then anything. It just happens to be that minorities / women historically get paid less then white males. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Do you support Gas/Coal over more renewable alternatives. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-24 17:58:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-24 17:25:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The cost of the wall is minuscule relative to the budget.

The issue isn't only the initial cost of the wall (Estimated at 21 Billion). This wall will also require upkeep which has been estimated at $700 million annually. 

And were spending all of this to see what in return? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-24 16:33:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This wall will do nothing more than represent the racism and prejudice still present in the United States. If there wasn't such a demand for drugs in the country there wouldn't be drugs "pouring into our country".  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-24 16:28:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What i found:
2009- http://abcnews.go.com/Blotter/story?id=7354412

2017- http://www.nbcnews.com/news/us-news/drug-smugglers-mexico-use-border-crossings-spite-walls-n724341 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-21 18:59:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> ~~Clean up~~ Redefine Corruption in Washington Act. Enacts new ethics reforms to ~~Drain~~ Fortify the Swamp and ~~reduce~~ increase the corrupting influence of special interests on our politics.

FTFY </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-21 18:51:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Eh I think if they had the capabilities you would see a much larger interest. But either way them nuking South Korea isn't much better. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-21 00:57:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That's honestly impressive. Pimpin ain't easy </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-19 22:40:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Shouty Spice back at it again! This dude dodges talking points like hes training for dancing with the stars. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-19 20:01:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If this were passed on to consumers, the 10 cent farm labor cost of a pound of apples would rise to 14 cents, and the $1 retail price would rise to $1.04. 

Sorry you are right i read that section wrong it would be $1.22 per pound assuming the farmer still only took 30% </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-19 19:40:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> No that's right. 10 to 14 = 40% increase. 10 to 21 = 110% increase. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
