<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject4427</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> President Trump, Secretary Tillerson to Meet Russian Foreign Minister Lavrov at White House </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-10 13:17:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-10 03:47:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Well we now know why Comey was fired today.... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> In shock move, Trump fires FBI Director Comey </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-10 03:23:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-09 23:58:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It really is a special lens. Very light weight, very inexpensive and it takes beautiful pictures. The only problem with the 35mm is that it makes me neglect my other lenses! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> FBI director James Comey fired </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-09 23:55:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Trump FIRES FBI Director James Comey after he misled the Senate on Huma Abedin's emails </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-09 23:54:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> In blow to U.S.-Turkey ties, Trump administration approves plan to directly arm Syrian Kurds against Islamic State </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-09 19:56:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Comey's claim to Congress about Clinton aide's emails wasn't true </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-09 17:13:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-09 17:12:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I don't know if you can get a Nikon D5300 for $250, but a used D5100 run about that price on EBay and it is still a great camera. Don't be afraid of manufactured refurbished either. And remember, glass can be more important than the body itself. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-09 17:05:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I have been luck enough to travel through Europe a few times. I would recommend the Nikon 18-140mm for a general walk around lens. I would also take a 35mm f1.8 for indoor shots inside castles or  other buildings and walking around at night. I have been to most of the places you are planning to visit so if you have any questions, feel free to PM me. Have fun! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-09 16:42:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Comey is essentially Garak from DS9. You can't tell if he is good or bad, who he is working for, or if he is lying. Both seem to follow their own moral compass, which no one else can pin down....  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Comey misstated key Clinton email evidence at hearing, say people close to investigation </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-09 16:31:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> After Yates, more questions for the Trump White House </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-09 16:02:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Clapper: Putin did it to demean Clinton and help elect Trump </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-09 02:00:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> GOP's message to Americans: You're on your own </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-08 20:08:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-08 17:42:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It must have been excruciating for Obama during his last days. He knows Trump is compromised, but he also know what would happen  to the country if he tried to stop him.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
