<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject5027</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-09 07:34:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> How do you not? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-09 06:53:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> They should have stopped painting his eyebrows on halfway </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Signed, seal, delivered </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-09 06:29:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-09 06:21:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's nice to see language like this in political news again. It will be tough no matter which way you slice it. It's a lot to manage, effecting many. 

Unlike some leaders who come out saying, "Gosh who knew it was going to be tough!". At least the language he uses has a relevance to the topic at hand. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-09 06:18:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This is the wrong kind of uplifting news </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-09 06:15:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Let's all take this guy serious, his username is runner up to dogfuck ...  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-09 06:13:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Call it fucking lies. We already have a fucking word for it you sociopathic fucks. It's called a lie, call it a fucking lie. What, you need more syllables to feel like a big man Mr. Dictator? 

But of course it's not actually a lie... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-09 06:09:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I believe that can be chalked up to conditioning. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-09 06:01:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This is embarrassing. You know this will accomplish nothing except make you look as bad as The_Donald...

Kind of gross to watch when people compete to see who can be the biggest shit slinger </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-09 05:26:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Haha came here to find this. Very good. As you were </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-09 05:15:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This was by far one of my favorite jokes to return too. Clearly didn't appreciate his inanimate gesture as a youth but I die a little everytime I see it again now days </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-09 05:13:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Haha I knew *you'd* like it.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Settle down Fallout </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-09 04:50:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-09 04:43:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's what we do every day that becomes us.

You've shown solid determination with this and I have no doubt that this drive *will* leak into the rest of your life. Hang in there when it gets hardest!! Thank you for sharing

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-09 04:38:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Can I get a plaid shirt on that little guy to make someone's day.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-08 22:33:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> How Facebook and all social media is just accepted as standard. I've never had it, it's fine I do great without it and I honestly couldn't give a flying fuck why you have it so don't defend it immediately when I clarify that I don't have it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-08 21:55:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This needs to be posted in another sub. It demerits it's value coming from an anti Donald subreddit.

Don't get me wrong I'm in full agreement with you all. But get this in a more neutral sub to get real action. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-08 21:01:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> After reviewing the evidence in trashy court I rule this is a Photoshop where the woman originally wore the tight rugby shorts. The colored panty lines, disappearing crack, and shorts stretch marks on the lower right buttock seem to support this more than any other theory.

Still trashy. Court is dismissed. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-08 18:50:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Do you really think you know more about coconuts than this man? Where's your coconut related Videos mister two cents </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-08 03:00:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Seconded </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-07 05:03:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You are one of us </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-07 04:59:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hey I have to ask, and just your opinion on the matter but..

With the amount of star wars productions planned, and those to come beyond, do you feel the series is going to lose any of its "special" magic it's had in the past? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-07 04:38:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> One look at you and I thought,
Not even worth a roast. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-07 04:35:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> My dick is thicker than your arms, don't be afraid to lift something now and then Ms Daisy.

And that faux leather chair really compliments your decorative empty liquor bottle collection, you really are the epitome of taste and class aren't you.

Thankfully the square glasses help compliment your square head and five dollar haircut, I barely notice your rapey half hearted attempt at style you might call facial hair.

You make me sad. Also my dick is somehow more tanned than your arms too I don't even get that </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-07 04:25:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I have to agree with you. If you play seven hundred hours it's a recommendation in itself. Sorry gang </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-07 04:21:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Clever girl </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-07 04:18:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Lethal weapon 5.


Cinematic brilliance </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-07 04:17:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Twelve year old trial lesbian that had to break the rules in a safe space cause the real world would tear open it's anus enough for two of us to step inside. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-07 04:08:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Her self confidence must be through the roof. What with fake glasses and tits, a fake tan and cliched apparel. Yes sir I'm sure she's got it all together.
  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-07 03:59:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I shit and remind myself I'm single as I take a selfie. Cause I'm that fucking cool </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-06 20:05:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Fucking you and me both mother fucker  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-06 20:02:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Why do you bother to open that cock holster, the gang is right when they say it's an indicator, tired cliche or not, it's relevant to the post, unlike your comment buttercup.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-06 19:57:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Finally someone talks sense </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-06 17:27:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The ecstacy of gold. That track by Ennio Morricone just fucking solidifies that cinematic moment. Love it. Good call </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-06 17:22:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> *Slow clap develops into thunderous applause* </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-06 05:58:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's not OK to erode a democracy and claim, hey at least we'll get to be shit heads next run. It's not ok.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-06 05:35:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> South American I believe it was traced back to </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-06 04:01:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Some lot of stupid mother fuckers in this post about a smart mother fucker I'll tell you mother fuckers that much </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-06 03:49:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Spotted the guy without facial hair </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-06 03:43:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That's a lot of em I'm afraid. I think the gang might be right here, you can do small things based on the current situations as they present themselves, but otherwise this is business. You can also remind people eating there that you have other tables waiting for a seat and they will have to pay up if they're not continuing to order </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-06 03:40:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's against for code to seat in the floor like that. Suggest that to them and kindly remind them you've mentioned it before and you can't have it happen again </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-06 03:37:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's a squirrel emoticon dealy thing </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-06 03:33:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> *trumped up charges
I suppose with her face like that she can't speak properly, poor child </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-06 03:24:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You realise there's a huge scandal emerging about karma farming and corporate shill accounts crushing Reddit's true nature? 

It's very interesting but it is actually a huge problem coming down the pipes where it's really easy to control top comments and general sentiment of the hive mind. 

Imaginary internet points by shill accounts let them manipulate Reddit further and, generally, It's being done by systematic repost bots that gain accreditation enough to create their own subreddit or appear as if they are a valuable member of a community instead of a product with a design purpose.

While most people call out a repost because they call it like they see if, I invite you to talk your own advice and move on instead of hassling people who call out reposts. Some of them are more concerned for this place than you are aware of. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-06 03:18:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> All humans everywhere are racist?
 
You're large ego with a name like epicwisdom comes off as laughable I hope you know. You should talk less child. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-04 21:37:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hahahaha yes. Sure why not </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-04 19:12:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The Redditor has an overwhelming amount of negative comment karma and seems to be just genuinely ignorant. Most likely a child, I wouldn't give them the hate they are asking for. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-04 18:56:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Why would I lie to you stranger </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> When cosplay is still a hobby and not a job </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-04 17:18:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-04 08:27:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Is that a Nintendo switch with breath of the wild?!?!?!???!!!!! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-04 08:21:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> "We talked to Arkane, and they were like, Look, if we can just treat this as a reimagining, and sort of distill this IP down to its very basics, and go nuts with it, and make it our very own, we're totally on board with just doingPrey,'" Hines said. "'Not as a reboot, we can just reimagine it. We'll keep the basic principle of Aliens are hunting you,' and do what we envisioned  that's what we should do. We like the name; if you distill and take out everything you know about the previous game, or the canceled game, and just said the namePrey, it's a cool name. We think it really fits what it is that we're making.'"

That's from Pete Hines talking to the lead designer of Ariane. Blatantly calling it "not a reboot".

Just saying
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-04 08:12:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Just finished the DLC tonight. Fucking savage, it's beautiful, so well done, detailed, they did not spare any effort with it and it really departs by just enough to reinvigorate your commitment to the game. The baddies were awesome, the stories great, the armors insane, the new mutations crazy, just so much man so frickin much!! Get to it!! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-04 07:01:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> No it's not. He planned and attempted to do as much torturous pain as possible, leaving them with permanent scarring and requiring surgeries and a medically induced coma for months.

Do you not know how to read? Do you think you'd be ok with this happening to you? The man is an absolute detached psychopath that planned this out and had much time to turn back. Pre meditated attempted murder on two counts, how are you not getting this? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-04 06:57:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm gonna suggest there dumb as fuck, clearly looks like they didn't read the article at all.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-04 06:27:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah there's a number of shading issues that came up through the early seasons, even though Groening was supposedly hardcore on it, the commentary is awesome for all of this stuff. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-04 06:07:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That makes too much sense, get out of here </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-04 06:06:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> 3 billion fucking dollars, fuck I hate his movies but I'll worship em for that </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-04 05:31:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This situation is so desperate and disgusting it continually outages and infuriates. A black stain on the American saga. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-04 04:07:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah but they don't have to defend it in this manner.  You profess knowledge of the law but you know this is just blatant overstep and the lads would have won the court case if they had pockets as deep as zenimax </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-04 04:05:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hahaha I like that last bit. Nice. I'm gonna use that </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-04 04:05:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I gotta say it, fuck zenimax. When the elder scrolls six comes out and it's bubble characters and they sucked the last bit of enjoyment out of it for mass appeal I fucking hope it's the end of those guys </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-03 19:52:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I hate to say it but this just seems like ugly people who are too cowardice to show their face in support of their vague ideals. Children. Actual children. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-03 05:01:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That's wrong and you're clearly American haha

"The least shit country" ... Nope
"To ever exist" ... Nope

Then you go on to call other people extremists without perspective?

You lack self awareness.

Go look at any "best country to live" statistical analysis ever. Like ever. Even American publications won't say it's America. You're out to lunch, get out of your bubble and travel a bit. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-03 01:42:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Eye contact. And heed social cues, which are numerous and varying. But learn them from people and understand your own. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-02 06:24:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I think you're the joke here cupcake </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-02 06:21:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> But a good way to live is to criticise and generalise large populations from your computer/phone on Reddit though? 

Not sad and pathetic at all.  

You must be so fulfilled, and not a hilarious joke of a person like we all assume.

I love how you display weakness and pretentiousness to try to bring down "city folk" with the same adjectives.  You really are ten pounds of shit in a five pound bag there friendo. I feel for your mother. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-02 06:14:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Your name is dog fuck... On Reddit. And you're gonna post about what you consider to be infantile or sophisticated?

You poor fucking twat you probably have no idea what an idiot you really are. Or you're just a troll, either way... 

Fuck you,
Sincerely everyone in this subreddit. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-01 22:34:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Well that finally explains my fetish </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-01 21:52:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Gumball and the gang summarise it best with the blame song. Fucking nail it.

https://youtu.be/qpqoarZNfwk

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Computer games don't affect kids! </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-01 19:49:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Dogwatch </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-01 18:22:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-01 07:32:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The Bible by Neil DeGrasse Tyson </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-01 05:46:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Fuck you too friend, fuck you too </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> God I love this franchise </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-01 05:45:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> This manhole cover in Japan </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-01 05:40:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-01 01:20:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> *dispenses acid* </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What i love about Sundays </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-30 22:54:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-30 21:41:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Why use many word when few do </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-30 17:21:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It crossed my mind but it's far from cool I'm afraid </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Saddam Hussein with a gun to his wife's head. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-30 17:17:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Parmesan aging wharehouse </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-29 23:38:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-29 22:59:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Fuck me you're right. Thanks yo </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-29 21:56:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Get off the stage </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-29 21:48:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yes sorry I meant a board game for fallout, the announcement was just the other day, my bad </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-29 20:58:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That would be absolutely sick. I know it's probably unlikely, I heard Bethesda is releasing another card game now related to Fallout, but until the elder scrolls six comes along this kind of thing could really satiate the appetite </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Skyrim platform fighter style. Yes please </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-29 20:44:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-29 18:31:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Love the concept, got it immediately, good with you! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-29 18:31:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> 10/10 for realistic post. Into it </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Please more bread hooman </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-29 18:27:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-29 03:41:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> She really has that look. She famously made snacks and meals for the cast of his movies often. Insisting they had to have a good home cooked meal if they were to be working so much. How cool is that </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Robert DeNiro with Martin Scorsese's mother, snacking between takes </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-29 03:17:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-29 02:50:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Well now they'll have a head start ! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> It's all in the accent </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-29 02:34:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Me_irl </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-29 02:24:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-28 00:37:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's a big noticable difference eh. I immediately felt better about the fee </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The ATM at my local liquor store donates all transaction fees to MADD (Mother's Against Drunk Drivers) </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-27 22:54:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-27 21:15:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Absolutely phenomenal! So happy to see when you post, and so eager to forward it to my non-redditor friends. Pretty clear the whole community is salivating at your work and I for one am super grateful to the team working this into fruition. Love the new logo, it's all moving along so fast. I'm gonna go full fan boy here any minute so just again, thanks for this impressive, dedicated work.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-27 21:11:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Testa-mint. Got to have my chocolate Jesus </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Bill Murray, Times Square, 1979 </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-27 21:05:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-27 04:55:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You obviously have an extremist attitude and it shows in even civil debate.  Everyone's welcome to their opinion in this world and often opinions can be wrong when they're based on an objective fact. His success or failure is not so clear as an objective truth in the first hundred days you're right. But your extremist tone, bringing his suicide into it, won't help your arguments. I would recommend remaining silent and letting others bolster your side. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-27 04:02:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If I was before life began, then I'm at peace with it now. 
If I was not before life began, then I'm at peace with now.
If I will not be after life, then I'm at peace with it now.
If I will be after life, then I'm at peace with it now.
 
Trick is in the now.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Savage but valid </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-26 05:42:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-26 05:04:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thumb thumb thumb thumb thumb thumb!!!! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-26 05:03:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> And thus the war began </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-25 22:26:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hahahhaha literal. I like it </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Every. Time. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-25 22:21:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-25 21:29:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Dang autocorrect </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-25 21:28:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> There you go. Thanks that makes sense to me. Tried with the fan base and the fan base didn't approve.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-25 21:27:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The experience system is in the shrines. It very clearly has level up mechanics and would not require, and I wasn't asking for, a rework. 
For instance, cashing in exp could be done through shrines, one bonus per shrine. Keeps everything intact but also encourages you to engage the environment. It's very much what they have already going except the require you to conquer multiple shrines to advance your character and limit the amount of shrines on the map to allow for the "max lvl".
I also understand loot. You don't need question marks after every sentence. Just asking if anyone else saw it. The removal of incentive. I knew I'd be getting a lot of snark from asking this question. But yes I understand loot, thank you </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-25 10:13:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So excited man, keep up the good work y'all! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Marilyn Monroe performing on her USO tour in Korea, 1954 </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-25 00:42:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Say goodnight </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-25 00:13:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-24 21:00:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Good show! Jolly good! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-24 20:56:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That exercise bike is sick though </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-24 09:32:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Tarsier studio developing
Bandai Namco publishing

Been following it for what seems like ever, independent game from a small Swedish studio I'm so excited for. Hoping for great things! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-24 09:29:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Overrated comment of the fortnight </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-24 08:13:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Ahhh I see what you did there </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
