<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject5890</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-09 20:55:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I don't even remember what happy feels like. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-09 06:43:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Already picked out my gift! Should arrive to them on Thursday. We had a favourite tv show in common so my gift is an homage to that as well. Yay, that was fun! I can't wait until they get it! 

I collect stuffed hippos and fun coffee mugs. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-08 22:40:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thanks! I hope you make and enjoy them, too!  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-08 19:47:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I used this one: http://sallysbakingaddiction.com/2013/01/17/bakery-style-chocolate-chip-muffins/ and followed the directions for mini muffins.

Somehow mini foods taste better than regular sized ones!  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-08 18:47:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Try the reset password link again. I did it yesterday but hadn't received the email for 20 hours, but I tried again a few minutes ago and received it immediately. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-08 17:16:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If I store my beauty blender in a wire egg holder, would it be ok kept either in the cupboard under the sink or the medicine cabinet? I have several cats that would see it as a toy if I left it anywhere out in the open. But I don't know how well it would dry if it was closed up in a cabinet. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [Homemade] Mini chocolate chip muffins </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-08 17:07:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-08 01:27:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If you zoom in on the price tags, it looks like they say Christmas Tree Shoppe. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-06 04:32:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thank you! I'll definitely do that from now on.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-05 18:30:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The top is pepperoni and the bottom is turkey italian sausage and green peppers.

Backstory: I went gluten-free for a couple of months to find out if I had a sensitivity (sadly, I do). Pizza is my favourite food group so I was craving it constantly. I found a recipe for a crust made of just three types of cheese, eggs, and optional italian seasoning. It definitely hit the spot!  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [Homemade] Pizza with crust made entirely of 3 types of cheese and eggs </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-05 18:29:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-05 18:07:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thank you! That definitely makes sense. I'll switch to doing StarBonds on Mondays before the cutoff time. I am excited for Tuesday! 

I won classic cash for the first time today and it was pretty much the highlight of my morning. :-P

Thank you again for the help! I just started playing a week ago and mostly feel like I have no idea what I'm doing. This sub has definitely helped a bunch though!  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> StarBonds </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-05 14:55:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> After some advice from my last post and poking around old posts here, I invested in 2 StarBonds based on the info on Kaigee. I chose HMIRR and JSTAT, both adjusting on Tuesday and with DROI of 2.16 and 1.22 respectively. Their changes are green so I bought, not shorted.

I invested earlier in the week and if I'm understanding currently, I should have made some money off each daily. Instead, I'm at 0.00 net gain with HMIRR and I've lost $700 with JSTAT. 

Did I mess up my understanding of how SBs work?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [Homemade] Cinnamon roll cookies </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-04 18:14:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-04 04:04:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This is the recipe I used: http://sallysbakingaddiction.com/2013/11/07/apple-cider-donuts/ I used a mini muffin pan to make them!  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-03 20:14:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thanks I'll look into it. Actually, I think I do have a cream one that came on the other end of a concealer. I'll test that one out next!  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-03 19:17:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Sure! That is, if I can get to the post office before these all disappear in my face. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-03 18:49:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thank you! I have been doing some reading but haven't delved into StarBonds yet. I want to get a better feel for the movie and warrants part first before I spread out. I am also curious about the tv shows.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [Homemade] Apple cider doughnut holes </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-03 18:41:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-03 18:38:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thank you! That is a lot of helpful info - I appreciate you taking the time to help!  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-03 18:03:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thanks! I am using Wet   Wild bronzer in the lightest shade as a highlighter. I'm not sure how that compares. I'm not currently using a primer because none have played nice with my CC cream. I'm hoping to make the switch to Ordinary foundation and use their pore primer but I'm still waiting for my order to arrive. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-03 16:17:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thank you! I'll experiment some more with different products. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-03 16:04:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Should you avoid highlighting in areas with larger pores? I use a powder highlighter and I think it's accentuating the pores on my nose. Is it just my imagination?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-03 04:33:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Sure! This is the one I used: https://www.twopeasandtheirpod.com/vanilla-pudding-chocolate-chip-cookies/ </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-03 02:57:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> On mobile, Snoo rotates his antenna when a search is being performed. Your stamp just caught him mid-rotation. :-) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-02 22:05:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thank you for the links and info! It helps a lot!  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
