<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject2635</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-06 22:17:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I can't place it, but I've seen this exact same text several times before. This is definitely a scam.

Ah, [here's a few](https://www.google.com/search?q=%22I+hope+you+are+familiar+with+Airbnb%2C+but+if+not+i%27ll+explain+you+how+it+works.%22 oq=%22I+hope+you+are+familiar+with+Airbnb%2C+but+if+not+i%27ll+explain+you+how+it+works.%22 gs_l=mobile-heirloom-serp.12...31199.49597.0.50391.7.4.0.3.3.0.443.1003.0j2j1j0j1.4.0....0...1c.1.34.mobile-heirloom-serp..4.3.118.Gj1Q5AKwUVY). </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-06 19:59:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thanks, that's a great point. Appreciate the advice! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-06 19:29:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm sure you're right, and that's probably what I'll end up doing. 

My county makes it pretty easy. They have preprinted adoption petitions that you just have to fill out and a list of what to attach. If it wasn't for the pesky "not wanting a convicted murderer to know where his former domestic violence victim lives" thing, this would be a snap. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-06 19:02:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I like /r/wholesomememes. 

Their only narrative is that you're pretty swell and a lot of things are great. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-06 18:58:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> We have to stop this chain before we hit nine references. You know, because Eight Is Enough.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-06 18:50:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm not saying that's the wrong thing to do, but couldn't that give them the head's up that something's going on? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-06 18:10:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah, that was my impression as well. I couldn't find anything on their site, but they did invite me to look through "the laws" to find exceptions.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-06 18:03:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> 18, but my understanding is that an adoption several a legal relationship so "consent" is required. I thought that legal relationship was severed when he signed the termination of parental rights, but I'm no lawyer. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-06 17:29:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> They used the term consent, but then again they're not lawyers. 

In California, the bio father signed a form terminating his parental rights. The local person said that didn't transfer because it's a "California form."

edit: I just called again. They said that the form he signed in California terminating his parental rights (which was notarized in the prison) is "moot" because we didn't go through with the adoption in that state. So he... has parental rights again? Something about that doesn't sound right. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [MD] Do we have to get consent from the biological father for an adult, step-parent adoption in cases of domestic violence and rape? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-06 17:17:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm trying to adopt my step-son, who just turned 18. Both he and his mother consents. We had started the process in California, but were still on the waiting list for a year before we moved. At that time, he was a minor.

The biological father has not been in his life since he was one, and has not been in contact with either him or my wife since that time. Currently, he's in prison for 80-something more years for an unrelated crime. 

We didn't want to give him our address at that time, since he had already escaped twice (both times during transit, he didn't get very far. But still...). My step-son's conception was non-consensual during a domestic violence episode, so my wife certainly doesn't want him to know where we are now. We had waited to try again until he was an adult, under the mistaken belief that we wouldn't need consent.

I talked to the adoption office for our county today who said that consent is still required, but there "may" be an exception for consent in the case of abandonment or rape situations, but she wasn't sure. Whatever the case, she said it's our responsibility to find the answer as they can't provide legal advice. 

As a practical matter, I know we can use a PO box or alternate address in the county, but that's still a lot more information than my wife is comfortable sharing with him. She's got her OPSEC down. 

Are there any provisions in Maryland where we won't need the consent of the biological father?


EDIT: I found this in the Maryland adoption... law... stuff... which seems to indicate that they honor the termination of parental rights in other states. Am I reading this correctly?

53B04.    
(a)   In this section, order includes any action that, under the laws of another jurisdiction, has the force and effect of a comparable judicial order under this subtitle.  
(b)   In accordance with the United States Constitution, this State shall accord full faith and credit to:  
(1)   an order of another state as to adoption or guardianship in compliance with the other states laws; and  
(2)   **termination of parental rights in compliance with the other states laws.**  
(c)   As to a jurisdiction other than a state:  
(1)   an order for adoption or guardianship entered in compliance with the jurisdictions laws shall have the same legal effect as an order for adoption or guardianship entered in this State; and  
(2)  **termination of parental rights in compliance with the jurisdictions laws shall have the same legal effect as termination of parental rights in this State.** </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-01 18:50:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'd imagine it happens to a greater or lesser extent every 4-8 years. I know folks that said they wouldn't ever work under Hillary, and folks that said they'd quit if Trump won.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-22 15:13:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The 'detective' only said that they were leaving it up to the 'father' as to whether or not they press charges. Detective Fakie never asked for money, but of course the 'dad' did right after. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-20 18:15:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Wise words from grandpa gas! I'll have to remember that when I go back to work tomorrow! :) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-20 17:52:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Lol, fair enough! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-20 17:26:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Aren't you a delight? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-20 17:13:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> And do you know you can read (or ignore) someone's opinion without bitching about it, right?

But, hey, whatever works for you. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-20 14:31:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'd trade you in a heartbeat. 

Well, maybe not. I like fighting over them once in a while, but not 11 at a time (like last time). Honestly, that's just not fun for me.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-20 14:29:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If this 2 ways is not your way...try other games... 

That's kind of where I'm headed. It's not that I don't like either of those ways, it's just that I've been losing interest and the resource base thing is kind of the last straw for me. 

Nothing personal against anyone that likes the game, it's just what pushed me over the fence. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-20 14:04:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Actually, I've been in a pretty good TF for a while. That's really the only reason I've been playing. So you're right, and it's a good idea to get into a good group. I guess it just feels like I can get that same experience in a game where I enjoy the other aspects.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-20 13:53:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I don't expect new content often. I don't really need it at all. By 'something new', I was talking about a new game.

Resource bases isn't the reason, like I said. It's just the last reason. You might not agree, but I'm just sharing my thoughts on a game that I've been playing for years and why I'm leaving it. 

Appreciate your interest, though. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-20 13:51:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Why not? I just don't like it how they have them all cycle at once. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Boom Beach, I'm breaking up with you </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-20 13:34:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's not you, it's me. Specifically, it's how I feel about you. 

I mean, it's not just one thing. I've been playing for a long time, and sometimes you just need something new, you know? We've had some good times. Lots of laughs. But now it's time to move on. 

I guess the thing that did it- the straw that broke the camel's back, is the way you shuffle resource bases. Last night, nine of mine were taken over all at once. Last time, it was eleven. I wouldn't mind if you spaced it out, but I'm tired of having it happen all at once. 

So that's it; I just had to say my piece and move on. Thanks for some good times.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-27 16:55:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Birth rates would probably be much lower, if so. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-27 16:50:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Or even domain names like "cnn.co" or "foxnews.net" (if available), and clone the real site while changing the actual articles. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Petition to rename the Pittsburgh International Airport after Mr. Rogers </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-27 16:12:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-23 02:46:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Sighting at 5:24-ish, for my friends on mobile. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> A sighting in the wild. There's a browncoat in that office. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-23 02:45:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-24 22:49:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Too late, I already did! It did seem kind of warm vs hot though. I didn't think to check the temp :( </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-24 22:40:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Lol! Good point, and sounds pretty good! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-24 21:59:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Dang. But I thought that might be the case.

Looks like it's a traditional Christmas Eve pizza for dinner tonight! :)

Thanks for the confirmation. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> MAJOR mess up with dinner tonight. 7 hours on warm! </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-24 21:54:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm cooking a corned beef brisket, and the instructions have it on low for 7 hours and high for one.

I've had it on warm for the entire 7 hours. Oops. Is it bad now? Can I save it? I turned it into high, but I'm concerned about bacteria or something.

Edit: Thanks for all the great replies! I ended up throwing it out, but before some of this feedback came in. So maybe my loss, but perhaps it was better safe than sorry. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-20 22:55:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Or, is it at all possible that you were legitimately downvoted for being unnecessarily confrontational (and a little bit of an ass) about it? 

Or is it inconceivable that you can be the problem, so you have to blame someone else?

Hint: I'm not from t_d and I downvoted you for you. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-24 04:20:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Same cat. Same household. It's all good. You were wrong about this one, but that's okay. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-10 04:08:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Failed? You mean like how the Reavers FAILED to catch out beloved crew on Whitefall when Wash pulled a Crazy Ivan? Man, that was awesome! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-09 22:27:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It wasn't an agency, but the #DeployOurDaughters campaign came from 4chan and reddit. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-08 02:50:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The funny thing is that the 'other buyer' fell through, so he came back to me to see if I still wanted a box. Didn't need it any longer, so he didn't end up selling any of it at all.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-07 01:29:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That's interesting, thank you. With both major parties talking about voter fraud this year, I hope it's not an issue! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-06 23:43:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What sort of procedures are in place to detect and deter election fraud? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-06 18:32:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This is all great advice, thank you. And thank you for taking the time to share it! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-05 23:33:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thanks for the tip and advice! I appreciate it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-05 22:07:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Rough day, fella? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-05 20:37:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> They're really great, and were able to get the price down a bit! They work up to a certain point, so my high copay still leaves a good amount out of pocket. Of course that'll change here pretty quick at least! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-05 20:29:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> *you're </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-05 18:46:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That's really good to know, thank you! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-05 18:46:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah, good point! Although I'd be pretty upset if I was at the pharmacy counter and the pharmacist tried to bump up the cost when another customer showed up, lol!

Thanks for the tip, I'll keep that in mind! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-05 18:11:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Is it still good? I mean, as a backup or anything? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-05 17:57:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> We're in that weird zone- income is too high for most benefits, but student loans and other medical expenses take up a lot of the 'ol paycheck. So we just gotta be smart about these things. 

Thanks for the tip about the needles- I wasn't sure where to get those! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-05 17:52:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hmm, interesting point. I mean, personally I wouldn't mind buying it from anyone that has it (craigslist or the pharmacy). But the idea that they're playing that sort of game with medicine doesn't sit right with me. It's not like I'm buying a used phone or something! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-01 22:37:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Oh! That's interesting. I saw an iOS version but hadn't seen the Android one. Thanks! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-01 15:26:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [Guess Who's Coming to Dinner](http://www.imdb.com/title/tt0061735/).

"Is it Richard?" 

"Nope." 

"Frank?" 

"Nope." 

"Thomas?" 

"Nope."  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-01 03:33:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> We actually picked up a walmart meter today, and we tested it against the one touch that we got from the doctor. The results were exactly the same! So that's definitely a plus.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-01 03:32:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yes! We got cards for both types of insulin, and we're down to $268. So that's a start! 

We're with GEHA, and they consider all diabetes medications and supplies to be brand name drugs, which they only cover at 50%. So I'm glad for the half off, but half off of expensive is still expensive. 

We're also grateful for the doctor, who did give us some samples! We got a few pens, some lancets, some strips and some other stuff to last us until we sort out the insurance issue. He (the doctor) really seems to hate diabetes, so he seemed happy to do it. 

The nurse dropped the insulin into the sharps container, otherwise I was going to :(

And thanks for the tip! I'm talking to the benefits coordinator tomorrow, so hopefully I can get it sorted out. 

Thanks again! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-01 03:24:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> By nature, I'm a pretty private person. But if someone wants to give my child free insulin, they can have and resell my disposable email address. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-30 16:00:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> We're in what I like to call the "dammit zone." Income is too high for some of the great programs out there, but not quite high enough for this not to be an issue. But I definitely have to get better insurance- or at least insurance that's better for diabetes. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-30 15:58:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I was just reading up on the Relion! 

Wait... we talked about that, didn't we? Heck, I'm starting to lose track. There's a lot to learn, lol. 

Can you please clarify a little how you marry up the two results? I really want to make sure he's getting accurate results. I'm pretty fond of my son, of course :) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-30 14:08:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Great point, thanks! We're with a great endocrinologist who, unfortunately, isn't covered by our insurance. But we're good through another meeting with him at least. He's on 15 carbs to 1 unit, which seems to work out pretty well math-wise. And already he's feeling a lot better, which is great to see!

Thanks for the book recommendation. One of the doctors had mentioned that we need to think like a pancreas, but I didn't know that was a book title! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-30 14:03:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thanks for clearing that up! I finally realized that the strips are proprietary- glad I did before I went and ordered something!

And thanks for clearing that up about the Glucagon! I certainly hope drinking won't be a problem, at least not yet, lol </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-30 13:49:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> $2000's a whole lot better than the $6000 my insurance company was quoting- that's crazy!

Thanks for the tip! Sounds like a great plan for the diabetes management. I'm a little concerned about his (and his mother's) other appointments and medication. How much do you pay for office visits? 

And I'll happily give you a pass on the writing if you do the same for me! We've been staying at the hospital, which isn't exactly conducive for a good night's sleep, you know? 

Thank you again for the information, and I'll definitely PM you! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-30 13:41:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I've heard a few people (here and online) mention that the strip and meter companies can sometimes send out supplies. That really blows me away that a company would be willing to send out some of their product for free, just because people actually need that to live. 

In an amazing coincidence, I think the Verio is the one his doctor ordered! If that's the case, we definitely appreciate your kind offer. Can I let you know as soon as I find out for sure? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-30 13:16:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thanks, I didn't think about that! It would probably be a good thing to be able to switch to a more diabetes-friendly plan before Jan! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-30 13:13:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That's a good point! I think open enrollment, while starting next month, doesn't take affect until January of next year. So switching sooner would be a good thing if possible. Thanks for the tip! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-30 13:09:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Oh, that makes sense. Thanks!

I do see blue cross blue shield in my list of plans, so I'll explore that first. Thanks again! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-30 05:30:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah- we spent all our time and energy thinking about his blood sugar and hospital visit, so the prescription question was almost an afterthought. Hopefully I can get a good answer tomorrow. Once I do that, the dr. will put in the new prescription. It's all pretty confusing, but we're getting there. And at least Joe (my son) is doing better! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-30 05:29:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I guess it's time to dust off the ol' Facebook account and check in then! I was really hoping to keep out until after the election, lol! :) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-30 05:24:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> He doesn't reddit, but I'll point him in this direction! Um... after I clear out some of my comment history and block a few things at the router level... lol! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-30 05:22:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Oh, lol! No worries. I guess in this case I'm a D.O.D., but I'll pass on your well wishes to the M.O.D. And just for good measure, I'll let the L.B.O.D. (little brother, there) know as well, lol

I'll keep looking on the site and try to get someone on the phone / live on Monday. But if you wouldn't mind asking around in your groups, I'd really appreciate it! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-30 05:06:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Ooh, some lingo I gotta learn! What does that stand for?

(also, quick question: is [this](https://mmcp.dhmh.maryland.gov/chp/pages/home.aspx) kind of what you were talking about? It looks like this one is income-based and we're above that threshold. Or were you talking about another type?) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-30 05:02:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thank you! That'll get me started. And I appreciate the offer- I'll definitely reach out.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-30 04:48:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That was new to me! I thought a strip was a strip was a strip- I didn't know they were coded to a particular meter. So I'm glad I learned that today. 

Have you ever tried any of the meters with the less expensive strips? Until I get a better insurance plan, I was looking into other options. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-30 04:41:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thanks for this info.

I don't see those ones in [my search](https://www.opm.gov/healthcare-insurance/healthcare/plan-information/compare-plans/Plans?zipcode=21061 FFSSearch=on empType=a payPeriod=c) based on my zip code. Does it go by another name? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-30 04:34:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> 5 a day, wow- that's a lot. Of course unless the insurance covers most/all of it. Hopefully I can sort it out with the insurance then to make sure he has enough. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-30 04:22:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> As prescription drugs? That's what I was expecting, and normally our prescription drugs are very inexpensive. Relatively, at least.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-30 04:17:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That's a good point. The brochure's a little bit vague on that point. But I'm going to try talking to them again tomorrow and see what they say. The doctor gave us some other options (with a preference to the pen) for me to bring to the insurance folks tomorrow. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-30 04:15:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Okay, so I'm NOT completely crazy! I felt the same way. I'm calling them again tomorrow, so hopefully I can get some answers. Thanks for the validation! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-30 04:14:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thank you very much! I x-posted to /r/diabetes and I'm getting some great information. 

I'm not sure why my insurance was charging so much, but I'm going to revisit it with them tomorrow and look into a new insurance plan that covers things a little better. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-30 04:13:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thank you.

Yes, I am in the US- Maryland, specifically. I didn't know there was anything like that! Do you have any idea how I would find the right office for that?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-30 04:10:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The doctor (who's awesome, by the way) said he was going to bring a meter tomorrow. And our insurance provides one as well, so I guess we'll be okay there. But the strips seems to be where the money is, lol. 

$150 for 100 strips?? Wow, that's insane. How long does that last you? I think you use three a day, if I remember right. 

Can you please let me know how the walmart brand is working for you, once you get a chance? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-30 04:00:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> We're going for pen needles, so hopefully that'll work out. Don't the lancets get rusty or anything over time? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-30 03:58:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I think I'm learning the same thing- really have to be careful to pick the right insurance plan for something like this. We had a pretty good plan, but turns out it's terrible when it comes to diabetes supplies. 

That's good to know about the insulin- I really need to get a breakdown tomorrow. Even with all that, I can't believe how expensive it all is! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-30 03:49:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I just spoke to him and he gave me 4 long-term options and 3 short-term choices, in order of preference. I have to call the insurance tomorrow and see what they might cover a little bit better. 

I'm not familiar with those names. Are those the long-term or short-term ones?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-30 03:21:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> They didn't, the whole thing was confusing. I called the pharmacy who thought it was a mistake, and they advised I called my insurance who said that it was covered at 50%. I guess I didn't think to ask why. The doctor's calling me in a few minutes, and I'm going to ask him about other (maybe less expensive, but equally effective!) options. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-30 03:11:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah, in network! It's the same place we get his unrelated medicine, which only has the copay. My insurance was saying that they're only covering 50% for some reason, so I'm thinking it's time to find a new insurance company! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-30 03:08:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> $1500 a year is a lot better than $6000, so that's a plus. 

My insurance will send me a one touch (something) meter; you're saying that any strips will work with a reader? I wasn't really sure how that worked. How off would you say the generic strips are, compared to the other ones?

We were going to try to get the pen, have you tried those? The thing with the dial? That might be easier for him, if we can get it. 

And, yeah, you're right about the system as a whole. I really didn't think it would be so complicated, seeing as how people need it to live. Hope we can fix it in our lifetimes, you know? 

Thanks for the advice and the well wishes. I really appreciate it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-30 03:01:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thanks, I'll check that out </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-30 03:00:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> My friend's wife, turns out, is a pharmacist. And she said she may have some of those cards or information on how to get them! I'm definitely interested in saving money. Someone's going to get my money, and I'd prefer to save some of it whenever possible, lol </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-30 02:59:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I didn't even know that might be an option! I'll look into that next month during the open enrollment period. That sounds like a great deal. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-30 02:17:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This is actually really encouraging to hear, thank you. It's hard, and it's good to know that it's not as bad as it seems. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-30 02:05:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That's not bad. Seems a lot better than what my insurance covers. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-30 01:38:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Oh, wow, that's really cool! He has an Android, so that one's not compatible (sadly). But I will look into that now, thanks! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-30 01:27:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Great tip, thank you! We're staying two days in the hospital, and we've all gotten pretty good at measuring the sugar levels and the math that tells us how much insulin to use. 

I will definitely look into the education classes, thanks!

And you're right about carb counting! He's at a 15:1 ratio now (the measurement is right, but the name might be wrong. I'm still learning the lingo!) so it's pretty easy to measure.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-30 00:59:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thanks for this information. I really appreciate it.

This is probably a stupid question, but if I get the free reader (a one touch brand) can I use any strips with it? Or is there a compatibility issue?

Yes, I think glucagon is the gun they're talking about. So that might be a thing to get when we can, but maybe not worry about it for Monday?

Insulin, right. Sorry, I forgot to mention that part. I think the insulin is completely covered, or at least mostly. And you got it righ- we're getting lantus and novolog.

Is there anything else we need to make sure to ask about? I think that's all the supplies, right? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-29 23:52:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I am, yes. We never thought to check their diabetes coverage, but it doesn't seem to be great. It seems that they only cover 50% of supplies. Or at least that's what they said </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-29 23:34:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thanks, this is very helpful. Are you getting your supplies through your insurance or buying them directly? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-29 23:33:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thanks for the reply!

I suppose it would be an employer plan, but we have options. I'm a federal employee, so it's through OPM (https://www.opm.gov/healthcare-insurance/healthcare/plan-information/plans/2016/state/md/summary). 

Fortunately, the open enrollment period is coming up in two weeks. I was thinking about calling each of them next week to find out how they cover diabetic supplies like this. 

I can't recall the very long list that my insurance was talking about. They do cover one meter a year, but there was a cost for everything else including the strips, needles, glucose gun and some other things I can't recall.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-29 22:53:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm with GEHA. I'm a federal employee, so our open enrollment period starts in a few weeks. I'm having trouble reading the plan brochures, since none of them seem to discuss diabetes supplies specifically. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Affording diabetic supplies and medication </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-29 22:41:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> My son (17) was just diagnosed with Type 1. We're on day two at the hospital now learning all the ends and outs of diet and injections and all that.

I'm terrified about Monday. We'll need to get his new medication from the pharmacy then, and I have no idea how to pay for it. They're saying it'll be $1000 (our share!) for everything, and there's no way I can come up with that in two days. I mean, I will- it's his health, I'll do whatever I have to do... I just don't know what that is.

How do you pay for your medication and needles and all that? We're looking at about $1000/mo up to $6000 a year, which we don't have.
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> How do you afford all this? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-29 22:18:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> My son (17) was just diagnosed with Type 1. We're on day two at the hospital now learning all the ends and outs of diet and injections and all that. 

I'm terrified about Monday. We'll need to get his new medication from the pharmacy then, and I have no idea how to pay for it. They're saying it'll be $1000 (our share!) for everything, and there's no way I can come up with that in two days. I mean, I will- it's his health, I'll do whatever I have to do... I just don't know what that is. 

How do you pay for your medication and needles and all that? We're looking at about $1000/mo up to $6000 a year, which we don't have.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-16 03:18:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thank you very much! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Taking a last family picture. Where's the best vantage point for a fall foliage backdrop? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-16 01:17:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> My grandparents are getting up there, so we have four generations together for what will likely be our last big family portrait. 

My job is to find the best backdrop for the picture- something that really shows the leaves. Do you have any recommendations of where we can get the best view? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-15 16:14:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If they've never recovered any bodies, then how do they know the people are dead? It sounds to me like this river may actually be the entryway into some magical world, filled with sweets and fun. It's probably also where your pet actually went and it might get your parents back together. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-15 16:10:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> "It is believed that not a single person who has fallen into the Strid has ever come out of it alive. Not even their bodies."

That's the scariest part. Not only are they not alive, but not even their bodies! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-11 13:41:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [OMG, I tried but I was soooooo high](http://i.imgur.com/TEvbSZb.jpg) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-09 20:34:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> To his credit, he's actually just a 200 pound hebephile. But the fact that he was believable as a 400 pound pedophile speaks positively about his acting skills. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-09 19:32:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Here's the encyclopedia [definition of theft](https://www.britannica.com/topic/theft), which specifically notes that it requires an I tent to permanently deprive someone of their property.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-09 19:31:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> He's right, though... Part of the [definition of theft](https://www.britannica.com/topic/theft) involves intent to permanently deprive someone of their property. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-09 18:10:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> He might have alligator already, though.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-08 20:05:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yes, in a sense. That's actually a broad characteristic of the younger workforce, who believe that work, life and fun should be able to meld together in a (preferably, for them) seamless way. And 75% of the millennial generation would take or has taken a pay cut for work they enjoy or to join a company with a good reputation. 

It's going to be very interesting as the "work to live" mindset starts to give way to the "live at work, work while living" one. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-08 18:33:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> A big romantic gesture in which you tell the bride that you always loved her and that she should be with you, not the other guy.
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-27 18:15:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Million to one shot, doc... Million to one. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-26 22:37:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I heard the homeowner was hunting and discovered oil, so they packed up the truck and they moved to Beverly. Hills, that is. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-24 00:50:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Can you tell the story of meeting him? That must have been amazing. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> xkcd: Temper </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-23 13:09:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-22 21:29:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Even the professor they referenced in the clip [didn't really agree](https://thinkprogress.org/professor-retracts-mr-rogers-smears-a58bbde88537#.qg4s0528c) with their claim! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-22 21:25:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> "Imagine what our real neighborhoods would be like if each of us offered, as a matter of course, just one kind word to another person. There have been so many stories about the lack of courtesy, the impatience of today's world, road rage, and even restaurant rage. Sometimes, all it takes is one kind word to nourish another person. "

-Mr. Rogers

He would very much like it if we all just *tried*
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-22 21:22:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Mr. Rogers [enjoyed that sketch](http://www.fredrogers.org/facebook/eddie-murphy.html), and took the opportunity to tell Eddie as much. Can you imagine what must have gone through Eddie's mind when he opened the door to find the REAL Mr. Rogers there? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-22 20:12:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's been two months since you made this comments. I stumbled across it, and now it's spread to me. 

It will never die.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-22 20:06:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> And give /r/MrRogersNeighborhood/ a little bit of love! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-22 18:07:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Of course! I don't know the details beyond the KKK having to destroy the tapes. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-22 18:06:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Sure did! The KKK had to destroy the tapes. I'm not sure what happened beyond that, though. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-22 16:05:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> To be (reasonably) angry at the parents, she would need to know the reason why they didn't pay. You could be angry at the parent if they spent all their money on drugs and neglected to feed their child. If there were medical considerations that made it temporarily difficult to make ends meet? Maybe anger wouldn't be the right emotion there. So she (and we) can't reasonably be angry at the parents without assuming the worst about them.

We have to remember that the school board acknowledged that poor children have been affected by this policy simply because the parent was unable to pay. Not unwilling- they're aware (now) that some parents were unable to pay. It's possible, although I can't say for certain, that this child's parents were one of those unable to pay. 

Remember, too, that the amount this child owed [was from last year](http://triblive.com/news/regional/11176905-74/lunch-students-district). Making efforts to collect from last year is fine, i suppose, but the way the policy was implemented here is flawed at best.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> TIL in 1990, Mr. Rogers sued the KKK for impersonating his voice in prerecorded messages. These messages said "AIDS was divine retribution" and included radio skits simulating lynchings of black children on a playground. The tapes were circulated among elementary and middle school children. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-22 14:50:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-21 21:15:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> No, it doesn't. If you read the article, it says that the policy wasn't designed to target children who were poor and in poverty. That doesn't mean that those that are weren't impacted by it. 

It seems to me that you're making a lot of assumptions. But do you agree that the child himself didn't do anything wrong? 

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-11 23:20:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Or just tell them you're on the do not call list at the kingdom hall. Even better of you actually get yourself on that list. They take that very seriously and seem to leave immediately at that point. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-11 20:57:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> 'Please find attached a list of family members who may be murdered in the future:' </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-09 02:59:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> /r/HiCorporate 

Edit: what the hell? That's actually a sub. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-06 17:22:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Except for those that [force capitalization](https://www.reddit.com/r/reddithax/comments/3gw1pd/autocapitalize_submission_titles/). Not saying this one does, but some subs actually do. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-29 22:15:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I've been smoking too much week, I guess.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-29 19:03:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> For those that don't want to look it up, the movie being referenced here was El Seor Tormenta, and it came into theaters in 1963. 

Therefore,/u/ IAMA_SeaOtter_AMA has been smoking week for 53 years. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-27 03:45:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Not sure what your plan is, but the Avalon shelters allow alcohol with a $35 permit. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-26 22:04:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> For once I have something relevant to add! 

My name's Chris, and I developed the first formal command-level OPSEC program at the National Training Center. As a part of that, I also developed the first Critical Information List (CIL), which is still being used today. So we can all relax- I can assure the previous poster that no one disclosed any Critical Information here today. 

For anyone wanting to know more about OPSEC, I also founded [The Operations Security Professional's Association](http://www.opsecprofessionals.org), a national non-profit Operations Security organization.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-25 02:11:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Great, thanks! The property manager (who is the point of contact for these things; she *thinks* we have an actual board but there appears to be some uncertainty there) says she's "looking into it." 

This might change things. Apparently, there's two accounts. I wasn't aware of this, so for the past year, I've been paying both fees using the same online portal. And every month for the past year, they've been applying it correctly. They applied it correctly on 8/22, but after two months of not applying any payment to any account. It was just sitting there giving me a positive balance.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-23 00:09:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Great, thanks. That's a load off my mind. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [MD] Legal fees for a disputed debt </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-23 00:00:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I received a surprise letter from my HOA's lawyer today. They said we were two months behind in dues, and demanded the full amount plus $50 in legal fees. 

The error was on the property manager's side, and it's been cleared up. They received the money but didn't apply it to our account. So now I'm showing a zero balance. 

I assume I still need to dispute the debt through the lawyer (they included a document explaining that it's an attempt to collect a debt and how to dispute it), because it's obviously not valid. But what happens to the $50 legal fee they included? Will the still be expecting me to pay it, or does that go away when the debt is found to be invalid?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-20 17:40:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Ianal, but that would probably be evidence, but not conclusively proof. I was thinking more like toll charges, things like that.

I'll defer to the smart people here, but it seems like you have a pretty solid defense from the ticket. You laterally weren't there. And if you can prove that your car was with you, the court should fond in your favor. 

Whether or not you should mention your boss is a good question for a real lawyer. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-20 15:49:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Out of curiosity, would you be able to prove that you and your car was in Tallahassee on that day? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-02 12:10:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hooah! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-01 22:33:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I think some of us are making assumptions about what this means. 

ISIS will not send a mass of fighters up against the Russian military. They'll use the jihad to try to call the 16 million Muslims already in Russia to commit violent acts. It's the exact same call the group made when encouraging lone wolf attacks in the West.

They get the credit, as well as the funding. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-01 12:59:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> (FYI: you're replying to a troll account) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-01 12:46:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That gives me hope. Hope that someday, somewhere, the red ranger was able to say, "It's morphine time!" </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-30 23:40:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The sharpened prongs get dull, and it doesn't thread very well. It becomes a cheese okayer. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-30 22:31:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'll tag them in the Facebook post. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-30 22:25:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'd be very interested in the ven diagram of the members of /r/atheism and /r/childfree </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-30 21:58:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [deleted] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-30 19:14:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Look at the history. It's just a really lazy troll account. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-30 18:17:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> There have been three times in my life someone has knocked on my door late at night: once my wife left her keys in the door, another time someone found my building access badge that had gotten lost in the snow, and another time was because my car was on fire.

So far, late night knockings have been a positive experience for me. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-30 18:15:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I don't believe you. You're that landshark that's been eating people, aren't you? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-30 18:07:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Doesn't it seem a little bit morbid for fish to call their offspring a fry? I mean, that's lretty much the worst thing that could happen to a fish, so it's a little inappropriate for them to make light of it. It would be like us calling our infants SIDs or something. Not cool. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-30 04:52:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You're an adult now. Make it happen.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-30 04:10:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That's why I store my ice cream in an offshore fridge. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-29 04:20:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> *advice </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-28 13:01:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Naw, wasn't trying to hit *you" there. But then again, my aim is pretty bad. 

And, yeah, that movie is hilarious. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-27 18:19:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Interesting, thank you! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-27 14:36:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=EMTbkfgT_jc </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-26 16:33:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Remember those skittles ads from a while back? The one where it told you to put your finger on the screen, then it cut to some guy licking where your finger was? 

Those were hilarious. Not only did I watch them, but I showed other people. I forwarded them to my friends. I was (knowingly) advertising for them, but I was *entertained*. That's all I wanted out of those commercials, and they gave it to me.

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-21 13:30:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If passengers are boarding you in a bathroom stall in Sacramento, they're really not going to care what you're watching. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-20 01:35:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Nowhere- roosters don't lay eggs! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-18 22:02:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> In a way, it's not too late. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-16 21:15:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> "Oh? What did you catch?"

"Chlamydia." </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-15 18:47:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Good to know, thanks! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-15 18:06:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That's a great point, thanks. That was my concern, that they would think that I'm trying to ask them to commit fraud.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-15 17:56:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That's good to hear. Any suggestions for approaching it, beyond what /u/ilovedean said? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-15 17:34:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'd better be careful in the future then, thanks! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-15 17:24:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thanks for this information.

Every time I have a checkup or physical, the doctor asks if I have any specific concerns. If I do and he answers them, does that make it a diagnostic visit then? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
