<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject8635</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-09 13:44:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Oh, no, we aren't. The fuckers who messed with us? Well... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-09 13:43:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> She won't let me out much anymore. I'm 12, she's 23 now.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The birth of Leah </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-08 21:13:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The birth of Leah

My name is Cornelia.  Not Cory, Lee, Lia, Leah, Nelly CORNELIA.  And for the guys who think it is funny to make my name male: Im not Cornelio or Cornelius either.  Named after my mothers grandmother, who was a short lady.  I guess I got more than just the old womans name.  Everyone in my family is freakishly tall, like giant-esque type of tall. My eldest brother had to bow his head to get into a normal doorway.  With the result that everything, and everywhere, we had custom-made high doors and ceilings.  My family was a bunch of freaks well, except for me.  Mum told me that my great grandmother Cornelia was also short.  Im not short in the eyes of society, but in the eyes of my family Im a short ass.

**That's right, a motherfucking short ass who -**

My name is Cornelia.  Im 23 and Im an education student.  I live with my parents and my puppy, Kira.  My mum and I are just great  Im very close with my mum.  My mum knows all my secrets, shes my best friend in the world.

**Or she did know all of my secrets.  She likes to think that she does, but she's an ignorant old twat who -**

I have four siblings.  Two brothers and two sisters, all of them older than me.  I was born in 1994, in April, while my youngest sibling was eight years my senior, and my oldest sibling was fifteen years my senior.  I wasnt close to any of them.  Just my mum.  My youngest sibling left home when I was about ten years old, and I honestly cant remember much from my first decade on this eart.  I just remember tiny bursts  me fucking with a claw machine, kicking my mum, giving stepsister-to-be bread, playing on an old black-and-white computer with my brothers, my father finding it scandalous that I, at the age of 4, wore a bikini while running through the sprinklers in my own backyard.  Stuff like that.

**That fucker did more harm than good in this world.  He was a firm believer of beating the shit out of your children, a fucker who - **

I remember more about my father than I would like to.  I remember him sauntering into the house to scream at us, to accuse my mother of whoring around and finally collapse, his breath stinking of beer and rum and dried vomit coating his shoes, while my eldest sister covered him with a blanket.  I dont like those memories.  Of course, this was before I even went to school.  I might be remembering all of this incorrectly.  I mean, I thought a man that looked like Triple H (the wrestler) lived under my bed.

**HE WAS THERE TO PROTECT YOU, YOU DUMB LITTLE BITCH!**

Anyway.  When I was 12 my mum married my stepdad, though theyve been doing the dirty since I was about six.  That was the year my mum and my father separated, but they didnt have a divorce until years after that.  My father moved away, my mum stuck around to raise me.  I just know that Pete Greer has made my living hell for eleven years.

**Understatement of the fucking year, Cornelia, fucking honestly?  That fat fuck motherfucking raped you, he motherfucking tortured you, he motherfucking broke your soul and you liken it to living hell?  There is something worse, Cornelia, and that would be what that fat fuck did to you!**

I call my stepdad daddy.  He is the one that raised me since I was six years old.  My real dad never wanted me.  He he told my mum that he would rather write me off as a daughter than to pay the monthly sum that my mum needed to look after me.  He gave me gifts, but it was a broken printer, a scratched CD and, once, a hand towel.  Honestly, what type of father was he?

**HE WAS BETTER THAN THE FAT FUCK.**

I soldiered on.  I didnt have a lot of friends, but I had Carinne.  Carinne was a few months younger than I was, but I liked her and hanging out with her.  We were inseparable.  At least we were inseparable for the first thirteen years of our lives, before we made new friends.  I know where she is now, but I dont talk to her.  I dont like her.  I didnt like who she changed into when we got to high school.   Then again, I dont like anyone.  Though I do a pretty good job of pretending I do.  People know me as the nice girl, the smart girl, the girl who is likely to end up a billionaire because she is just that fucking smart.  I have absolutely no modesty, nor do I have the patience to fake it.  This was what drove Carinne away.  I always did better than she did  tests, assignments, even the stupid fucking little baking soda volcano.  I was a genius, and my teachers loved me.  My friend?  Well, she was smart, but the fact that I didnt apologize for my good marks deterred her.  She abandoned me as soon as we reached high school.  Not that I mind, I enjoyed solitude and the silence is wrought.

**I... well, she makes a good point.  I'm only here because I can't fucking escape from this damn body.  I don't want to be her friend either.**

Of course, I still excelled at everything I did.  I was a genius, after all.  I was an alto in choir  the only alto, mind you.  I ended up on the first hockey team in the second semester of my fourteenth year, mostly due to my vicious attacks that had the other team hurrying away from me.  I once slammed the hockey ball into a girls forehead, and there was a sizable dent in her skull after that.  The enemies stayed clear of me.  I once managed to get a goal from the other side of the field where I was guarding the goalie, solely because the team was terrified of me.  

After the game, I put on my ditzy smile and apologized to the girl.  She shook my hand, though she was shaking.

Mostly people thought I was innocent.  I mean, Im the girl with the perfect grades, the perfect personality, I did sports and choir, I participated as much as I could.  I was the innocent, if somewhat egotistic, girl.  Witty, funny, pretty, smart, athletic, artsy  Perfect.

Only it wasnt just Cornelia at that time.  By that time, Lee had been born  quiet, bookish, shy.  She went to school for me.  She did all the studying and wrote the tests and exams too.  She was a little ball of nerves all the bloody fucking time.  Cornelius managed to calm her down, though.  Cornelius was the silent, strong one.  They called him the protector.  He always came out when it was play time with daddy.  He didnt say a word, he took the punishment.

And we were fine for a while.  Lee took care of books and studies, I took care of sports and the artsy things, and Cornelius protected us.  I was innocent. 

But Im not innocent.  People like to think I am.  Im a pretty girl and I come across as childish to many people.  Of course I do  thats the faade Ive created.  Im an innocent little girl, at 23.  Dont get me wrong, I do love Disney, and I do love dolls and stuffed animals.  I love Barbie and My Little Pony.

Carinne tried to reach out again after school, but by then I was arrogant and dismissive of absolutely everyone.  Okay, Leah was all that.  She took the wheel, because I was tired.

The crux is that I was Cornelia until I hit twelve.  By that point it had been happening for three years, and I just couldnt take it anymore.  Cornelius couldnt take it anymore.  Of course he couldnt, he was a twelve-year old boy.  And that was when Lia came to the fore.  Lia was an old lady, very wise.  Shes the one that finally helped me to make friends.  Okay, made the body make friends.  Lia was close with a tall girl with flaming red hair, Monica.  Lee met a boy called Marcus, equally shy, equally awkward to her.  Me?  Cornelius and I ended up hanging out more often.  I let the others take the wheel, because I was just tired.

When boys came into the picture I ran like hell.  I hid in the recesses of my mind, hiding from anyone who tried to touch me.  Could you blame me?  Twelve and already severely mentally scarred.  Fucked every other night by the man I considered to be my father, but he just showed how much of a father he wasnt.  He stole my body from me when I was twelve.  He forced his cock into my tiny body, and no matter how much I protested and begged, he didnt stop.  He did it thrice a week in the beginning.

**I'm sorry.  I'm fucking sorry.  What do you want me to do, Cornelia?  I'll do anything to keep you... to keep us safe.  You are my sole reason for existing.  I didn't mean it.  I didn't mean it when I said I didn't want to be your friend.**

At fifteen I was broken.  My father hated me, because I now refused to have contact with him.  I refused to let anyone know just how broken I was.  If anyone got too close, hey had to go.  Monica left.  Carinne left.  Marcus tried to stay.  He really did.  He could get Lee out of her shell, which even I couldnt do.  

**Lee's a sweet kid.  A little high-strung, but sweet.**

When I was sixteen, it was my sisters husband.  A large man  in his forties, massive, his stomach protruding from his body like a balloon.  A disgusting man.  

**Cornelia hates this story.  She isn't strong enough to tell it.  But I am.  That time I, she, would have gone on vacation with my, her, sister and her husband.  Some sisterly bonding time, you know?  Only the fat bastard fucked that up one night by making his advances known.  I, she, screamed and ran.  I, she, ran out of that house, out of that damn fucking city.  They found me... her... us... days later, hiding out in a gas station bathroom.  My, her, mother was the one to find me, and I told her everything.  She believed me.  She wasnt even angry that Id, that we'd, run away.  But I couldnt retaliate.  I couldnt press charges.  I couldnt even talk about it.  Mum said so.   Or Cornelia couldn't retaliate.  She was just a fucking kid and... and this happened?  What did the poor girl ever do to deserve his?**

First daddy, then my brother-in-law.  My sister hadnt spoken to me for years after that, and I honestly resented her.  

This new event didnt deter daddy from sneaking into my room at night.  He choked me, his hands tightening around my neck, and he came inside me.  Multiple times.  And

**I'M SORRY.  I'M SO SO SORRY.  I WISH I HAD BEEN THERE!  I WOULD... WOULD HAVE CUT OFF HIS DICK AND SHOVED IT UP HIS ASS.  I WOULD HAVE KILLED, CORNELIA.  FOR YOU.**

I couldnt tell anyone, could I?  It wasnt one of those scandalous things anymore, but no one would have believed me.  I tried to tell people about it.  The guidance counselor, my teacher

That had been weird.  I, Cornelia, was at the front trying to talk to Mr Ludz about my life.  For the first time since my head was so full of voices, I blacked out.  I knew that people who had these voices in their heads often blacked out, unable to remember where they were or what they did.  But I was aware of everyone.  Lee, Lia, Cornelius.  I knew them all.  I knew us all.  I knew who we were and who was at the front.  Usually Lee, but Lia whenever someone tried to get close to me.

I woke up in bed.  My last memory had been standing in front of Mr Ludz, nervous, about to tell him everything.  I liked Mr Ludz, he was one of the kindest teachers Id ever met.  

The next morning, we walked into his class.  He usually waited for us outside, but this time he didnt.  I was the first to class, the first in the doorway I was the first on the grass too, emptying the contents of my stomach.  I screamed, I knew I did.  For once I was at the front, and now I regretted it.  Someone else should have been at the front.

Mr Ludz sat on his chair  or rather, slumped in his chair.  He was dead.  That much was obvious, because there was a deep gash in his neck, and his pristine white checked shirt was covered in blood.  Blood that had flowed from his neck, down his clothes and dripping on the floor.  I felt euphoric when I first saw it.  Nostalgic, and then nausea washed over my body.  His trousers were open, his brown pants stained with blood.  His dick lay on the floor beside his body.

An investigation was launched.  It was found that Mr Ludz had been handsy with the teenage girls, and threatened them continuously.  It was never found out who killed him, but nobody was sad to see him go after finding out he was a serial rapist.

I was... well, I was broken.  My mind was broken.  If only rape had been all that they'd done to me, I would have been fine.  I would have... I would...

**You would be dead.**
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-07 20:37:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> A very grim game of tag then, isn't it? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-27 11:42:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Nancy Drew woke up my love for reading when I was like 6. Then Harry Potter. But the book I love most in this world is King of Shadows by Susan Cooper. I know it's a typically kiddies or teen book, but I've read it over and over. I'm 23 and I still love it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
