<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject6469</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-20 18:54:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  Now, that footnote: you're 24. So if a 23-year old dude rolled up on you, you could pretty well gauge if he had his shit together. If he was living at home, getting an allowance from his parents and dropped out of community college, you'd know he was some kind of fuck-up, right? How would you know if this dude at 42 has his shit together? What does "normal 42-year-old-adult" look like? How would you judge that? If this dude had the emotional maturity and sophistication of a 25-year-old, how would you know? That's the big risk.

**OP, please listen to this.** Also, read my post history, because I've been in your shoes. 

I thought my much older boyfriend was so smart and sophisticated. Looking back, he was a moron and a loser who couldn't get his act together ... but I couldn't know this back then because I was so young. How was I to judge what success looked like at 37? (I found out later he lied about his age and was even older than that.)

As an older adult now, I can't imagine dating someone even ten years younger than me because as an older person, **I know how vulnerable younger people are.** I understand their good intentions and naivete because I've been there. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-20 18:43:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Please read my post history. I was once in your shoes. Long traumatic story short, it went down like a plane on fire.

An older man seems so amazing and makes you feel worldly, right? Years later, you'll wonder why he wasn't dating women his own age, and you'll suddenly remember all his behavior that in hindsight made him seem really immature. 

Burke's never married and doesn't know if he wants kids. Really? Most people have figured that shit out by their 40s, so I'm leaning toward immature. 

Worst case scenario, he's with you because you're young and easy to control. I would have been so offended if someone said this to me back then, but time would have proved them right. There's a lot of painful truths about life that you refuse to accept when you're young, especially when older people say them, until one day you're older and realize shit, they were right.

You guys are in completely different stages of life. Do you want to go to grad school? Change careers? Travel? Have kids? You're going to do the most of your growth in the next few years. I'm 30 now. You'll be fucking shocked where the next few years take you and how much you've changed. Meanwhile, most people at Burke's age are pretty settled and what you see is what you get. Burke still doesn't know what he wants. What's that tell you about him?

If you're going to upset your parents, make sure it's a hill worth dying on. There are so many problems with dating a man 20 years your senior when you're only 24. Having been in your shoes, I can't say it's worth it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
