<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject2924</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-10 06:12:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Holy shit it may be that actually looks very familiar!!!

Ha well I guess it doesn't look like a rancor after all!

Assuming this is it, thank you so much! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-10 06:10:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I don't quite think that's it </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> I need this for school. Please fill out which of these is the worst. Thank you. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-10 06:09:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-10 05:50:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I don't think it's either of your guys', thanks though. The monster didn't look like bigfoot, and it wasn't scrawny and boney. If I had to think of one monster similar, I'd say the Rancor from Star Wars, but very bright orange and slimy. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-10 05:18:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Sing Street! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Can anyone help me figure out what this movie is called? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-10 05:17:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So, one late night when I was a little kid, the TV was on in my living room, where me, my brother, and my Dad crashed for the night. I remember it being a cheesy 70s-80s horror movie and being terrified by it at that age. I want to watch it again so I can laugh at probably how bad it is.

So what I remember from the movie is that it:

A. Is a horror flick from the 70s-80s. 

B. It has this big orange monster. 

C. I remember it being gore-y, I think. 

D. It took place in some sort of camping site. I think the orange monster came in and started to eat people. 

Thanks!  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-10 05:12:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> How do you see advanced screenings like this? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-10 04:57:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Ay, I gotta pay the bills somehow you know what I'm sayin' </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-10 04:56:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I found it to be a solid movie, but nothing spectacular in any way. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-10 04:54:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If I were I'd be asking for downloads lol. TECHNICALLY if I don't download it, I'm not breaking any laws wink wink nudge nudge </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Does anyone have links to any of the following movies in HD quality for free? (No downloads please) </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-10 04:52:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-09 23:40:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's being re-released in black and white, you should go see it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-09 22:24:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah, I was gonna add it in but it completely slipped my mind


OH WELL </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-09 22:24:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's my favorite as well. Beautiful, isn't it? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-09 19:06:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I found it to be predictable. Right when Ego arrived I was like "Okay he's luring Peter into some sort of trap and he's gonna use him," and then later when he talked about the planet and how it works I was like "And he's gonna use Peter to power it or whatever m'kay." </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What's your favorite film of 2017 so far? (Release Dates are American) </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-09 16:19:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-09 16:11:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The beginning of the second one gave it away lol, I found it to be very predictable. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Should I watch The Fate of the Furious? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-09 16:10:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So I wanna watch The Fate of the Furious, but I haven't seen Furious 7. Do I really need to see it before watching 8? I don't think it will matter that much, but I don't know since I haven't watched eithet 7 or 8 yet. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-06 05:43:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> YUCK </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Guardians of the Galaxy Volume 2 is all right (No spoilers guys) </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-06 05:42:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-05 02:53:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Idk about food stuff, but The Social Network is similar in some aspects to The Founder I believe (Still haven't seen The Founder but from what I know of the true story and saw from the trailers, that's what I inferred) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-05 02:51:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Oh no, it's retarded! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-30 20:01:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What were all the sizes? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
