<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject8607</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Federal Court Grants Spirit Airlines Temporary Restraining Order Compelling Union Pilots to Return to Status Quo </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-10 14:10:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> House Passes A Bill To Cheat Workers Out Of Overtime Pay </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-06 22:26:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-05 00:57:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> They'll just find new, innovative ways to fuck us over, like freemium games and surge pricing </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-04 21:40:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Rage is a great outlet for grief, especially when it's justified. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-04 20:22:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Being a Democrat in one of those states must suck, like being the town witch. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Trump's Cuts to US Refugee Program Lead to 300-plus Layoffs </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-04 20:04:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> "Why The Capitalist Gun Is Inferior" The Black Panther Party, USA, 1970 </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-02 21:00:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> This Is A New Day: Hundreds March In May Day Rally For Immigrant Rights </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-02 20:54:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-02 20:48:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> My point was that a lot of important change actually takes place outside of elections. A true challenge to Trump will come from people organizing together to exert pressure on all parts of the political   economic system, not just the vote.

Gandhi, the person everyone associates "be the change" with, was after all a protester who proved civil disobedience could win the independence of a whole county, no elections required.

The same goes for Nelson Mandela in South Africa, and Martin Luther King Jr. in America. Their lives were proof of what could be accomplished in spite of elections, not through them.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-02 19:53:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If you want until 2018 to do something, you're toast </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> McDonalds to offer fixed hours contracts for all its 115,000 UK employees </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-02 19:46:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> May Day rallying cry: 'People united will never be defeated' </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-02 19:43:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> UPS air maintenance workers threaten strike ahead of shareholders meeting </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-02 10:16:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> "May Day" USSR, 1963 </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-01 22:56:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Thousands of people in US rally against Trump, for workers </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-01 22:49:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Man Attacked Students In a College Coffee Shop With A Machete According To Their Political Affiliations </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-01 18:22:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-01 08:56:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Translate  and  separately, or add a comma there to help Google read it better. It becomes "For the revolution, exercise" -  i.e. "Exercise for the revolution". </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> "Exercise For The Revolution" China, 1975 </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-30 22:11:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> "Cursed is the man who integrates"  White Christians protest racial integration in New Orleans, 1960 [1200x780] </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-30 20:01:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Justice Department Says No To Funding Vote On Puerto Rican Statehood </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-30 19:41:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-30 17:19:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> www.nasdaq.com/symbol/t/financials?query=income-statement </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-30 17:12:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  a strong-arming union

Oh, no! The power to negotiate better pay and better healthcare! What literally every human wants for themselves and their children! Terrible!  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-30 17:09:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Average inflation rate in 2016 was 1.3%, 0.1% in 2015. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-30 16:34:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> By that logic, *your* annual bonuses, raises, and benefits *also* raise our prices - and that happens a lot more often than strikes. Would you like to forego your raises for the next five years? AT T made $86.9 billion in profit in 2016, up from $79.7 billion in 2015 - they can afford to cushion a wage / benefit increase. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-30 15:49:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> No it's not  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-30 15:47:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> 1. "Some petty bourgeois journalist" isn't organizing the strikes and demonstrations tomorrow.

2. You're not the only worker who's ever risked their job for a strike, or been asked to do so.

3. [There are practical ways to demonstrate solidarity](https://www.thenation.com/article/how-to-join-the-day-without-immigrants-on-may-day/) apart from leaving work yourself, that don't involve undermining other people's calls to action. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> "May Day" Australia, 1986 </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-30 15:00:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> This May Day, Dont Go to Work, Take to the Streets and Strike </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-30 14:51:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> 21,000 AT T workers poised for Monday strike </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-30 14:42:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Illinois House approves public funding for abortions </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-30 00:14:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-29 22:21:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  Not sure why it's a pity. You serve the country and in return get citizenship that you earned. I mean, it definitely should be easier to gain it through other means but I have no disregard for anyone who wants to serve a country they're tying to get citizenship to.

Most Americans don't earn their citizenship, they just get born. That alone shows how arbitrary so much moralizing over citizenship is. The forgotten fact is this country was founded in the first place on the basis of *human* rights: "We hold these Truths to be self-evident, that all Men are created equal, that they are endowed by their Creator with certain unalienable Rights" - but I *never* said people shouldn't pursue whatever opportunities they have in front of them.

 As far as higher education, it's more of a fault with the bureaucratic nature of applying for and receiving grants, scholarships, etc. This is a lot more of a fault with the governments stance on education and the schools who charge ridiculous amounts of money to attend.


I never blamed the military for any of this. These are just the conditions that help make military service so appealing, and why high school is a better time to recruit vs. in college. Economic location matters, too. My well-to-do suburban high school had zero recruitment presence. The overwhelmingly immigrant urban high school I taught at had a whole calendar full of events from every branch.

 I came from a low to middle class family and joined just to join and serve. I've been in for over 10 years and have yet to use TA or my GI Bill for college because I instead have worked to starting a small business. The military definitely taught me the responsibility and character in order to take those steps where I never would have if I didn't join.

"When the contemporary man steps from the street, of clamorous insincere advertisement, push, adulteration, underselling and intermittent employment into the barrack-yard, he steps on to a higher social plane, into an atmosphere of service and cooperation and of infinitely more honorable emulations. Here at least men are not flung out of employment to degenerate because there is no immediate work for them to do. They are fed a drilled and training for better services. Here at least a man is supposed to win promotion by self-forgetfulness and not by self-seeking." </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-29 21:40:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> MVP right here </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-29 21:39:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Rally

Against

T...heresa May </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-29 21:38:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Probably some centrist liberals who chickened out at the last minute and said "we don't want to get put on a list."  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> 'We Reject Politics of Fear': Groups Urge Congress to Build Schools, Not Wall </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-29 20:01:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-29 19:46:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's more of a pity that military service is the only secure path to citizenship and/or higher education in poor, working-class communities. There's nothing glorious about that, and trying to rose-tint the reasons why people join the military does nobody any service. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> "Attention All Whiggers And Mixers" USA, 2011(?) </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-29 18:04:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-29 18:04:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The rationale for invading Afghanistan was that the Taliban government sheltered Al-Qaeda, who carried out the 9/11 attacks under the direction of Osama bin Laden. But the Taliban were only in power there because the U.S. government spent billions of dollars arming religious radicals (i.e. mujahideen) to overthrow the secular Afghan government in the 1980s. [That's called blowback.](https://www.thenation.com/article/blowback/) And then it took even more money and a whole decade to actually get Bin Laden, who was actually hiding in Pakistan. And we're still in Afghanistan today, even though we also overthrew the Taliban. None of it had to do with being "free". </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-29 17:49:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The military also actively recruits within high schools, and did you know none of those kids have college degrees? But with servicemember benefits, they might be able to afford one. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-29 06:21:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thousands of Americans went to Iraq because college doesn't pay for itself - *America* went to Iraq because it had nothing to do with 9/11. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-29 06:19:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If non citizens could vote, veterans would not get deported. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-29 04:12:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Imagine being in a shittier timeline where that hasn't happened </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Newest Trump order targets Obamas marine sanctuaries for possible oil drilling </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-29 04:09:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-29 03:55:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  **Service Guarantees Citizenship!**[*](http://www.npr.org/2016/01/13/462372040/service-members-not-citizens-meet-the-veterans-who-have-been-deported) 

 [Would you like to know more?](http://media.defense.gov/2011/Sep/20/174740/-1/-1/0/110920-M-0000F-009.jpg) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> "And how will your children honor your efforts and teachings?" USA, 2010 </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-28 23:26:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> J-15's on the deck of the Liaoning [4000x2666] </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-28 23:11:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> "Rally Against Thatcher" Australia, 1988 </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-28 21:25:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> "Come Out, Ye Black And Tans" Ireland, 1920s </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-28 06:57:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-27 20:06:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I don't know where this was published exactly, but John Groth drew cartoons for *The New Yorker* and *The New Republic* magazines, which cater mostly to capitalist liberals. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Shenyang J-11 in a live-fire exercise [930x634] </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-27 18:15:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> "South America Under The Axis" USA, 1938 </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-27 17:59:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-25 20:48:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> in other news, society is unequal. gasp! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Facebook won't penalize staff taking part in May 1 political protests </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-25 20:46:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-25 20:32:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> lol </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Retired NYPD Lieutenant, Cops and Ex-Brooklyn Assistant District Attorney Allegedly Traded Fast Gun Permits for Booze, Strippers, Trips </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-25 20:28:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> NYPD cops accepted strippers for expedited gun permits </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-25 20:25:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-25 13:47:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Sad but true. Trump constantly mocked his older brother for being a commercial pilot instead of a businessman and called him a "bus driver in the sky". His brother later drank himself to death and Donald wrote all of his kids out of their grandfather's will. They had to sue him for their inheritance. Just one of his many classy lawsuits. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-25 13:42:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  "The intention of the article was to inform the public about where the President has been hosting world leaders. We regret any misperception and have removed the post."

Vomit. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-25 13:38:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Then read this: http://www.salon.com/2017/04/25/the-democrats-hypocrisy-fest-disingenuous-attacks-on-bernie-sanders-persist-and-his-popularity-climbs/

And then this: https://www.jacobinmag.com/2016/03/bernie-sanders-whites-race-voters-primary/

Sincerely, not a white person </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-25 13:08:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Trump's latest bankruptcy: America.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-25 13:06:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> (Also Trump's army secretary pick thinks trans people are an evil that needs to be crushed, nbd) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-25 13:01:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Money and gullibility. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-25 13:00:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> "Pres. Trump has taken bold steps to clean the bathroom by shitting in the toilet, on the second try." </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-24 16:20:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  ~~blasts~~ bawls </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Restaurants need to stop treating low-wage workers like avocados </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-24 16:19:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-24 16:10:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Weapons. Grade. Idiot. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-24 16:09:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [The whole fucking network is full of sleazeball creeps in need of a societal restraining order.](https://youtu.be/nlddDLeUyXs) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-24 16:07:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> ...no, it's not </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-24 16:04:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> "controversial" </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Illinois Democrats aim high with minimum wage proposals </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-24 16:03:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-24 07:25:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> John Kasich: Complains about cultural erosion, cuts school budgets for half of Ohio.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-24 07:19:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> He's a troll jerking another off.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-24 07:17:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Half of South Korea supports negotiations with North Korea. You're talking out of your ass.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-24 07:15:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Least of all the South Koreans. Any American who thinks we should take out the North Korean government should move next door first. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-24 07:11:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> One solution: revolution </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-24 07:05:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The biggest joke in America </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-24 07:05:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Kasich is on the way out </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-24 07:03:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Poor Donald Trump: Too much of a Nazi for the normal public and not Nazi enough for his fringe base of support. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-23 22:53:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> *Firearm Deaths in 2015:*

Alabama: 958 (19.6 / 100k)

New York: 849 (4.2 / 100k)

*Homicides in 2015:*

Alabama: 348 (7.2 / 100k)

New York: 609 (3.1 / 100k)

Jeff Sessions can't even take care of his own state and he's complaining about others. Throwing rocks from a glass house. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-23 22:13:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> But Republicans *always* win 1000% of the popular vote, just like Trump !!! /s </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-23 22:10:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> "Town halls should be a safe space for like-minded people to ignore the rest of their community!!!" - ~~zombies~~ Republicans </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Protesters Chain Themselves To Bakery Truck In Solidarity With Immigrant Workers </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-23 21:56:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Jeff Sessionss Crime Rhetoric Aimed At New York City Drips With Hypocrisy </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-23 21:48:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Protesters Chain Themselves To Bakery Truck In Solidarity With Immigrant Workers </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-23 21:37:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-23 01:46:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Not everyone on the list is an economist by trade, but they all have a background in economics or economic policy. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-23 01:25:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> https://berniesanders.com/wp-content/uploads/2016/01/Wall-St-Letter-1.pdf </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-23 01:15:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Won't someone think of the billionaires! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-23 01:09:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The Central Park Five </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-23 01:08:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If you put them in the same room you'd throw away the key. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
