<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject1402</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Next Week Adidas Releases A New Running Shoe Made From Ocean Plastic </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-10 15:01:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Even your sea salt is almost certainly contaminated with plastic... (although in very small amounts) </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-09 19:09:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The Technology Divide is growing - let's not leave people behind. Be the change. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-09 15:30:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The technology divide is growing - let's not leave people behind! How can we help tackle the digital divide together? Be the change! </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-09 14:49:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> These Flowers Hold Clues to Spreading Life Beyond Earth </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-09 12:10:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Millions in Donations Allow Ocean Cleanup to Tackle Great Pacific Garbage Patch </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-08 13:31:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-08 04:33:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Although to be fair it's mostly an issue with tap water in rural areas with less than 500 people per water supply. Does anyone live in an area like this? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Think your tap water is perfectly safe? Think again </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-07 22:48:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-07 11:32:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Because plastic is basically killing our soil, ground water, lakes, rivers and oceans at the moment. We will soon not be able to eat fish anymore. This is NOT sustainable. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-06 09:41:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Like the other people here have said there are plenty of jobs for you and salaries for mid (5+ years) and senior (10+ years) of working experience have gone up substantially. You can pick and choose and live a very comfortable life. There are also plenty of freelance jobs. In addition to startups look at companies such as Nestle, Bayer, Softonic, eDreams, DMI, etc that are all looking for people. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> It's time to stand up to the plastic bottled water industry. Be the change! </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-05 19:37:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-04 02:58:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Sorry about this. Unfortunately you will have to return to Barcelona to finalise the police report. Good justification for another holiday trip?

Barcelona is the capital of pick pocketing in Europe. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-04 02:53:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> While living in SF and shopping at Costco I always ended up buying twice as much as I needed and throwing away half of the food. But yes, cheap and good quality food and beverages.

Now I prefer small box goods. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Bottled water is a scam for most Americans  but a new report reveals some surprising places where it's dangerous to drink the tap </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-03 20:42:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
