<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject1055</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-10 16:33:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> All really good points definitely and hadn't crossed my mind watching it.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-10 15:29:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It became messed up after the fact, when First Class/DOFP retconned how characters met and changed everything. I'm just thinking in relation to the other two in the original trilogy. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Why do people hate X-Men: The Last Stand again? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-10 15:26:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> On break for a couple weeks and decided to watch the X-Men movies again starting with First Class, was prepared to skip through most of X3 because though I enjoyed it when ti came out (I was 9 I think) I knew its reputation hadn't aged well at all. But honestly after 1 and 2 I'm struggling to see what's so awful (shitty young Patrick Stewart CGI notwithstanding). Professor X's death was really emotional and well done imo, and the action and cinematography is top notch. It's definitely cheesy with the whole Iceman/Pyro faceoff sort of stuff throughout the movie, but everything else about it seems like it makes up a perfectly good conclusion to the original trilogy to me. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-10 05:35:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> this shit is Tom Clancy on steroids with a bit of House of Cards thrown in for good measure </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-10 05:33:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Genuinely. If C-Span or whoever somehow obtained rights to be the sole bearer of that debate and charged a $500 rate for each debate I'd fucking happily pay it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-10 05:26:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> leaked footage https://68.media.tumblr.com/878ecca62f08ad314f9fe7d3e0305e2e/tumblr_mpxte3St5q1qm8jbeo2_500.gif </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-10 05:25:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That Dana woman who's been on and off CNN all night must be getting a bit tired of expressing her shock at how the WH is surprised at the blowback from Dems. 

"Anderson I just couldn't believe it I mean wow"
"Don I just wow it was weird"
"yes Jake it was weird I guess idk can i go home please </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-10 05:22:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What are major world leaders thinking as they're finding out about this fucking shitshow? What must Angela Merkel, Trudeau, even Macron be thinking? what an embarrassment. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-10 05:19:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Assuming Trump makes it to 2020, a debate between Trump and candidate Warren ('pocahontas') could be potentially biblical.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-10 05:18:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah I think people forget how comic-book-villain like Putin truly is. Dude's evil and probably loving all this. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-10 05:10:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Ah yes, Jake Tapper here to sooth us all with his calm but confident analysis. i know that probably sounds sarcastic but its not pls never leave us Jake </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-10 05:07:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> ughgghghhhHHHHHHHH </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-10 05:01:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> how the hell does that motherfucker sleep at night </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-10 05:00:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You can't be serious?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-10 04:42:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Ah well, at least we'll get his reaction soon enough. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-10 04:42:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Really? That's awesome to hear, can't wait for that! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-10 04:34:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'd say Seth Meyers is sneaking his way in there now. The Closer Look segments are great. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-10 04:32:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Damn, Colbert had Jon Stewart and John Oliver on tonight. I assume it was taped well before all this came out, which is sad if it's the case because seeing all three of them talk about it would be something.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-10 04:18:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> hot take </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-10 04:13:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> They gotta fill the time with repetitive conversation until Trump/Comey/Spicer/whoever makes a statement or any new info comes out.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-10 04:11:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I think there'd probably be a parade in the honor of anyone that did that. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-10 04:10:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I just mean Jeff Lord as a person and his demeanor, not the fact he's pro-Trump. They should have opposing views but from people who are not Jeff Lord, imo. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-10 03:57:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> ugghh Jeffrey Lord. There are many pro-Trump conservatives who aren't as hated by the majority of the public and as generally fucking annoying as Jeffrey Lord is. Why do they continue to have him on? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-10 03:47:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Can we all just take a second to appreciate this masterful eyeroll from Anderson Cooper.  https://twitter.com/OfficialMisterC/status/862116127870156802 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-10 03:38:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This is unprecedented, but it's not like it's never happened before. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-10 03:23:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> "You can do the right thing for the wrong reason, in the wrong way, at the wrong place and time" Van Jones nails it </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-10 03:09:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Because she just won't come on again. You hear all the time about how one somewhat antagonistic interview will make someone like Kellyanne or any political figure never appear on that show ever again, or with that interviewer. If I remember correctly Obama wouldn't do any with Jake Tapper after an interview about the BP oil spill. So Anderson and others have to just find the balance between calling her on her shit but not so much that she won't come on again. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-10 03:05:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> "Anderson, I'll just ignore how unkind that is :(("

Anderson Cooper's little smirk at Kellyanne's bullshit in that moment made my night. How he kept his composure during that interview I'll never know.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-10 02:22:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Anyone watching CNN coverage? That fucking Trump wannabe who was on about an hour ago with the shitty goatee defending this shitshow deserves a slap. ufghidjfng </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-10 02:06:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Coming out now that he may still testify before Senate Committee in a closed session over next couple of days, but not sure how anything coming out of that closed session can be trusted. 

The last few months have made it hard to trust any Sessions...

(I'll show myself out) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-10 01:57:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Is it unreasonable to think that Comey now has cause to drop serious shit on Russiagate/Trump in general? I mean he doesn't have to worry about job security anymore and surely won't be eager to defend Trump's reputation. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-10 01:05:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Just about sums it up. https://twitter.com/Snowden/status/862069019301601281 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-10 01:04:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Last week: Wow that House of Cards season 5 trailer is awesome! Just when everyone thought they couldn't get crazier than the Trump administration, they drop that and reassure everyone, can't wait!!

Right now: nope House of Cards just lost its crazier status </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-10 01:03:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> No. Comey thought Clinton would win, like just about everybody else including Trump and his campaign, so decided to release the letter to save his own ass in case it comes out that he 'concealed'. Anyone thinking he was trying to just aid Trump is ignorant. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-10 01:02:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> muhh god-emperor </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-10 01:02:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The opinion seems to be that he made a stupid mistake in November when he, like everyone else, probably thought Clinton would win and decided to release the letter to save his ass in case it came out he 'concealed' or whatever. But nevertheless it was known he was making efforts to investigate Trump and that Trump didn't like that. So this is no reason for Dems to be happy, unless you count the fact that it'll probably speed up the impeachment hearings tenfold. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-10 00:58:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> 'tax-payer funded charade', the irony is actually painful. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-10 00:57:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Can't be said enough. Even if a Dem presidential candidate wins a landslide in 2020, they won't be able to do shit if the Senate and House looks like it does now. People need to fucking vote their asses off next year. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-10 00:56:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> this just in: America still burning to the fucking ground. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-10 00:56:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Jesus, come on. The political contexts of the two times couldn't get much different. Back then the pleas for firing him were for breaking the rule of interfering in an election (debatable whether he did), now the most obvious case for firing him seems to be that he was about to drop a bomb about Russiagate.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-10 00:54:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> How did the letter from Trump leak so quickly? Or are these sorts of letters always publicly released almost instantly? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-10 00:53:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> How did this leak so quickly? Or are these sorts of letters always publicly released almost instantly? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-10 00:52:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Best comment I've seen all week. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-10 00:49:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If ever we needed that Russian golden shower tape, it's now.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-10 00:44:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Somewhere, the person who'll be in charge of making ads for the 2020 Dem Presidential candidate is shrieking with glee. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-10 00:43:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Haha, you're exactly right. US politics for the last year has been stranger than fiction </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-10 00:42:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> God, I hope so. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-10 00:39:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm in Ireland and I am bursting to talk to someone about this but no one I know really gives a shit about what's going on over there, even on this level. but jESUS CHRIST THIS IS FUCKING INSANE </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-09 13:29:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's so infuriating when he smiles and laughs through answers on incredibly serious topics, he's trying to hide how awful his answer is with his idea of 'charm' and making it light hearted. It's even worse when reporters play along with it. Fuck sake. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-09 13:26:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I didn't even realize he used to be so far along the balding process or that he had work done at all, wherever he got that hair transplant did a pretty fantastic job.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-09 12:31:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Source on this info? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-09 02:13:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I find it weird that so many people are discounting any performance from Jared Leto just because of his Joker in that shitty Suicide Squad movie, or even his general douchiness or whatever idea people seem to have of him. He won an Academy Award for Dallas Buyers Club and gave incredible performances in Requiem for a Dream and Mr. Nobody, so I think he at least deserves the benefit of the doubt when it comes to Blade Runner or anything else in future. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-08 17:59:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Been reading that a lot on their videos. I wonder if they knew that when they picked the name and it's sort of a joke, if not it's a fairly unfortunate coincidence.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> MUNA - Crying On The Bathroom Floor [electro-pop, dark electro, alternative pop] </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-07 20:41:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-07 20:38:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> One of the top posts there about the election is one calling Macron a huge cuck because his wife is 15+ years older and it's not a traditional relationship. But Trump marry a twenty something model when he was already middle aged (and twice divorced) is completely cool because he's the 'god-emperor'. I don't know why I still check it sometimes, it's fucking infuriating. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-06 11:57:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Alright. I think you're assuming a lot about the way I think about money and happiness and life, and I think you're coming off a bit condescending, and taking my comments a bit seriously. The fact that I'm a bit put off that someone can make so much money from doing what Meg or Jessica Nigri or whoever does does not mean that I view money as the be all and end all to life and 'if only I could make that much money I'd finally be happy!'. It'd be nice, and easier if I made more money, but god, I know it's not everything and I don't need someone on a subreddit for looking at pictures of a hot girl to teach me that lesson. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-06 03:11:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Jon Batiste and Stay Human add so much charm to the show too. Jon can get a little annoying with his adlibs during Stephens monologue but the little piano hits he does during it are awesome and the band is amazing.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-06 00:18:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I agree with your sentiment but I don't think comparing the extremely few people who are so talented that they can become well off from sport to cosplayers who make their living on Patreon is accurate. I appreciate the comment, but the life lesson isn't necessary. I'm not stewing in jealousy at all - just making an observation and a bit annoyed, but thanks. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-05 23:22:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I really try to avoid hating on people like Meg who have patreons that rake in 20k+ a month for things like cosplay. But god, that is so much more money than most of us will make doing regular jobs, or most jobs at all, and when it isn't clear where exactly it's going besides making her rich for making costumes and doing photoshoots, it's hard not to be bitter about it.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-28 19:34:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yup. He's the dog that caught the car.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-24 23:43:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Wouldn't have really thought Coster-Waldau would be on that list, his character doesn't get as much attention as the earlier seasons. (or maybe he is and his story just got a bit less interesting so it feels that way) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-24 23:41:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hopefully they'll go with some better projects than they have already, Kit Harrington's been in a few failed action movies and Emilia Clarke with Terminator. also Dinklage with Pixels, dear god </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-24 15:47:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> No, Richard E. Grant doesn't drink. He's well known for being able to play a very convincing drunk while not actually being a drinker himself. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-22 06:15:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I bet you're real fun at parties.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> :D </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-21 20:02:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-18 06:30:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah I definitely found that odd. Like I would've thought the baby would sort of have the same complexion as Charlie maybe? Definitely no way the baby would really look that way but I guess it's just a minor thing.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-18 04:17:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It is just a show but 6 seasons and however many episodes builds quite an emotional connection to these characters and investment in their growth so there's real disappointment there when the characters act a certain way, at least for me. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Is anyone else disappointed that the final episode portrayed Hannah at her most frustrating and insufferable, even if the idea was that she's be redeemed in the end? (just need to vent somewhere) </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-18 02:09:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I love this show, and liked that the finale was different and understated. I really hoped I'd finish the series with a better opinion of Hannah and feeling like her good qualities would ultimately outweigh the flaws, but the flaws were pushed so far this episode that I finished the series just feeling angry at her and yet again frustrated that she can't see how awful she is, and that's disappointing.

I know that the point was to show that Hannah still has a lot of maturing to do, and the final scene to show that she's on her way to that, but how many times has this arc played out? Not on the scale of maturing into being a responsible mother, but generally maturing, realising that her problems aren't the end of the world. i.e. Becoming friendly with Mimi-Rose in the end after resenting her so much, or realising how narcissistic she really is and what she really wants in life after the two day escape with Joshua. After all these arcs play out she seems to never ultimately change in any meaningful way. I feel like the Hannah we saw tonight could have been the Hannah from season 1. If she'd gotten pregnant in episode 5 and this had been the first episode of Season 2, I don't think anyone would complain that her character has suddenly dramatically changed for no reason.

I don't think I've ever been more angry at Hannah before than when she was acting horrible to Marnie and her mother. Marnie was annoying as hell with the singing and condescending advice at times, but Hannah was acting more like a child than we've seen in a long time, and she should be willing to put up with Marnie's worst quirks considering she's basically provided her child with a second mother. Hannah telling Marnie "You're suck at this, you're doing a bad job" made me so genuinely annoyed and I hoped Marnie would push back more. Marnie's done incredibly self serving and selfish things in the past seasons but deciding to help raise Grover is not one of them, so it didn't feel good at all to see her be told off by an incredibly ungrateful Hannah here. When the three of them were sitting on the porch at the end, I felt like the idea was that the viewer would feel good that they're together again, and putting their spats behind them, but all I wanted was for Loreen and Marnie to tell Hannah off for her behaviour and how hurtful she was to the two of them. She shouldn't have been able to just sit there between them as if she didn't say those things, and letting her get away with it without any consequences will only perpetuate those sorts of hurtful outbursts in future. How many times is this show going to have the whole conversation of Hannah's false victim complex ultimately losing out to her good side, only to be reset again?

**Hannah**: I'm in pain! My life is so hard, can't you see?

**Other person (Adam, Noreen, Shosh)**: You're not the only one with problems, get out of your own head and into the real world where everyone's suffering!

How many times is a conversation like this going to play out only for Hannah to seemingly get worse a few episodes down the line?
Ultimately, the finale left me feeling like Hannah is at her core a selfish, nearly irredeemably narcissistic person who has shown good qualities coming through that personality at certain times throughout the series in spite of that, and not a good person who's shown narcissistic and unlikable qualities at certain times throughout the series, as I hoped she'd be. But I also know that I could be being unreasonable and missing the point, and maybe no one else left with this feeling, and that's ok too. I'll miss the show either way. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-16 00:22:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> On the most basic level, I could definitely imagine sitting down and having a beer and a conversation with W. Bush and liking the guy as a person. The idea of trying to do the same thing with Trump sounds horrible and I'd probably want to off myself out of frustration after 5 minutes. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-14 22:20:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The irony is just painful. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-14 22:05:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> True but I meant more about trilogies in general i.e. Temple of Doom, Two Towers, The Dark Knight. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-14 18:05:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> 1:18 The AT-ATs in the distance. Ominous as fuck.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-14 18:02:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Looks like they're pushing the whole 'middle film of the trilogy being the darkest one' thing to the absolute max this time. Can't wait. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-13 20:47:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> There's no way that that sentence was typed without the intention of tricking readers into thinking that the 11 meant 11 kilo-tonnes. So damn annoying. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-12 03:01:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'd definitely argue that she has more of a gift for spinning Trump's garbage into shinier garbage than pretty much anyone else we've seen speak for him, so I think she'd do a better job (bowling green gaff notwithstanding). But obviously if the goal is to worsen Trump and his administration's image then Spicer is by far the best candidate it seems.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-12 02:57:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I don't think she's evil, just let herself sunk much lower than most people would.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-12 02:52:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> As someone who knows next to nothing about the inner workings of an administration, how far fetched would it be for Kellyanne Conway to be asked to replace Spicer as presssec? I mean I'd assumed before inauguration that she was a shoe in and clearly she has a gift for using language to spin ridiculous things into far less ridiculous things. More so than Spicer, anyway.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> With Halfnoise </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-10 18:46:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Can anyone identify the piece Eric Lewis is playing here at a performance at the White House? (at 2:35) </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-10 18:41:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-10 03:04:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's at 2:35 in case the time stamp doesn't work. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Can anyone identify the piece Eric Lewis is playing here at a performance at the White House? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-10 03:04:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-30 17:54:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Honestly, from everything I've heard it's painfully boring for 80% of it and I don't feel like sitting through that just because I enjoyed the other series. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Been out of the RT loop for quite a while now - what are some of the best podcast episodes from 300 on? (and other general highlights if anyone cares to share) </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-30 06:26:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-29 21:33:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Damn. Thanks! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> As someone who doesn't care about spoilers and just wants to watch the highlights of Iron Fist; do any of the other Defenders appear in any of the episodes? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-29 21:06:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-26 01:30:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I only learned about that recently from a Claire Danes fight scene in Homeland. good stuff. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-24 02:42:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Ohh ok, I didn't. Hadn't listened to that since it came out and the way they released this seemed more like a 'first single' sort of release. Ah well </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-24 00:26:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Was kind of hoping they'd change up their sound a little more for this one, maybe a more Architects/dark electro djenty sort of route. It's still cool but doesn't really sound like anything new for them or the genre in my opinion, but not everything has to be game changing and this is definitely pretty solid. (but my god that chorus chord progression has been beaten to absolute death) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
