<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject2622</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-09 21:41:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Who the fuck wants to bend down for food? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-07 04:05:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I've seen it. I've lived it. Maybe I have a somewhat unique perspective on it, but I feel like bringing down pedophiles would always be a good day. Especially on this scale.
You do wish it didn't exist. But it does. I sometimes feel bad for the people that don't realize how big this problem is. Not to mention the idea that these aren't just solo actors, they have communities and support systems to help them commit atrocities! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-06 20:08:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Times like this I wish I had gone into law enforcement. I can't imagine how satisfying the job must feel on a day like this. 
Flip side of that coin, I have a lot of respect for the people that have to deal with the evidence... it can't be easy to see all those children being abused.

The fuck is with the downvotes?! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-03 12:54:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Not that I'm with the CIA or anything...
But would you say you've gotten into bed with Isis?
Speak clearly into this tape recorder please. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-01 02:24:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm an open book. Ask away! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-30 07:31:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Not gonna do that, because she has OCD and plucks them nonstop. We're working on that together.
But thanks for being a cunt. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-30 07:03:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I believe it was a lost bet with my older brother. I ended up keeping it for the entire school year though. I went through a few different color combos in that time.  I met a lot of people that only approached me to ask about it or ask for a picture. I'm still friends with a couple of them. It was definitely an interesting year, and I don't regret it at all.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-30 06:39:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This is me. It's my 9th grade yearbook photo.
I originally posted it under WTF 3 or 4 years ago. After my post got the front page, awkwardfamilyphotos.com contacted me about purchasing the rights to it.

Here's a current picture of me and my fianc rocking purple hair. http://imgur.com/U0Dp4R0 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-30 06:15:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Also, I sold the merchandising rights to awkwardfamilyphotos.com for $150 after my original post hit the front page. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-30 06:13:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I commented on the post with a link to a current pic of me and my fianc rocking purple hair. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-30 06:06:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I posted it originally? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-30 05:21:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> u/RedOrangeYellowGreen
This is me.

Here's a current picture of me and my fianc rocking purple hair. 
http://imgur.com/U0Dp4R0 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-30 05:19:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm probably better looking than you. :) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-30 04:14:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Brian! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-30 03:57:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> 12 years ago, I was. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-02-19 02:50:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I personally said "What the fuck?!"
But funny seemed more appropriate.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> My sister just found out she is pregnant so my mom bought her a book of baby names... </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-02-19 02:36:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-01-22 08:32:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Just because It's spot on doesn't mean I have to agree with it. The fact that it was posted under /r/funny and not /r/sexism or another more serious subreddit, should be a huge clue that it was satirical. I've only ever heard this analogy used as a joke. Unlike most people, I don't take myself too seriously. I find humor in everything because white males are the most difficult people in the world to offend.

Since we're getting serious though... Stereotypes are in place for a reason. As outdated as those reasons may be, they still existed.  Males are supposed to try to fuck anything that moves. Females, however, are supposed to have strong filtering mechanisms to weed out the unfit males. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-01-22 07:56:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Absolutely not! 
It's a spot on reference to society's view as a whole.
I lost my virginity at 21 to a girl that had no interest in being with me, she just wanted to take it. I made the decision to do it thinking it would be more, it wasn't.  I've been in a relationship with both the girls I've had sex with since then and am currently engaged to the last one.  I've never had the desire to just fuck as much as I can, and I've never held peoples past against them... Turns out I should have with the first one. 

You don't know me and I don't know you, but I'm only now making the assertion that you're a condescending fuck. Whereas you judged me for making a relevant, accurate, yet satirical statement on a post labeled "funny".

Cheers </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-01-22 07:39:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's fucking spot on.  And that's my fault? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-01-22 03:54:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Dammit... I like yours better. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-01-22 03:16:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If you have a key that opens many locks, it is a master key.

If you have a lock that is opened by many keys, well, that's just a shitty lock.

*EDIT* Really? No only is this funny, it perfectly encompasses how society views promiscuity among males (who are applauded for their conquests) and females (who become viewed as easy or less desirable).  If you feel the need to downvote this, you've got some issues to overcome. There was zero judgment in my comment, just a statement relevant to the original post. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-11-23 16:52:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> First glance, I thought the duck was mercilessly devouring a poor defenseless owl... Though I've been wrong before.
  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-11-23 02:42:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I can't think of one. Someone do me! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-11-23 01:38:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Not sure why, but for the last 5 years or so I've started a campaign on or around Thanksgiving...

This year I can't find my copy anywhere. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-11-22 13:27:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> He looks kind of like Aaron Paul </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-11-22 13:20:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You have just legitimized the phrase "Old as shit" </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-11-22 13:11:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thank you, kind citizen. I am but a man. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-11-22 05:56:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Making dildo clones of my dick for her friends... to commemorate our threesomes. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-11-19 01:01:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [Reminds me of this.](http://www.youtube.com/watch?v=xxPENnSuNQw) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-11-16 02:55:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Robbie? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-11-15 19:49:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah, actually this sub is for pictures. My picture qualifies. A lot more than most if not all engagement rings. So if you don't like it, why did you click it? You could easily have scrolled past to the next picture. 

You know what? I actually feel bad for you. Did you turn to drugs and alcohol after a failed marriage? or did your marriage fail because of them?
Either way, take a good look in the mirror. Re-evaluate yourself, because you're kind of a douche.  Best of luck to you finding your own happiness. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-11-14 21:51:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Its a picture. Where the fuck else am I supposed to put it? Every subreddit has rules. Some subs tell you to go elsewhere and they point you to a sub that points you back to the one that sent you there in the first place. EVERY picture is uninteresting if you dont know what the hell the is going on in it. Is it too much to ask that you just take it for what it is? Im not asking you to be happy or congratulate me, just realize that the ring in that picture is more than just that. It's something you dont see every day that you will see less and less of as time goes on. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-11-14 21:25:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Whats that? A redditor had something awesome hapoen that he wanted to share?

He must be lying! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-11-14 14:02:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thank you very much. I knew right away that it was the perfect choice. Nothing could come close to how much this will mean to her. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-11-14 13:59:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> After looking at rings the other night, I came home more confused about what I wanted than when I began. 

I sat down to discuss a ring with my dad and he did one of the greatest things he has ever done for me...  He offered me his grandmother's ring.  This ring has been a part of 80+ years of successful marriage.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> It may not be the newest or the prettiest, but soon I'll use it to ask her to marry me. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-11-14 13:54:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-11-14 13:15:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> He used his legs! You all saw it! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-11-14 09:55:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Nice try, Ollie North! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-11-13 20:48:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> "Milk's done that body good!"

(Hoping that your comment was a Rookie of the Year reference also) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-11-11 05:52:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I live in Jefferson County, near DuBois. This is a terrible area for idiots with guns. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-11-11 05:50:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> PA has an EXTREMELY limited elk season. They draw a lottery to decide who gets the licenses because there are so few and they are only in one area.. And yes, I would think the rule is dawn-dusk everywhere. I'm an avid hunter. People disgust me. I'm not sure if the kids up your way have picked up what they call "critter beating", but it's when teenagers decide it's fun to drive around at night and kill and/or torture small animals...  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-11-09 12:51:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This is in PA!?

I'm surprised some asshole hasn't drove up and shot it yet... Since apparently it's ok to do that. We have elk where I live and someone recently shot a 5x5 bull in someones front yard at like 2am. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-11-09 03:55:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Cool beans man, I live by Pittsburgh, we should hang out by Pittsburgh sometime and throw THINGS down there.
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-11-07 10:08:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Also not true. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-11-07 02:55:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Not true. You can also get pulled over for travelling at unsafely slow speeds. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-11-01 07:45:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [When did THAT happen?](http://images.wikia.com/simpsons/images/6/6c/MoePickleEgg.png) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> I finally put together my Steampunk costume. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-11-01 05:22:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-10-31 20:37:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> And Cobie Smulders above her. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-09-27 21:32:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This is not my story.

I received so many likes on my own page after sharing my kittens little story that I decided to share it on here as well. 

When we got my little kitten Kimba, her eyes were barely open. She was probably only about two weeks old; with an extremely low chance of survival. Josh and I tried everything we could to keep her healthy in her extremely young age. He would spend hours helping me feed her milk and egg protein through a syringe. When she got a little less wobbly on the legs he spent time playing with her and when she was tuckered out from that or it was one of those blistering cold Pennsylvania winter nights he would cuddle up on the floor with her until she felt comfortable enough to sleep. When she got a little bit older we had to start taking her to the vet; something that was defiantly not on Kimbas list of favorites. Josh would always drive me there with her when he could. Shed be terrified but after a while would come out of her crate and go straight to his lap, hed always tease me that he must have smelled better than I did to her. 

I could tell she really had taken a liking to him, his shoes automatically become her favorite thing to stick her head in when he came over and I noticed she would only sleep in my bed if Josh was there too. Kimba never EVER slept in my bed when she got older unless he was there, and hasnt since the last time Josh slept over last Christmas. I remember we were watching Rudolph together and Kimba had jumped right up beside him purring like a motor and fell straight to sleep. I had accepted that she wasnt going to sleep with me no matter how many times I put her in my bed at night. Only Joshs naps before Track practice could seem to get her to do that. Tragically, as you know Josh was killed earlier this year in an active duty training mission just a few months prior to his first deployment to Afghanistan. When the Marine Corp sent Joshs belongings back we decided to have teddy bears made from his uniform. I had brought mine home and laid it on my bed: not expecting what I would stumble upon next. When I came back up to my room I was surprised to see Kimba sleeping IN MY BED and how loudly she was purring. And then I noticed she had her paw over the arm of the bear we had made to remember Josh. Even though his uniforms had been washed by the military she must have still been able to pick up his scent. I still couldnt believe it because it was completely out of character for her. This definatly made the tears fall because I realized she can still feel like shes sleeping with him even though hes been gone for six months. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> A Soldier and His Kitten. (story in comments) </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-09-27 21:31:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-07-23 03:56:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [Shitty quality, but still funny!](http://www.youtube.com/watch?v=iy10A9Xq9hw) SFW </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-07-23 03:48:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I remember Lita's nipple slip... Best Monday night Raw ever! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-07-23 02:40:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> No more... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-07-19 10:00:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That is one of the only times in my life that I've been simultaneously filled with fury and sadness. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-07-19 09:40:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Big... irish... 

*I like where this is going*

juggalo...

*oh*

1

*at least he finished strong* </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-07-19 00:53:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thank you, but I'm not too broken up about it.  Life goes on, eh?

I bet that would be quite the thorn in your side... I love how most people have either time or money. You rarely have both.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-07-19 00:42:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Not at all. The last of my grandparents on that side passed away a few years ago. It's just one of those things I wish I had been old enough to ask about.

With my luck I'll never make it. :/   I work 6 days a week with no vacation time.  I've got plenty of money though. haha
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-07-19 00:21:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I thought you took marijuanas anally? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-07-19 00:12:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I wouldn't know where to start. He left when my grandma was just little. My great grandma hated him so badly that she burned every trace of him and refused to talk about him.

Research is good, but it's nothing compared to tips from a local. I would rather see a country's beauty from the point of view only a local would be able to show me, rather than the obvious tourist experience. On that note, if you're ever state side (Pennsylvania in particular) I'd love to show you around! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-07-18 23:46:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Scotland is my top travel choice. I've never been, but my great grandfather was born there and moved to the US when he was 18. Unfortunately that is the extent of my Knowledge of him...

So what do I need to see and do if I ever make it over there? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-07-18 21:41:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Scottish?! I have another legitimate question...
How does it feel being sexy as fuck 24/7? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-07-18 12:15:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Also I do realize how my post could come off as assholery, but I have nothing but the utmost respect for most other countries.
  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-07-18 11:56:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Well sir you didn't let me finish, I was going to say Aussies know no fear, not all people on the internet are assholes and I would like you to think before you jump to conclusions. There is absolutely no problem being Australian, Australia is fucking badass, it's my fourth favorite country after the U.S. then Ireland then Scotland and last but certainly not least Australia. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-07-18 11:52:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Because Aussies know no fear. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-07-18 03:57:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> A legitimate one?

If Aussie is a derogatory term, I apologize.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-07-17 04:13:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Are you an Aussie?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-07-17 03:34:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I read it as "Thumb Dings" </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-07-17 01:55:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Getting hit in the balls. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-07-16 10:53:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Well... I'm sort of an awkward fellow to begin with, so when I arrived at the park and didn't see them I decided to sit in my vehicle (to not look like a creepy 20-something scoping kids in the park). I kept looking around because I wasn't sure when they were going to show up because she was about ten minutes late and I hadn't heard from her. There were two women sitting under a pavilion watching their kids play and talking. After a while of sitting there, I noticed they were watching me. So automatically, I got nervous. Then I noticed one of them motioning toward me. The other one decided to take a quick stroll down to their vehicle and made the return trip past the back of mine, eyeing my license plate the whole way... She got back up to the other lady and they talked a little bit and stared at me some more. Then just as she was pulling her phone out, my gf pulled in and I jumped out to greet them. The ladies gave another look and put her phone away. 

It could be that I'm just paranoid, but I think there were too many coincidences and too much staring on their part to say that they just wanted to come say hi. My dark clothes and tattoos probably didnt help. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-07-16 06:58:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> As a small town volunteer firefighter, I've been called countless times to assist EMS in carrying patients. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-07-16 06:33:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I almost had the cops called on me while waiting at the park for my girlfriend and her son once...  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-07-16 01:02:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Am I the only one around here that feels his balls and thinks "There's no fucking way I'm going to notice a lump on these things" </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-07-16 00:59:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If the homeless guy is giving you his change, You should probably go to a hospital... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-07-16 00:54:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Jamaican me cry, man. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-07-15 07:24:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I said KIND OF be a dick.  Trust me. To guys like him, being confident seems like he's being a dick (in his mind). Because they're always trying to please other people, guys like this seem to lack confidence. By projecting this confidence, they feel like they're putting other people off (subconsciously, of course).  

Does that make any sense? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-07-15 07:14:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Post a picture.

You're probably overweight and/or not very attractive (I know this because you're describing me).  Also, your friend is right. You have to build a foundation before you bust out the relationship stuff.  You need to stop giving them everything. Let them know your after them WITHOUT gifts and sweet gestures. Use your words. Once they know you're into them as more than a friend, you can start the romantic crap. as long as they're obviously on board.

As much as I hate to say this, you kind of have to be a dick.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-07-15 06:34:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> At least OP acknowledges that Zimmerman is NOT white

Half of the blacks in the U.S would tell you he was.

Don't get me wrong, I was all for Zimmerman being charged with manslaughter.  The world needs to get over this race bullshit. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-07-15 06:27:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> In a court of paw </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-07-15 05:40:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Philosophy 101:

Which came first, nudity or lack of phones? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-07-15 02:42:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Who the fuck takes their baby out after 10pm? 

That's just bad parenting. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-07-15 02:30:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You can't always get a babysitter. Parents need to do adult things too.

If the baby starts crying, you leave as not to disrupt other movie goers. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-07-15 02:24:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You busy this evening? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-07-15 01:54:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> And he'll feel bad ass after he grows those balls he's always wanted. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-07-15 01:52:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Like Ron Weasley </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-07-15 01:51:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Bart is the Meg? 

They can cancel The Simpsons now... I never thought I'd say that.

We'll trade The Simpsons for Futurama. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-07-15 01:40:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Try to poop directly onto one of those metal rods used to fire model rockets. You know, the ones that blinded so many future astronauts during my youth. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-07-15 01:34:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> **HE'S** 35 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> This will help you out with the ladies... </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-07-15 00:51:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-07-14 09:28:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Graphic Novel. 

Blankets by Craig Thompson. It's an autobiographical story about life and relationships.  It's really good.  

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-07-14 09:06:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I think the general consensus on that is, "They don't give a shit, why should we?" </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Actor Cory Monteith, Who Played Finn Hudson On 'Glee,' Found Dead </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-07-14 08:29:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-07-14 07:46:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> "Your honor, my mom is always up in my private area" </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-07-14 07:40:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [Oh god.. It's starting.](http://imgur.com/iEYF9Du) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Dammit white people, stop being so fucking racist! Oh wait... </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-07-14 07:27:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-07-14 06:28:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> My favorite part is that George Zimmerman isn't even white. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Dammit white people, stop being so fucking racist! Oh wait... </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-07-14 06:21:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-07-13 13:59:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This is why I'm in a constant state of masturbation </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-07-13 05:24:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> friendly game of blurnsball with chum-pals. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-07-13 05:08:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hook me up with some nitrous and let's see how funny this shit can be! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-07-12 08:45:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Are you offering her a pussy mullet? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-07-12 08:42:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> They were texting. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-07-12 08:19:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Nah, I'll just wait until she dies of cancer/in an accident and my daughter that I didn't know I had shows up at my door. That shit practically writes itself. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-07-11 13:11:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I could have. She never said anything if she was. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-07-11 12:21:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I had sex once... once. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-07-11 09:31:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> My female friends' parents always let me crash at their places whenever I  was out late with them. I'm straight, but it turns out they knew I was too much of a loser to score... They actually told me this. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-07-11 09:25:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Nice try! Everyone knows only Asian cars come stock with pandas. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-07-11 07:32:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> C'mon... That dude is obviously a redditor. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-07-10 14:30:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I've used a spoon when all the knives are dirty. It works well. I'm probably just too lazy to make it a habit. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-07-10 14:22:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Exactly. Thank you. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-07-10 14:00:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I always wondered how they were cutting themselves on it in the books... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-07-10 13:45:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I feel like I should buy you breakfast. Because you just blew my mind. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
