<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject5813</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-03 18:39:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Really? This is a LPT? What part of understanding everyday communication makes this a "life pro" tip?

If you feel that alone and need to unload your burdens, go to a psychiatrist or confide in a SO; the people who are actually there for that kind of stuff. Don't become that melancholy friend that no-one wants to be stuck dealing with. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-03 02:31:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Don't twist your jorts in a knot. You're basically a 70 year old 32 year old. If looking like shit is something you take pride in, have at it. The rest of us who evolved past Neanderthal will keep on keeping on. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-02 15:47:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Does anything in my post history say advertisement?

The post was originally designed for /r/malefashionadvice where the brand would have mattered, but it got taken down due to not technically asking for advice so I moved it to /r/DIY. God forbid I mention the brand name, I guess. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-02 15:12:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You gave enough of a shit to chime in on my fashion, though.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-02 07:22:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You can take it the color but you have to neutralize the bleach. 1 part hydrogen peroxide to 10 parts water basically pauses the degradation. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-02 07:19:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You can be my guy, friend. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-02 07:18:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> One of my cats has resting bitch face, the other is tired. Can't really argue with you at the end of the day. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-02 06:25:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Amusingly, it's actually from an indoor water park but I see the similarities. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-02 06:03:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Judge away. I'm here for the feedback. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-02 05:46:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Spoiler alert, man! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-02 05:44:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> They aren't. They happen to be Levi's sneakers, ironically enough. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-02 05:13:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Fair enough. I'll be sure to let you know about my lack of care regarding your posts when you make it to the front page of /r/all, just to return the favor. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-02 04:43:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thanks, I appreciate it. They actually feel pretty much the same. Didn't lose any stretch or anything. I think the key is not burning them in the bleach; 15 minutes tops and it'll strip the color without degrading the fabric. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-02 04:40:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> As a skinny dude, these probably fit me like a normal cut would fit you. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-02 04:36:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I appreciate that. I'll be your friend, buddy. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-02 04:32:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This is a thing? I just might do that. Thanks for the suggestion! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-02 04:12:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thanks, I'll have to check it out further when I have more time tomorrow. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-02 04:11:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The ol' bean counter eh? I'm an engineering accounts manager. I feel sorry for your employer. If you can't get the "yours" right, how many times have you screwed up your balance sheets? Attention to detail is not your forte. I bet you put your dollar signs after your values, as well. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-02 04:05:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Chemical reactions can be your friend. Neutralizing bleach by soaking the pants in a neutralizer counteract the degradation. I did this with these. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-02 04:03:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I neutralized the chemicals via Hydrogen Peroxide. Hopefully this will increase the longevity. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-02 03:54:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I think you missed that I said that the bleach in these jeans has been neutralized, meaning it is no longer chemically unstable. (1)Hydrogen Peroxide + (10)water chemically balances bleach, making it no longer corrosive. I actually agreed with you that raw, unbalanced bleach on your skin is bad for it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-02 03:45:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If it's neutralized, it's not an issue. I hear you with bleach on skin in general, though. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-02 03:44:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This is the most absurdly teenaged comment I've had the privilege of reading.

You're* 
dudes'* 
-And* 
face?*

Good luck with the rest of high school, buddy. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-02 03:33:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hey, we can't all be as fashionably out of touch as you. Wear your cargo pants and jorts with pride, my friend. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-02 03:31:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I enjoy the brand. I don't see the issue with bringing attention to the products I appreciate while simultaneously answering 100 "what jeans are those?" questions at the same time. I get where you're coming from, though. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-02 03:30:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What would you call it? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-02 03:29:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm 30. You keep being the captain of /r/niceguys and I'll keep taking home the girl you're holding the door for. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-02 03:25:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> 5/7 sounds about right. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-02 03:22:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I guess I would say that these are very similar. Different fits for different preferences though, I'm sure. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-02 03:20:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> And here I thought chivalry was dead. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-02 03:14:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> He never is, unfortunately. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-02 03:11:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If I'm getting paid, I'd like to know where this extra Levi's bank account is. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-02 03:00:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thanks, dad. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-02 02:51:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm pretty tall (6'4") and have always had a skinny frame. I get what you're saying but to counter those general gripes, these are stretch denim. I don't like tight feeling clothes but I think the look is cleaner. I could wear boxers and feel like I have room, and if I could do the splits, these pants would have no problem handling it (alas, I haven't been able to since being a hockey goalie).

Fabric selection is as important as the fit and cut. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-02 02:47:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I originally tried to post there but because it wasn't advice related, it was auto-deleted. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-02 02:05:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I've had a ton of people tell me that you need to neutralize the bleach. I just finished soaking them in a hydrogen peroxide/water solution to do just that. Hopefully this will help them with durability. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-02 02:03:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Just finished doing this. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-02 02:02:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I don't know much about this floor, unfortunately. The house was built in 1942 For all I know, it's the original. I'm in SE Michigan, for reference. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-02 01:39:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You need to neutralize the bleach so it doesn't keep degrading the material. 10:1 water:hydrogen peroxide dip for 10 minutes should do it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-02 01:32:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Sarcasm? Last picture is a two cat pic... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-02 01:17:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> My cat has resting bitch face. I accept him though, permanent attitude and all. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-02 01:15:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Answered this one, but I wanted to be sure that the stain matched the rest of the coverage, so I stayed consistent with the stain source and any side chemicals that could have potentially tinted it as such. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-02 00:41:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> But now it's a homogenously colored pair of jeans, which was the whole point in the first place. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-02 00:40:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> American Eagle is considered "good" these days? TIL

I wear Levi's because they make a nice pair of jeans that fit a tall, thinner frame. If I don't have a reason to stray, aside from variety for variety's sake, I stick with what works.

Also, thanks for the bleach compliment, much appreciated. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-02 00:37:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Just sitting here waiting for that paycheck. Call me back Levi's! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-02 00:35:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Someone else responded that Nylon doesn't absorb chemicals (like bleach) like denim does. I was surprised myself.
EDIT: Clarity </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-02 00:17:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> No, we do not. These shoes are brand new. I break mine in around the house, but this is not exactly a normal thing to do. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-02 00:16:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Feedback noted. The 80's and /r/streetwear references I've received led me to believe some of you might not hate it. You're obviously not in the "some of you" crowd; to each their own. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-02 00:12:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It was already a loss, so the option was either "still a loss" or "maybe they turn out alright". Opinions have seemed to vary, but I'd still think it's an improvement over a single bleached knee. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-02 00:07:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Neutralizing them right now. Thanks for the advice. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-02 00:06:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's a T-shirt I used to clean in. I would have taken glamour shots and posted but I wasn't exactly expecting the front page of /r/all. I agree with you.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-01 23:40:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [Well...](https://www.bing.com/images/search?view=detailV2 ccid=KrHKb%2fNR id=DF97A3920EA16C141DDD0C1285F53FE348EE7C84 thid=OIP.KrHKb_NRxfrlW3RsrHTqPwElEs q=that+s+just+your+opinion+man simid=608049615442611734 selectedIndex=1 ajaxhist=0) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-01 23:38:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I have jeans for working around the house and jeans that I'd wear out on dates. The date jeans are definitely the "good jeans" versus the others.

Completely unwearable may be a stretch, but "demoted to house jeans" would be their new status with that stain. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-01 23:36:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I was tempted by vinegar but thought that might not be great for clothes. The peroxide is the solution that I found as well. Will be completing the perox-detox in the next 20 minutes. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-01 23:34:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The thread must not be dyed and that's it's native color. Either that or that particular material is resistant to bleach while the denim is not. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-01 22:48:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If there is a pants section for 6'4" young adults there, then sure. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-01 22:38:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Same as my username. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-01 22:35:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> These are brand new out of the box. They are indeed sanitized. I wouldn't dare wear a pair that has been outside around my house. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> New to the sub, but I've been told you guys might be into my accidentally custom 511's. Feedback would be much appreciated. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-01 22:30:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-01 22:23:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That's what I've been told. I appreciate the tip and will be doing so when I get home. Thanks! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-01 22:17:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You can neutralize bleach so it stops degrading the fabric. Not difficult to do. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-01 22:16:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Run them through the wash with bleach, probably. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-01 22:16:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> A missed opportunity. Damn... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-01 22:15:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If you soak them in 1 part Hydrogen Peroxide to 10 parts water, it stops the bleach effect. This should save the fabric and I'll be doing this when I get home from work tonight. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-01 22:05:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> My new PM's beg to differ. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-01 22:05:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I am slim, and I don't like restriction. These are not form fitting and the stretch is nice for a more fitted look without hindering range of motion. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-01 22:03:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> These have been repromoted from yard duty. The standard stable of early 2000's jeans will be continuing their run as the supreme yard commanders. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-01 22:01:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If it is, can you tell them to send me my check? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-01 22:00:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It does. I now have clean tiles as well. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-01 21:55:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'd rather over-elaborate than underwhelm. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-01 21:54:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Rinsed them a ton with water in the laundry room tub, then washed with detergent and tumble dried. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-01 21:52:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Don't forget the vinyl collection. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-01 21:50:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> They make pants that fit me well and I can buy a ton of their shoes that look decent on the cheap. Call me a shill, but I like what I like. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-01 21:47:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I have one pair of 510's that I would call "skinny jeans". I'm skinny and tall to begin with so these are actually not tight at all. If I could do the splits, these pants could handle it.

Yeah these were not cheap Levi's. If they were cheap jeans I wouldn't have bothered. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-01 21:43:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's my house mom, not yours! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-01 21:42:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Was ensuring a homogeneous look with the original stain if there were any compounds that may have tinted them. I washed all of the compounds out with regular bleach and detergents when done to save my skin. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-01 21:40:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The cats are great and still relatively unbleached. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-01 21:39:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> To each their own. I'm just not a fan of stains. I enjoy consistency, even if that means being consistently bleached. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-01 21:35:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> TIL that the way my cat sits is called a catloaf. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-01 21:33:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I have 3 pairs, all different colors. I do not have identical colored pairs or I wouldn't have bothered. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-01 20:53:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> To see how my pants go with them and to also break them in a little bit before extensive use. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-01 20:47:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Brand new pair literally just outside the box. I would never wear them inside if they weren't new. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-01 20:44:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's a sin, I know. Been looking into speakers. I just got the player this past Christmas and I would definitely have something more appropriate if it weren't for car troubles early this year. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-01 20:43:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> "Can't be a trendsetter if you don't set the trend."

Yeah, I'm going to go with that... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-01 20:42:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I was hungry. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-01 20:40:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Positive. Wearing an identical but still-colored pair right now and just double checked. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-01 20:29:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> People bleach their whites all the time (at least I thought so), so I'm not really sure how this would be any worse for wear... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-01 20:26:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Good catch! FTFY in return. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-01 20:21:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> My house, my rules!

Really though, they are brand new out of the box. I wouldn't do this with anything but a new pair. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-01 20:20:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Admittedly I usually do a better job of hiding them in the shoe. Twas a lazy Sunday. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-01 20:16:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Lesson learned for next time, no doubt. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-01 20:01:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Indeed. Chuck Norris could do the splits in these and they wouldn't tear. I love 'em. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-01 19:59:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hah I got about 3 seconds into this and immediately flashed back to the entire commercial. I'll take the reference! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-01 19:57:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That was my thought process. Tilex is like 5 bucks at the store, I didn't really care that I had to use all 5 dollars worth to save the jeans. Homogeneity was the end goal. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-01 19:55:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I don't have the specific model on me at work and can't really seem to locate it online, but I'll take a look a the box when I get home and report back. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-01 19:48:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> At least it's only in the laundry room. The kitchen has a laminate that you can see in the third pic. They're both on the to-do list of things to be replaced. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-01 19:26:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I figured that a standard cycle applies about 15 minutes worth of exposure and that's usually enough to ruin the extra colored sock that gets in with the whites, so I went with that. The denim feels pretty strong at this point, but I may look at the bleach-stop product that someone else suggested to make sure it stays that way. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
