<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject6750</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> (Homemade) Mac and cheese balls </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-10 05:03:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-10 03:24:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Job well done </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-09 01:16:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Saying bless you.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-08 03:47:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Make a copy of your passport and keep it away from your actual passport. Also never keep all your money in one spot.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-08 03:43:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The Lewinsky dress  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-08 03:42:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Winner winner chicken dinner  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-05 23:28:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> No but the screen was ripped off. He had to have stood on something to reach it that's why I knew I had time to gtfo. The police were called and nothing ever happened -.- </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-05 06:58:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thank you :) you don't realize how creepy something is when you are younger.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> My first time being home alone </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-05 04:47:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I grew up in an okay part of town. My mom didn't work and my siblings and I are all around the same age. One morning we were all getting ready for school and I stepped on glass. I was going to make everyone else late, I couldn't find bandaids and what not. My dad took my siblings to school and I got to stay home. Score! 

My mom and aunt went shopping and I had the whole house to myself. I was about 13 and honestly I didn't even think of dangerous things happening. 

I sat outside for some time in the yard playing with our cat and reading a book. I grew bored eventually and went inside. I was watching tv and I noticed a man creeping into the window. When I jumped up he looked scared. But then he knocked. I thought since he knocked and didn't run away it was cool. He asked me about a beat up car in the drive way. I told him I would let my dad he was interested. 

Looking back now I realize that he was trying to figure out if I was home alone. 

I shrugged it off and continued watching tv. about an hour later, I heard someone trying to open the kitchen door. I got a little spooked and moved into an adjacent room that had glass doors connecting to the yard. I heard a window being rattled with. Then I heard the glass door next to me being tampered with. I was so scared I couldn't even breathe.  Looking back it gives me chills knowing the sheer terror I felt right before possibly being attacked. 

After this my glass door was being fucked with I heard a tiny bathroom window being messed with. The bathroom window was never locked it was high up and took some effort to reach. I took this as my opportunity to get the fuck out. 

I ran out from the front door and started screaming about having a gun and camera in the house. (I was a tween idk I thought this would work) 

I got to my neighbors house and waited for my parents. My family asked the entire block if anyone had seen anything suspicious and NO ONE saw a thing. Needless to say I was scared and I still hate being home alone. 
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-04 02:00:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I bet you anything she smells like cigarettes  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-03 02:07:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> One time I had so much of the marijuana I almost died </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-02 01:14:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Looooool at working loooool so haaaard. See I'm stretching my worddddsssss cos that was funnnnny </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
