<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject8089</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-10 13:58:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> NIN - "Closer"

AKA, the song most people think is called, "I Want to Fuck You Like an Animal." </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> WTOP track work guide: Surge 15, May 16 to June 15 </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-10 13:36:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-10 04:46:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I entirely see your point, and fervently hope you're right.  But lack of access to information isn't the the only reason that atrocity-committing authoritarian regimes rise to power and even thrive.

A huge portion of Argentina's upper class was aware, at least on some level, of what was happening when people started disappearing, but they did not speak out against what was occurring, or even admit that it was happening.  Rather, they scoffed at the suggestion of such a thing and called those who dared to speak out hysterical lunatics, not because they didn't know, but because they believed that the "leftist dissidents" who were being kidnapped and murdered deserved that treatment.  Moreover, many were complicit or actively involved in the machinations of the incoming dictatorship, because they owned business concerns that in some way profited from the ensuing regime change and domestic turmoil.

It's true that time and place matter in applying the lessons of history, and that technology works in our favor here, but I don't think we are as different as a people as we need to be in order to be unconcerned about them. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> DeVos compares school choice to switching phone carriers </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-10 04:16:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-10 03:46:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The folks over at r/trees are going to be very bummed out if you don't x-post this. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-10 00:38:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Here are some links to get you started.

[Argentina's grim past](http://news.bbc.co.uk/2/hi/americas/4173895.stm)

[Unearthing mysteries of Argentina #39;s  #39;Dirty War #39;](http://edition.cnn.com/2009/WORLD/americas/11/17/argentina.dirty.war/index.html)

[Americas role in Argentinas Dirty War](https://www.nytimes.com/2016/03/17/opinion/americas-role-in-argentinas-dirty-war.html?_r=1)

[Children of the Dirty War: Argentina #39;s stolen orphans](http://www.newyorker.com/magazine/2012/03/19/children-of-the-dirty-war)

["Nieto Recuperado"; - Born to Parents Disappeared by Argentina's Dictatorship, Kidnapped and Raised by a Military Family, a "Recovered Grandchild" Finds His Way Home.](https://www.democracynow.org/2010/11/12/nieto_recuperado_born_to_parents_disappeared) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-10 00:30:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm so flattered!  Thank you.  By all means, please do.

The more people that can see the historical parallels at play here, the better off we all are. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Virginia math teacher competes on 'Jeopardy!' </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-10 00:14:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-10 00:10:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Chilling.

People in this thread keep mentioning Nixon, and they're not wrong, but this sort of thing is altogether too reminiscent of the precursor to how Argentina ended up under the control of a military junta and embroiled in their horrific Dirty War.

The alt-right and the rest of the Trumpets can go on about leftist histrionics all they want, but we've arrived at the point where anyone who *isn't* worried is being foolish. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-09 20:54:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> In education, this is known as laying the foundation for a [growth mindset](https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Mindset#Fixed_mindset_and_growth_mindset) (as opposed to a fixed one), in which children have been imbued with the belief that they can *become* capable at whatever they choose with purposeful effort.

This really is one of the biggest favors you can do for your kids. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> 2 cows, calf on loose in Loudoun Co. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-09 18:54:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Police arrest serial killings suspect after months of unease </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-09 18:50:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> A duck in need: DC Fire and EMS rescues ducklings from storm drain </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-09 05:12:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> AP: Sex assaults in high school sports minimized as 'hazing' </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-09 04:17:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-08 21:43:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Aha! I *knew* the phrase was disturbingly familiar, but couldn't place it.  I read it in Spanish many, many years ago (and now I think I'll goo reread it).  It all makes sense now. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-08 21:37:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's WTOP...trite, hackneyed clichs are kind of their thing. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-08 21:36:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I can't even concentrate on whether your recollection is accurate, because the only thing I can think is, "*Who* is vomiting rabbit kits, and *why*?" </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The troubling state of DC-area bridges: Not far from the White House and Capitol Hill, some of the bridges in the D.C. area make the list of the busiest, most structurally deficient and functionally obsolete bridges in America. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-08 18:15:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Clash over middle-school sex assaults: Did they happen? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-08 18:07:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-08 17:23:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I stand corrected.

 also known as the Upcountry, which is the historical term.

This is the terminology I'm familiar with. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-08 16:37:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> In Allegany and Garrett counties, to some extent, yes.

But these days, prescription opioids and plain old heroin are the much bigger issues. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-08 15:18:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Howdy neighbor...western MD, here.  That's why my guess included both of us.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-08 15:17:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Which part of NC? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-08 15:16:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If you're American, Wisconsin.

Otherwise, no fair. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-08 15:14:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Denmark.  Lucky bastard. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-08 15:14:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Portland, ME.  You might not be wrong. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-08 15:11:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> South Carolina doesn't have an "upstate." </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-08 15:09:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Virginia? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-08 15:08:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Western PA? OH? or MD? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-08 06:23:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Reddit has gotten to me; I've been here too long.

Something I just couldn't place about the tone of your comment whispered, "check the username."

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-08 00:04:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You let me know when those venture capitalists show up with your funding, and I'll come running to head your Spanish and History departments.  Deal? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-07 23:15:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The Dead's mistake was recommending the Hell's Angels to the Stone's management to run "security" for the event.  Jerry and the boys felt absolutely *awful* about it, and as the article notes, "New Speedway Boogie" was a sort of catharsis regarding what happened there. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-07 21:43:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  Somehow we can trust the upper middle class white kids to be out of uniform but not the kids in DC/PG. The school may be unaware of its racism, but there absolutely is a systemic issue of race when it comes to school uniforms.

And there you have it; we are seeing this issue through the same lens. I was born in DC, raised in MoCo, and moved to PG when I was 18.  My son attended PG county schools his entire life and graduated a couple of years ago.  I can't imagine how *anyone* could live in the DC area with their eyes open and earnestly argue against your point. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-07 20:01:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  But saying they're detrimental to learning is baseless. 

I'm not going to rehash the "soft bigotry of low expectations" argument.  It's mainly a convenient way to deflect responsibility for institutional and systemic biases...but that's not even what the piece of my comment that you quoted was *about*.  

The whole signaling one's SES thing typically applies to *wealthier* students, who, like those with economic privilege everywhere, want you to be aware of what they have because of the power it accords them within our society.  That part of my comment had nothing to do with lower-SES students violating the uniform policy by not wearing it or wearing it inappropriately -- although certainly, lower-SES students may alter the appearance of the uniform to visually mark members of their own ingroup/outgroup as well.

 Around the world uniforms are compulsory.

Only in certain contexts, and for people of certain class/social statuses.  Uniforms exist where conscientiousness, procedure, and obedience are prized over critical analysis and creative thinking.  Saying they *can be* detrimental to learning is decidedly *not* baseless.  [Here](https://www.naesp.org/resources/2/Principal/2006/J-Fp50.pdf) is a report that found the implementation of uniforms correlated with statistically significant declines in overall and reading achievement in 10th graders.

Another study from 2010 found that:

 The findings indicate that student uniforms have no direct effect on substance use, behavioral problems, or attendance. Contrary to current discourse, the authors found a negative effect of uniforms on student academic achievement. Uniform policies may indirectly affect school environment and student outcomes by providing a visible and public symbol of commitment to school improvement and reform.

One of the most cited studies on this topic (Brunsma, et al., 1998) concludes:

 The findings indicate that student uniforms have no direct effect on substance use, behavioral problems, or attendance. Contrary to current discourse, the authors found a negative effect of uniforms on student academic achievement. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-07 18:40:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Feisty, inquisitive, insatiable. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-07 18:30:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Pro-uniform advocates always try to make it about eliminating distractions and leveling the playing field for economically disadvantaged students.  Both of those are admirable goals for the school climate, but uniforms simply don't address those issues.

As you note, they *create* a whole class of infractions rather than solving them, and people, especially kids and teens, will always find ways to signal their socio-economic status/subculture affiliation to one another, regardless of dress code mandates. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-07 18:24:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I can't speak for /u/BlackMilk23's school specifically, but this nonsense is generally couched in terms of "extreme" hairstyles being a "distraction" in the classroom.  If that sounds like bullshit and doesn't make any sense, that's because it is and it doesn't.  The real reason, even if administration (or *management*, in the case of corporate charter schools) isn't aware of it/doesn't want to admit it, is nothing other than a fundamental belief that styles conducive to the texture of White people's hair are normal (*i.e.*, "good") and that those made to work with different textures of hair are weird (*i.e.*, "bad").  It's textbook implicit bias. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-07 17:34:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Regarding the hairstyle policy:  Sounds about right.  They know the policy won't stand up to legal scrutiny, but they're invested enough in exercising their value judgments about Black culture by keeping the policy on the books (so it can be selectively/punitively applied) until/unless it is challenged by someone who knows it is unenforceable. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-07 17:10:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Nice.  Hoodies and sweatshirts are a critical security/discipline issue...unless you've paid the school $50.

 We also have a rule that says the only permitted hairstyle for girls is straight.

Do you mind saying what jurisdiction you're in?  Or whether it's a private school?  I ask because employers have lost several EEOC suits brought against them for dress code policies that require women (or men) to straighten their hair or that prohibit natural, braided, or locked styles, unless there is a bona fide occupational necessity for such rules.

Even in a private school, I'm having trouble envisioning how such an obviously biased policy around hairstyles is permitted to exist.  Has the policy been challenged, to your knowledge? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Legend of 1977 Grateful Dead show at Cornell lives on </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-07 16:46:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> University of Texas stabbings put campus carry law to the test </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-07 16:20:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Old Line, New Wine: Maryland Wineries Grow as the State Rushes to Catch Up </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-07 16:09:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-07 15:45:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Actually LOL'd.  Nicely done. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-07 05:08:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Admittedly, a guilty pleasure that went downhill pretty fast, but the first few seasons of *Dark Angel* with Jessica Alba as Max.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-07 05:05:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Great call.  That show doesn't get enough nostalgic love.  Also, my heart will never *not* skip a beat for Danica McKellar. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-07 04:43:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The part where this article discusses that "Federal government studies have shown blacks and Hispanics are far more likely to face such harsh punishments" (under these policies) and how other research shows that minority students aren't just punished more severely, but that such policies are *selectively enforced* against minority students at higher-than-proportionate rates.  IOW, even when Black, Latino, and White kids break dress code at the same rate (or controlling for same), the Black and Latino kids are much more likely to A) face sanction under the policy at all, and B) when they do, it is likely to be more severe than a White student who *is* punished would face.  This is especially true when the teachers and administrators making these enforcement decisions are overwhelmingly White, as is the case in the district in this article. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-07 02:52:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's not a false choice in any way.  To say that public school resources are severely limited is a gross understatement, and I'm not referring to monetary resources alone.  

To the extent that uniforms serve a more productive educational climate, a requirement for them is *arguably* reasonable (although there are plenty of reasons why, even if uniforms do promote discipline/orderly school culture they might still be undesirable, but that's a different thread).  However, when the student's only discipline infraction is one of dress code/uniform violation and not *conduct* in the classroom, then it serves *only* to create offenders out of those students who are more likely to have the policy unfairly applied and enforced against them.  That doesn't promote discipline or structure; it promotes contempt for unethical law enforcement, and disproportionately labels minority students as offenders, prepping them for the school-to-prison pipeline. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-07 02:26:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Reading the article would probably help elucidate:

 School districts around the country have been revising policies to reduce suspensions and expulsions. Federal government studies have shown blacks and Hispanics are far more likely to face such harsh punishments, and as a result of more police involvement with schools, instances more frequently lead to arrests in what is known as the school-to-prison pipeline.

And

 This is the purest example of promoting discipline over academic performance, said Robert Goodrich, a co-founder of Radical Advocates for Cross-Cultural Education in Waterbury. He likened it to broken windows policing, which aims to keep peace by cracking down on minor offenses. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-07 01:43:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> They're doing the same thing in schools in terms of *not disallowing* -- and this double-negative passive construction is very important -- anti-LGBT bigotry and bullying.  It's the conservative way.  If they can't pass legislation that legitimizes discrimination, they just deregulate and defund everything to the point where protections against discrimination are toothless and unenforceable, or outright nonexistent.  The advantage (because of who comprises their base) is they can then claim they didn't support bigotry, just small government. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> DOJ signals to plan to undo rule against anti-trans bias in health care </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-07 00:56:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Dress code crackdown suspends 150 high school students, bringing new criticism to a Connecticut district of predominantly Hispanic and black students that was already under scrutiny for having low numbers of minority teachers </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-07 00:42:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Strawberry scientist is sued over the fruits of his research </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-07 00:22:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-06 23:40:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Sorry people are apparently shitting on you for stating this fact.  Bill Watterson has *expressly* refused to authorize any licensing of Calvin   Hobbes images for decals.  They don't exist. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-06 23:23:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm willing to believe he is *unaware* of the significance of his choice of "gift."  That's why I took care to clarify that the intent may have been other than conscious.  Just because he isn't consciously aware of these thoughts and motivations doesn't make them any less real, though.  

It's a weird, wholly inappropriate, needlessly gendered "gift" to make a show of.  Especially in a public place.  Especially when he has created a scenario that leads you to expect a wedding proposal.

The women's march was in January.  If he just wanted to give you an item that would have been useful to you, he would've done so in February, March, or April...not waited 4 months so he could use it as a blow to your ego/boost to his own at your expense.

Please hear me when I say this:

**The courting stage -- the period when he might propose -- is as good as it will ever get.**  If he's making you feel this way now, and choosing not to hear you when you attempt to communicate with him about it, that's a really big deal, because it's only ever going to get worse from here on out, never better.  I promise.

I saw your comment upthread that you're worried about "throwing away" 5 years.  I was, too.  So instead, I wasted **19 years** trying to make OK something that was rotten inside.  When it was all said and done, *he* left *me* (I was older than his taste, by that point).   Staying in a relationship because of the sunk cost fallacy is one of the most damaging things we do to ourselves.  And no, you can't get 5 years back, but you can get tomorrow back by making a choice today.

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-06 22:44:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Unless there's a long-standing tradition of elaborate practical jokes between the 2 of you, this strikes me as seriously bad news.

Zach's not only taunting you about not proposing, he went to some effort to do so...most guys don't want to bother with involving a waiter in their date even when it *is* to plant an engagement ring.  That means your bf put some thought and planning into hurting your feelings so he could see the "look" on your face.

It's also not lost on me that **the butt of his "joke" was your womanhood** -- consciously or not, the gift he gave you was intended to highlight how your anatomy is not only different from, but inferior to, his.  Taken together with the rest of his message, I can't imagine what you'd be choosing to stick around for. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-06 06:19:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Everything-but-the-kitchen-sink pasta salad.

Tri-color rotini with feta cheese, spicy pepperoni, green/red/yellow bell peppers, grape tomatoes, broccoli florets, sugar snap peas, cucumbers, carrots, and summer squash tossed in a highly seasoned and herbed Greek yogurt/olive oil/lemon juice based dressing.

Oh, and green, black, and kalamata olives on the side so we can enjoy our pasta salad in peace without the anti-olive contingent whining at us. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-06 06:08:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> /r/asktransgender may be a better jumping-off point for resources/referrals.  The community there has a reputation for being friendly and helpful.

More generally, I think you keep being your kid's mom.   And whatever you're doing so far is clearly more good than bad, because you have a 17-year-old who doesn't just talk to you, but who trusts you enough to come to you with something as potentially earth-shattering as this.  Listen more than you talk.  Love unconditionally.  But you know that. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-06 02:26:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Gorgeous!

Is that a calla lily? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-05 23:36:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Mmmm...Just hearing you talk about it takes me back instantly.

Do you remember the other dolls' scents, too? ~~Huckleberry Pie~~ Blueberry Muffin was my *favorite*...Angel Cake smelled like marshmallows, though, not angel food cake. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-05 21:22:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> r/incels is offering cancer.  Both the literal and the "of the soul" variety.

I don't know exactly what that looks like, or how you market it, but evidence shows *they* sure as shit do. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-05 18:06:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> All of them, but 2 I always think of:

"Tangled Up in Blue"

"Don't Think Twice, It's Alright" </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-05 17:32:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This really, *really* depends on where you are, even in public schools.

Source: am friends with *many* public school teachers and completed most of a secondary education major to be able to teach HS history, including observing, shadowing, and interviewing classroom history teachers in my county. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-05 05:49:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah...you *thought* it was Snape...until Umbridge came along. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-05 05:16:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I always flirt with the idea of invisibility, but ultimately, my answer is "compulsion." </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-04 23:51:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Did you want that list alphabetically, by order of severity, or...? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-04 01:08:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I graduate this month, too and I am sooo envious of you!!! I'm really not one for grad swag, but I waaant this!

It's probably too late for anything to be done about it this year, but I'm going to suggest to the bookstore on my campus and Spectrum (our LGBTQ+ organization) that they might want to start thinking about next year. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-03 14:58:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  2) don't throw your hat onto the bed

Holy shit!  This is a Russian thing?  That explains a lot about my childhood.  My great-grandfather was a Ukrainian Jew and emigrated to the US.  I grew up living in the same house with him, his daughter (my grandmother), and *her* daughter (my mother).

In my house, the punishment for putting a hat on a bed was swift and violent...but I assumed, that like most other madness I dealt with as a kid, the source was Jewish culture.  When my great-grandfather grew up there, Ukraine was part of imperial Russia, and to hear him tell it, everyone considered it to be Russian.  So it's really interesting to hear you say that because it means that this belief probably came from the dominant culture, not that of the shtetl.  TIL.

 4) don't get upset at the bird that poops on you

I had this nonsense, too.  It's supposed to be "good luck" when a bird shits on you.  I never did understand how *that* works.

What about breaking mirrors?  Do Russians have that superstition, too? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-01 23:55:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Washington, DC:

[A 2300-sq ft, 5-bedroom, SFH on the outskirts of town in a funky-chic neighborhood with 3 baths on a ~6200-sq ft lot](http://www.realtor.com/realestateandhomes-detail/814-Fern-Pl-NW_Washington_DC_20012_M67096-83247)

or

[A 2300-sq ft, 4-bedroom, 4-bath rowhouse condo in the very heart of downtown, 3 blocks from the US Capitol building](http://www.realtor.com/realestateandhomes-detail/416-Constitution-Ave-NE_Washington_DC_20002_M57370-87638) 

or 

[A 1700-sq ft, 3-bedroom, 2 bath townhouse condo in Georgetown on a ~2300-sq ft lot](http://www.realtor.com/realestateandhomes-detail/3819-S-St-NW_Washington_DC_20007_M57608-89203)

or

[An 1150-sq ft, 2-bedroom, 2-bath coop condo in a newer mid-rise on U Street with no lot](http://www.realtor.com/realestateandhomes-detail/401-9th-St-NW_Washington_DC_20004_M64248-06453) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-27 04:49:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> But it *is* the way you do it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-27 01:43:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The rest of the world vehemently disagrees with me, but *Jurassic Park*.

I found everything about that movie "meh," at best...plot, effects, character development, even the cinematography, with the only exception being Jeff Goldblum's performance, because he's never been not awesome in anything. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-27 01:10:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That's a pretty sharp observation for a drunk Russian.

Kidding aside, the double entendre in the title is an element critically lost in translation. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-27 00:14:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Che! You've got yourself a deal.  :) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-27 00:01:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> My high school Spanish teacher (and idol) was Argentinean.  She was passionate about everything, especially her fierce love for the country she had left behind and about telling its story to anyone who would listen.

She inspired me so much that when I had the opportunity to do a student exchange program the summer before my senior year of high school, I chose Argentina without hesitation.  I lived in San Juan for about 3 months in the summer of 1992 and it served only to captivate my imagination even more. Me encantaba su pas hermosa, y hasta hoy, cada da la extrao.

I returned to college at the age of 38 and decided to make use of my major (interdisciplinary social science) to examine some questions that remained unanswered, even after the time I spent there.  (In hindsight, I realize that 1992 was too close to the end of the Dirty War for anyone to want to talk about it, and it makes sense that I left feeling more bewildered about that era than I had upon my arrival.)   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-26 18:31:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Argentinean political history is a minor academic interest of mine, and I can't second this movie recommendation enough.  It's remarkably well-done, especially considering how close its production was to the events it depicts. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-25 23:23:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> No.  Never.  Not once. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-25 17:49:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Bummer.  It must have dissolved right after he graduated and we moved.  Sorry for the misinformation.  I know pickup isn't the same when you're looking for league play, but it's definitely still fun! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-25 05:02:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Got that.  Please see my edit where I quoted the FTC site on changes to the regs. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-25 03:36:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It was always legal; previously, it was simply barred by every merchant agreement in existence.

Are you saying that Dodd-Frank made it impermissible for Visa to require a clause *prohibiting* minimum transaction amounts (as long as they are only imposed on credit card purchases and don't exceed $10)? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
