<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject8599</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-10 12:50:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Zelizer: It appears to be Trump's nuclear option for dealing with probe into the very foundations of his power
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-10 12:50:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Julian Zelizer: Trump's firing of Comey in middle of Russia probe is stunner that recalls Nixon's "Saturday Night Massacre" </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Graham: I want to know Trump's business deals </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-10 11:39:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Senator: FBI Director James Comey 'as popular as cholera' right now </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-09 21:37:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-09 21:15:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> In truth, it doesn't really matter why he screwed up </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> James Comey just made a big mistake on Hillary Clinton's emails </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-09 21:12:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-09 15:52:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> At a press briefing, White House spokesman Sean Spicer said Jared Kushner has no involvement in the project. An attorney for Jared Kushner said he had sold his stake to a trust benefiting other members of the Kushner family, and would recuse himself from related policy matters while serving as an adviser to Trump.

Though the foreign investor immigration program has become a source for cheap real estate financing for projects like the Kushner family's, questions about its fairness and national security implications have made it a political briar patch for years. One recent scandal involved Hillary Clinton's brother </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Kushner firm apologizes for reference to White House ties </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-09 15:52:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Senate ref holds power over Trump agenda </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-09 12:18:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Nations urge Trump to stay in Paris climate agreement </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-08 21:31:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Stunning French Interior Design That Will Fresh Your Eyes </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-08 21:28:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-08 20:38:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Spicer said that Trump officials used the Obama administration's approval of Flynns security clearance in hiring him.
The question that you have to ask yourself really is if President Obama was truly concerned about Gen. Flynn, why didnt he suspend Gen. Flynns security clearance? he said.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-08 20:04:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The spokesmans comments confirm multiple media reports detailing Obamas advice offered privately to Trump in the Oval Office after the 2016 election.
Flynn was fired in February after just 24 days on the job after it was revealed he misled senior administration officials about his conversations with Russia's ambassador to the U.S., Sergey Kislyak.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> White House confirms Obama warning on Flynn: He wasn't a 'fan' </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-08 20:04:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-08 18:01:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Its at 2:30 ET and airing on CSpan </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-08 18:00:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> 2:30ET </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Pyongyang University of Science and Technology: 2 U.S. Employees Detained </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-08 17:32:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-08 17:22:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Is Flynn gay? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-08 17:02:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Five things to watch at the Sally Yates hearing.

It's not just Sally Yates testifying
Former Director of National Intelligence James Clapper is also set to testify. Look for questions about why his earlier assessment of Russian interference in the election contradicted the well-established version now, which is that not only was Russian interference omnipresent, but it was also designed specifically to help Trump.
Republican lawmakers have periodically brought this up over the last few months. Now will be their chance to hear directly from Clapper about whether his previous belief still stands. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-08 17:01:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Five things to watch at the Sally Yates hearing.

Will there be anything left for House investigators?
The House intelligence committee was supposed to get the first crack at Yates in public, on March 28. But that hearing got swept up in the fiasco surrounding Nunes' clandestine White House trip and later led to him stepping aside from leading his panel's investigation.
It took a month for House investigators to even settle on inviting Yates back for a new hearing, but by that point Graham had already booked her for his investigation with the Senate Judiciary subcommittee. As of last Friday, House investigators still had not settled on a date for her new hearing or if there will be one at all. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-08 17:00:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Five things to watch at the Sally Yates hearing.

Did Yates' warning make it all the way to Trump?
We know now that Yates alerted White House counsel Don McGahn to Flynn's phone calls with Kislyak. Flynn's misleading comments, Yates said, made him potentially vulnerable to being compromised by Russia, according to sources familiar with her version of events. She expressed "serious concerns" to McGahn, making it clear -- without making a recommendation -- that Flynn could be fired.
What happened next isn't clear. After that meeting, the White House took three weeks to fire Flynn, which happened in February. But did McGahn ever tell Trump about Yates' warning? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-08 16:58:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Five things to watch at the Sally Yates hearing.

2. How limited will Yates be?
Democrats have pinned a lot of hopes on Yates, privately promising blockbuster testimony from the former Obama administration official. But a key question is how much she will be limited in public, either through questions regarding classified material, promises of attorney-client privilege or claims of executive privilege from either Trump or former President Barack Obama.
Yates' first public hearing was scheduled for six weeks ago, but it was canceled at the last minute by Trump ally and House intelligence committee Chairman Devin Nunes. Reports later emerged that the White House blocked her testimony, which press secretary Spicer vehemently denied.
Monday's hearing comes a week after FBI Director James Comey spoke to the full Judiciary Committee as well as House investigators. Comey, too, was limited in what he could say, citing an active investigation. As senators tried to pry any bit of information out of him, Comey beat back questions about the continuing federal probe into Russian interference in the US elections, and he likewise revealed few new details to the House intelligence committee. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-08 16:57:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Five things to watch at the Sally Yates hearing
1. What was the extent of Yates' warning?
Yates told White House staff and other top officials that Flynn could be a security risk after he discussed Russia sanctions with Russian ambassador to the US Sergey Kislyak, CNN reported last week. That testimony is expected to contradict the White House's description of her warning, framed by press secretary Sean Spicer as "a 'heads-up' to us on some comments that may have seemed in conflict with what he (Flynn) had sent the vice president."
Trump on Twitter Monday blamed the Obama administration for giving Flynn, who briefly led the Defense Intelligence Agency during the 44th president's tenure, "the highest security clearance." </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-08 16:50:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> May be but not confirmed </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-08 16:49:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Sally Yates will testify before a Senate Judiciary subcommittee at 2:30 p.m. ET </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-08 16:47:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thanks its confirmed
https://twitter.com/MoveOn?ref_src=twsrc%5Egoogle%7Ctwcamp%5Eserp%7Ctwgr%5Eauthor </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-08 16:47:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> its Confirm hearing time is 2:30ET </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-08 16:45:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Timing of hearing is 2:30ET </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-08 16:32:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> We are aware that former AG Yates intended to speak on these matters, and sought permission to testify from the White House, Schiff said at the time. Whether the White House's desire to avoid a public claim of executive privilege to keep her from providing the full truth on what happened contributed to the decision to cancel today's hearing, we do not know. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-08 16:32:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> No </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-08 16:27:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The House panel is now seeking to reschedule its Yates hearing. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-08 16:26:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Sally Yates was first scheduled to appear in March before the House Intelligence Committee, but the session was canceled </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-08 16:22:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> because they commit treason  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-08 16:22:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> when you wanted to </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-08 16:21:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Agreed </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-08 16:21:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Investigators say the congressional probes are expected to go far into the future </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-08 16:21:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Former acting Attorney General Sally Yates will testify on the Hill on Monday </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-08 16:20:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The Hill inquiries into Russian meddling into the US election are navigating around an FBI probe </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-08 16:20:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> still no idea </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Sinclair announces deal to buy Tribune for $3.9B </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-08 16:17:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-08 15:34:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Former Acting Attorney General Sally Yates will testify before the Senate that she gave a "forceful warning" to the White House regarding National Security Adviser Michael Flynn, sources familiar with her account tell CNN </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Sources: Yates to contradict WH about Flynn </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-08 15:34:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Trump under pressure to fill Pentagon posts </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-08 12:19:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-08 12:18:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> In the words of one longtime party leader, Its never too early, unfortunately, to start thinking about the next presidential election. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Democratic lawmakers such as Amy Klobuchar start making 2020 moves  and the base starts making demands </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-08 12:18:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-08 11:53:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Currently held:

 Kim Dong Chul, the president of a company involved in international trade and hotel services, was arrested in 2015 and is serving 10 years on espionage charges.

 Otto Warmbier, a University of Virginia student, was sentenced to 15 years of hard labor in 2016 for removing a political sign.

 Kim Sang Duk, also known as Tony Kim, a university professor, was detained in Pyongyang in 2017 and accused of attempting to overthrow the government.

 Kim Hak-song, a native Korean born in China (Jin Xue Song is the Chinese version of his name) and professor working at the same university as Tony Kim was detained May 6 on suspicion of "hostile acts" against the regime.

Americans released in 2014:

 Kenneth Bae served nearly two years of hard labor after accusations he was part of a Christian plot to overthrow the regime.
 Matthew Todd Miller was also accused of "hostile acts" after tearing up his tourist visa and seeking asylum after entering North Korea.
 Jeffrey Fowle spent five months in a North Korean prison after being caught with a Bible inside the country. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> North Korea detains fourth US citizen </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-08 11:51:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Iran will hit back at most of Saudi Arabia with the exception of Islam's holiest places if the kingdom does anything "ignorant", Tehran's defense minister was quoted as after a Saudi prince threatened to move the "battle" to Iran </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-07 22:27:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Chancellor Angela Merkel's conservatives won a decisive victory over their Social Democrat (SPD) rivals in a vote in Germany's northern state of Schleswig-Holstein, boosting her prospects of winning a national election in September. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-07 21:17:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-07 16:12:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> My goal is to actually expand coverage for those 28 million Americans who still lack coverage today despite the ACA," she said.
Collins also said during the interview she has a "lot of concerns" with the House GOP's healthcare bill. But she noted it is difficult to assess the bill because she has not yet seen a Congressional Budget Office (CBO) analysis. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Collins: 'The Senate is starting from scratch' on healthcare </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-07 16:11:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> 'SNL' asks 'Where in the World is Kellyanne Conway?' </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-07 06:58:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
