<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject8593</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-02 10:24:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That looks really similar to a Keel Toys or D S Nicholass bunny. I can't link at the moment, as I'm on mobile, but if you search ebay for those two brands followed by 'rabbit' it throws up a few of them in all different colours and sizes. The only difference is that yours seems to be missing the foot pads those two designs have and they have flocked noses. 

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-12-16 13:07:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Your points are spot on. It's sad that most people aren't educated enough on rabbit welfare to realise 4x2 is way too small for a litter of babies, and especially too small for more than one dwarf adult. :/

Edit: And on top of that I'd like to add that they require daily (if not constant if possible) access to a run of at least 6x8 - just in case anyone sees this and thinks just putting them into a 2x4 hutch/cage and leaving them there is reasonable. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-12-10 17:46:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Sounds like he was totally *kid*ding around to me. 

(seriously though, that is messed up.) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-12-07 21:55:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You could certainly give it a shot and try a different one, if you're all out of other options. That pain is truly awful, so I feel for you. 

I can't be 100% certain that going on my BC was the thing that stopped it, but I do know that I haven't had any pain since around that time, so... it makes sense.

Funnily enough, I've just come off my pill, so if that pain comes back I guess I'll know for sure. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-12-07 21:36:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I don't know what the cause of this is, but I've had it too! Exactly the same as you describe it! So you're not alone. Mine went on for about a year. When I went onto birth control (Microgynon, a year ago) it seemed to stop, as I haven't had it since. 

I've also since had a pelvic exam and while I do have cysts at the opening to my cervix, they're benign and the doctor can't see any reason for the random pain I was getting.

I'm so sorry that you're feeling this too! I don't have any answers, unfortunately, but hopefully it's somewhat comforting to know you're certainly not alone in feeling this and that I got the all clear from doctors too.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-12-04 17:43:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Aww, you are too sweet! Thank you so much. 3 I'll keep an eye out for that second part! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [Thanks] Thank you CatLadyInTheMaking for my Holiday Exchange Gift! Now I know what I'll be doing tonight! :D </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-12-04 16:52:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The brooding, sulky face of Rory Torrens. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-11-13 13:11:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-11-13 12:38:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I have two small ones on one of my cheeks that I was teased relentlessly about during school. 25 now and just starting to embrace it. I love that this sub exists! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-11-13 12:20:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Now this is something we need. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-11-13 01:02:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I literally just said 'aww' out loud. That story is adorable. :) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-11-13 00:49:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> "Miserable dullard is in love with his dead best mate, but not really."

or "A novel length description of trees."

My story is set mostly in and around a forest at Autumn time. All I ever seem to do is describe the goddamn leaves. D: </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-11-13 00:23:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Here's mine: http://www.wordle.net/show/wrdl/8310287/antlers

That huge 'like' is mocking me. I love similes a bit too much. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-10-24 21:51:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hello and welcome! :) I'm also a big anime lover! What's your favourite/s? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-10-24 13:32:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I know that jealousy, I get really envious of people who can sew clothes. I'm absolutely useless at that!

According to Google's conversion a bat would be $40.10 (shipping $17.64) and that's with custom choice of fabric/colour etc. And Toothless would be $160.33 ($22.45 shipping), he's a big cuddly plush, 22inches from nose to the tip of his tail. :) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-10-24 13:22:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Oh wow. I think that dream might be even worse than the last one! When I was having my really bad ones, I was seeing a psychologist at the time and when I explained them to him he told me that horrible ones like that were usually a manifestation of anxiety and possibly a side effect of the medication I was on at the time too. I was dealing with really bad anxiety/depression then, so it made sense! I don't know if you have anything making you a bit anxious or worried, but it's something to think about! :)

I'm trying to remember mine, but it's been *so* long since I had any. The only one that really sticks with me now is very NSFW! one I had about walking through a park at dusk in autumn. The path was windy and littered with leaves and I eventually came upon a huge black tree in a clearing. It had a massive thick trunk and was stripped of leaves. All the branches were gnarled and reached up into the sky, pointed at the ends, like claws. 

A woman in a white dress was sitting in the bough of the tree. She was sobbing. The bottom of her dress was covered in blood and blood was gushing down the trunk of the tree from between her legs. I knew, somehow, that she'd been raped so violently that she was bleeding out, but I was rooted to the spot and couldn't move to help. I must have stood there for about ten minutes as I watched her die. I remember looking down at my feet and seeing that the pool of blood was almost touching my toes. Then I woke up. 

Also just remembered a dream which is super fragmented, where I'd been kidnapped and bundled into the back of a car at night. I managed to get out and started to run away but the attacker grabbed me by the foot, tripped me up and then hacked off my leg at the knee with an axe. I managed to crawl away through a field before waking up. 

Man, dreams are so weird!
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-10-24 12:52:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Omg. So we have. xD

Only a month?! I was expecting it to have taken much longer than that! That's amazing. What's the new one like? Is it the same character? :)

Go for it! I can help if you ever need it! Haha, when I was working in retail I used to take my crocheted things into work with me and just kind of shove them off onto anyone who paid a bit of interest in them. I don't even think half of my friends actually *wanted* them, but they went home with them anyway! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-10-24 12:38:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> *Blush* Thank you so much. The bats are probably my favourites so far, I wish I'd prepared for Halloween better so I could have made more of them. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-10-24 12:30:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I will definitely give those tips a go. I really want to make myself a few winter scarves this year. 

I sell through Etsy, yeah. I do have a website/blog but it's a bit empty and terrible at the minute. I'm hoping to find more time to update it in the new year. Aw, kids costumes would be tons of fun.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-10-23 21:13:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Oh wow! That is incredible! Seriously good stuff! How long did that take you to make approximately? 

Ahhh, thank you! 3 :) Send me your username, or a message over there, and let me know who you are so I can watch you back! 

You should definitely give it a go! I think you'd be good at it, considering what you've already managed to achieve! It's funny, you know, I thought that when I started I'd want to keep everything, but I haven't kept a single thing I've ever made. The biggest reward for me is seeing it go to another home and make someone else happy. :)

And you should! It's [this](https://www.earlymoments.com/upload/EarlyMoments/DBC/thelionking.jpg) one. I don't know if the whole thing is as bad I remember, but some pictures are definitely questionable. Like, what's going on with Mufasa's back end in that far right picture for a start, hah. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
