<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject5591</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-19 15:56:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I actually work out at home! I have a treadmill and elliptical which is nice. Yeah, it was probably around April/May after school finished. I started out slow, maybe 2-3 workouts a week for 30 mins. Wooo! Its so fun seeing results, good for you! :) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-19 15:54:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yes!!! You can do it! You're almost half way there! Keep it up! :) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-19 15:53:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> LOL  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-19 15:51:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yes it was! I'm glad I saw him even though I didn't end up having surgery. I saw the cognitive behavioural psychologist because of my social phobia, I could barely go out in public, and when I did I had crippling anxiety attacks. She also helped me realize my self worth. I hated myself. Why? I'm a good person! I had relied on validation from others for my self worth, and worked really hard to change that. I AM worth it. I doubted myself, how could I be that person who loses all that weight? It sounded impossible. But here I am :) not where I want to be, but a hell of a lot closer than I was! You CAN do it. You ARE worth it. 
This really relates to my social anxiety, but when I'm anxious about something, I'll write down the worst case scenario. Everything awful that I can imagine happening, I write it down. Then I read it out loud. It always sounds ridiculous and soooo unrealistic. Which makes me feel better. Something the psychologist taught me :)
Thank you! Hahah yeah, its strange having people do a double take!  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-19 15:44:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Food wasn't my only issue. I had gone from a straight A student to almost failing out of my second year of uni. I had severe depression and social phobia. The psychologist I see is amazing. She specializes in cognitive behavioural therapy, which I would recommend for anyone with social anxiety. She, more than anything, helped me realize my own self worth. I didn't like myself. Now I can say I'm starting to love myself :) and healthy eating and exercise is something I do because I love myself and my body. I definitely recommend talking to someone! Everybody is different, but I always felt like a huge weight had been lifted every time I left her office. Good luck on your journey! :) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-19 15:38:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thank you!!! I didn't track calories much in the beginning. When I started I tried to keep it between 1200-1500. That's still about where I keep it now, it really depends on the day. I don't track precisely anymore, but sometimes I'll track roughly in my head so I know I'm where I need to be :) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-19 01:28:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Its really tough dealing with mental issues. Good job on your progress that's awesome!!! Your comment makes me really happy, I can't believe all the supportive feedback I'm getting! You're the best!!! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-19 01:06:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The second picture was taken in a mirror! haha its still on my right foot :) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-19 01:06:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thank you! Yes it does :) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-18 23:05:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah its a tough habit to break! At least we're trying! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-18 22:51:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thank you so much! :) Yeah my mental health has improved tremendously! But aside from that, my body feels great. Just doing every day things is so much easier, and sometimes I forget how hard it used to be. I can run up stairs now and not be winded, and before I would have to catch my breath just walking. I feel just generally strong and healthy which is new! Its unbelievable how healthy food and exercise DO make you feel better. Now if I eat crap, I feel like crap, which I never really noticed before.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
