<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject6431</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Clean-up underway amid oil spill into East River off Brooklyn </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-09 21:52:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-09 20:56:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thanks for the recommendation. Springs really much better than the regular kind? Do they get as tight? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Best fins for a guy about to start Rescue and DM training in the Caribbean </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-09 18:30:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Any recommendations? Should I buy my own fins? If so, what works best in tropical conditions?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-08 22:26:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> He thrusts his fists against the posts and still insists he sees the ghosts.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-05 17:13:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Fuck you Bot </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> So this Wikipedia page says the ACA was 906 pages, any idea how many pages the Republican bill was? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-05 17:05:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-03 17:21:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Kinda looks like the MIB is chasing Roland which is completely ass backwards. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-03 05:12:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Why the fuck is he looking down? Seriously? who approved this poster? If he's looking down because he just dropped Jake -- why does he have both blue guns out? This is NOT good. They should have stuck with the teaser poster. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-03 05:10:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Or like the marketing people writing for them don't have a clue. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-02 18:19:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Nicely done!
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-02 18:12:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I actually like this image. Which is shocking as I've liked nothing I've seen from this yet. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-02 06:07:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Studios be what they be. Art house films don't get made to make money, they get made to win awards. Franchise films get made to make money so they have to be as vanilla as possible, which kind of makes we wonder just how neutered this film is going to be... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-30 17:04:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah but Roland dropping Jake is crucial to the development of both characters. There is no bond, no tension, no nothing without it. Losing that evaporates any connection between them. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-30 17:02:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Serious question: is this rated PG-13? Because if so, I want a grown up DT movie like I was promised.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-30 16:57:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Very cool and terrifying at the same time! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-30 03:43:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Somewhat reductionist thesis of Kerouacs' work, there is a oneness to the spirituality he chronicles that isn't contained within such a reading. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-30 03:37:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Nor mine but I remember when they were going for far less.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-30 03:35:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> No, but there is a level of the tower where there is a version of the Gunslinger that is released that is a SMALL, little film with arthouse sensibilities depicting an existential struggle between Roland and the Man in Black, showcasing a vision that Sai King made iconic. They could get onto the NEXT CYCLE stuff on say, film four or five (which would be much larger budget TENTPOLE type releases with corresponding PR), but by that time the franchise would be a thing unto itself. 

A small, thoughtful intro to the series is what is needed, not some mashup best of compilation.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-30 03:30:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I hope they EMBRACE the cycle and it ends with Man in Black triumphing and begins back again at the start with the iconic opening/closing (something that they really have to NAIL for their to be any hope). </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-30 03:28:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Roland was colder in the original, more believably other. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-30 03:27:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Trailer got rated so it's coming out soon. Then we shall see.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-28 05:34:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> TBH I would prefer to see the adventures of Roland and Susan's child in a world where Roland had really gotten it right. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-28 05:31:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I wonder if anything we're building with today will have to be sealed up like this based on stuff we just don't know now. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-28 05:25:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What about the Donald M. Grant editions? Those things are gorgeous.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-28 05:09:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Never thought about this before but it makes complete sense. does the same logic hold for something like lead paint? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-28 05:07:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> But that would mean misleading headline is misleading. Have you watched That Sugar Film? It's pretty good. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-28 00:15:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I never said what Russia was doing was good, all I said is that this action would not have happened without the unilateral wars started by the USA in Afghanistan, Iraq, Yemen, etc. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-28 00:04:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Honestly, I think I'd rather be waiting.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-28 00:04:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah thanks but I've never been there and if you don't see the dangerous connection between unilateral wars of occupation started by the USA and the Russian action in Crimea then you're either a shill working for the US government or your head is so far up your own ass you'll never be able to see what's really going on. 
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-27 22:42:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Successfully? Some would argue that the end of the series was incredibly rushed.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-27 22:33:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Was leaked months ago. Common knowledge on this subreddit but not in general. Most people know nothing about this film because Sony is doing like zero marketing for it.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-27 22:28:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This is leaked trailer, no? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-27 19:05:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This is what happens when illegal wars of occupation are started by the USA, other countries start thinking they can just do whatever the hell they want too.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-27 17:34:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Gulf o' Tonkin Two-Step </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-26 17:30:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> They didn't tour to support it. Not a real album.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-26 17:20:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's all about salary. He's older so he gets paid more.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-26 05:05:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> A TV show would be ideal. It would allow enough time to get into the other worlds multiverse that to be honest, the movie doesn't stand a chance in hell of even attempting to nail. King only did it by tying the DT series into many of his other novels. The film doesn't have that going for it -- unless it throws out allusions IT or the Stand, but regardless, there is no depth of work to draw upon, leaving the film to stand for itself.

And we haven't even seen an official trailer. Just an image or two and a poster. 

They need to take their time with this material. Let it breathe.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-26 05:00:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I think it was described as being An-Tet but I can't remember exactly, more like part of them rather than OF them. And if you think about the arc of Callahan, it makes sense for him to be more of a singularity, more of a Roland than a member of another tet. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-26 04:58:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Those Grant editions are sweet. Sadly I've never had the coin for them, but they live in my dream Library.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-26 04:56:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> To be fair, part of what helps get research funded is the interest of the public, which is def cultivated by clickbait BS headlines like this. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-25 20:07:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Dove with Bali Dive Academy on Lembongan -- couldn't recommend Andy the marine biologist any higher as a dive guide. His knowledge is superb.

On the north side of Bali we dove with Matahari Dive Resort and did the USAT Liberty (definitely worth it)!
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-25 17:40:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Later BRAH </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-24 05:20:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Sorry to hear that. Hold steadfast to your course. Remember his face. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-24 05:19:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The journey IS the point. Sai King gets that but the moviegoing audience does NOT. Not do the suits @ Sony. Making this the next iteration of the cycle is a brilliant idea, but making it less than a tweaked version of the novels is disrespectful to the fans and to the source material. We deserve to see 7 great DT films, at least. At yet, we're probably just going to get this one because no one at Sony has the balls to negotiate contracts like Feige over at Marvel. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-24 05:14:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> No one in the film community knows it's happening, either. It's an abortion. Sony isn't talking about it. Hell they aren't even paying for a trailer.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-24 05:12:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Oooh this is disconcerting. If Howard is backpedaling, it means he isn't even attempting to publicly appear confident in the expanded universe that Sony should be touting if they have ANY confidence in the film generating sustained interest. Instead, it seems as if they have rushed and botched the first attempt at a DTCU.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-24 05:01:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  Baraka is life changing. as is Koyaanisqatsi </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-24 04:59:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Cart before horse. Not a good sign.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-24 04:58:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I hope not since Eddie isn't in this and that's one of the coolest scenes from DOTT. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-24 04:57:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> They HAVE to be trolling us with the horn, right? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-24 04:53:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So sick. Amazing dive. What was the depth? 
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-24 04:47:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> BNBG </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-21 18:31:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Funny video but sigh. Don't touch unless you want to lose fingers.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-21 05:10:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> To be fair, I think CC should get a lot of credit for encouraging a multi-season mythology that is now the norm in the second golden age of television. But when he was doing it on the X-Files, it was kind of "out there".  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-21 05:09:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Someone clearly needed to call CC on his shit and be like dude, what the fuck are you doing? Then again, at that point the X-Files was a cash cow for fox. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-20 22:43:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Good video. Nice find.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-19 21:53:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Good riddance. Dude had everything and he threw it away. See also When Keeping it Real Goes Wrong. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-19 20:28:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I always assumed it was the reason the Towers were brought down in that Universe -- to destroy Black 13.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-19 18:19:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What material was released last month?
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-19 18:18:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> At this point, I'll be happy with NO trailer.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-18 23:28:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> instead of fighting for "this great nation" how about "fighting for the Oligarchs in the longest illegal war in American history." </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-18 20:33:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Normally I wouldn't either but it was an anniversary present for my ex  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-17 19:49:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Last time I saw them was Plastic Beach tour at MSG floor seats ... one of the best shows I've ever had the honor to witness. Glitter Freeze alone was worth the $400 I shelled out for those tickets. The song gives me goosebumps to this day.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-17 00:06:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The Familiar </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-17 00:04:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> People still buy Blu Rays? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-17 00:03:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You don't know that they HAVE issued a new poster. Let's not defend obviously shitty worst practices. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-17 00:02:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> One with the WRONG date on it? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-16 15:07:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> There should at the very least be a teaser </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-16 14:53:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hate to say it here but Marvel knows how to make wide release movies that hit the right beats time and time again. Sony is struggling in that vein and this should be a sure fire thing but then again we're working on a script from a hack (AG hasn't done anything good really, ever) trying to adapt one of the most singular visions ever put to paper. Having said that, it should be possible because King's opus is imminently cinematic ... I really hope they just put the brakes on it go back for even more reshoots, hell even a rewrite and release it in 2018. get it right and you've got a franchise for a decade or more, blow it and you're Paramount. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-16 14:48:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Exactly this. it's also why they have not done a poster reprint despite the date change.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-16 14:38:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The fact that they haven't issued an updated poster is a very BAD sign. It shows zero confidence in this film. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-12 17:08:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Not only that but one of the witnesses banging on the window is what stopped the attack the first time. Then the attacker sat in his car and realized he could finish the job, so he went back and killed her.

And Kitty died in the arms of her friend in the lobby of her building after the second attack.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-12 17:06:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Kitty Genovese only has to do with diffusion of responsibility in so far as the media completely made that story up. Watch The Witness on Netflix.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-11 21:19:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Not a good sign.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-11 17:34:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Did it have a release date on it? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-11 17:32:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Concur. The comics are OK but they're like an expanded universe thing, not really cannon IMO </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-11 17:05:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> He's like, why can't I drink all this? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-10 23:03:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Wow. That is incredibly horrifying. Kind of insane that he survived a free ascent from that kind of depth.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-10 22:30:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Amazing. And a little scary. But more amazing.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-10 22:26:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This is the stupidest thing I've ever heard!! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
