<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject2418</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> /u/Soros_Bucks_or_Bust suggests a hypothetical in which FBI Director James Comey gets fired, less than an hour before it actually happens </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-10 02:06:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-10 00:19:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Also coloring glass but letting the background show through? I'm not even sure how you show transparency like that? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-09 23:54:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Special Prosecutor: James Comey </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-09 23:54:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> He didn't leak the letter. Chaffetz did. He has done good by his investigation... and if you ask me, this firing proves it.  
  
edit: [Trump's letter to Comey. Read Paragraph Two](http://i.imgur.com/jr8btVV.jpg). </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Here's the view from outside my office window </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-09 19:29:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Looking for ecletic dance spots   art spots, and if anyone wants to hang! (next week) </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-09 19:03:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hey all, I'm super into dance spots (hipsterish, vinyl spinning especially) and cool underground art stuff. Anyone have any recommendations based on that? Would *love* any recommendations based on that.   
  
I'll be in Condesa next week the 18-22, holler if anyone's free but super interested if anyone has any art events ideas! Thanks!  
Here's my soc: [Fb](https://www.facebook.com/brennan.mcfriend), [insta](https://www.instagram.com/brendowell/)  
  
Thanks! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The beautiful old theatre in my neighborhood, I visit maybe once a week for blockbusters   classics </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-09 17:23:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-09 07:51:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Saudi Arabia is a plague upon the planet. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-08 22:13:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Iphone 5, no edits! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-08 19:16:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> His voice.... man he did something creepy cool with it </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> He's on me like this so I'm stuck, but it's okay cause I don't want to go anywhere </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-08 14:38:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Sonic Youth's Thurston Moore reflecting on visiting CBGB in 1976 </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-08 12:52:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Poet Max Ritvo passed away at 25 last year, I was reading his NYTimes obit which struck me deeply with its ending on this incredibly powerful note </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-08 12:13:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> His poetry sustained him, his family said. He said the day he stopped writing, that would be the end of it, his wife said in an interview. She added: He was writing three days before he died.
  
On Monday, Dr. Ritvo-Slifka said, her son was too weak to write poetry.  
  
Thats it, she said quoting him. I cant write any more.  
  
The family called in the hospice nurses, who gave him sedatives. He died the next morning.  

([link](https://www.nytimes.com/2016/08/27/books/max-ritvo-poet-who-chronicled-his-cancer-fight-dies-at-25.html)) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-07 20:16:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'll take globalists over facists any day. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-07 02:06:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> In my opinion, violence aside (and no one seems to have a perfect solution to that) and policing aside, this city has greatly improved under his administration. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-06 23:04:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yupp </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-06 23:03:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hell they learned it worked. Why not try again! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-05 15:58:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's true,  he mentioned his friend Andrew Jackson is an example of somebody whos done an amazing job and is getting recognized more and more. He's been one of his closest advisors. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-03 21:36:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So is the joke dead yet or is there anything I can do to help? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-02 15:25:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What is easier, screaming for hatred or standing against it in its face? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-02 05:52:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> And make sure it's slighty too small for him so he's just a little uncomfortable! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-02 00:02:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's a simple thing: pride. People are VERY unwilling to say they regret their vote, even in the face of anything, so they keep going all in. Why? Because voting is a part of ones identity, and to say you regret your vote is to admit being wrong, and admit that a part of you is flawed. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-01 23:09:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Or Milo. Or they all call themselves "pedes" hmmmm..... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-01 22:37:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> There's also giant letters all over you </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-01 15:03:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The best is when they pause their barking, stop, look at you as if to say "yo can you believe the nerve of this random person walking 30 feet away on the sidewalk??" then turn back and continue barking </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-01 05:48:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Iphone 5SE </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-30 23:13:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Just my iphone? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-30 21:06:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Oh I know you </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> ITAP of the sunset at my trainstop </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-30 08:45:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-30 08:18:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Whoa! Awesome! I mean, destruction isn't awesome but your arting is </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Looking down at L.A. from behind the Hollywood sign </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-30 06:10:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-30 04:08:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> And then I had to walk back </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> When I got off the train after work mid-sunset the other day </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-30 03:57:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-30 03:41:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> yeahhhh but after 3 some hours of walking I just didn't have it in me </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> When I visited SF, I walked from Coit Tower to over Golden Gate, up the hills, and had this view of the wide open Pacific </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-30 03:36:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-30 03:17:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Or wtf I love deficits now? Or wtf I love a golfing president now. After roaring about this shit for 8 years. Amazing. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-29 21:46:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> r/goretitlesofthewebsitereddit </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-29 05:02:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> K so this isn't Pursuit of Happiness 2? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-29 01:28:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> *I will not be a hostage to be bartered, mothafucker* </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-28 19:48:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Folks are dying for this, I don't mind being reminded. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-28 14:59:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> **You wouldn't boop a car** </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-27 18:07:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The weird thing is the immense support he enjoys at home. Their propaganda apparatus is such that the folks inside see reality elementally different than we do. However, the 2016 election gave us a huge dose interally of what it's like to have segment of the population who believe separate realities... one perhaps much more constructed than the other. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> I wander the streets of Tokyo at night, looking for cinematic moments. This is what I found... </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-24 20:36:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-24 19:36:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> To be fair, who knows, it could be different in some way. I'm only guessing here.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-24 19:28:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I suspect that they have solid intelligence that a nuclear test is being prepared (which has been reported), and they are considering a response of some sort, possibly pre-emptive.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-24 17:20:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You are the guy we're looking for. Yes, that little sports bridge, I hopped over a wall too and got down to the river, which it seemed like a bunch of people were doing </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-24 17:17:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Best part was it ends on a clear ramp up for a new adventure.. like if I remember right Peach rolls in and says hey Mario and Louie we need you saving the day again. And... that sequel never came so it's an accidental cliffhanger. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-24 15:42:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I have no idea if it has proper names but it was the river at about Foster and Kedzie </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> I walked for awhile yesterday and ended up here.. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-24 14:35:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> A work at the lovely National Museum of Mexican Art made of thousands and thousands of tiny beads </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-23 22:37:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> This is thousands and thousands of tiny beads </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-22 21:33:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-21 17:30:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That distinction is apparently not important enough to the 127 people who upvoted this so far. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Riding into the sunset from Chicago </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-21 15:55:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-19 19:10:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Kudos to NYTimes for breaking this.  

Kudos also to the women who stood up against, especially the ones who did so with no demand for money. 
  
edit: I originally saluted FOX News for having the guts to fire their top slot. But after 100 replies saying they deserved no thanks, I took that part away, you're right. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-19 19:09:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Heck, the current one endorsed him.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-19 16:56:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Bill O'Reilly, Milo, Chaffetz, Flynn fired, Nunes dethroned, Puzder btfo--  
I cannot get enough of this **winning!!!** </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-19 15:50:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> But he's like so over the jedi now  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-19 14:05:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Problem: half the gahdamn countey votes for these fuckbags. It's one thing to be a fuckbag, but that millions upon millions of people will vote for you even if you continually be this shitty as a party... I have just no idea what that says. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-19 06:29:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Reptillians never die, only their host bodies do :) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-18 16:58:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> *punches nazi swine throws from zeppelin* </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-18 04:22:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It sounds to me like you're appreciating the uniqueness in humanity, and of this one individual and that something was so sensely and purposelessly taken away. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-17 18:15:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> GOOD </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-17 17:50:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I was there the other day. Had five black old ladies say hi to me in just such a sweet compassionate manner, no one ever says hi in my area. Some scum rolling through but all and all is quite pleasant. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-17 17:27:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> My area is quite diverse, and that's partly why I chose it. However, before I lived in densely Puerto Rican area before. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-17 17:13:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> There are plenty "safe" areas. It's mostly some of the south side and the west that are writing all these headlines you're reading. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-17 17:11:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's so weird living here. Like you guys read those headlines and it seems like a world away, but shit I live here and I've never seen anything like the headlines go down. It's just a totally separate world. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-16 21:58:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Who didn't see that comin? Enjoy your dictator, Turkey. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-16 01:22:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Wonder if Trump is right now being updated in full view of Mar-a-Lago members. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> I saw a thousand worlds today </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-15 06:05:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-15 03:13:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Stay seven get one free </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Courts Block 7 Executions Set For 11-Day Span In Arkansas </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-15 02:40:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-15 01:40:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Whatever crooked Hillary would have done the same thing. Outspent Obama's entire travel budget before the first 100 days, used taxpayers money at his own places, defunded planned parenthood, allowed IP's to be a shared commodity, launched attacks against the Syrian state, dropped a MOAB for because, banned muslims, mispelled tweets, appointed folks with undisclosed meetings with Russian, provoked North Korea even though a ten minute talk with Xi Jingping revealed you didn't understand the topic at all, golfed every weekend instead of running the country, studied top secret intel in full view of people at a restaurant, charged us *millions* to put ten body guards on her Sec of Education and Sec of Energy and her children as they went and made business deals on her name brand. She would have done all that and much worse. It was a choice between two bad choices, equal opportunists. She was the crook, how could you not see it? She was CROOKED. I said it so it's true. This is what is true, you need to understand that. ^(/s) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Ziggy Stardust and the Smiles from Mars (1972) </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-14 17:36:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Ziggy Stardust and the Smiles from Mars </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-14 17:35:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-12 19:05:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hahah.. uhhhhh. What the heck. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-12 18:43:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Probably one of the better places to be if there actually is one. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-12 14:12:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Lol he wasn't their campaign manager, according to Spicer he was just a summer intern.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-12 04:58:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I mean, have we ever once seen Trump accept responsibility for any error however small? Honestly asking. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-12 00:04:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> #"Now I am become Mod, the destroyer of worlds." </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-11 16:49:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Are... are you still there? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-11 14:34:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Just like her bombing targets. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-11 07:29:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> OP isn't a nasty vengeful coworker, just a teasing roommate. How disappointing. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-10 18:21:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm from Chicago, [I feel you Nordic fam](https://static01.nyt.com/images/2011/02/03/us/CHICAGO/CHICAGO-jumbo.jpg). </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-10 17:27:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Here's a great video of a man walking through this area in [the earlier hours of the morning](https://www.youtube.com/watch?time_continue=1 v=Yhs4pvlTKyU). He just seems to be on a peaceful stroll. I watched it a few times before I went it's so peaceful. So when I was there, I took my own morning stroll through that area. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-10 15:13:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> He blew it all on plastics. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> In the South Side of Chicago there's a Japanese garden in the middle of a lake </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-10 05:30:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Osaka Garden, a little hidden gem on the South Side </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-10 05:29:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-09 19:58:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You can look in r/worldnews. This post isn't about the mass dead, it's about the one hero. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-07 18:50:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> #"Coke: reach for one if you still can." </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-06 19:37:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> But hey you know what it means.... perhaps our greatest weapon of changing the plans of the Reality TV President.. is TV itself. Using his image obsession and TV as a vehicle to mock the shit out of him, mock him into change. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-06 19:28:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's how Marine Le Pen is doing it. While simultaneously openly courting Jews. But you don't actually want Jews, you just want to use them as leverage against muslims, who you also hate. It works [like this](https://www.nytimes.com/2017/04/05/world/europe/france-jews-marine-le-pen-national-front-anti-semitism.html). </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-06 19:02:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Which seems to be all too often. If only they had a legal means of stripping minorities and women of their voting rights, they'd finally have *their* great america back. Fuck em </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-06 18:30:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I want to point out the first time I heard this song. I think I was sixteen maybe 13 years ago and I had been reading this book by Terrence McKenna that supposes that part of the evolution of our sophisticated cerebral cortex is due to when we were monkeys, we ate psilocybic mushrooms and expanded our mind. I found this website, www.elftrance.com, which is really something to behold. and [this video](https://youtu.be/ZXRAmX5BaOw?t=1m57s) which uses sandstorm as the moment a monkey realizes *self* thanks to consuming mushrooms. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-06 17:22:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> According to the NYTimes they followed up and asked what he meant by "operationalized" and he refused to clarify lol </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> After a day's work... </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-06 03:23:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-06 02:28:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Which never made any sense anyway. Why would the biggest polluter say its a hoax when theyre now taking more action to prevent it than the states even are. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-05 22:38:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Handing off the revised hit list in person. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-05 19:25:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yes. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-05 19:24:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Believe me, you just kiss. I dont even wait. And when youre a star, they let you do it. You can do anything. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-05 18:59:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Such a fucking embarrassment. But, hopefully by it's his very nature of being such a slimy fuckball that he's done criminal actions that will take him down. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> I made it a point to get a full sequoia in frame on a visit to Big Sur State Park </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-05 17:32:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Donald Trump throwing the first pitch at a Boston Red Sox game in 2006 </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-05 06:06:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-04 21:50:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Or folks with real experience are to see a  36 years old bitch boy taking tasks *far* beyond his scope (he was in goddamn real estate) and they're gonna start shoving and create massive infighting. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-04 20:32:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Totally! When I was first walking into it, I described it as like stepping into the inside of a rainbow. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-04 20:31:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Milo? Bill O'Reilly? Ailes? And [mannnnny more](http://www.ranker.com/list/people-fired-from-fox-news/rydavis). Is there some kind of syndrome all these scumbags have? Is there something inherent about the Republican party that draws in the most disgusting people? I wonder. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-04 17:20:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Good question. The French Revolution gave it a hit, but   
[Much of the chapel as it appears today is a re-creation, although nearly two-thirds of the windows are authentic.](https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Sainte-Chapelle#Later_reception_and_restoration)  
  
Another tidbit I learned when I was there is that it was built to house a relic [Crown of Thorns](https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Crown_of_thorns#France) that cost more to purchase than it cost to build the church itself.  
  
bonus edit: [here's a 360 pano of the space](https://www.google.com/maps/@48.8552417,2.3451117,3a,75y,148.88h,121.23t/data=!3m8!1e1!3m6!1s-YUumWFved5k%2FV0zw11bpkeI%2FAAAAAAAAv1Y%2Fq2PSQ7ZFkCAm_r5v87uPyoYRvZVwnQ0ewCJkC!2e4!3e11!6s%2F%2Flh4.googleusercontent.com%2F-YUumWFved5k%2FV0zw11bpkeI%2FAAAAAAAAv1Y%2Fq2PSQ7ZFkCAm_r5v87uPyoYRvZVwnQ0ewCJkC%2Fw203-h100-k-no-pi-0-ya283.71457-ro0-fo100%2F!7i7168!8i3584!6m1!1e1) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Steps away from Notre Dame is Saint-Chappelle, completed 100 years before in 1248, it's wall-to-wall, floor-to-ceiling stained glass </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-04 17:01:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-04 15:28:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It was insanity. Every comment I made here would garner 5 psychotic responses. Now... crickets. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-02 02:59:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It is definitely time to just call it like it is. Dems have been playing nice for far too long and look where it got us. It got us Trump. Now I'm not saying be nasty, but rather, be honest. Be honest about their agenda, what it really means for America. And since the Republicans are the party of the past, to contrast that Democrats need to clearly define how they are the party of the future, and they must completely and clearly define what a bright future of America *should* look like. It's time for big balls politicking.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-01 20:25:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Still amazes me that the party of God and Country voted for a thrice-married molestor who couldn't give a fuck about God. How could millions of Christians in good conscience choose such a man? It is absolutely baffling.  
  
Edit: not even the party, the individuals themselves who claim Jesus as their savior. I mean what do they think Jesus would think of a guy like Donald J Trump. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-30 14:25:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I don't get it. A whistleblower from inside the whitehouse? Leaking information that Nunes won't show us? How is it a whistleblower then? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-29 23:38:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> D- until clarified </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-29 16:06:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Nunes is complicit and he's a gatekeeper. Who watches the watchmen? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> A grieving mother in Wester Mosul this week </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-28 21:59:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-28 02:39:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I saw my own father on death's bed. He lost his job in the recession and receded into wine bottles. For months he did nothing but drink wine. Would go to the grocery store at 10 am, pick up bottles and swig all day. He was in such a delusion. I spent every day trying to snap him out of it, but to no avail. It was brutal, seeing the kindest sweetest smartest man I knew get reduced to a zombie, his soul was taken from him. One day I was upstairs my sister yelled I ran down he was on the ground convulsing. He had gotten so saturated the liquor had won over.   
  
Ambulance came took him away. He seemed moribund. We went to the hospital and they did what they do. Then they knocked him out. On the bed he was a bloated, shapeless, sallow form. He was not my father. Just this molasses colored blob. When eventually he came to, he didn't know what was anything. He kept trying to escape, pulled the catheder out, didn't know us.   
  
That was some six years ago. He made it out, did rehab, and been clean since. [Here he is](https://static1.squarespace.com/static/55805638e4b03608a941dabc/558245a6e4b0e4c2b1545bde/56bb7cae859fd0422da8d452/1455127729894/8mqO6DO.jpg?format=750w). Works out every day, rides his bike, back in form. That good man that got pulled under got the second chance, and he has made the most of it, spreading good in all he does. I am so freaking blessed, I don't know who I'd be now if the end of his story had been as a blob on a bed. Me and my two sisters still all have dreams where he starts drinking again. Thank all that life gives those who want it their second chance. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-27 23:29:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> "Son if you don't kill me from stress it'll be with a lightsaber." </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> My first night at the Opera, in Teatro dell'Opera in Rome </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-27 12:54:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-26 21:34:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Dude no way that shit's *basically* heroin! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-26 20:30:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Could only have been carved by the patriot palms of woodmaster Ron Swanson. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-25 19:50:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Actually it does have something to do with Trump. He reorganized launching strikes so that the authority goes further down the hierarchy. Under Obama these types of strikes went up to higher channels for authorization. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Johann Friedrich Julius Schmidt's model moon, completed in 1854 after five years of construction </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-25 03:49:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-24 16:39:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yabba dabba flabba </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-23 01:39:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The reality of it is already ridiculous. Wonder if /r/conspiracy is bothered by this news? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> On Valentine's Day of 1884, Teddy Roosevelt lost both his wife, and his mother- this is his journal entry from that day </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-22 21:42:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-22 16:59:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The thing about diamonds is they never stop shining.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-21 13:01:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The rurals will have you all lose your jobs, if they don't have em you can't have em either. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-20 14:46:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Sucks when you drop a clever comment only you check later and you see you spelled something simple stupid. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-19 23:44:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Wow awesome insight. I can't argue with 10 years of cloud reporting- apologies that my eyes were tricked here </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-19 23:39:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The sun's setting right now so it's at a low angle- </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-18 02:02:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That's the thing. That happened. Flynn was in on it. Session and Kushner talked to the diplomat too. Thing is, they didn't push for that and sanctions just because. No, there was a deal. Russia gets sanctions pulled and in exchange Trump team gets..... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
