<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject1790</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> As they fight the opioid crisis, counselors see a grave new threat: the GOP </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-10 14:50:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-10 14:15:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Two words that destroy pretty much every conspiracy theory  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-10 14:13:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Then the holograms would take over! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-10 14:12:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Uh

What? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-10 14:09:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> They seem like red pillers who are self aware of the fact that no one cares about them </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-10 13:35:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I loved when slay knocked dez Bryant down  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-10 13:29:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> At this point would it take that much money? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-10 13:22:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I mean it was enough for the wolverines to dismiss him during the season </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-10 13:17:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Because he can play football good </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-10 12:19:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Forgetting to pay your bills is a mistake

Beating on a woman is a character flaw  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-10 12:16:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Frank Clark has always been a scumbag </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-10 12:15:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Well she's a woman expressing an opinion and this is Reddit  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-10 11:57:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thanks country bumpkins </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-10 03:44:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I don't sympathize. Most of the problems of small towns are self inflicted. They oppose tearing down old houses for new businesses, they don't want things other than manufacturing entering their areas. It is very much known that people who are able to do something with themselves will leave the area </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-09 22:00:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> We've ready got a guy for that </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-09 21:53:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Beyonce is actually very impressive for being as big as she is without having a billboard #1 album in a long time </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-09 21:51:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I grew up in a small town and since a young age viewed the US as the "melting pot of the world ". It was disappointing when I got older and found out how a lot of backwoods people around me thought about that topic  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-09 21:45:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If being inclusive to all Americans is why they aren't showing up then it's better slamming the door on them and leaving them in the cold </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-09 21:44:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I wouldn't even say democrats completely ignored them. They had infrastructure plans. They just didn't bother advertising them

Also at the end of the day those plans would have been difficult but necessary and Trump promised the impossible </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-09 21:41:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It can be summarized as small towns mad at cities for leaving them behind </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-09 21:38:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm assuming you left that area? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-09 21:36:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I don't believe that sizable portion of them will change and have adopted a philosophy that it is best to let small towns fail. They are disappearing on their own and are now only propped up through federal tax money that disproportionately comes from cities  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-09 21:33:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> http://www.chronicle.com/article/The-Rural-Brain-Drain/48425/ 

This may be interesting to you  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-09 21:27:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You shouldn't make excuses for adults who refuse to ever get out of their Podunk town and see another place in this country </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-09 18:47:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The main thing I'm questioning is if future Barry kills iris then what made him originally turn to savitar? It seems like a backstory episode is needed  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-09 17:52:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Watch film last season to see how bad hyder was at holding the edge. I wouldn't call whitehead a run stopping specialist, he's just not good at anything else </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The Lions had one of the most effective offenses in 2016 - Pride Of Detroit </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-09 17:48:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-09 17:37:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Get off our lawn! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-09 17:37:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> We're used to it  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-09 17:08:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Too brown for them </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-09 17:05:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> A group that lets themselves be modded by people from TRP shows what kind of people they are </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-09 17:03:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Atlanta is nice
 
You just don't want to leave the metro area  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-09 16:59:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Inclusion for one.

Perhaps many felt as if their voices weren't going to be heard by someone that didn't even bother to listen to their concerns 

All the white kids stating that black people didn't get Sanders and that's why they didn't vote for him didn't do much to get minorities behind him either. 

This is compared to someone who had decades of outreach within that community. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-09 16:55:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It pulls the most basic self help stuff to hide the radical misogyny 

It is not a place for decent people </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-09 16:31:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> He's a loser from TRP he has nothing useful to offer anyone </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-09 16:29:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'd hardly call Sanders as having a diverse group of fans.

This article does a good job at mentioning his issues

http://fusion.kinja.com/how-bernie-sanders-lost-black-voters-1793860129 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-09 16:25:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Maybe the Vikings fan is from west Virginia  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-09 16:17:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Well I need some eye bleach to unsee that </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-09 15:41:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> These kids are not here for discussion so we shouldn't try and debate with them. Just bash them down until they leave </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-09 15:38:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Reddit only bans subs that give them bad press </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-09 15:37:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The subscribers of that sub will still be unemployed but soon they'll lose their healthcare too </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-09 15:34:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Small towns oppose democrats because the two options are someone lies about how they'll bring low skill manufacturing back and the other one talks about a path forward that'll be difficult but necessary and they keep buying the bullshit instead </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-09 15:28:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Well they had that one miss </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-09 15:24:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> He didn't offer anything reasonable. All he complained about was not being good enough to be employed in a global marketplace  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-09 15:00:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I think it is a record. 

It's just important to remove that from lawson's performance since it was not his error and it makes a bad number on his average penalty yardage </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-09 14:15:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Wasn't Tim Wright only 225? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-09 14:14:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'll just be happy to see him come in on 3rd and medium to 3rd and long.

A LB who can actually cover  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> New Detroit Lions CB Jamal Agnew 'a big-time competitor' </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-09 14:12:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-09 14:08:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Digs was pretty bad last season. With all the new guys at corner I could see him out </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-09 14:07:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Tomlinson should be an option on the block and depending on how we look in preseason so should hayden. He's on a one year deal and picking up Tabor might make him expendable </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-09 14:04:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> James, Wick, O'Conner, Bellore, Armbister, and Carter 

O'Conner and wick are PS options  

I think Landes makes the team over Muhlbach </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-09 13:59:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's possible. Lawson's biggest issue is not making plays on the ball. He has good coverage. If he can start swatting the ball or picking it off then he would be an appealing FA. Teams overpay on corners  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-09 13:57:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> At the money we gave him he better be playing. My hope is that Tabor proves me wrong and can start which would let us deal hayden in the preseason if both look good. He's making too much this year to cut him </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-09 13:55:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah but that was a terrible call. 

The NFL apologized to him later that week  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-09 13:54:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Unless he has a great year then I don't see it. He doesn't get a lot of interceptions </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-09 13:54:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> He has good coverage but he doesn't make a lot of plays on the passed thrown at him. 

If Tabor is good which I'm skeptical on then Lawson can move inside to nickel which in my opinion he's better suited for. His height won't be as much a disadvantage inside. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-09 12:16:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Stick to cities and you'll be fine  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-09 12:15:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm hopeful that his policies destroy small towns </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-09 12:14:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I've thrown myself fully into the idea that it's best for rural areas to collapse.  They take way more than they receive and want nothing but to roll the clock back to the 60s </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-09 03:18:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Wut </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-09 03:15:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Both sound like terrible schools for bio </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-09 03:14:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yep. Ours doesn't make us think he's 15 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-08 21:06:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The amount of agreement with that guy is a sign of that community  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-08 21:04:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yep. We've seen them make up stories of what monsters are in the white house for over 2 decades yet when one is in there who is the corrupt monster they've described they fall in line  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-08 19:54:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Looks like le pen captured the social rejects demographic  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-08 19:13:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Because she is a xenophobic nationalist  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-08 18:56:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The real question is why didn't he pick up a rock </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-08 18:51:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Ok George Carlin  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-08 18:48:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Because they both used populist overtones. And people don't research candidates nearly well enough  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-08 18:39:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Can Franklin play Mayhew? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-08 18:31:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> For me Abdullah is much more important than Theo. The offense for that first game and a half was so much better than the rest of the season. Once ameer went down we lost our ability to run the ball. If Abdullah was in teams would have to respect the run and we would be able to throw it deep </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-08 18:25:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Don't let this distract you from the fact that the Minnesota Vikings first home loss in their new stadium was to the Detroit Lions </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-08 18:24:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So he was an eagles fan? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-08 18:22:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm expecting a surprise out of Cornelius Washington.

I think ebron will have a very good season if he stays healthy. If not him then I'm interested in how Glasgow does in his second year  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-08 18:19:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Rural towns heavily back GOP. That isn't going to change </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-08 18:18:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Voter turnout in the cities was really bad. Rural areas voted the way they always do </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-08 18:17:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Great news! Glad to see Burleson doing well </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Notes: Former Lions WR Nate Burleson lands job on CBSs pre-game show - Pride Of Detroit </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-08 18:16:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-08 16:24:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> My empathy went away when they turned down job retraining and voted for someone who preached about doing things that would hurt others.

They were fine voting for him when it looked like he wouldn't hurt them. 

Growing up in the rural Midwest also did not make me very empathetic for them. Even when they had options they did not seek to get trained on something needed and instead would just tell people "the factories will come back" </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-08 15:33:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yep so shameful being a well adjusted adult. The fact you're using it as an insult reflects more on you  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-08 15:24:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I don't want to look up of Oklahoma Baptist college is a thing.

It sounds like a shitty school some backwoods redneck would go to though </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-08 15:21:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> He absolutely means he's super white. He's also holding it as a banner because he has nothing to offer society  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-08 15:19:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> All you need to see about that subreddit is their reaction to the idea of minorities outnumbering them. They seem afraid of being treated as bad as they want to treat other people </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-08 15:14:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Neonazis in a Trump subreddit?! Color me shocked </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-08 15:13:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> My experience of living in rural areas has definitely made me very cynical of them. I don't see anything there worth saving. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-08 15:11:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Man those losers get really mad when they don't get their way  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-08 15:06:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's because they lined up behind a nationalist and are still mad that the world isn't theirs. Even worse is that some minorities are still more affluent than them. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-08 15:04:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The conspiracy mindset springs from an inability to reconcile that the bad things in the world are not due to a select cabal manipulating things but due to random chance.

A key part to is that this secret force makes things harder than them and that is why they aren't more successful in life. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-08 15:01:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Posts like this are why I got on Reddit this morning  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-08 14:56:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Well JCM is still an idiot </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-08 14:53:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> 
Automation has taken low skill labor away not free trade.  Complaining about them not adjusting by getting trained to do something else is similar to complaining about farmers not changing when the industrial revolution took off.

I feel for people facing addiction but at some point they do make a choice to continue doing heroin.

Wal-Mart is bad but they choose to shop there. If they don't want their local stores run out of business then they need to be willing to pay a little more. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-08 14:48:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I think you're ignoring that many of those people have left the Midwest. I was one of them. The Midwest has been trending in a very conservative direction lately. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-08 14:14:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I grew up in a rural town. I'm very aware of the issues there I just view many of them as self inflicted

The experience of growing up in those areas drives my feelings towards those communities  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-08 13:52:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> In a global economy it ignores how the world functions. And if we're talking about modern usage then economic nationalists are usually just a cover for ethno nationalists </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-08 13:48:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Technology infrastructure is a necessity for companies to invest in a region.

In either case there were also job retraining plans but they voted for someone who promised to roll back the clock to the 60s. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-08 13:44:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm always surprised that everyone blames free trade instead of automation for losing their job </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-08 13:43:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> In either case only a moron backs nationalism </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-08 13:37:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Blue states not subsidizing red states anymore would be great
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-08 13:33:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Not like they won't vote for him next time  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-08 13:31:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> No they really are not.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-08 13:26:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If the wannabe fascist didn't make them break party than I don't think they will.

At a certain point you have to face that the racist parts didn't alienate a lot of them and was a big draw  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-08 12:15:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Medicare strikes again. A huge number of Trump voters are on the Medicare expansion. 


Only good part about this 

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-08 12:14:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Because the cities didn't show up to vote. The rural towns were always racist </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-08 11:58:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> They can move to a decent state </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-08 11:52:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Towns are failing though. Rural brain drain has only accelerated. They rejected the candidate who wanted to expand rural infrastructure like increased cell phone access </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-08 11:39:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The people complaining about economic anxiety do respond to racist dog whistles though </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-08 11:37:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So stop bailing out small towns and people will be forced to live around cities weakening rural America's voting ability  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-08 11:35:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So in other words people were mean online and it made rednecks vote for a racist candidate? They deserve more responsibility for their choices  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-08 11:32:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> No we don't. People just need to show up </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-08 11:30:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> They want to roll back time to the 60s. Nothing they advocate would work. They would impoverish the country just so rednecks could have their low skill manufacturing jobs  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-08 04:26:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So why do country bumpkins deserve special treatment? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-08 04:23:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Oh please everyone whines over the heroin epidemic and coal workers losing jobs but you focus on drug and a lack of jobs in the inner city and people say they need to work harder </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-08 04:22:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I grew up in rural America. He's correct </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-08 04:21:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah post election I took on an idea of let them fail. They are a drain on society and don't give back anywhere near the amount they take </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-08 04:19:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I doubt it. They're not very smart. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-08 04:18:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Maybe they should move to where jobs are or get trained for something needed instead of whining and trying to reverse the clock back to the 60s </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-08 04:17:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> As someone who grew up in the Midwest it really doesn't. The cities are nice but the towns are terrible </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-08 04:16:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> He should focus on the rural areas

They weren't a 60/40 split </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-08 02:28:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Then they get so mad you looked at their public profile </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-07 16:27:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> P R O J E C T I O N

R

O

J

E

C

T

I

O

N </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-07 16:21:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I remember them getting bent out of shape at the black Swedish runner at the Olympics  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-07 15:38:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> http://www.snopes.com/bill-nye-gender-chromosomes/ </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-07 05:17:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Subscribed. Thanks for the new sub </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-06 17:47:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> We paid a lot for a DE so that could be interesting </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-05 21:45:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm just very skeptical that the hamstring affected him as much as he acts like it did. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-05 21:24:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> He also ran a 4.7 at his pro day. I've seen Treadwell say he was great only problem is Treadwell sucked his rookie year. He could barely crack the lineup on a bad offense.

I'm afraid that Tabor is gonna get burned a lot </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-05 15:59:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Kentucky will vote for them again </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-05 15:58:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Like yall, Im still waiting to see if its a boy or a girl, said Sen. Lindsey Graham (R-S.C.). Any bill that has been posted less than 24 hours, going to be debated three or four hours, not scored? Needs to be viewed with suspicion

My favorite quote </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-05 15:52:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I think of them as a slower oversized wr. Blocking is not focused as much in the college game as it used to be so that is probably the reason for the change 
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-05 15:48:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I don't think Lawson will lose his job immediately if anything he would drop to the slot  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-05 15:48:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> At 2.5 million guaranteed he would have to be pretty bad to not make the team. I imagine he would be above Tabor for this season and start at nickel. Admittedly I am much more skeptical of Tabor than many I'm this sub </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-05 15:30:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The way I see it is they voted for a bully because he told them he would reverse the clock for them and they were happy others would get hurt. They are only upset now because it turns out he lied to them and will hurt them too. This doesn't make me feel empathy.

Also I grew up around a lot of these people and I saw a lot of their problems were self inflicted. I also noticed how exclusive and rigid these towns were. That experience made me very cynical towards them. 

I used to have a little empathy but even having seen the issues rural towns have this election killed what little empathy remained.

Also I'd avoid using the term "globalist". Conspiracy theorists frequently use it as a way of saying Jewish. 

I'll link two articles one is about the problems facing rural areas that takes a more empathetic approach and talks about rural brain drain and how it is impacting these communities and the other is about the problems with the mindset in rural areas and who they blame. The chronicle one seems to touch more on what you are arguing for. I agree with the problems they bring up but I'm not sure their solutions would work.

http://www.chronicle.com/article/The-Rural-Brain-Drain/48425/

http://www.nationalreview.com/corner/432796/working-class-whites-have-moral-responsibilities-defense-kevin-williamson </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Detroit Lions draft Q A: Jalen Reeves-Maybin always gave 100 percent at Tennessee - Pride Of Detroit </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-05 14:56:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-05 14:22:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The coal miner should seek to move somewhere else for work. People used to do it all the time. Not only that but those places are resistant to anything new opening up. Call centers are a great option but they are against doing that type of work.

As for the section about minorities. I was referring to minorities in the US not being shut out from jobs that they used to be shut out from.

Since you also seem to blame free trade; automation is what took these jobs away and the death of coal is due to the free market, natural gas is a better option. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-05 13:15:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I mean we can be concerned about both things  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-05 12:16:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> All 2 of you? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-05 12:16:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Don't worry they'll lose when it counts  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-05 12:11:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Most of the time subreddits get banned because they catch the attention of the media.

Fph on the other hand harassed imgur admins for deleting their photos and if I recall brigaded a subreddit for helping people deal with suicide   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-05 11:33:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Very few in rural America work on food production. They have refused to move forward and adjust to the changes to the economy, disliking that they need either advanced training or the fact they have to compete with minorities for labor.

Meanwhile they take more than they give back and have the gall to complain about overspending. And my lack of empathy comes from having lived in a rural town. The election just freed me from the little empathy I used to have </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-05 04:27:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Wow. That is a crazy difference </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-05 03:26:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> He now does indie films so it makes sense </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-05 03:14:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Have you seen the Netflix special on David brent? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-05 03:13:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The UK version was better  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-05 01:51:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Wish I lived in district 6 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-05 01:45:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Be disgusted with our rural citizens. They hold us back </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-05 01:44:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> And the mechanic will want to know which half. 



So toss the rural part out and build off the urbanized side </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-05 01:42:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I don't feel empathy for them. I hope small towns crash. I'd love it if we took away farm subsidies  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-05 01:37:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's actually closely tied into viewpoints of evangelicals </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-05 01:34:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I mean I'm kind of at the point of thinking too many are too stupid to keep saving

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-04 20:58:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Cheap political points to bring back and tell their supporters </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-04 20:56:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> GOP Expected To Pass Its Health Care Bill At Long Last, But Still A Long Way To Go http://n.pr/2qDpi9U

This has some answers for you  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-04 20:51:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> They make me think of Stepford Wives </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-04 20:50:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I agree but he complained about downvotes. That's a near automatic downvote for me. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-04 20:47:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Pretty high. It'll either be massively changed or shot down. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-04 19:22:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> He ate a toddler didn't he? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-04 15:36:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Apparently he laughed at the rap battle ERB did of him </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-04 14:57:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I think it was a thing in a really bad Dexter novel that was immediately ignored in the next installment  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-04 14:56:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I always love seeing it when their family abandons them </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-04 04:28:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> They don't though. Many backed trump </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-04 04:17:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Realism </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-04 04:16:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Of course it was Texas  

He'll lose bad  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-04 03:40:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm wondering if it's some Barry from a different dimension  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-04 02:08:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm afraid it'll be Tabor.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-04 02:00:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Oh me too.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-04 01:12:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> North Carolina really is worst Carolina  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-04 01:09:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> And atlanta isn't exactly a red area </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-04 01:08:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Shit if we pulled farm subsidies they'd flee small towns  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-04 00:59:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Outside of Ann arbor and detroit metros michigan is just a frozen part of the deep south. And those are the areas that'll be most affected by this. Oh well enjoy it suckers. Low skill manufacturing isn't returning either  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-04 00:11:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I hope they don't. 

Let it be an albatross.

This is what people voted for let them deal with it
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-03 23:59:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> There are lots of socially conservative Hispanic people </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-03 23:59:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The first one had no changes for cost of living to get the subsidies

Families had to make 70000 to qualify. That would have hit rural towns like a boulder  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-03 23:57:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> They don't need to support it </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-03 23:56:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This is why I think it's in the best interest of the country if the cities stop funding small towns and let them collapse </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
