<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject6310</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> More Connective paths between cities and other refuge areas </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-21 23:50:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> TL;DR subway tunnels or other connections could be used to make short range weapons more viable when travelling from city to city.   

 nbsp;

So this is the conversation i've been hearing happen on the front page. 

Person A: Not enough loot with the new update can't find an AR within the city.  
Person B: You just have to search more, this is a looting battle royale game, try going to other cities.   
Person A: Yeah but to get to other places to loot i have to cross over wide open expanses and unfortunately the mini uzi and shotgun i found don't have the range or accuracy to suit the chance of a battle in that kind of environment.     
 nbsp;

I changed the wording up a bit to fit my need, but you guys get it. In this case with the new patch loot is right where it needs to be. AR's are rare and subs are not. What is not on point is the map. Besides some little clusters of cities with CQC area's, usually AR/Sniper rules the land. There are way too many open fields and expanses between cities that suit rifle play and not shotgun/smg/pistol play.   
 nbsp;

What i am suggesting for the next map is there should be more inter connectivity between the hotspots. 
Some examples could be
 nbsp;

-subway network underground that connects the cities as an alternate means of travel  
-more ridges and hills that can give cover while moving from city to city  
 nbsp;

These different networks connecting the cities could be help for any player not lucky enough to find a long range rifle in their first drop point and travel where their weapon that they picked up would be viable.   

To make these areas not so OP we could have the subway tunnel flood in certain areas (kind of like the red zone)  
   
 nbsp;
Just my thoughts  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-21 23:23:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> 50 buildings? so you loot all of Georgopol by yourself, then move to Rozhok and then you find an AR? your story seems super fishy </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-09 18:52:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> ah i see, i did misunderstand just a bit but you cleared it up. Originally you were playing in that style where you hunted people down, but just weren't able to find someone or got killed by someone just hiding in a corner using 3PP. So begrudgingly you decided to go with the flow of the game instead. Thanks for explaining that! What do you think they can do to quicken up that mid game? im drawing a blank </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-09 18:41:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> maybe I am misunderstanding, but didn't you complain about people not going out hunting others and just camping? here you admit to sitting in one spot yourself. I feel you're feeding into your own problem. I apologize if i misunderstood the context.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-31 23:30:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> My friends and i just call it PUB-G very easy to say 
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-27 23:50:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> hey i found the guy that screams at the top of his lungs on the plane! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> How to get your pioneer crates for cheaper. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-27 04:38:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If you didn't already know, changing your characters appearance for 3k will reset your crate prices back to the original 700 price. My suggestion would be to get up to the 4200 price and pay 3k to reset your character and rinse and repeat the process. Also if you're asking, Yes you do keep your clothes that you earned. 

Bonus tip: you can right click and sell your items that have been earned </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> When the nerds find out about your secret spot </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-27 03:56:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-02 19:36:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> i know what you're saying baby, what im saying is when i start auto running and i hit the in game chat key i stop in place. it doesn't matter whether im autorunning or autofarming. It stops all movement as soon as i bring up in game chat.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-02 19:32:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> i have a key to run, its just whenever i bring up game chat i stop running. Any solution to that?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> (QOL) type in game chat and run at the same time </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-02 17:02:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> (Suggestion) Tampons should be added to the game </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-19 23:11:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> -Cost 10 cloth  
-Instant stop bleeding  
-Heals only 1 point  
-Quicker than applying a bandage  
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
