<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject9720</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-08 03:15:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Sadly yes. I think part of that is because the police didn't take it seriously at first. If they had maybe he'd have been caught. Even with the later postcard there was very little to go on. There's always a chance he might send another. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-08 02:43:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Teachers who hurt the students they are supposed to protect make my blood boil. I'm sorry that happened to you. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-08 02:42:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I got the post card in 2010, right as I was going into graduate school. I'm sharing it now because every lead has gone cold. I was barely a teen when this happened. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-08 02:16:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Really badly at first, they've become more overly protective and paranoid because of it. But they're hanging in there. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-08 01:57:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The police have the postcard. Unfortunately all they found were smudged fingerprints. And they can't trace where it came from or where the picture was taken. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> I'll Take Very Good Care of Her </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-07 22:28:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> My sister Ashley had always been beautiful.  She was the first-born, my parents pride and joy.  No matter what grade she had been in she was always the most beautiful girl in the school.  I was several years younger than her, but I had always looked up to my sister with a kind of awed reverence.  When I was a child I had followed her everywhere, and for a long time we had been extremely close.  She was the one who was always willing to play hide and seek with me, and she would dress me up in her clothes when she had sleepovers with her friends.  Sometimes she would even let me stay up with them and chat about big girl stuff, which seemed so much more interesting than my world of Barbies and tea parties.

It all changed when she was around thirteen.  She was officially a teen, at least in her eyes, and she had begun to fill out into a womans body.  I was blissfully unaware that our relationship had changed.  However, she no longer let me follow her around, and her new favorite thing to call me was annoying.  

This had hurt me and I had retreated to my parents to tell them of how she had changed.  They laughed and said it was normal sister stuff and that I needed to leave her alone as she was getting older and did not have time to tolerate my childish attention.
Needless to say, she had always been the favorite child.  Not that my parents ever treated me badly.  In fact I had always considered them very good parents.  But with my sister they always had their blinders on, to them she could do no wrong.  When I realized that I did my best to avoid Ashley and give her the space she so desired.  It was almost like having a stranger living in the house with me.  As I got older I had hoped that we would be back to the close relationship we once shared.

Ashley kept herself busy, and my parents were always looking for things to add to her regimen.  They were obsessed with keeping her well rounded with extracurricular activities to make her eligible for scholarships.  Luckily she was naturally smart and athletic, and she fit right into gymnastics and always got her homework done on time.  Sometimes she would even find time to tutor other students who needed the help.  Between her homework, gymnastics, and her active social life she was always on the move. Even I was not immune, I was forced to join band and even take martial arts to pad out my high school resume.  

Boys suddenly became a huge part of her life.  From the age of thirteen to eighteen she always had a boyfriend somewhere, hanging around in the background. My parents were extremely strict though.  They were adamant that she not date anyone while she was in high school.  You got to focus on your grades, they would say, so she learned to be cautious and became a rather talented liar.  She mostly dated her friends brothers, so when she went to their houses to visit or study it did not raise my parents suspicions.  If they had known she had been having sex for years they would have blown a fuse that would have decimated at least a city block.

The only reason I had known about this was because I heard her giggling and telling her friends one day.  Yes, I was eavesdropping which I know was wrong, but I still did it.  Besides, they were in my house and they shouldnt have left the bedroom door wide open.  Luckily she didnt know that I had overheard her or I probably would have gotten a punch for being a snoop.
A few months before she was set to graduate high school the AP English teacher, Mrs. Bragg, had been diagnosed with cancer.  There was a huge outpouring of support for her as she was really loved.  Even though she was never my teacher I felt bad for her, as she was one of the few teachers that everyone liked and I had never heard a single bad thing about her.

With that news, and the fact that she would take a leave of absence, the school scrambled to find a substitute teacher to fill her place while she was gone.

They eventually found a substitute, and he sent the school into another uproar for an entirely different reason.  The new substitute teacher was gorgeous.  As in, he had to have been a model at some point in his life.  He looked like he should be sitting on a beach in LA rather than the halls of a high school.  Over six feet with brown hair, clear blue eyes, a perfect physique; it was not long before he had a legion of female admirers.  Before the end of the day every girl in the school had walked by the classroom trying to catch a glimpse of the new guy.  Even the female teachers were making their attention obvious.  

His name was Mr. Adam Ray, and he quickly became the most popular teacher in the entire school.  He even seemed to be really good at his job, I didnt hear anything bad about him at all.  And my sister quickly became his favorite pupil, for all the wrong reasons.

I had only seen him a few times around the school.  Since he was teaching the seniors there was never a reason to interact with him before.  There was something about him that always set me on edge.  It was the way he would interact with the students, especially the female ones.  The intensity in his eyes was unnerving, like a dog eyeing a piece of meat.  But since everyone else seemed to adore him I just thought I was crazy.  I was secretly glad I wouldnt have any classes with him.

Ashley started staying late after school not soon after Mr. Ray started teaching at the school, at first she said that she was staying late because she wanted to get extra help from her teachers.  Later she said she was staying late to help tutor other students who were struggling in English.  My parents nodded their approval and reminded her to put on her college applications that she was doing volunteer work.  She smiled at my parents and assured them that she would.

Months past, and my sister got accepted into college with a complete scholarship to her dream college in North Carolina.  We were all ecstatic for her.  She had worked hard and I remember both my mom and sister crying with happiness.  It was a month to graduation and my parents were already planning to throw a huge graduation party.  They were going to invite everyone they could think of and started sending out invitations.  Now, my parents are actually very wealthy so they treated this thing like it was a wedding.  They were spending enough that it might as well have been.

My sister had been getting more and more secretive though, the entire time her grades never slipped so it never registered with my parents.  In fact her English grades were fantastic, she had been getting straight As for months.  But since we shared a wall between our bedrooms I could hear her late at night talking on her phone, giggling, and even sometimes moaning which I didnt even want to think about too much.

I had my suspicions.  Her friends came over less and less and she started spending even more time away from home.  I assumed it was a new boy that had caught her attention, but I had no idea who it was.  She would frequently miss dinner and tell us that she had picked something up on the way home.  My parents started insisting that she come home for dinner on time every night, it was the first time I had ever seen them get even remotely stern with her.  She huffed and fumed but started coming home every night on time, but as soon as dinner was over she went into her room to study; but I could still hear the faint sounds of her talking on the phone with someone.

The day of the school graduation had arrived and my parents were prepared and beaming for the event.  My sister looked beautiful in her white dress that she wore under her robe, and my mom had taken her to the hair salon to get her hair done for the ceremony. Even I dressed up as I wanted to look nice for my sister on her big day.  She was getting ready to become an adult and go to her dream college.  She was even nice to me that day, which I relished.  I was hoping that while she was away at college I could come visit her, and maybe we could become close again like we had been as children.

At the school, we struggled to find a place to park and then shuffled awkwardly to find a place on the bleachers as every parent and extended family member seemed to come to these things.  When Ashelys name was called and there was huge cheer as she went to accept her diploma, she stopped and waved and my mom cried as she took her picture with the camera.  After her walk across the stage she stepped out into the hallway, to join her friends and the other students.  

My mom wanted to go and wait for my sister in the hallway, but we were boxed in and couldnt get out easily.  So we waited until the ceremony was over and everyone finally started filing out of the auditorium.  About thirty minutes had passed since we had seen Ashely walk off the stage and my parents were smiling ear to ear.  But we couldnt find her anywhere.  My dad even looked outside to see if she had given up on us and was waiting by the car.  She wasnt there.

My mom called her cell phone but all she got was voice mail.  By this time we had been looking for her for another thirty minutes and the hallway was mostly empty.  I spotted one of my sisters friends leaving and I ran over to her, asking her if she had seen my sister.  My sisters friend got this weird sort of smile on her face and laughed, telling me that she was sure that my sister had already left with someone.  I started getting worried, as I knew that she would have at least called us to let us know she had caught a ride with someone.

I ran back and told my parents and they just got even more upset, but they assumed that she caught a ride with a friend.  Perhaps she had been too excited about the graduation to call them.  Still, I knew she would be trouble for leaving like that.  We all just assumed that she was back at our house.  Thats where the graduation party was going to be so maybe she had wanted to get an early start.  We got back home in record time, hoping to see one of her friends cars parked there.  But we didnt see any of her friends cars there, which was weird since they were all invited.  The road was lined with lots of our friends and relatives cars, and I saw perhaps a dozen of my family members milling around in the back yard.

Once we parked my mom went into the house, and my dad walked towards the backyard.  I could tell by the way he moved that he was really angry.  I was certain that he would ground my sister from her own party at this point.  I stayed outside talking to my aunt and explaining the situation when my mom came running back out of the house.  She had a note in her hand and I had a sinking feeling in my stomach.  My mom was hysterical and couldnt speak so I gently took the note from her and read it to myself.

Dear mom and dad, 
By the time you read this I will be gone.  I know you wont understand this but I am in love.  Mr. Ray and I have been in love for several months and he has asked me to marry him. I said yes.  We are moving to North Carolina so I can attend college with my scholarship.  Mr. Ray already has a new job for the next school year and has promised to support me, so I will not ask you for money.  I knew you would try to stop us so I left in secret. Please dont be mad, Ill call you when I get to North Carolina.  Keep in mind Im eighteen and a legal adult so I can make my own decisions. I love you guys.

P.S. Youre really going to love Mr. Ray, hes the greatest guy in the world!

And under that note was another message, written in a fine cursive hand.  Dont worry, Ill take very good care of her.  

It was not my sisters handwriting, so I assumed it was Mr. Ray.
After reading this I handed it over to my dad who scanned the note and became completely red in the face.  He pulled out his phone and started calling the police.  My aunts consoled my mom and I ran upstairs to my sisters room. It was pristine, but I noticed that some things were missing from their usual spot. A framed photo of our grandmother was gone, along with a stuffed pink bunny that shes had for years.  I looked in the closet and her favorite clothes were missing. Not all of them but enough to show that a lot had been packed into a suitcase.  She was really gone.

The next few hours were a blur, the cops could do nothing as she was eighteen and not really a missing person until 24 hours had passed.  My parents and I called up all her friends, but they seemed to be deliberately unhelpful, and I suspected that they knew more than what they were telling us.  The food sat untouched until my parents insisted that people eat some so it wouldnt go to waste.  We even cut the cake that read Congratulations Ashley.  People ate and talked, no one had wanted to leave as they waited to see if there was any news about my sister.  Her graduation presents sat unopened on the counter until I moved them to the closet, they were too depressing to look at.

It was on the seventh day that we finally got some news.  Her suitcase had been found on the side of the road twenty miles from home.  It had been identified because her wallet and purse had been stuffed inside.  The news sent my mother into another fit of hysterics and she fainted.  

We also finally got one of her friends to talk to us when she came to our house in tears, saying that she had gotten a call from Ashley.  A phone number she did not recognize had called her but she ignored it thinking it was a wrong number.  When she saw they had left a voicemail she had listened to it.  It was a twenty second long message where my sisters voice could be clearly heard screaming for help.  A mans voice could be heard in the background and the call went silent.  My sisters friend was certain that it had been Mr. Rays voice.

After that her friends were a little more helpful with their information.  They told us that my sister and Mr. Ray had been having an affair from almost the very first day.  They thought it was romantic and helped her hide the relationship from everyone. It had been planned months in advance that they would run away together.

My father and mother did all they could to find my sister.  A private investigator was hired and it finally came out that Adam Ray was not who he said he was.  He had used a fake name and all his information was false. To give some context this all happened in the late 1990s, when smart phones were still years away and we still used dial up internet.  Looking someone up on the internet was not as simple as it is today.  Nowadays a quick google search would have revealed this guy had been a liar. His real name was Adam Raymond, but what made our blood run cold was that he had been in trouble with the law before.  In fact he had served time in jail for beating up a former girlfriend.  

Months went by and we had no idea what happened to my sister.  They never turned up in North Carolina.  They didnt turn up anywhere.  Adam Raymond had vanished from the earth and he had taken Ashley with him.  The investigation stalled for both the cops and the private investigator.  When that happened they hired other private investigators but they also turned up nothing.  My parents sued the school corporation for not running an adequate background check and letting a criminal into the school system.  They settled out of court for a substantial sum of money.

Years passed, all of my sisters friends went to college and graduated.  I graduated high school as well though it was a more subdued affair.  They even had a graduation party for me, but I could see it in their eyes that they were thinking of my sister the whole time.

I went to college, though I went to a nearby college so I could live at home.  My parents wouldnt say it but I knew they were relieved that I was close enough to them to keep an eye on me.  
I eventually graduated college, and I was getting ready to move out of my parents house to attend graduate school.  It was a happy and nervous time, as this would be my first time living on my own.  My parents even seemed proud of me.

I was sorting the mail one day in the few days before my college graduation.  There were a lot of cards for me, people sending congratulations through the postal service.  There was one card that stood out from the rest.  It was a postcard and it looked dirty and tattered, like it had sat on the ground before being put into the mail box.  I didnt think anything of it till I flipped it over and saw what was on the other side.  There was a Polaroid of a grimy and disheveled woman, wearing an oversized white T-shirt that looked just as dirty as the postcard.  I could easily make out her ribs and see the leanness of her legs, she reminded me of a holocaust survivor.  She wasnt wearing anything else. At that moment I froze, as I looked at the womans face I recognized her.  It was Ashley, emaciated and looking far older than a woman in her 20s should ever look.  Her gaze was vacant and empty, like a beaten dog, she didnt even seem aware that someone had taken her picture.  And beneath it was a short sentence.  Im taking really good care of her.
	
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-07 22:07:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I buy lots of things on sale. Cheap fruits and beans and rice! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-19 02:53:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I just ordered one! It's 52 after tax plus shipping. But I needed a nice new warm parka for winter next year.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-03 16:52:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I love Goodwill and thrift stores. All of my fall and winter clothing is from there. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-03 16:49:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Good for you! I try to keep my grocery budget at 200 a month for two people. Been doing it successfully for over a year now. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-24 20:56:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I hope that you FI/RE as soon as you can! Thank you for your reply, I'm always curious about life in other countries.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
