<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject9314</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-10 15:45:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> My first thought was of the British News column:

https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/William_Connor </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Lefty Reporter Jonathan Pie Gets It, Breaks Down Exactly Why Trump Won (US news site thought JP was real reporter - Nov 2016) </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-10 13:21:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Interview: Jonathan Glazer on Under The Skin </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-10 10:36:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-09 13:58:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Its not actually a part of the ZX80 which had no monitor and used a TV. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-09 13:46:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> /r/britishproblems is quite fun. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-09 09:33:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> There is a banana peel in the foreground, and what looks like another at the foot of the mattress. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-09 08:37:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Depends if there are any dumb jellyfish around there. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-09 01:22:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What do you mean by unnecessary?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-09 01:20:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It wouldn't in a vacuum chamber. (Aside from the fact that it would probably burst). </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-09 00:56:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> We could already feed all the world's poor. The reasons
 that we don't will not be surmounted in a reasonable amount of time, if ever. If we wait to eradicate poverty before going to Mars then we will never go.    

Also, money spent on Mars does not mean we won't have money to feed the poor.  It's not a simple matter of not having enough wealth.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-09 00:12:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I can see perhaps that one might need manual controls to move the car in a blizzard or other extreme conditions which the automatics can't handle. 

I really don't see any future in the idea of a self-driving car doing its thing while a person has to set there, ready to grab the wheel if anything goes wrong. Nobody will keep paying attention to the road for hours on end like that. There would also be no cost-saving for companies who currently employ drivers. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-09 00:09:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> In case the driver suddenly gets an uncontrollable urge to drink it?
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-09 00:04:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  Of course that's wayyy down the line.

You say that, but it is only fully untended driving which will change the world. Its that which will render driving obsolete as a job. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-08 18:19:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Bill Gates will be impressed. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> John Oliver's amazing new Net Neutrality video crashed the FCC's website </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-08 17:22:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-08 15:41:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> We should remain in the EU. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-08 14:51:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You need Piero Manzoni in your life:

http://www.tate.org.uk/art/artworks/manzoni-artists-shit-t07667 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-08 14:50:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> While I am sure this seems terribly funny to somebody who knows nothing of 20th century art history. It does seems rather ignorant. It's playful but rather dull.

It is a theme which has been thoroughly investigated by the art world, 100 years ago.


https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Readymades_of_Marcel_Duchamp


 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-07 23:17:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thanks, I think. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-07 15:57:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I think I need to see that one. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-07 15:56:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Episode 1 seemed ok as a starter, though I was bothered that he seemed to imply that the seas will rise due entirely to thermal expansion. My understanding is that meltwater is more significant.

I lost interest midway into episode 2. It didn't seem aimed at me, but perhaps to somebody much less knowledgeable. I suppose there must be such people but I doubt they would be watching it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-07 15:30:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I have seen knees being picked up by face-recognition. They were sort of facial knees though, if you know what I mean. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-07 15:29:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [Here's an uncensored version, if you feel the need.](https://metrouk2.files.wordpress.com/2014/12/ad_154595209.jpg)

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> A Diplodocus deconstructed </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-07 12:57:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-07 12:08:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What's that going across at the bottom of the frame?  A cliff or another wall? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-07 03:12:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I think the point was already made. There isn't a problem with the fashion industry irresponsibly using other non-healthy images.

I am not sure I'd call the use of very thin models a fad. It has persisted for many decades now. The fashion industry periodically acknowledges the problem with some token non-skinny models, but it just never cleans up its act. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-07 01:41:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Here's a recent picture of a Chelsea Pensioner.

http://www.toms-travels.net/wp-content/uploads/2010/08/30-08-10-085.jpg </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-06 19:57:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I think its this one. It looks like a phone, as the orientation is incorrect. However it appears to be mounted on the dash.

https://nypost.com/2017/04/05/passenger-from-hell-threatens-to-accuse-uber-driver-of-rape/ </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-06 19:05:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Maybe we need to give reddit a break? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-06 17:15:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Why didn't they call it a memument? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-06 15:24:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> There was a case of a passenger who threatened to accuse the driver of assault. He had a dash-cam if I recall correctly. She was banned by Uber. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-06 15:19:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah I was on my phone and couldn't find the words to describe the structure of spiderwebs. I still can't. 

Edit: it has come to me. The word I was struggling for was *spiral*.

https://en.m.wikipedia.org/wiki/Spider_web#/media/File%3AOrb_web_building_steps-01.svg </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-06 02:28:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It looks nice but not like a spiderweb. Spiderwebs are roughly circular. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-05 23:23:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It would be an act of war. That would be awkward regardless of China's attitude.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-05 11:17:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If they are plane mirrors they won't focus the sunlight, just redirect it. The area near the fence might be under double unfocused  sunlight though. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-05 01:03:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It'll have two posts and be forgotten.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-04 14:20:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I thought a rouge wave must be a thing. An 'actual' rogue wave doesn't seem very interesting. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-04 14:03:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I hate the word 'meat' and it occurs 32 times on this page. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-04 13:53:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So no example then?

Reading other comments that you have made it seems that you believe any international agreement means there is no sovereignty. This seems a bit silly. Why bemoan a supposed lack of sovereignty when no sovereignty exists anywhere? You need a better definition. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-04 09:29:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The UK entered into those treaties freely. They were voted on by our MEPs and ratified by our parliament. 

You might as well dispute the authority of the UK in any individual trade agreement that it makes. The nature of such agreements are of mutual concessions.   

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-04 09:26:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I laughed. Can you suggest something which the EU has done to us over which we have not had absolute authority?  

Pick your most egregious example and let's have a look at it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-04 01:39:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If you are concerned about Islamification then the proportion of Muslims is more significant than the gross numbers. I expect if Eastern European immigration is reduced but Indian and Pakistani immigration is increased as a consequence of post Brexit deals, then this will accelerate Islamification of the UK. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-04 01:34:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You seem to be assuming that all companies are in tough competition for their income, which isn't true. Many companies have reliable incomes and can be complacent.  Also it's not true that all government departments can be complacent about their incomes.  There are various incentives and trends to reduce budgets. 

There are some good examples of relatively efficient government activity if you look into it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-04 01:21:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yes but not everyone on the dole has the dole as their sole income. Hopefully that would be the minority.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-04 01:10:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> For many years their was an effective cap to Housing Benefit set at the median value of a sample of rents offered in the area. The new cap for all benefits was originally set at the level of average earnings and has been reduced to 80% of average earnings.  

The government has resisted doing proper studies of the effects of their changes. However it's clear to me, working in the field, that the majority of families affected by the new cap are Muslim. It doesn't seem unreasonable that the movement of those families out of cities into more rural areas might have had an influence on the EU referendum.      </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-03 22:59:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The UBI will be a large proportion of the income of the poor, but a small proportion of the income of the rich.  It will have a reduced influence on the politics of the rich. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-03 22:55:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> In the UK many businesses and government departments offer 'London weighting' which is additional pay for those living in Swinging London. There are also weighted parts to the calculation of Housing Benefit (welfare payments for rent) 

Lately welfare payments for expensive areas have been capped and this has encouraged migration to cheaper areas. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-03 22:44:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Doubling the dole would not double the money available to be spent by the population unless everyone was unemployed.  The idea is that most people have jobs and income from that. This means sellers could not double the price of goods if the dole doubled, as the dole would not be 100% of the money in the system.  It should he as small a proportion as possible. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-03 22:28:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I am not convinced that companies are in general more efficient in their spending than government-run organisations.  One difference might be that government adheres better to decent HR, safety and ecological policies. I don't welcome the private sector's tendency to cut corners on those.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-03 22:23:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The UN target for foreign aid is only 0.7% of GDP. Military spending is much larger. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-03 22:20:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Revenue? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-03 19:13:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> He's ok now you have seen it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-03 19:12:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yes. Tie a rope to your feet and have your friend lower you. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-03 19:08:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> For a moment I thought they were knockers. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-03 17:29:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I imagine he is setting it high so as to make the eventual figure look better. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-03 17:13:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I don't suppose its worth mentioning that the influx of people from the EU in recent years has reduced the proportions of Muslims in the UK?

That whole thing puzzles me. Why do people seem to think the EU is Muslim? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-03 15:46:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You could make that remark about any policy by any minor party. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-03 14:57:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> 'farticles' </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-03 14:40:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It would be interesting to know how many of his finacial interests now are related in some way to being popular with the Bush administration.

As for the oil point, I think it seems very likely that a wish to put the oilfields in more amenable hands was a motive. I actually am a little persuaded by the argument that a resource like that is too important to the whole world to be left in the hands of such a despot. 

Even if the reasoning was purely for the enrichment of Bush's personal friends in the oil and other industries, that's still a motive for Blair separate from war for the sake of war. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-02 01:15:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Prince Philip doesn't believe it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-01 18:45:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The miners did seem to want the mines and mining as a lifestyle to continue though. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-01 18:31:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It doesn't seem likely to me that the reason was that he wanted a war. He must have thought that the war would have effects which would be a benefit in some way, even if it was just for his own welfare. I don't see a direct advantage for him though. I don't think the after-dinner speaking circuit would have been so attractive for him.

Personally I hypothesise that he thought the geopolitical situation for the UK would be better after the war if we supported the USA, than if we had stayed out of it. He unwisely thought the advantages of this would outweigh the harm caused by using deception to justify our involvement. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-01 16:03:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What do you suppose his ill intentions actually were? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-01 15:41:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That's not the way it is often presented. There is a notion of happy, dignified, skilled manual workers, in their communities. I am not sure how real it is, I don't think my parents really expected to be anything other than skilled workers  and to stay at that educational level and income forever.

Think about the miners' strike, about Tony Benn's opposition to the right to buy council houses (though that was a popular Thatcherite policy). Films like *Brassed Off*.

These are just a few bullet-points as I am busy and can't write at length. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Leo Baxendale, star Beano cartoonist  obituary </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-01 14:54:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-01 14:33:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I think the historic Labour supporter base has largely died away. No-one aspires to be working class any more. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-01 14:32:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I guess it is even possible that he meant well, in going with Bush into Iraq. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-01 13:58:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Ah so the red-herring here is the idea that Deinonychus was in the movie? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-01 12:45:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> A dog lies near a log. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-01 12:44:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> A comparison of logs and dogs  

Both are very popular at Christmas  
But it is not generally considered cruel  
To abandon a log  
And dogs are rarely used as fuel  

-John Hegley, *Can I Come Down Now Dad?* </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-01 12:40:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I remember seeing a TV interview about *Jurassic Park* in which one of the designers said that they exaggerated the size of velociraptor, but later a larger raptor fossil was identified. Googling it now makes me suspect it was BS though as Deinonychus was first found in the 1930s. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-01 11:07:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> He would have got seven gallons of milk. One and then six because they had eggs. That always bugs me about this joke.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Why did the monkey fall out of the tree? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-30 22:52:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Because it was dead. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-28 19:47:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Aww </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> I thought this kitchen bin was wifi-enabled for a moment. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-28 14:51:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-27 23:36:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I know the story from this one:

https://www.goodreads.com/book/show/411477.Samurai_William </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-27 23:35:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I know the story from this book, which is a great read.

https://www.goodreads.com/book/show/411477.Samurai_William </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-27 14:40:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I went to a Catholic funeral of a gay friend who committed suicide after contracting AIDS. This was out of town and busload of his London friends went to his home town for the service.

His family and the congregation of the church had communion while we sat at the back. However when he was taken to his grave it wasn't in a Catholic graveyard but a Protestant one nearby. None of the congregation except his parents came to his burial. Suddenly it was just us, his London friends. Its been 17 years but it still makes me angry. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-27 14:26:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> However much  
You shake your peg  
The last few drops  
Go down your leg. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-27 13:58:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I have a colleague who tends to phone me and just talk at me, and there have been occasions when he has told me some very long complicated situation, and proposed a plan, with me trying to stop him all the way, only for me at the very end to tell him some fact that supersedes every point he made. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-27 13:50:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The first Englishman to go to Japan was William Adams who arrived there in 1600. He died there and was basically forgotten in England. However when Japan opened up to visitors in the 19th century, it emerged that he was well-remembered in Japan. There is a district of Tokyo named after him. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-27 13:16:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Ah yes it doesn't comply with the Representations of Upholstery Act of 2003. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-27 13:15:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I did that on a Japanese bed once. It looked like a soft western bed with blankets. The thin mattress was almost as firm as a board. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> A model of Lord Horatio Nelson's coffin, made from actual timber from his ship HMS Victory. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-27 00:43:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-26 23:18:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Ah OK thanks.

I suddenly wonder actually if he sat on the floor expecting to make a political point, or if he did so unaware that the press would make a big deal about it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-26 18:10:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It would mean he's not very observant. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-26 18:08:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  The other passengers agreed with him that it was full - they only filled the train up after staff came along and moved them on manually.

I am having trouble parsing that. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-26 14:34:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The NHS has gone 'Digital by default'. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-26 14:33:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> *Doctor Who* is always just finishing. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-26 14:32:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The one where people alternately look puzzled and cross at you for having an umbrella? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-26 14:27:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> OK. I have been talking about what happens when FGM is known to have been performed on a child.

I don't think yearly inspections are very workable, but it doesn't seem unreasonable to try and incorporate it into a health-check at some point.

I still don't really see how yearly inspections could make it worse. It would no doubt harm community relations, but probably not the FGM situation itself. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Britain might be getting a sex doll brothel </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-26 14:25:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-26 00:06:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  is kneejerk reactions which make things worse.

I see your edit. I am wondering in what way questioning the parents thoroughly could make it worse though? 

Remember we are talking about the grievous and permanent mutilation of children. It might be made worse if as a result FGM happened to more children, or more serious types of FGM were applied, or if children were harmed even more severely in some other way. I can't see any of those being a likely consequence. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-25 20:24:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm surprised that European Middle Earth already had potatoes, which were native to the Undying Lands. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-25 20:08:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I wonder if that prevented him from getting his leg over? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-25 20:03:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Gosh :

https://en.m.wikipedia.org/wiki/Wroc%C5%82aw_water_tower </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-25 19:52:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> There are many concrete water-towers in Europe, including new ones.  France has lots in particular. I guess they are cost effective. The UK has quite a few 19th century ones in brick.

https://encrypted-tbn3.gstatic.com/images?q=tbn:ANd9GcRuSdQ0eci_I4QuW-Hedlo-a37vmYfzkJ-QmyJXSxj4J5IPDZG11g </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-25 18:21:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I acknowledge all of that, but I think it would be pretty unusual for FGM to have taken place with neither of the parents knowing about it.

I also think that parents can issue instruction to their relatives not to do it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-25 18:14:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Well, they aren't actually. 

I'm encouraged by the statement, but discouraged by the results. We have over 150 known cases which have not been put forward for prosecution for various reasons. Are we confident everything that could be done to collect evidence was done? I am just not. Sorry.


victims of FGM may not want to report it if it means them being put into care or their parents interrogated.

Yes I have read about that. I think its a case where the well-being of other children outweighs the sensitivities of victims who enable the crime. Obviously child victims need to be treated with care, but adults, not so much if they are being obstructive. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-25 18:08:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> using them as some kind of deterrent? Come on.

No-one likes being arrested. If mutilating parents know that at a minimum they are going to give a full account of their actions, in a police interview room, then yes, I think that could have a useful deterring effect which is protective of people's rights.

we need level heads rather than desperation.

We need action. Currently everyone is standing around wringing their hands while hundreds of children are mutilated. How much longer should we hum and ha about it? It's been decades already and if anything its getting worse.

It could even make things worse.

I'm intrigued by that. What are you thinking of?

What do you suggest we do? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-25 17:51:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You really seem to lack understanding of how police interviews actually work. They are dull as ditchwater, even for serious rapes and murders.

Quite. Jazz them up a bit for these cases. Don't get distracted by the light-in-face description. It's figurative. There is certainly no harm in at least asking a parent if they knowingly caused grievous bodily harm to their daughter. I don't understand why everyone is so opposed to this.

Fine, but proving it is the hurdle they need to overcome.

Proof and prosecution isn't entirely necessary if parents get to know that they will be interrogated at length if they allow it to be done. That in itself can be a deterrent, and educative.

Also proof beyond reasonable doubt isn't required to take children at risk into protective care.

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-25 14:04:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Go good cop / bad cop until they give in and confess everything?

Yes exactly. That is something that might work, and which doesn't seem to be tried in this issue. It is done for other crimes so why not this?

Then what? Go to Ethiopia and arrest their Auntie who took them to some doctor who carried it out 10 years ago?

Extradition might be considered, but would surely be difficult. Mainly I'd like to see prosecution of the parents who sent them there for that. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-25 14:02:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> To be honest I don't know why we aren't prosecuting but I doubt it's a conspiracy. 

From articles I have read on it I think the main problem with prosecution is that it is rarely detected until long after it occurred, and the parents can just deny that they knew about it, to the extent that it would be hard to make a conviction stick. Also I expect there are 'cultural sensitivities' meaning the police are squeamish about arresting people, similar to the issues with Pakistani sex abuse gangs that we have seen. 
This is why I think a good thorough grilling for parents would be an improvement on the current situation. Some might make statements which make prosecution easier. Some might make statements which would justify the removal of their children from their household. Some would not confess but would find the process uncomfortable and would tell their relatives and friends what might happen to them.

there are stories of grandparents looking after kids who get it done behind parents' backs. Then the parents are in an awful situation too, how many of us would send our own parents to jail?

Haul the grandparents in, shine a light in their face and give them a thorough grilling for 24 hours. These people are serious and unrepentant child abusers. Don't let them get away with it scot-free. Don't let their enablers enable them.

We need to create an environment where the parents can come forwards and get help and support for the kids and if we only do that with blame and jail then, again, we will just push them away from the help the child needs.

I understand your sentiment, but I don't think there are significant numbers of people coming forward about this.








 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-25 13:47:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> https://www.fantasticfiction.com/p/kit-pedler/mutant-59.htm </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-25 09:28:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I don't think we have stopped those techniques in general. They can still hold a person for 24 hours without charge, and more on terrorist investigations.

What's your thought though? that there might be false confessions? This would be in the circumstances when its known that FGM has been done. I don't find it plausible that the parents would be unaware, in all but the weirdest cases. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-25 09:25:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> More like vulva inspections. Its a difficult issue. I think we need to allow the girls to refuse. I think there should be some type of routine detection process though. Maybe the schools should ask them? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-25 09:17:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Aside from the problems with detecting FGM, it does bother me that we are so slow to prosecute anybody over it. We know of over 150 cases and have only prosecuted a few recently, one of which was a surgeon apparently repairing damage.

I think we need to haul the parents of any FGM'd girls into a police station, and shine a light in their faces and interrogate them for 24 hours, at the very least. That doesn't seem to be happening. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-25 09:09:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It fits them like a glove. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-25 08:56:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I see the camera-person started the tradition of stopping looking a the subject when the good bit happened. At least they held the camera the right way up. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-24 21:15:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> At least it wasn't a box of Persil.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-24 14:22:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Saying your willing to fire first makes you a Kim

[Or a JFK](https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Flexible_response) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-24 14:14:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Some might argue that the strikes on Japan were right. I don't think its as clear as that personally. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-24 14:10:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I don't think NATO has had a change of policy on this, It has always promised a 'flexible response', in contrast to the USSR which had a no-first-strike nuclear policy.

Edit: Googling it a bit reveals the term 'flexible response' was a JFK/Robert McNamara innovation. This wiki article speaks of it in the past tense, but I can't find any indication that NATO has changed its policy.
https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Flexible_response </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-24 14:06:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> More correctly, he doesn't know the difference between use and detonation. They are strategic weapons which are used every day. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-23 21:23:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm glad to hear it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Securing Driverless Cars From Hackers Is Hard. Ask the Ex-Uber Guy Who Protects Them </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-23 21:23:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Securing Driverless Cars From Hackers Is Hard. Ask the Ex-Uber Guy Who Protects Them </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-23 21:22:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Spinal Tap Workprint - The Uncut Rainbow Trout Studios Fight </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-23 14:33:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-23 14:05:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I guess humour is subjective, but I don't see any. it just seems factual. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-23 13:20:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> *Adventure Hornblower* seems an apt name for it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-23 13:12:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yes that is a really nice one. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-23 05:14:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  Dragonfly eating a wasp.

That was taking a Beeeating. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-23 05:09:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Its a funny perspective though, as literally billions of newly-hatched male chicks are mashed-up alive by the egg-farming industry every year. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Whale Watching Boat Crashing Into San Diego Dock </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-23 05:03:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-22 22:58:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I for one feel that jumping around in front of cycling criminals falls within reasonable dispatch. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-22 21:56:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The bits about the etymology of 'zebra' are ok. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-22 21:54:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> When there is a central island the other opposite carriageway is not a completely different  crossing. It may be treated as a separate crossing in this context.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-22 20:14:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> He has not allowed him to cross first, and he is not on the opposite carriageway. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-22 20:11:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The rule means that he should wait until the pedestrian has stepped off the road, unless he is on the other lane and there is an island between them.

They were both being dicks but the cyclist was breaking the law and the pedestrian was within his rights. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-22 20:06:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  I go to San Francisco about once a year and every time I almost get hit by a bicyclist who is blatantly breaking the law.

How does he know when you are in town? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-22 14:57:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> even something small that happened over years and years.

Just what are you implyin'? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> This pedestrian means it. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-22 14:31:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-22 14:19:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I don't know them, I just saw it on imgur and thought /r/starwars might like it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-22 12:40:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Then sadly, money isn't going to fix it for him. Also the vid description implies that the US government hasn't tried to help. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-22 12:39:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  Where is he going to go, if he flies to the US? Who is going to be responsible for his ongoing care?

It seems reasonable to expect his son to comment on the situation. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> WHY IS JESUS WHITE ? - BY MUHAMMAD ALI </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-22 12:04:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Delivering the Death Star plans. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-22 11:55:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Biisuke Ball's Big Adventure Part 2 </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-22 11:34:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-21 14:19:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Is the server in the buffet responsible for that determination?

Supposing the customer did something more dangerous, like ask for coffee in a glass champagne flute?

I was amused that the customer in this story was so stubborn about it that they refused to use one disposable cup, and went thirsty. That achieved basically nothing. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-21 13:59:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yes its about civic access too. Local and central government is moving services online more and more. Internet access should be a right. There are public access computers in libraries and council facilities. They need to be protected. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-20 16:09:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Also the outlay for phones isn't much, and TVs are very good value, considering the usefulness of them for entertainment and information. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-20 16:07:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I dunno it worked for Trump. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-20 16:00:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It sounds fair enough. The buffet staff presumably don't have the resources to have customers sign a disclaimer to use their own mugs. Even then it would be a legally murky area concerning the company's liability, should the customer be injured. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-20 15:55:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> They do put a dent in things. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-20 14:06:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> All of it is sunny sometimes, apart from some crater-bottoms in deep shadow. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-20 14:04:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I love you. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-20 12:58:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> But there is no suction as such, only stickiness and viscosity. Sure you can die in sticky mud or quicksand. You are unlikely to sink though. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-20 12:28:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'd imagine the density of loose-packed grain in a silo can be lower than the density of a human body, so yes you could sink in that. Sand and water, especially sea water, is going to be more dense than human bodies. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-20 00:37:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You could probably squirm your way under, but there is no inherent downward direction to the stickiness or suction. There is gravity, and the flow of the mud, and the relative density of it compared to you.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-20 00:35:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Ah thanks. I saw the films but didn't remember that. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-19 23:41:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Pardon? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-19 23:38:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You actually reminded me of some student hi-jinks when a friend and I jumped into an ornamental pond for entertainment. It too was full of mud and for just a second it seemed as though we were both stuck with our heads under the water surface. Lots of wriggling freed us both though. The taxi-driver later that night was not pleased. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-19 23:27:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Unless Labour go full Blairite again they will no longer benefit from FTTP enough to form a government. PR Would secure them a loud voice in the future, during all governments. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-19 21:50:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Even then you wont be sucked under, but flooded and submerged that way. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-19 21:35:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That can be a bit of a bummer, admittedly. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-19 21:32:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Well there are plenty of cases of people getting stuck in mud and dying, but it usually takes something else to actually kill you.

https://youtu.be/HtkxQ1x6N20 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-19 19:43:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yes. A human body is more buoyant than mud or wet sand. You might get stuck but you wont be sucked under. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-19 18:20:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> How about And   Ampersand ? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-19 12:07:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I have had an experience when I was pretty sure a French waitress was pretending not to understand my spoken French. I thought it was a myth but it did happen that once to me. Having said that, I was with a female friend who dresses like a hooker. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-19 11:24:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> There is actually a lot of interest in mattress-store economics.

http://freakonomics.com/podcast/mattress-store-bubble/ </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-19 11:09:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I recently was asked to fill out my name, address, 2 numbers and email just to have a print-out of a quote. I wrote the amount down with a pen. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-19 10:38:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It sounds interesting. It does sound different to the UK were as far as I know anglers don't always expect to catch anything, I think there are some special private fishing ponds where that might be the norm, but not with general rivers, canals, lakes, or seas.

I'm surprised that the USA waters sound more closely managed than UK ones, which goes against my preconceptions of US wilderness etc. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-19 10:05:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I am British so we don't have a dept of natural resources as such. We do have British Waterways and various parks authorities who stock fish.

That could be beside the point though. If a US angler is bad at it and fails to catch fish because she uses the wrong type of lure, who is responsible for that? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-19 09:44:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Some licenses yes. In the case of fishing I'd expect to be able to fish, but catching something would be down to the natural conditions and fish behaviour, and my skill. I wouldn't expect the government to have a duty to provide those. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-19 00:10:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I don't really want to see his stomach pop out of his mouth. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-18 17:57:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> There were just enough more people with a Leave preference than Remain preference, so that even though fewer of the Leave preferring-people voted, they won. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> I am forming a mutual support-group for people who have been ripped-off by locksmiths. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-18 14:54:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> My door is always open. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-18 14:01:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> They are Not Poodles. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-18 09:35:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This would be good reversed, if he had jumped in backwards. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-18 09:28:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Oh yes, he was actually using atheists as an example of evil. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-18 09:23:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I love 80s pop. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-18 09:16:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I suppose this might be useful when we have self-driving cars, to minimise occasions when the cars need to stop. I am hoping they will not need to stop at intersections for red lights, as they will be able to interlace with traffic streams on other roads. Pedestrian crossings might be solved like this on multi-lane roads. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-18 00:19:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Is that Pope Francis who spoke up in support of the Charlie Hebdo murders?

 I didn't think anyone was listening to him any more, and let's face it the Vatican never were. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-17 15:47:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It happened in the UK 51 years ago, with a heap of government -controlled mining waste.

https://en.m.wikipedia.org/wiki/Aberfan_disaster </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-17 15:04:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That's interesting.  You make it sound like you expect to catch fish as a customer might.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-17 14:11:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I was disappointed that he did not provide any numbers for purchase price and 20-year generation potential when he announced them. He must have those numbers already. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-17 14:05:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Solar freakin' roadways are also solving a non-problem. Shortage of space is not really a limiting factor for commercial solar production. However doubling-up on function is hopefully worth it for a home generator. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-17 13:12:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Ah the old big and floppy mode. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-17 04:36:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> WW1 soldiers. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-17 04:31:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> She's his problem now. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-17 04:29:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I had a woman at work send me some mysterious messages from an alter-ego account on FB. The account was displaying her email address though. I played along with not knowing who it was. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-17 04:08:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What made you stop? I assume you can just stop with no risk of your clown-fetish confessions actually being sent? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-17 04:03:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Having that set just on your laptop is no good, What if the laptop is destroyed?

Here is a remotely-hosted one. (I don't know how good)

https://www.deadmansswitch.net/ </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-17 03:54:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I don't think you can really domesticate reptiles. They don't have the brains for it. Some reptiles make interesting but not very affectionate pets, but they are chosen for their inability to eat their owners. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-17 02:22:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> One thing counter to that that I have noticed, really since using reddit, is that some women claim the absolute right to have an abortion, because of their bodily autonomy. This is a harder, and more principled stance than that common in the UK, which is that abortion must be available when it would be harmful to the mother to continue the pregnancy. That is determined by two doctors here, not by the pregnant woman.

So there is a tension between the rights of the pregnant woman, and the right of the foetus, even though the foetus is not a person until it is born. (in the UK the time limit for abortion is set at the typical point at which a foetus can survive if removed from the pregnant woman's body). </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The year I hung out with Lou Reed at university [article] </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-17 02:15:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-17 01:28:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah it means great in the way that [great tits](https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Great_tit) are great. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-16 16:05:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I am picturing the chubby flaps. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Drivel Tube made these pictures move: Feb to April 2017 </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-16 01:25:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Peter Capaldi - The Graham Norton Show </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-16 00:02:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-15 23:47:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Welcome, traveller. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-15 23:45:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> No U. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-15 20:00:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It relevant because atheists are the only people who can assess all religions equally, on their merits. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-15 18:58:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That would be awesome. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-15 18:55:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> He just sounds like a Catholic mislabeled as an atheist, on the basis of that.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-15 16:50:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's not something to rush, though it does puzzle me that so many years usually pass while the appeals take place before most people are killed. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> SpaceX's plan to colonize Mars, explained (sceptical) </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-15 15:16:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> SpaceX's plan to colonize Mars, explained. (sceptical) </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-15 15:15:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-15 14:42:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> it is actually a downgraded version stripped out to be more affordable. Elon has been trying to bring this fact to light as much as possible.

Do you have any links about that? Sounds interesting. The point of the next Tesla is that it will be cheap enough to be a regular family car, one hopes. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-15 13:47:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Eww.

I really want to know what Elon was trying to say.

Edit: [here is the whole thing which does redeem it slightly, as they have a reasonable conversation before this part.](https://youtu.be/bF2-11LRHe8) I'd still like to know what he was trying to say at the end though. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
