<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject1044</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-10 02:32:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> These were made quite by mistake and easily by using 2x the amount of butter in a standard shortbread cookie recipe. They flattened out nicely and were buttery and crisp. You could adjust to taste I'm sure. I added chocolate ganache to the center. Finished w/ powder sugar. I also melted the butter, instead of softening.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-10 00:05:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Got a little drunk, deboned the brined turkey, cooked some sausage stuffing, turned the double breast over, plopped down the stuffing turned it back over and tucked it all in then baked it. I keep the legs and fry them later.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [Homemade] Stuffed brined turkey breast. From Thanksgiving. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-09 22:18:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [Pro/Chef] Mocha silk pie; chocolate cookie crust; sweet mascarpone </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-09 22:14:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-09 17:22:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Once it's set out and pics have been taken there is a separate wooden board for crostini and the cuttable cheese.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-09 16:36:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This is what the couples want, looks nice in photos. When your wedding day is over all you have left is the pics. This isn't some high class catering gig where people are dishing out thousands of bucks. It's wood fired pizza and apps. These are cool, relaxed people who love everything we do. You're right though, without the flowers and micro I probably could have fit one more tacky cheese cube on there.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [Homemade] Milano cookies </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-09 15:03:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-09 15:01:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Tongs did the job, as they always do.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-09 13:47:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Pepper jack, Gouda and cheddar cubes. This is from catering season last summer and this particular wedding they also wanted brie and blue. Prosciutto, salami, and capicola for meats.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-09 03:05:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Fox </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [Homemade] Pecan pie inside chocolate cake w/ chocolate ganache </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-09 02:46:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [Pro/Chef] Meat   Cheese Board </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-09 01:55:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
