<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject8863</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> US White House Press Secretary Sean Spicer Tweeted a Bitcoin Address  Not His Password </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-10 11:35:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> US White House Press Secretary Sean Spicer Tweeted a Bitcoin Address  Not His Password </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-10 11:34:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Press Secretary Sean Spicer Tweeted a Bitcoin Address  Not His Password </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-10 11:33:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-10 11:17:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If Donald Trump was not born rich he would be that guy who owns a NYC whole in the hall store front that sells overpriced camera equipment and treats his employees like shit while he drives an overpriced red foreign sports car and wears pants that are too tight and has the first few buttons at the collar undone, with a coney island Russian or Ukrainian mail order wife. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-10 10:49:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> actually yeah. 5.1 is the standard now for audio mastery for shows unless its documentary / news / or educational 

Watching downloaded shows in 5.1 really helps in horror or atmospheric dramas.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-10 08:29:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> there are bond measures though and a estate and corporate tax restructuring which is really important so we can actually pay for our schools and transit. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-10 08:25:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> we live in the age or the alt-right and /r/The_Douche please use "/s" to denote sarcasm.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-10 08:18:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> bitch, shit be shades of grey as fuck! so pump those breaks and better box turn the heck out of here or i'm about to break my foot off in your 0 with my 1 if you catch my drift? /s </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-10 07:20:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Can we all agree NOT being racist does not mean your are Conservative or Liberal. You can be Liberal and still racist.
I'm liberal and not racist and I know many conservative people who are also NOT racist. But a racist is just that a racist, it just to happens a lot of racists are also conservative but that is because a certain political party playcates to that since it gets them votes.

Like you can evangelical christian republicans who are against drilling for oil and are environmentalists and believe jesus and god demand we are stewards of the environment. They are still republican and "Conservative" but they don't go DRILL BABY DRILL.



/r/quityourbullshirt is more what the reply was doing.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-10 04:07:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm just gonna say she looks perfectly normal in her old photos too. Girl has child birthing thighs. Thicker than a bowl of oatmeal.

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-10 04:05:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> just like the heritage foundation wanted you to.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-10 04:01:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You are aware you would be the bad guy in the incredibles right? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-10 01:58:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Does this man get his honorary Asian card now? Because I have only seen Chinese people enter stuff in this fast. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-10 01:52:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> fuck man we love no one from law enforcement but the fact is he testified and now is getting fired. Thats some Nixon level fuckery. Comey was a tool but the fact is surprisingly he is an honest tool  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-10 01:47:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It seems donnie doubles down on gaslighting. His book even says that's what he does. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Sinclair beamed a short commentary piece to many of the companys 173 stations. Promoting Trump's idea of "Fake News". Including on Portland's KATU which they own. They are now buying Tribune Media for $3.9 billion and own 70% of the broadcast tv market. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-10 01:13:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-10 00:06:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> we do, but the fact is he is testifying and he just got punished for it. Which is a serious sign of witness tampering and intimidation. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-09 22:22:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Holy fuck that was perfect.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-09 22:18:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> To them I would say ["Don't Be a Sucker"](https://youtu.be/23X14HS4gLk) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-09 06:19:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That vichy water is so refreshing, is it not inspector? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-08 20:56:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Sounds triggered, better find a safespace </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-08 18:34:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> There you go, stupidity, finds a way. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-08 17:27:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Undelete is know for being kinda alt-reichy with the_donald level of sycophantic orange ass brown nosing </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-08 17:17:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yes and you never saw antisemitic propaganda from the stalin or lenin at all /s </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-07 21:36:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Your academy of science is top notch </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-07 08:45:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> "May the shwartz be with you!" </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Vhs tape theater sound codec and other issues </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-07 08:30:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Is there a way to add ac3 audio support with open source codec pack or something for the vhs tapes? Also do you have surround sound virtual directional audio setup in the vhs theater? Lastly can you add the ability to sit in the chairs? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-07 08:29:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Os there a way to add ac3 audio support with open source codec pack or something for the vhs tapes? Also do you have surround sound setup in the vhs theater? Lastly can you ad the ability to sit in the chairs? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-07 08:19:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You mean one of the two newspapers that edward snowden went to with leaked information because he knew assange was a dangerous egotistical asshole who has a woman hating agenda like everyone in the hacker community who has dealt with assange knows you ayn rand fluffer?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-07 04:07:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> * The Wizard Of Oz (1939)
* Seven Samurai (1954)
* Star Wars: Episode IV - A New Hope (1977)
* The Wiz (1978)
* Alien (1978)
* Star Wars: Episode V - The Empire Strikes Back (1980)
* Raiders of the Lost Ark (1981)
* TRON (1982)
* Blade Runner (1982)
* WarGames (1983)
* Star Wars: Episode VI - Return of the Jedi (1983)
* Trading Places (1983)
* Ghostbusters (1984)
* Indiana Jones and the Temple of Doom (1984)
* Brazil (1985)
* Back to the Future (1985)
* The Goonies (1985)
* Legend (1985)
* Labyrinth (1986)
* Aliens (1986)
* The Princess Bride (1987)
* The Great Outdoors (1988)
* Indiana Jones and the Last Crusade (1989)
* Little Nemo: Adventures in Slumberland (1989)
* Ghostbusters II (1989)
* Back to the Future Part II (1989)
* Kiki's Delivery Service (1989)
* Back to the Future Part III (1990)
* Groundhog Day (1993)
* The Joy Luck Club (1993)
* Mighty Morphin Power Rangers: The Movie (1995)
* Hackers (1995)
* Ghost In The Shell (1995)
* Star Trek: First Contact (1996)
* Princess Mononoke (1997)
* Star Wars Episode IV - A New Hope: Special Edition (1997)
* Star Wars: Episode V - The Empire Strikes Back: Special Edition (1997)
* Star Wars: Episode VI - Return of the Jedi: Special Edition (1997)
* The Red Violin (1998)
* Office Space (1999)
* The Matrix (1999)
* Battle Royale (2000)
* Blade Runner: The Final Cut (2007)
* TRON: Legacy (2010)

Will add more as i remember more that I remember ones i have watched over 11 times </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-07 04:04:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Actually it's theoretically possible to have a Magnetic monopole. But in the end its still only mathematically proven, and has not been observed in the natural world yet.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-07 04:02:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> seriously if I was this manlets mother I would smack the shit out of him for wearing this. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-07 03:45:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> yes because the ayn rand libertarian yellow rag Reason, funded by the Koch brothers, never gets things wrong or ever covers things from their particular bias ideological bullshit way when it comes to taxes or government at all. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-07 03:36:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> want to fill us in for why the 36 PCI-E Lanes? Doing massive Cuda SLI video rendering workstation? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-07 03:24:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Like pee in your mouth when they want to? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-07 03:22:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> American Born White Right Wing Terrorists attacks have killed more americans in the united states than Middle eastern wahhabist death cult jihadist terrorists  since September 11th, 2001.

74% of the deaths from terrorist attacks in the united states have been committed by right wing white terrorists since 2002.

- https://www.cato.org/blog/gao-weighs-countering-violent-extremism

- http://time.com/3934980/right-wing-extremists-white-terrorism-islamist-jihadi-dangerous/

- https://www.cato.org/publications/commentary/americans-fear-foreign-terrorists-overinflated </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-07 03:15:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [Did someone say Pizza Party?!?!?!?!?](https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=mxvKuEWeVg8)  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-07 03:12:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> an amen .... AN!!!! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-07 02:21:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Not the typical stealth mission stuff. trust me. There is an element to it but it is not like Metal Gear stealth. Its intense atmosphere building and if you don't cry at least once playing this game you are a heartless bastard. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-07 02:04:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> brew install FUCKNO </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-07 02:02:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Windows version runs better sadly, like encoding is significantly faster. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-07 02:01:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> apple really should just stop that $100/year fee. Its annoying as all hell. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-06 23:20:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> ummm first, the senate hasn't even had a hearing yet and the house was being run by a trump transition team member who was not allowing any testimony of key witnesses till it was acknowledged that Rep Devin went to meetings with the white house with documents given to him by the white house to shut down the investigation. Not to mention Devin also went to several meetings with Flynn to talk with Turkish government reps to extradite a united states citizen illegally without due process to a dictator at stage 2 of demolishment of Turkish Democracy. But hey whatever ... who cares about due process and constitutional rights? Oh that right NOT TRUMP!!!! Got to open up those "Libel laws" blocking law suits over words that make you feel bad, you know what i mean "Pig Vomit"? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-06 23:15:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Dude has to work. I can understand that. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-06 23:10:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [I posted this](http://i.imgur.com/SdS3p21.jpg)

**-EDIT-** 

Feels good brah, [feels good](http://imgur.com/gallery/Uoz5M) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-06 23:09:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> wow, you guys are fucking paranoid as fuck! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-06 22:35:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Unless it's the Marriott Hotel then it has a book of mormon. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-06 22:30:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> https://vid.me/wzqT </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-06 22:22:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Old people. Medicare cut back. It's like RELEASE THE HOUNDS on republican politicians now. It is the 3rd rail of politics, you don't fuck with medicare, you make it cheaper for old people not more expensive. Average Baby boomers have no loyalty to party if they feel their "birthrights" are being taken away. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-06 21:12:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  The Last Supper

Reading the synopsis it sounds like Ron Perlman's character would be a Rush Limbaugh type and have no sense for the fine line between Individual Freedoms and Autocratic power. His Character sounds like Donald Trump. 

Which is hilariously the exact opposite. Maybe when I said Authoritarian and Libertarian its the difference between where the separation of the individual vs the state begins. Knowing the fine line for self autonomy while also giving yourself part to the society you live in and following under a set of rules / laws that allow for freedoms with moderation as well as strong protections for the consumer/ citizen to prevent harm from unfettered profit over conservation in community stewardship in capitalism. 

I was a fan of Both Teddy Roosevelt and Franklin D. Roosevelt in their stances and policies to corporations, citizens rights. But in modern times I think Carter was my favorite, next to Obama. No one is perfect and Teddy and FDR had serious faults in relation to race issues. Carter was railroaded and Reagan getting rid of the solar panels on the white house and killing the solar panel subsidy was the same level of petty bullshit as the republicans have been trying to do for the last 8 years for the Affordable Care Act.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-06 21:00:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Ok so there are TWO types of HDR video. There is HDR10 and Dolby Vision. HDR10 can be handled by software and is an open standard while Dolby Vision (proprietary format) requires, up until recently, a special chip. Dolby though has said they should be able to shoe horn it into some older tvs though with a new software version they developed. But here is the rub, HDR10 and Dolby Vision media is not guaranteed to play on every tv in HDR color.

https://www.lifehacker.com.au/2017/04/brace-yourselves-the-hdr-format-war-is-coming/


First you need a 10-bit color display with 4k support. Then you need HDCP 2.0 compliant encryption media devices all the way through the chain. So if your Receiver has 4k passthrough but no HDCP 2.0 then you get no HDR playback or even 4k playback with external boxes.

For streaming, Netflix and Amazon currently support both HDR10 and Dolby Vision. Oddly enough, VUDU only supports Dolby Vision and wont provide HDR10 content.

If you get a player your UHD disks might not provide HDR video depending on what is on the disk and what software is on the player.

And it looks like Samsung has to fuck the pot and come out with yet another FORMat of HDR called HDR10+

https://www.cnet.com/news/samsung-introduces-hdr10-format-to-combat-dolby-vision/ </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-06 20:45:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The different ads for different people thing kind of scares the crap out of me. Talk about pigeon holing bubble society. Political ads that change based on your viewing profiles of what you watch and what tv you watch it on.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-06 20:40:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> also the medicare being gutted, cant forget old people who hate socialism crying about their socialist healthcare system </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-06 20:39:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> the AHCA really helped them a whole bunch. they raised 4 million dollars for direct donations i heard in the first 18 hours after the AHCA passed in the house. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-06 20:34:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hey look a douche bag pizzagater! point and laugh kids! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-06 19:58:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Actually yeah they do in matters like this. They also need to Justice Department working with them as well. But it seems that there are a whole lot of dirty people all related to this who don't want any of that to happen. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-06 19:20:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  le centristisme vaincra contre tous les nationalistismes 

Qui Qui! Pardon mon franais, je suis amricain, mais un monde ouvert est celui de la croissance, de l'apprentissage et du partage des connaissances. Le nationalisme et l'isolationnisme ne font que tuer l'innovation positive positive, la croissance culturelle mondiale positive et la dcouverte mutuelle des vrits universelles de la connaissance

Universal Political Centristism sans austrit, mais l'quilibre est la seule faon de dvelopper n'importe quoi. Politique avec une protection forte pour la sant des citoyens, l'accs  l'ducation publique sculaire, l'accs  une formation gratuite pour des emplois qualifis de travail qualifi, comme tant un plombier ou un lectricien, l'accs  l'enseignement suprieur gratuit et la protection du consommateur et l'autodtermination individuelle sur son propre corps pour les hommes Et les femmes sont ce qui fait une socit productive et heureuse, nous l'avons vu  maintes reprises.

In english:

healthy politics must be seen as riding the razor's edge of both Communist and Capitalist, Authoritarian and Libertarian, it must be centrist to get the best mixture of all to best serve the people.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-06 19:06:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> don't forget sanctions, they can also tax the fuck out of you if you don't follow the laws ;) That is if you are not self-employed. But they can freeze your assets too though. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-06 19:02:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Wikileaks was never "Useful" what Edward snowden did by going to trusted news journalists Glenn Greenwald, Laura Poitras, and Ewen MacAskill from the The Guardian and The Washington Post  and Poitras was a progressive liberal documentarian was how you do this. 

I have met Assange twice and the first time he got rapey at a hacker con where a security head of the con had to come and punch him out because he wouldn't stop and take no as a response from my drunk female hacker friend. 

The second time was just after wikileaks manifesto was released at another hacker con and his cult status started to grow. Assange is an egotist and he runs Wikileaks like his own personal cabal where he can dictate his views of the world to others who blindly follow or quickly removed or gas lighted or goaded into doing what he wants or he cuts you off from the group. He is a man who is an egocentric victim complex who has always let it known he hates aggressive women, he openly mocks verbal vocal women at hacker cons in the past and is pretty much a walking poster for /r/TheRedPill after his persecution for the rape of two women by not having sex with a condom and lying about it to them. 

The point is he used that to fuel his conspiracy tinfoil hat wearer mystique who hate uppity women type. He hated clinton since the 90s if you read his earlier rantings before wikileaks for whatever reason. And he is a man who like Peter Thiel thinks there is nothing wrong with having slaves or having a slave caste and that "racism is over", coming from an albino looking james bond villain henchman  looking punk ass motherfucker like him I find that hilarious. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-06 18:47:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The intelligence agencies are working on that but the hearings to investigate that require Senate and Congressional support. Guess who isn't playing ball kid. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-06 15:57:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> reddit hosts images now too. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-06 15:26:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> yes because i'm sure mods like /r/realgirls /r/4chan and others really support limiting the freedom of self expression of freedom of speech as they seriously state as their argument  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-06 14:46:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The levels of cringe in these comments were just what i expected.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-06 14:35:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Si cela est vrai, je serai trs heureux. J'espre que Marcon gagnera. Le centristisme est toujours le meilleur, avec des esprits ouverts au monde. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Report child porn - universal Child porn report button that goes to Reddit Admins for a child porn que / questionable age / no info on model / person taking photo </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-06 14:21:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I have noticed that a lot of highly questionable age of model images are getting posted to reddit that might be child porn. An example of this would be stuff posted on /r/RealGirls which makes it to /r/all a lot. 

Can we get a universal Child porn report button please that supersedes the mods of individual sub reddits and goes straight to all the top admins? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-06 14:00:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> http://i.imgur.com/TBLomoZ.gif

But seriously read this article from the new york times about the price to get a colonoscopy in the united states.

http://www.nytimes.com/2013/06/02/health/colonoscopies-explain-why-us-leads-the-world-in-health-expenditures.html?pagewanted=all

skip down to the part "A Market Is Born" there is a video that shows the map and prices per state / city for major locations. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-06 13:56:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> its almost like xenophobic, isolationists would never learn another language because they are so lazy and isolationist. LEARN ENGLISH DAMN YOU. In Russia though its mostly that english is the language of pop culture and french / france just isn't popular enough from what I know to have enough Russians be able to speak it. The only twitter posts in french i see have Trump user names and photos but obviously are fake bots with poorly written french. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-06 13:51:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> they need to just start cutting mics when you have guys like this.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-06 13:40:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> In the united states they would charge you 1500 to 3000 for the ultrasound, 150 to 1000 for the cortisone shot, and like 500 to 750 for the doctor visit (USD) and you wait up to 10 hours in the ER as well or got to Urgent Care which is cheaper less life threatening doctor needs but does not have Radiology or ultrasound imaging equipment and only open typically during normal 9 to 5 biz hours and wait 2 to 3 hours to see a doctor and be told can't do much else, here have a script for some drugs and a bill. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-06 13:33:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> /r/wholesomememes last I heard was founded by trumpets same with /r/BlackPeopleTwitter 

/r/LatinoPeopleTwitter was caught up by an actual Latino before someone could do the same to it as /r/BlackPeopleTwitter, some of the comments on there I swear to god look like they are lines talking about genetics from the 1950s that is how racist </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-06 13:26:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You can get free healthcare from the state or you can pay for the private sector in order to not have to wait in the terrible lines.

I don't know what anyone is talking about. I wait longer to see the doctor in the united states than when I have gone to the ER / Doctors in Europe. I have been to the doctors in the London, Dublin, Munich, and Amsterdam. Wait times were nothing compared to the 2 hour wait for some of my GM doctors visits and the ER / Urgent Care visit took me significantly less time than the USA. In the USA even with a car accident and laceration i took 7 hours for a doctor to see me and even then it took 2 hours to get taken to the back area in the first place so from start to finish it took 12 hours for an ER visit and I asked them and where I live that was a SLOW day too.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-06 13:14:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Russian diamonds make anyone sell out fast. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-06 13:08:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You don't think they haven't monetized what your post? Please, they sell off access to the firehouse which is used by tons of market analysis groups and intelligence agencies to build profiles on people. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-06 09:35:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I do belive this is most likely child porn by legal definition  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-06 09:34:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What state? I'm gonna guess Kansas? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-06 09:00:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> But the very best thing of all
Theres a counter on this ball
So see if you can beat your very best score
See if you can skip a whole lot more!"
Skip-it, skip-it!!! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-06 07:50:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> God damn!!! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-06 07:42:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Youll get caught up in my cross fire if you dare me to a pogo ball off </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-06 07:35:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Kids of the 80's HIGH FIVE! Im '84 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-06 07:30:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> In just gonna say I randomly came across this on /r/all

There is no way you are 35 with a kid! You got the body of an 18 year old. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-06 07:20:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Bill on the new doctor who </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-06 06:55:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I NEED TO DOWNLOAD THIS NOW!!! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-06 06:48:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> well they still didn't like the Jewish people though. the fact that the [The Protocols of the Elders of Zion](https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/The_Protocols_of_the_Elders_of_Zion) (Russian:   ) or The Protocols of the Meetings of the Learned Elders of Zion was written and published in Russia and started it's spread there  in 1903.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-06 01:43:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm not going to lie. There is something so satisfying about watching it come out from the gentle tugging. It borders on the same level as /r/popping  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-06 01:42:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That's not a pimple that's a straight up MRSA sore i bet </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-06 00:39:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Republicans can only orgasm when they know they denied someone else the right to orgasm. That is why most republicans don't ever let there girlfriends or wives they call mother climax. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-05 22:32:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Or you could have it even more worse, being a Canadian one hit wonder pop star of the 80s that was only known aboot in Canada. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-05 21:38:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Oh it will get so much freaking worse for you. 

- https://www.nytimes.com/2015/02/24/us/govern-yourselves-state-lawmakers-tell-cities-but-not-too-much.html

- https://www.texastribune.org/2017/03/14/bag-ban/

- https://communityimpact.com/austin/at-the-capitol/2016/12/16/texas-attorney-general-texas-supreme-court-austin-plastic-bag-ban/

- http://www.wastedive.com/news/plastic-bag-bans-could-end-up-in-texas-supreme-court/434037/

Can't have Texas with out hypocrisy. Because Big Federal Government bad, and small local government also bad! But middle sized State mandated rules over local government is A O K, especially if it strangles Democrats that were democratically elected by the majority of the citizens in living those municipalities, like Austin for example! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-05 08:08:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The Freedom Caucus (Blackhearted Extreme Religious Social Darwinist Republicans) wanted to make people who were at risk be in pools that made them pay more and remove all the taxes to pay for subsidies. They voted No on AHCA 1st go because the bill didn't gut the support enough and didn't make people suffer enough. They voted Yes this time around because they now took out the requirement for pre-existing conditions for any state exchanges to exempt out that requirement if it has a governor say, "I want chronic sick people to suffer more"  And they also will be gutting medicare support which allowed children to be covered if they were poor and as well as poor people who couldn't get any healthcare any other way because they are poor or have pre-existing conditions, Like Me. Luckily I live in Oregon. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-05 07:51:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Your Deep dark secret and identity are out on the internet for everyone to see! YOU MUST BE SO EMBARRASSED!!! DO ME DO ME NEXT!!! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-05 02:18:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> As someone who was 19 when it first started, The only good thing about 4chan was the comicbook section where i found a lot of great comics to read I would have never known about. But all in all. It has always been a shit show and in the 14 years since I started using it when it first started, it has evolved into what it's user base is mostly made up of a bitter angry white male who can't find a job or if he does is in one that is technical but lacks human interaction. Everything they do is for hedonism and "liberty" to be an assole to other people. Basically the worst form of asshole Libertarianism with 10 years of Storm Front / Nazi / White Power propaganda designed to indoctrinate angry edge lord teens to join Hitler youth bullshit. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-05 02:00:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> And here i thought the reverse of being dominating A-Type  in your day life and a submissive in the bedroom was just a stereotype .... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-05 01:58:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Was hoping for this. You did the fire nation proud son! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-04 20:22:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Ultimate projection finish </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-04 09:11:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> is this what he did to look busy after he left the CBS interview in the oval office? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-04 09:01:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> spoiled brat Saudi or Emirati assholes just gonna be assholes </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-04 08:34:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> A dog of the military. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-02 08:14:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> These look like they were done in a prison. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-02 08:10:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> you are using it wrong moron. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-02 08:03:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Typically it is the guy carrying who is the asshole i have seen but i too am for the right to own arms but on limits to what they can be unless you are in a well trained and regulated state militia that is under command of the state government/ governor. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-02 08:00:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Its not gun hobby, it's gun fetishism. A gun is a tool that is meant to kill or destroy something. The way people who are hardcore no limits on "gun rights" are zealots who understand nothing of moderation or control for the most part. They will use fear to sell more guns and then say their gun is more important than anything even education and common sense. If you are so bent up about gun rights why is it so bad to demand you be tested on it and trained yearly by actual law enforcement or and organized well maintained state run militia with the governor of said state as the commander and chief of that militia? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-02 07:50:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Fuck spending more money. I paid 35 to 70 dollars for a damn game fuck them all to hell and just give me my damn full game i paid for with the weapons! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-02 07:43:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Oh bless your heart sweetie but really, someday you are going to have a daughter and you will have to ask yourself, would you leave her alone in a room with that man? I know i sure as hell wouldn't leave my daughter, or my wife in a room with him. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-02 06:48:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Im 33 i go to school and i work. So no adults got time for all that earning. Inuse to play competitive when i was a teen. But that was during cs 1.0 1.2 and early source days. Stuff now seems all geared to make addicts out of everyone. Fucking team fortress 2 with hats pissed me off so much. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-02 05:53:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So let me ask are you actually a trump supporter? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-02 05:50:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Just a prank bro. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-02 05:46:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I only respect men who are heads of state of the united states who don't get into twitter battles about ratings for petty shit or beefs with rap artists and can take criticism like adults and are not lying 5 times a day on some of the most petty things on record that can be proved they lied outright in the last 100 days.  I only support a president who damn well has support for the first amendment and isn't saying he will change libel laws to gut it. I only respect men who call for the de-escalation of war, who look at war with a solemn sad and heavy heart and realize that you can't take it back, it's not a vote vehicle, it's death. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-02 03:45:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> For me America has always represented a land that is sposed to be a mix of people and cultures. When some dumb ass says no it's a white nation i laugh my ass off at their stupidness. Because catholic Irish leaving the famine were not white we were hella looked at like less than white. But that is where Irish and catholics and italians, and polish played into the racist game and sold out on Asians and Blacks to just feel slightly better than them. 

Irish people would make sure they screwed black people harder culturally because if you looks at the black guy the irish catholic might finally be able to get a job. There is some fucked up history of irish particularly in america, early on as indentured servants and then later on after the famine as they came the the USA. 

But anyway The united states is one of the few countries where you can get away at mocking the leader and not have to worry about getting disappeared or sued. Its one of the national prides i have but i wouldn't say it gives me nationalism. 

Nationalism, i think you are using it poorly. Nationalism is illogical devotion to one's country, it borders on jingoism which is rabid illogical devotion to one's country. Patriotism is a better word ...

[You should look at this comic to see what i mean.](http://www.smbc-comics.com/comic/an-important-distinction) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-02 03:37:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> so its like providing a realistic path to mac ownership like say how being an undocumented migrant, many if given a realistic path to citizenship that didn't required to be high skilled or have family already here and take 7 to 20 years would become american then or at least have their children get those protections? Because realistically it can take up to 25 years for an Unskilled immigrant to get citizenship. Its just as hard as finding a mac that is upgradable in a enclosed unit, there is no legal path for it that makes it easy unless you do this grey area thing like a hackintosh. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-02 03:34:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> so its like providing a realistic path to mac ownership like say how being an undocumented migrant, many if given a realistic path to citizenship that didn't required to be high skilled or have family already here and take 7 to 20 years would become american then or at least have their children get those protections? Because realistically it can take up to 25 years for an Unskilled immigrant to get citizenship. Its just as hard as finding a mac that is upgradable in a enclosed unit, there is no legal path for it that makes it easy unless you do this grey area thing. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-02 03:30:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Might I suggest you look into some some support groups first. Your mom is the one to handle the money stuff. You might want to look into Social Security Survivor's  Benifits too. 

https://www.ssa.gov/survivors/

It's how Congressman Paul Ryan paid for his college actually, his father died of alcoholism related death and he got a bunch of money to go to college without any debt. You know how "smart" people go to school as /r/The_Donald would say. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-02 03:19:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Im confused nationalism for what country? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-02 03:16:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I watched the entire thing. It played like he was trying to make a musical akin to titus andronicus 1999 Anthony hopkins movie he produced. Playing on the modern take in elizabethan english like 1996's Romeo + Juliet directed by Baz Luhrmann.

Bannon is a chaos weaver and venom milker. And the fact you (((.))) shows you drink up his poison like warm glass of milk, while it rots you too the core eating your insides out making you a hollow vessel of hatred and puss waiting to spew gurgling from you fingers online and your mouth in the real word. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-02 03:08:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It went from roast to staight up an intervention when he started roasting msnbc, fox news, and cnn. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-02 02:48:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> taft was 320 lbs when he entered the white house half way though  lost 70 lbs dropping 240 lb but then gained it back and then some leaving the white house at 340 lbs </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-02 02:44:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I hate loot games for that reason. They are games of luck not stragey it feels then. If i casually want to play a game like when I was a teenager I'm fucked because someone has more powerful weapons or some other crap. I just want to go right out. Like how in Battlefield you have to pay for weapon updates or upgrades or add ons and crap it pisses me off. I Just want to have vehicles, weapons, and choice of classes and not have to pay extra for them. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-02 02:41:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> He doesn't believe in exercise. [He actually believes that you have a certain amount of energy in your body and you use it up by exercising](http://www.politico.com/magazine/story/2016/10/the-7-oddest-things-donald-trump-thinks-214354) and he actively looks down on people who work out at the gym or go running or jogging. This is a "theory" he developed in prep school and has had it his entire life. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-02 02:39:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> when i buy a game i don't want to have to earn shit JUST GIVE ME THE GAG DAMN WEAPONS and this buying crap with points i earn from playing is bullshit too. I don't want to play any Call of Duty Modern Warfare level shit where i have to pay to unlock shit.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-02 02:30:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> He also wears adult diapers too. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-02 02:29:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> rapist just gonna rape. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-02 02:28:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> yeah but he is nothing but talk, he would be the Dan of any fighting game. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-02 02:21:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Now show them the [carfentanil](https://ccfa-wpengine.netdna-ssl.com/wp-content/uploads/2016/12/salt-carfentanil-768x384.png) the recent surge in overdoses is being blamed on an even more potent drug called carfentanil. [It's 100 times stronger than fentanyl, or 10,000 times stronger than morphine to 5000 times stronger than heroin](http://i.imgur.com/WROYQcU.jpg). Carfentanil is used to sedate elephants. It can be dangerous to even touch it without gloves.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-02 02:20:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Now show them the [carfentanil](https://ccfa-wpengine.netdna-ssl.com/wp-content/uploads/2016/12/salt-carfentanil-768x384.png) the recent surge in overdoses is being blamed on an even more potent drug called carfentanil. [It's 100 times stronger than fentanyl, or 10,000 times stronger than morphine to 5000 times stronger than heroin](http://i.imgur.com/WROYQcU.jpg). Carfentanil is used to sedate elephants. It can be dangerous to even touch it without gloves.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-02 02:11:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I hate loot crate dynamics in games. Its hella sketchy and entirely built on Gambling addiction dynamic. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-02 02:07:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yup, asian. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-02 02:03:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I didn't realize it was that far north / east </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> C-SPAN youtube post of The Daily Show commentator Hasan Minhaj giving the roast at the White House Press Corps Dinner </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-02 01:56:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> C-SPAN youtube post of The Daily Show commentator Hasan Minhaj giving the roast at the White House Press Corps Dinner </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-02 01:56:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> C-SPAN youtube post of The Daily Show commentator Hasan Minhaj giving the roast at the White House Press Corps Dinner </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-02 01:55:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> C-SPAN youtube post of The Daily Show commentator Hasan Minhaj giving the roast at the White House Press Corps Dinner </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-02 01:54:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> White House White Nationalist fascist master mind Steve Bannons rap musical has been found, and it is some unhinged nonsense </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-02 01:52:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Steve Bannons rap musical has been found, and it is some unhinged nonsense </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-02 01:34:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Steve Bannons rap musical has been found, and it is some unhinged nonsense </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-02 01:30:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Steve Bannons rap musical has been found, and it is some unhinged nonsense </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-02 01:29:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-01 23:26:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I got relatives / extended family in Poland. My great grand uncle and his family were in Dachau for being Polish political prisoners who were also catholic. Yeah fuck this nazi shit ONR is nazi youth shit, my cousins and great aunts who live in Warsaw all fucking tell me this too. They are blonde and blue eyed and their great grandparents were in the Warsaw ghettos. Fuck those nazi shit stains is what they say about ONR. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-01 22:47:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> As soon as someone is outed as an abuser of the innocent I typically write them off. If it was a one time incident you can say maybe it was a mistake under significant stress and through therapy they could get help.  but serial abusers jesus you can't see anything they did out of the context of the horror they did to others.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-29 22:45:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> He would have to have a Borderline Personality Disorder to perceive the world as he did. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-29 12:48:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It seems he is all about the being Anti-Antifa 

This is being backed by Republican party and conservative dark PAC dollars.

https://www.reddit.com/r/The_Donald/comments/686yyb/new_berkeley_bus_stops_nsfw/ </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> TIL about Shepard Fairey wannabe knockoff, SABO A Ted Cruz - Donald Trump Republican, Bigoted, Homophobic, Evangelical Christian, Pro Fascism, Alt-Right, Misogynistic, "GOP Guerrilla artist" who is leader of a GOP and CPAC sponsored Right wing propaganda illegal Graffiti artist street team. YEEESH </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-29 12:45:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-29 12:31:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That's like saying "well countries with no nukes are not completely immune to nuclear attacks, as a developing nation we too should have the right to defend ourselves with Nuclear first strike capability!" </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> advice / support for interethnic / interracial relationship fight </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-29 08:23:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-29 00:15:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This really feels so pointed. It reminds me with how you talk of time of the movie In Time, which was a cheesy dystopian sci fi movie where the poor only have 24 hours a day to live and earn more time as payment for work and as the currency to buy things and the rich live in another time zone where they horde time and manipulate the inflation of the cost of goods to keep poor people from ever living as long as them. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-28 22:03:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You mean backs GOP Health Care Bill That Cuts Pre-Existing Conditions protections!!! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-28 22:01:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> because my photoshop skills are needed [here again](http://imgur.com/gallery/YUfjjG8) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-28 21:33:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Actually that is very common thing. You remove the extra pixels for color your image will become sharper as the fact it only has to process the gradients of greyscale. Color can give you depth but black and white gives you sharpness. This is why you use black   white and negative images in digital image analysis to find where things look funny. 


https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Grayscale

https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Color_depth </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-28 21:26:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hey can you do a video next time you do this to show the process of how you did it? I would love to get a better understanding of how you did this. I would imagine it would be a lot of rotoscoping and masking in after effects. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-28 21:22:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> He is also looking at the tunnels as a way to build a hyper loop under cities as well as provide a path for "burying" high speed fiber trunk lines as well. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-28 21:19:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Sorry, what does Sombra's Ult do? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-28 21:15:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> But but but .... my mom is dead :,,( </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-28 21:05:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It reminds me of Adventure time, Like i expect candy kingdom denizen [Starchy](http://i.imgur.com/yU4wFIL.png) to pop up and go, "Well it's me, good ol Starchy" </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-28 20:57:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I know this might sound stupid as i only play every so often but can you explain what they did here. I haven't played much since Sombra came out. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-28 20:46:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The computer that a first major gig for Old Spice funded  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-28 20:44:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Son, you should have linked to your own website for this then! if you gonna shameless self promote Link directly to the website! 

For shame! FOR SHAME!!!!!!!!!!!!!! 

j/k ..... sort of </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-28 20:32:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So he gets credit for such an amazing original take on mario brothers comedy comic strips 

This was done by [Chris McCoy](http://www.safelyendangered.com/) and here is his [twitter](https://twitter.com/EndangeredComic)

His newer strips can be found on [Safetly Endangered Webtoons site]
(http://www.webtoons.com/en/comedy/safely-endangered/list?title_no=352) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Fortune magazine changes title of article about FCC Chairman Ajit Pai calling Network Neutrality red communists because you know Capitalism </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-28 06:19:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-28 06:15:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> http://imgur.com/gallery/MbsZe

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
