<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject1410</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-07 16:49:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I need a think sweater as well. So I can think better. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> "Chris Motionless" </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-07 14:47:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-05 17:52:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Well, yes. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-05 17:23:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Backstory, please! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-02 22:14:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I hope to god that I can change the language. Since I have my iOS in my native tongue, some apps use that as in-game language and it bothers the living shit out of me. Mostly because the translations are utter crap. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-29 17:24:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I wonder how clips like these end up on the internet. Do the kids themselves put it up for some reason, or what? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-24 23:52:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> "ok" </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-23 23:19:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's like /r/michaelbaygifs in real life </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-20 22:25:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If that's what she feels like, sure. I don't own my girlfriend or her body. If someone wants to wank to the pictures she posts on snapchap, go ahead. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-19 23:45:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I feel like the easiest thing to do after maybe changing the sheets and so on, is to just ask "Can I do anything?". Maybe she wants a tub of ice cream and be alone for a few hours. Maybe she wants to punch something. Maybe she doesn't want anything different from any other situation.

Or as with some of my ex girlfriends, maybe she wants to fuck the living shit out of you. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-19 23:43:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I had a friend who is the stereotypical nice guy, but looks like a douche. Either v-neck or low cut tank tops, some shitty tribal tattoos, the right jewelry etc etc. So he's a little bit of this, and a little of that. His facebook was filled with "Why does nice guys always end up last? :(" posts.

I linked [this](https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=5rZu-tBi7DM) to him without saying anything. He was super oblivious to it and didn't understand a thing. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-19 23:37:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> "Trickshot" </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-19 20:16:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> How is this trashy? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-18 18:26:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Followed your instagram! That was some sick shit! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-17 18:36:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Dude, you've got a fantastic smile! It's heartwarming! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-17 18:36:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I love how the one on the left has given up and the one on the right is either thinking "That fucking wanker" or "I am so getting that egg." </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-16 01:53:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Love the keffiyeh! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Reworking Capture the Flag </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-15 21:15:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Capture the Flag has long been a favorite game mode of mine, so I was super excited when Blizzard announced it to OW. I remember spending hundreds of hours in Halo playing CTF.

It's an understatement saying that I was disappointed when I played it.

It's a super underdeveloped game mode if a legit tactic is "Sit by your own flag and wait for the other team to arrive."

Having only your home flag and your away flag doesn't create any dynamic game play. But there's a super simple solution. Every map should have a neutral flag in the middle. That forces players not only to protect their own flag, but it also makes them chase the neutral flag. In that way, you can't have players camping by their own flag, and you get a more dynamic game play which also forces the teams to make more strategic choices. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-14 12:10:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Spotify used to have funny things in the description. It would be like:

Update: Bla bla bla

Update: bla bla bla

Update: Bla bla bla

Complete lie: Some made up funny story </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-14 11:14:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Sean O'Connell, actually. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-09 21:56:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I think the contouring looks like shit because of the light and contrast. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-09 21:51:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> "Lol guys, I thought it was super cool to kill someone! What was I THINKING?" </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-09 21:51:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I am very curious to this as well. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-09 21:47:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Maybe a photo shoot or clip then? Only requires the camera! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-09 14:05:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> He's probably sitting there furiously wonderign why he doesn't get any matches. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> I met R2D2. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-09 14:03:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-09 10:32:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You could host a theme party and be an evil mermaid! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-07 21:49:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> My ex girlfriend has the same one! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-07 19:53:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> My biggest problem was his shaking. Jesus christ, he looks like he's had 15 cups of coffee. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-06 20:43:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Kan ngon frklara starten av det hr? Jag sg ngon som postade en Maryland/Sverige-flagga och sen posten med de tv studenterna och flaggorna.

Hur brjade det hr? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-06 00:49:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> A cam in slot? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-05 19:29:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Didn't have edge on my computer at that point. I had W8 at that time. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-05 17:38:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I remember wanting to watch Apple's press conference. Whoops, to bad I have a PC. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-05 17:37:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> As a person who's worked with these types of things, even if he thinks it's just fun and games, it's not. Being stressed out because you have someone breathing down your neck for 10 hours straight doesn't make you a happy go lucky person. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-05 17:35:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That somewhere in the world, somebody is kidnapped and kept locked in in someones house and we won't know about it until (or if) they actually manage to escape one day. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-05 00:12:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> She was just doing her job. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> BackerKits "Ready to ship"? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-04 11:06:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So, afaik I'm part of the backers who's supposed to get their cube in march. And well... I haven't received it yet. According to my BackerKit it's "Ready to ship".

Will that change when it's actually shipped? Because with our postal service, I have no idea if it's been sent and the postal service lost it, or if it's still in the states. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-02 19:44:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That title made my brain go "ow". </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-02 04:00:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Holy shit. Balloons are assholes. Now I understand why my mom never bought balloons for my birthday parties. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-01 20:51:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I wonder if they've made it into a kind of regular thing with Holly bantering Romesh and he goes on a tantrum about it.

It's hilarious. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What is up with the "Don't swear on my profile" pictures? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-01 20:02:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> More and more people are adding the "Don't swear on my profile" "badge" on their profile pictures on facebook as well as sometimes changing their cover photo.

It's either just "Don't swear on my profile" or it's a picture of a super ripped Winnie The Pooh and the text. Some have "This is a christian group" or "This is a christian profile" as well. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-01 15:21:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> She wears 40 a in a brawl?

So, she fights with a Country Club bottle? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-31 18:10:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Oh, so "back then" as in "White and colored people drink from different drinking fountains-back then"? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-29 17:46:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I don't like to use this kind of quote, but this really feels like an "I'm unemployed and it's the governments fault" person. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [SIB] Steep? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-27 21:23:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I played it a VERY short while during BETA due to a glitch, and then forgot about it.

Later I've been watching the subreddit a bit, but can't get my head around if I should buy it or not.

I loved both SSX Tricky and The Skate series (I've heard that it's been slightly compared to a "skate but on snow") so I wonder, will I like this? Is it just an open world snowboarding/skiing simulator? Is there a goal to it? Is there unlockables or is everything there for you right from the getgo? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-27 19:28:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The swedish postal system. It's owned by the Swedish and the Danish government but acts like a private company.

There's more complaints made against them than I've ever seen against another company before. They lose packages and mail ALL the time. Letters take months to arrive even if the sender has paid extra to get it delivered on a specific date. They leave orders out on the street if they've arrived outside of the agreed delivery time.

I came to my old workplace one day to see a package containing a machine worth around $2000 standing outside on the pavement with a note saying "Hope it's ok that I left the box here."

They sometimes refuse to deliver mail to certain houses because "the lighting isn't enough and the mailboxes are too hard to open. They could cause injuries to our delivery people" which is complete bullshit. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-26 19:14:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This could still be used today. But ironically. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-26 17:27:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Sadly she's gone down in a substance abuse again. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-21 19:07:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Upvote for Zlatan </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-21 18:56:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I came here to ask "What's with the lines?" until I realized it says "flight" and not "fights". </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-21 00:27:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Her smile is fantastic. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-19 15:49:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Det gr ont i mina ron. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-19 15:25:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Varg Vikernes would be proud. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-19 11:41:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It really, really bothers me that they change color/tone of the color all the time. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-13 20:21:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Big shout-out to the doctor who was working at half past five on christmas morning when drunken me got in with a broken nose! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-13 18:06:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> As a Swede, I find this hilarious!

Usually when they try to make a swedish version of something, it doesn't turn out that well. But this was funny as hell!

I'm a big fan off all the participants and they all have different kind of humor.

Kodjo's hysterical breakdown with the firefighter had me rolling with laughter. The same with Bianca's trailer. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-13 17:19:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> He is already the perfect Swede. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-13 17:03:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I've posted here and some other subs with pictures of me in my old septum piercing. Basically eight out of ten comments says "Loose the nose ring." "You look like a bull." "I don't like piercings.".

When I've posted here it's because I don't like the way I look overall. I put the septum piercing there because I LIKE it. The septum piercing isn't the problem. It's something I think I look better in. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-13 16:59:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What the actual fuck? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-12 13:57:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Are there any updates for this yet? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-08 20:47:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Uh... no.

Chocolate is not a "flavour of milk." </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-07 21:23:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> https://www.instagram.com/amills4091/ </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-07 11:09:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'd like the yellow ones. I am mostly used to be both playing and typing with Cherry MX Black since we have those on our keyboards at work (Yaaay, working with video games!) and I therefore feel they are the most compatible for me. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-06 00:11:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Malm whatup! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-05 23:57:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Det hr r omjligt allvarligt. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-05 23:55:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Tack gode gud fr det. Jag var osker i brjan nr jag lste. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Sensual dance </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-05 21:36:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-05 13:11:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I like the idea, but I can't stand Harry Hill and his "Harharhar, look at me! I joke around with everyone in a serious/not so serious/over the top way!". I just found it irritating. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-05 12:45:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> She is absolutely beautiful! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-05 02:39:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Fair enough. You gave me a better reply than him. I haven't played Trove for a while so I mostly reacted to his rather aggressive and half edgy tone in the message.

At least you explained the whole thing. Thanks. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Do you find the step relative porn plots to be a turn on? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-04 18:41:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-04 17:25:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I just used it as a quick example. That's why I wrote "If water is free". </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-04 16:56:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Of course you technically CAN. The thing is - you can't expect people to pay for it. If the "service" has been free before, people won't pay for it just out of the blue like that. That's not how it works.

For example - if water is free for everyone and suddenly one company wants you to pay for it, because they feel like it's the right thing, people will get pissy and turn their backs to it. Because that's how it works.

You do you, boo. But don't complain when people won't take you serious. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-04 16:49:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Dude, how old are you? With the way you're writing, I can understand why people would talk shit towards you. You can't demand to get paid for helping people out in the game. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-04 16:44:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What they don't tell you is that you have to stir it constantly for these 30-45 minutes. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-04 16:41:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Football* </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-02 22:57:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Wtf are those? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-02 22:54:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> 24, 193cm/6'4" </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-27 21:52:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Alright, sweet!
Thanks for the answers! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-27 21:26:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Sweet, thanks!

I posted before going into an actual game, and while actually in a game, I got the three cards to choose between. If I buy one of the cards, is it one time use or permanent? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What is the pink/purple bottle icon in the top right corner? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-27 18:46:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I know, n00b question, but when starting up Paladins today, I noticed an icon that I hadn't seen before. Next to the amount of crystals and gold there's a small pink/purple flask icon with a number beside it.

I can't wrap my head around what it is and google didn't really help me either. So what is it? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-26 21:41:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I seem to be the only one in my group of friends that isn't using this god damn app that's supposed to make you look cuter. I hate it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-26 21:39:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That can't be me. I sleep in my underwear only. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-26 16:49:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You may have a fivehead, but you're still rather cute. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-26 16:45:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What the fuck is this and why the fuck did I watch it? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-26 16:44:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> They all look the same.... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-26 16:40:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> No, he's actually doing his [Pavarotti](https://youtu.be/rTFUM4Uh_6Y?t=137) impersonation. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-24 20:40:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> My teacher in high school (I graduated six years ago) told me he went to WGT as well! We had a really good discussion about it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-24 20:07:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Oh... I just googled it. I get it now. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-24 19:12:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You are absolutely beautiful! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-24 19:09:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I live in Sweden, so we don't have those, haha. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-24 19:09:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I haven't had sugar or milk in my coffee for years, haha
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-24 19:08:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I remember when they stopped selling Twist here in Sweden and my friend always buying them from Germany whenever he went there for booze. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Lunch for office space employee? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-23 00:29:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I just started working as an administrator which means I sit around looking at a computer all day long and not moving around much. I also drink a bit too much coffee.

I've noted that I've started to gain a few pounds as well and want to be able to eat as healthy as possible. I'm getting a gym card as soon as I'm getting my first paycheck, though.

But yeah, I'm looking for tasty and nutritious lunches that can also be microwaved if needed.

I eat everything, I'm not allergic to anything (but we have a ban on nuts at the office because of airborne nut allergy) and I don't mind eating the same thing for a few days. Lunch for me isn't really about having a meal that's meant to be enjoyed. I just want something that tastes good and gives me energy.

I eat meat, but trying to cut down on it, so vegetarian and vegan is also welcome.

Thanks in advance. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-20 23:14:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> "[...] a comment that other cannot agree with or relate to."

WELL, NO FUCKING SHIT. It's called having different opinions and experiences. My fucking god. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-20 22:16:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Oh my god.

You are absolutely beautiful.

I'm dumbfounded. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-20 21:37:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's still 5,5 million women who's ok with that. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-20 00:28:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That looks so soothing. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-19 23:15:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Something, something "Hurrrdurrr, swedistan. I'm from america, but your country is full of muslims, hurr durr" </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-19 21:18:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That's why you don't buy shit boards. I've had boards hit by cars without a scratch. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-19 19:28:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You are absolutely stunning! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> 100 sneak confirmed. That Draugr is still asleep. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-19 16:56:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> 100 sneak confirmed. That Draugr is still asleep. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-19 16:22:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-19 16:02:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You're hot as fuck. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-19 03:17:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Well, that took quite the turns.... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-19 03:14:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Romesh was hilarious in this episode! They've could've skipped out on Judge Rinder, though. I didn't find him funny at all. Some things he said were things I would've found funny if someone else said it, but he just felt stiff and almost unpleasant. He really gave out an "I'm better than you" vibe imo. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-19 02:32:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The one or the *Juan*? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-19 02:22:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You don't know me. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-19 00:49:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> ...I want one.
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-19 00:00:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> My dad died in 2010 when I was 17.

"Not much" of a loss, if you ask me, really. It hurts of course, but it's "better" that it was him and not my mother. He was an alcoholic who couldn't keep his temper. He never touched or hurt any of his three children, but we fought and argued almost daily. When I say "we", I mean he got angry over every little thing and his way of arguing was "The one who shouts the loudest is correct." He drank all day long, smoked at least a pack and a half of cigarettes each day and god knows how he managed to pay the bills. I can't remember him having a legit job for years. Other people's kids were more important than his own. Me and my sister studied music in high school and my sister told me that he would always show up at her friends shows, but never to hers. He never showed up to any of mine either. 

I don't have any memories of him sober, actually. My sister told me about him being sober when we were going to the museum once. Until we reached the museum that also had a bar next to it, which is where he started.

My stepdad, on the other hand, is a great man. Rather weird and odd, but still a fantastic man. I realized after a few years that he has some kind of "mental blockage" in which he doesn't understand some social codes and things like that. He's very honest, in both a good and bad way, but he doesn't always know when it's appropriate to say something and when to just shut up. It's not like he's full on "Oh and btw, you're dog died.". He knows when to not speak about certain things, but often he's kind of "Well, it's my opinion, it's what I think. People don't have to care about it." without thinking about how other people feel.

But, as said, he's a great man. He's taught me everything I know. He took me fishing, we went and practiced archery together. We did everything a boy "is supposed to do" with his father. He's a kind man who's taught me a lot of things when it comes to life and how to "be a man". I love him to death. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-18 23:26:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I am in love with your super straight collar bones.

Also, 175lbs? I'm 6'4" and used to weigh 143lb and I looked like that. Weird!

(and yes, I know 143lb for 6'4" is an extremely low weight. Nobody needs to point it out. I weigh about 198lb right now. I have a goal at about 180lb.) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-18 20:43:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's like he's in a speeding centrifuge. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-18 03:22:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> As I've understood it, by reading interviews and so on, is that Frankie has got such an ego. Other members of Emmure have talked about him just being an egotistic asshole. Even Frankie himself has talked about him being a complete jerk, and how he's trying to keep away from being that person. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-15 21:31:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's not a proper fight video without someone shouting "WORLD STAR" </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-15 20:09:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [Here](https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=nxBbHkSlXHk) ya go </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-15 19:32:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Ironically, just clicking the preview plus sign from RES gives you [this](https://i.imgur.com/OSQu9E9.png), hahaha </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-15 15:45:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Didn't understand a single reference since I don't play dota2 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-13 21:46:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I would say that a gun is a great way to encourage the people you are training to work out! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-07 23:38:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Is it just me, or does that look like a cheese that is a lot harder than mozarella? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The fact that Reinhardt doesn't have a quote referencing MC Hammer makes me sad. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-07 23:30:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It could be either, or both, "Can't touch this" when using the shield, or "Hammer time" for just a voice line.

Something else that would be fun is another chatter between Rein and Torb comparing who's hammer is the best. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-07 19:24:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Allts, hellre det hr n att de gr det p matchen.

Hellre att de bestmmer att de ska mtas upp och slss n att de utstter oskyldiga fr skiten. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-07 19:08:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Jag har en sdan hatkrlek till Adinatoor. Kollade en hel del p Ex on the Beach med min dvarande. Han r asdoucheig, men kunde fan inte sluta skratta t honom. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-07 19:07:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> r glad ver att telefoner man kunde filma med precis hade kommit nr jag gick i hgstadiet. Finns ngra smklipp som jag laddade upp vid 13 rs lder, men som frhoppningsvis numera r lngt borta. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-07 19:03:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I constantly where a bottle opener on my keychain. You never know when it's gonna come in handy. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-06 22:29:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Read the linked article. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-05 17:18:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> One example is the IBP scandal. For those not knowing, [here's](http://wiki.teamliquid.net/counterstrike/North_American_match_fixing_scandal) a summary of it. In short words they got banned for match fixing.

Someone already mentioned the Fnatic - NiP game. Fnatic later came out with an apology about it.

s1mple has often been seen as an e-sport villain due to his horrible attitude towards other players. When he joined Hiko in Liquid, he got knocked down a couple of pins though and matured a lot.

Richard Lewis is always going to be a "villain" in my eyes, even though he's not a player. There's been quite a few controvercies around him due to his behavior. Both physical assault on a player backstage (Queue the "Well, that player shouldn't have been backstage anyway!!!" argument) as well as bullying and verbally assaulting other caster while live on air.

Also the polish crowd during Katowice. They weren't exactly "villains" since it only lasted one tournament, but they booed fnatic after they beat VP. It wasn't until Taz came out and told them not be jerks that they stopped.

I can probably come up with more later.

Also - the CS:GO and LoL community overall. They are the biggest villains overall. Bunch of sexist and racist homophobes high on monster and doritos. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-05 17:12:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I used to do this for a living about a year back. It's not 100% certain that it's amazon themself who ship the things (Unless it's actually sent from one of their warehouses, duh), but it could be a just a small seller.

When we didn't have packages that fit correctly, we sometimes had to put things in an a lot bigger package, just so we could get it sent away.

But then again, no filling seems a tad too weird. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-05 17:06:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> My boner isn't even confused. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> 3v3 Athena announcements </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-05 16:42:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I played a bit of 3v3 yesterday to get a loot box and I realized that the voice lines from Athena isn't matching up. She cuts herself off, can stop mid sentence and start talking about doing the objective after almost every completed game.

Shouldn't this be fixed?


Also, thanks OW team for NOT fixing the D.Va shoot out bug yet. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-05 02:57:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> r det meningen att man ska frst skmtet i brjan? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-05 02:42:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> h. Tycker snubben tar det jvligt vl. Str fr det han har gjort och tar boten. Inga problem med att han blir tagen fr vad han har gjort osv.

Inte s vrst pinsamt, imo. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-05 01:32:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Cheers! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-04 23:32:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> As in the tires been flat and you've later fixed and pumped it again? Or another one of the tire's been flat? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-04 20:40:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I know nothing about cars - what would cause something like this? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-01 00:43:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Holy shit, if this is who I think it is - it's one of the worst persons I've ever met. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-31 21:08:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> No. It shoots out **really far**, right to where the fish are! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-31 20:51:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Dapper af though! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-30 22:12:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Is it just me, or has Vegas lost weight since his last appearance? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-30 21:55:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Motherfucking [SWARJEEEE](https://s.yimg.com/ny/api/res/1.2/JMwkF_hyPUyXKo4flMuUVQ--/YXBwaWQ9aGlnaGxhbmRlcjtzbT0xO3c9NjMwO2g9Mzk1O2lsPXBsYW5l/http://media.zenfs.com/en/blogs/sptusolyexperts/yell.jpg) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-29 15:21:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I would love this! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-28 19:29:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I think that grinding them and then clean it out would work perfect. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-28 19:29:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Well yes. I am aware of that. I was pointing towards this "robot" thingy. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-28 12:22:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I was just about to ask "Aren't yoi going to grind the beans and drink that as well?" </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-28 12:18:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Clips like these makes me realize how many different, sometimes slightly odd, fantasies people have. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-28 01:36:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-28 01:35:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thanks! I'm really bad at maths, haha!

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [Request] People are commenting on the orange being 7 and the cherry being 10. I can't wrap my head around it </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-27 23:44:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-25 21:02:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> /r/gifsthatendtoosoon  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-24 20:08:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What does it stick to? I can only see the small bar protruding from the wall. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-24 19:45:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [Somewhat](https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=dJl55d6z0rk) relevant. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-24 00:22:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hej, broder i vst! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-23 22:33:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What if a small person does that? Will they create a black hole then? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-23 20:58:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The problem is that pacifism isn't going to work anywhere. There's no dictatorship or "evil forces" that sprung out of not using violence.

I'm not a fan of using violence either, but believing that pacifism actually is a viable method is a not very thought through idea. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-23 18:33:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I reported this a bunch of months back as well, together with screenshots. Didn't get any real answers. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-22 22:19:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Is this guy's parents related? Beceause if you feel that an IQ of 107 is gift given to you, I have some bad news for you. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-22 20:29:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [Here's](http://i.imgur.com/WvKFPUF.jpg) me sporting a 5mm/4g septum.

I was nervous, yes. But think of it like this - if you feel that you don't fit with it, you can take it out. In comparison with other piercings, the septum doesn't leave a visible scar. Well, as long as someone isn't looking very close to the insides of your nose, that is. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-22 20:20:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This feels like a picture that was taken so that it would look like something else in the thumbnail. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-22 20:19:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> They just released new coins here in Sweden. But the COA isn't the same, though.

[Here's](http://www.riksbank.se/Documents/Bilder/Mynt_nyform/2013/Press_high/mynt_montage1_high_130611.jpg) the coins! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
