<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject6945</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-09 08:40:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Current cutter here, I have borderline personality disorder. Attempted suicide in October of 2015. 

Cutting is a release. It's a way to deal with your problems. It almost feels validating. It feels like you deserve the pain. 

It makes me feel good. As shitty as that sounds. It makes me feel okay with myself. It's what I get for being the way I am. 

I wish I could stop. I really do. I did alright for a while. Then I get back into a rut and I'm back to it again. 

:(  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-09 03:23:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The Ring..."I saw...her face..."

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-08 07:56:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hmmm. Favorite overall is definitely VII. 

However I really like X's battle system the best. 

I like VIII but haven't played it in years, I started IX and didn't really enjoy it, probably going to pick it up again once I finish my play through of VII. 

Just started VI and I'm already really interested in it. I'm only 20 minutes in but the world is really interesting and the music and sprites/art design are great. 

Also have V that I'm looking forward to starting soon. 

TLDR - VII is my favorite but X has my favorite battle system.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-08 07:30:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Ayyyyy Oswego represent! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-05 04:33:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm not sure what you mean.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-05 04:32:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm not sure what you mean.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-05 01:45:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Like I said above, not living up to the hype might not have been the best way to put it. It's just hard to evaluate if his performance is due to himself or the guys around him. Either way he's a solid guard and still has a high ceiling, but as I said I'm glad we used our first rounder on Jones instead of Collins.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-05 01:44:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I agree with him being solid. But leading up to the draft he was being spoken of as one of the best offensive linemen in the draft. He may very well be, but it's hard to say for certain when you're playing next to 3 All Pro linemen. (Not that it's his fault who is in the trenches with him) let's just say I'm glad we used that first round pick on Jones instead of Collins.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-05 00:07:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> In the 2015 Draft the Cowboys selected Byron Jones with their first round pick, Randy Gregory in the second round (who was considered a first round talent until his stock dropped after a failed drug test) and they signed La'el Collins after he went undrafted (also a projected first round talent, who went undrafted due to a domestic violence investigation). 

Thus, when the draft and subsequent signings were over, some Cowboy fans claimed they won the draft because they had "three first round picks." As in, 3 guys that were all projected to go in the first that miraculously fell into our lap.  

Now it's a joke because Gregory's career is pretty much done with, and while Collins has a lot of potential he hasn't really stood out (not saying he's bad, he just hasn't met the hype yet IMO). However Jones is very promising, and is looking to be one of the centerpieces of our defense for years to come.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-04 18:36:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> THREE FIRST ROUND PICKS </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-28 01:48:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Shit I totally did. Oops.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-28 00:38:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah I get why people would be pessimistic about his ability coming back from an injury like this, but shit talking users (not even. Cowboy fans, I've seen other fans talk about how they think he'll end up performing well in the future) is just annoying. 

On the flip side people acting like he's gonna be the next Patrick Willis is equally as annoying. 

I just hope he doesn't end up like Bobby Fucking Carpenter.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-28 00:33:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> People so quick to hate on Dallas* 

Fixed that for you. /s  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-26 20:45:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That's what I've heard. I know I played quite a bit of it but I think I started getting into cRPGs and stuff like Dark Souls and Fallout around that time which would make sense as to why I don't remember much of it.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-26 15:51:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Agreed. Started with 4 Played them all up until IW. 

CoD 4 - was pretty good, really new type of game for its time. 

W@W - One of my favorites. Great maps and my favorite story mode. 

MW2 - My favorite one but I definitely have rose tinted glasses on. Played it again a while ago and it was just awful. To many killstreaks and the death streaks were annoying as well. I do miss collecting emblems and titles though. 

Skipped MW3 

Black Ops 1 - Solid game. Liked the money system for unlocks and the gambling system for Gun Game, Sharpshooter and Sticks and Stones. 

Ghosts? Was this one next? The campaign was fun but I remember the Time To Kill in multiplayer was so off that I never played it. 

Black Ops 2 - I have the guide in hardcover format, a journal with the logo on it, and the game for PS3 in a metal case, I honestly couldn't tell you a thing about it. 

Skipped Advanced Warfare 

Black Ops 3 - The last one I was really into. It was fun. Not many complaints tbh.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-26 03:29:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Labatt Blue Master Race. 

But if I have to drink a Big 3 beer it's anything but Budweiser. I don't mind Coors or Miller.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-22 02:08:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If the Chargers come in second I want them in Chico. 

The Chico Chargers rolls off the tongue so perfectly.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-21 22:46:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> He's at least a top 25 Small Forward all time. 

He might even end up as one of the top 5 players in Cavalier history. /s </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-18 20:22:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Doug Free (our RT) retired. He was a solid starter but was getting up there in age and inconsistency. Luckily we have a young guy in Chaz Green that should be able to pick up his slack.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-18 00:22:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It was basically a home game. But the Cleveland fans were great. Drunkest I've ever been at a sports event.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-17 23:17:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Nahhh I went to Cleveland for a Cowboys game this year and had an amazing time. The night life is honestly great. 

This is also coming from a guy that loves in a small town outside of Syracuse so.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-17 23:12:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Why are we acting like shutting down Prime D-Rose is good?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-17 20:54:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I admittedly don't watch a lot of KU games. I know virtually nothing about Jackson other than looking at BBref stats. What are some of his strengths and weaknesses and how do you think his game will translate to the NBA?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Is there any way to extract Guaifenesin from Syrup? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-16 03:41:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> My local pharmacy never restocked their DXM only gel caps so I figured I'd buy Delsym with Polistirex. I fucked up and ended up buying an HBr syrup with guaf in it. I'm not looking to throw up and get sick as hell, am I shit out of luck now? 

I've tried googling stuff and all of the blue light forums just say "Buy gelcaps." 

Any advice?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-14 04:56:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> L RON HUBBARD WAS A BLACK MAN  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-14 01:44:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If you turned these 5 into a starting 5 for a team who do you guys think they could beat?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-14 01:37:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The demo for FF8 that was on a Pizza Hut demo disc. 

What got me at first was that the turn based combat was similar to Pokmon (I think I was 4, maybe younger) but I loved the graphics of the cutscenes as well. 

The thing that really got me hooked was the music. It's still my favorite part of every FF game.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-13 18:32:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Obscured by Clouds is my personal favorite. Childhoods End3 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-13 17:08:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Being the best player in Canada is like being the cutest girl in Fulton. /s

Good to hear though. Can't wait to see how he pans out!  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-12 21:42:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'd say in the NFL well over half of the games in weeks 16 and 17 matter. Especially with divisions like the NFC East and North and then also the AFC West, South and North.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-12 17:10:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm guessing Suggs? Definitely agree. Just has to get over the sack hump.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-12 02:53:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It would have been beautiful.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-12 02:48:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Most people are old to a twelve year old.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-11 22:33:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What if Dez's no catch was ruled a catch?

What if Romo didn't go down last year?

What if Romo never botched the snap vs Seattle?

What if the Cowboys ended up with Drew Brees instead of New Orleans?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-10 16:58:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This happened while I was in high school and the thing that I noticed was most of the people that thought it wasn't too big of a deal played sports and experienced sort of the the same thing and the ones that thought it was a huge deal were mostly kids that didn't play sports and didn't really know that this stuff happens all the time.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-10 04:03:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Mezzanine worthy /s </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-08 22:33:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I thought A:R was just a fun movie. Funny one liners, the water part was stressful, and then just WTF moments. Definitely not a great movie but I've watched it quite a few times and always enjoy it.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Getting ready to play Final Fantasy XII for the first time ever! Anything I should know before getting into it? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-08 19:38:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-06 20:04:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Whatever you say buddy.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-06 19:03:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> No worries! As long as people get to read up on it that's fine. I don't care about karma or credit lol </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-06 17:31:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The horror.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-06 17:30:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Do what my uncle does. Talk about how Dallas is going to acquire every free agent, win every super bowl and is always the most underrated team going into every season. 

Sorry uncle Wes. Dallas wouldn't have beaten New England last year, they aren't going to trade Romo for JJ Watt, and they are in my opinion overrated going into every season. 
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-06 17:13:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Homer pick but I think Malachi Richardson does. I think with a strong sophomore season and (if we would have made it with him) a strong tournament run his stock would have gone higher. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-06 16:52:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> http://www.phillyvoice.com/naked-man-causes-stir-near-temple-us-campus/

also this

http://www.phillyvoice.com/naked-screaming-man-has-philly-neighborhood-edge/ </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-06 09:12:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I think you could MAYBE argue top ten. But no way could you do top 5. I'd have:

Rice
Hutson
Moss
Owens
Harrison
Largent
Carter
Fitzgerald
Brown
Irvin

Now I could see someone putting Megatron in front of Fitzy, Brown and/or Irvin, but I have the first two ahead of him for the sole purpose of longevity and I have Irvin ahead of him for being one of the key pieces of the Cowboys dynasty and also for being arguably the most physically dominating receiver of all time (think Dez mixed with Brandon Marshall if you've never seen Irvin play). One could argue that Irvin has worse stats and I would agree but his career was cut short due to injury. 

I would also probably put Steve Smith Sr ahead of Megatron but that's just me.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-06 08:05:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I can agree with you there as well. Sort of like how Calvin Johnsons peak is the greatest for a WR of all time, but he's not a top 5 WR all time. 

That being said KG is easily top 5. He's number 5 in my list.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-06 03:34:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That's true, I apologize. I definitely agree with the less likable player thing too.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-06 01:26:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I don't think KGs NBA legacy compares to TOs NFL legacy. TO is unquestionably a top 3 WR all time. I don't think KG is a top 3 PF all time and I don't know many others that consider him top 3. Top 5 I can agree with, definitely top 10, but not top 3.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-05 22:38:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Some other player (think it was Draymond) cropped it after KD made a bunch of jokes at the all star game saying he was ["cheesier than a Dorito"](http://m.imgur.com/R390EId?r)  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-05 22:36:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> TO not getting in first ballot would be like Dirk or Tim Duncan not getting in first ballot. Like. What? I still can't believe it.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-05 03:42:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'd love to see Duke vs UNC in a championship game. Have they ever been close to playing against each other?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-05 03:40:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I want the Big East that I grew up on back. 
:( I don't care about the ACC at all.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-05 03:23:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Syracuse either loses in the first two rounds of the tournament next year or doesn't make it at all. 

Whether it's the NIT or not doesn't matter to me. There is no wind in my sails after this year. :(  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-03 19:51:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I was playing devils advocate. But thank you for responding!  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-03 19:22:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I don't get why Jerry Rice is considered one of the greatest receivers ever for all of the records he has and people ignore the act that he had Montana and Young throwing to him his entire career but Emmitt isn't even considered a top 5 RB on this subreddit for all the records he has and people just point to him having a great oline his entire career. 

You can't ignore the hall of fame teammates around one player while also criticizing another player for having hall of fame teammates.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-31 22:36:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I would say off the top of my head it's Bobby Carpenter. Claiborne may have left but at least he turned into an above average CB. Wish he could've stayed though.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-27 18:39:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You can tell which ones were athletes and which ones weren't. 

Not just here but in all the sports subs really.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-26 16:54:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'll believe it when I see it. Hall of Fame is a combination of stats and success unless one of those two things severely outweighs the other. 

Do you believe that McNabb should be in the Hall?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-26 16:52:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What is he famous for? You think every single player with a long career and a handful of pro bowls should be in the hall? 

He has volume stats. Nothing more. You can't sit there and tell me that he deserves to be in the hall with the likes of Young, Montana and Elway when this guy has done nothing of actual notice in his career.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-26 03:38:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Except Hasek is considered one of the best (if not THE best) at his position and has the accolades and stats to prove it. Rivers won't sniff the hall and hasn't even been named to an All Pro team.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-26 01:00:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Cowboys won January 1996, so I'd still be a Dallas fan. Yay.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-25 23:37:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What did Colin say about Lebron? I missed it.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-24 17:38:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If you live upstate you name your hometown followed by the closest city to your home town (i.e. Syracuse, Rochester or Buffalo)  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-23 05:48:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So I'm not the only one then? Hahaha I figured everyone else ran plays all the time  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-23 05:41:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I agree. I think I'm just used to it because that's all I've ever used. I'm also utter shite so I don't get many fast break opputunities lmao. 

I barely even run plays  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-23 05:37:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Do people not use it? That's all that I use.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-22 15:41:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> lol </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-22 11:40:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Or James on Steph.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-21 03:25:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Sounds like a fun fuckin ride. 

Also, while I have you, I've heard a lot about Blade Runner, is that one any good? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-21 02:51:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Unfortunately I can see Dallas slipping this year. 

Losing Claiborne, Church, Wilcox and Carr is not only going to hurt our defensive performance but also our cohesiveness. 

Dak is a toss up, I think he'll do well but teams are gonna know how to better to defend him. 

Plus the 8-8 memes never die.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-21 02:22:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> As someone that hasn't seen any of them, should I watch them? What should I be expecting? I honestly know nothing about them.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-20 17:14:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> FASCIST! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-20 01:33:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  I know that. I paid for the subscription so I wouldn't get ads and so I could download podcasts in case I missed them while out and about. I don't use TuneIn just for ESPN.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-20 01:23:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Brian Westbrook for sure. He was actually the first non Cowboy that I bought a jersey for.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-19 18:36:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> They're misinformed then.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-19 15:59:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I don't think I've ever seen anyone argue that Emmitt is the greatest ever. My whole family is Cowboys fans and you'd be ill fated to find one of us that does. 

I personally have him in the 5-10 range.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-15 19:06:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Sorry what? You can't put someone in the Hall because of what they "WOULD HAVE achieved." That's ridiculous. 

He was only named to one pro bowl and never eclipsed 1,000 yards. 

Let's just put in Jamarcus Russell. He was a dominant physical specimen and could have achieved so much. 

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-12 03:30:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Very true.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-12 03:17:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Don't forget circumcision.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-12 03:09:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Currently work as a cook in a nursing home kitchen. 

In October I was sick with bronchitis, was sent home on Sunday, didn't go in Monday and went to the doctor. I was put on antibiotics and told not to come to work for 3 days (with doctors note). Went back in on Friday and was promptly written up by my boss for using more sick days than I was allotted (I only get 4 a year). 

It's ridiculous. I'm instructed by my doctor not to go to work because I could still be contagious. Mind you, I work in a KITCHEN for a NURSING HOME. Probably one of the most high risk places for a sick person to work in considering the lives at risk, and I still get in trouble for it. 

The best part? Couple weeks ago a girl I work with started to get a tingling feeling and the whole left side of her body went numb. She was rushed to the ER and stuff and ended up being out for over a week (mind you, after the second day she was on Snapchat and instagram posting pictures of her drinking/smoking/partying) and she didn't get in trouble for it because she was "sicker" than I was. 

Before anyone asks, yes, this is in America. Fucking ridiculous.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-12 02:13:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'll trade you Dez for a pair of Gisele's socks.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-10 03:38:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You also have to factor in the defense being provided by 2012 CP3 though. He was First Team All Defense that year (not to mention First Team All NBA) and would be stuck on Curry the whole game. Now, that obviously still leaves KD and Harden who, now that I think about it, would be guarded by two first team All Defense players in Lebron and Kobe respectively. 

I think the older team wins because the advantage they have in defense FAR outweighs the advantage that present day has on offense. All in all it would be interesting to say the least. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-10 02:14:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's got all the sports stations, different international stations and podcasts. It's not just ESPN on there.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-10 01:55:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I actually just got a subscription for TuneIn so I can listen to them at work. Best purchase I've made in a while!  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-09 18:11:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Definitely back then.

A team of

1) Paul/Rose
2) Kobe/Wade
3) KD
4) Lebron
5) Dwight

Would absolutely dominate. CP3 and Lebron could be the main distributors to Kobe and KD and they would also be great scoring options on top of it. Then you would have Rose and Wade coming off of the bench along with Howard shutting down whoever tried to drive into the post. 

Now that's not to say that the current team wouldn't perform, but the defense on the current team doesn't even come close IMO. The only players with defense well enough to slow down his man would be Kawhi and AD. Prime CP3, Rose, Dwight and Dwade along with a younger Lebron and pre injury Kobe would be very very difficult to stop.

But that's also assuming the matchups are going to be the ones I'm thinking of. It's all subjective really, you can't go wrong with either team but I think the older team would come out on top (I might also have a bit of rose tint on my glasses, admittedly).

In summation, again, my opinion:

Offensively the first team is more explosive, but they would also have a lot of trouble not only maintaining the explosiveness but also trying to keep up with the playmaking, defense and star power of the old team. However, the old team would have their hands full as well on defense, but I think their defense would prevail.

Nice post OP! I hope we get a lot of discussion on here. It's always interesting to here comparisons between eras. 

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-09 05:54:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Class of '14 here. Noticed that even when in high school.

I partied a lot, did drugs, but also got my work done and never got in really big trouble.

College was a wake up call but oh well. Been in an out of industrial contracts and am currently working in the healthcare field.

A lot of the kids below my age (and some that even are my age) are...squishy. They remind of that Jerry slug thing from Rick and Morty. They cave in to authority and don't want to disappoint even the most insignificant of people.

My younger sister for example is soon to be Class of '18 and she's the exact opposite and so are her friends. They're glued to their phones or laptops, they're scared to go out of their comfort zone and if anything so much as sneezes on their personal bubble they go into full on panic mode. 

My sister has quit two different jobs since turning sixteen because she messed up somehow and broke down in tears.

I just don't get it man. Even 4 years of difference is crazy. I remember every Friday and Saturday there was a party to go to, Sunday was the recovery day and Monday morning before the bell rang was when all the cliques got together and hung out and chatted about their weekends.

A few weeks ago I went to my high school for the day to visit all of my old teachers and such and I didn't see any of what I mentioned above. Kids were in the library frantically catching up on their homework, nobody was talking in the hall way together, and there was an eerie silence in the halls in between all of the periods.

I'm not sure if it's because these kids had almost always had social media and such (I didn't have a Facebook until 2011, I don't use twitter/snapchat/instagram at all really). My sister had all of those different social media accounts before she was even in high school and thats how they do everything. Very strange.

It all boils down to that comfort zone thing IMO. Like my uncle had always told me, "There's no growth in the comfort zone and there's no comfort in the growth zone." </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The biggest problem with stephen a smith </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-08 16:22:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I've been watching First Take for years now and while I wasn't every the biggest fan of Stephen A it took until just now to realize why I can't stand him.

Backstory: I lived in an apartment for the past 4 months with no cable which means no ESPN/First Take/Mike and Mike/Russilo and Kanell, today was the first day where I got to watch First Take before work due to having ESPN again.

Ignore the constant race card pulling, the stupid faces he makes when Max/Skip are talking, the constant talking over everybody, his annoying as shit cadence, my biggest problem with Stephen A Smith is that he is not good at debating or explaining his opinions.

Today I've seen him and Max talk about Desean Jackson and Brandon Marshall. He compares Eli Manning to Aaron Rodgers without explaining his reasoning. Max tries to dissect that point and Stephen A is just being a whiny bitch basically going "La la la I can't hear you." He states that the Cowboys are "The gift that keeps on giving because they always do bad so I look like a genius." Again, when Max asks him to explain his reasoning he goes back to the "La la la I can't hear you" tactic. 

The best part, when he does finally explain his reasoning he sounds incoherent and his argument is chock full of backpedaling and outlandish statements.

If he would act mature and treat First Take like the debate show that it is I'm sure a lot of people wouldn't mind him, but as it stands he's a has-been talking head with his head so far up his own ass he can chew his lunch twice on the way down.

Rant Over. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-08 15:43:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I would recommended they watch the greatest player of this generation. So have them watch either Cleveland or Oklahoma City. Wait. Never mind. 

Waiters is on Miami now. 

I'd have them watch the Heat.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-08 09:13:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Patriots fan maybe? That's just how r/NFL like to be sometimes. Rubbish.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-07 23:43:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> G-Mac 
Jonny Flynn (injuries)
Greg Oden (injuries)
Tyler Hansborough
Jimmer Fredette
Trey Burke

Maybe Christian Laettner? He ended up being decent and made an All Stsr team but never really dominated like in college. 

Homer pick but Michael Carter Williams won rookie of the year but never did anything after that. 

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-07 22:42:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Man. Strictly speaking SU players for myself but I miss CJ Fair, Devendorf, Jonny Flynn, Carter-Williams, Paul Harris. 

There was also a player that played for Pitt that would always kick our asses. Can't remember his name but he had wicked long dreads. My dad called him the Predator. Any Pitt fans have any idea who I'm talking about? Played prolly between 2008-2012.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-07 21:44:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That could also be it. I'm gonna try and fix it once I get home. Thank you!  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-07 19:43:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Exorcist 3
Session 9
1408
Mulholland Drive
Shutter Island
The Shining
The Changeling
Rosemary's Baby  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-07 17:37:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Shit, is that an automatic download? I have the season pass so I probably did without realizing it. 

EDIT: Currently eating lunch, I'll check in 20 minutes or so to see if it downloaded. It probably did. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> I really need some help and I'm not sure who to go to. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-07 17:24:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I've been playing Fallout 4 on PCsince release. I used to be able to run it with most settings on high and also be able to have Antialiasing and Anisotropic Filtering both maxed out. 

Recently I've been trying to play it again and now I can barely run it on low. Is there a reason for that? I had uninstalled it a few months ago and only just reinstalled this past Sunday. Is there something I can do to get the game running well again? I'm not too concerned with quality. I just want to be able to actually play. I'm getting sub 30 FPS and severe input lag. 

My specs:

16 GB RAM
AMD FX 6300 Six Core Processor (3.5 GHz) 
AMD Radeon 7850 2GB

I'd like any help you'd be able to offer me. Thanks advance!  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-07 08:01:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm with you on Sinister. Honestly in my top five all time, and that's saying something. I can understand why a lot of people would hate it but it was the first movie I had personally seen in years that scared the absolute shit out of me. 

*SPOILERS*

The only only thing I didnt like was that whole sequence with Ethan Hawke and the ghost children. Other than that I loved the entire thing. The only horrors I would personally put ahead of it are The Thing (1982), Alien and Event Horizon.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-05 20:33:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That's shitty to hear. Loved watching him at Bama. Thanks for the reply!  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-04 03:30:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Can any Jets fans fill me in on the guys not named Decker? I thought Pryor was a decent player. I remember wanting the Cowboys to draft him.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-03 00:27:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Personally:

1) Resident Evil 3
2) Resident Evil
3) Resident Evil 4
4) Resident Evil 7
5) Resident Evil 2
6) Resident Evil 5
7) Resident Evil 6

If I get to include ALL of the ones I've completed it would go more like...

1) Resident Evil 3
2) Resident Evil
3) Resident Evil 4
4) Resident Evil Outbreak
5) Resident Evil 7
6) Resident Evil Revelations 2
7) Resident Evil 2
9) Resident Evil 
10) Resident Evil: Code Veronica
11) Resident Evil Revelations 
12) Resident Evil Outbreak File 2
13) Resident Evil 5
14) Resident Evil Umbrella Chronicles
15) Resident Evil Darkside Chronicles
16) Resident Evil: Operation Raccoon City
17) Resident Evil 6 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-02 18:56:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I didn't think of it like that, I'd have to agree with you there. 

I guess SU, UCONN, Zona and Louisville would be "Purple Bloods" then? One tier below the Blues?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-02 16:05:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Definitely agree with Zona as well.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-02 15:49:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I would add Syracuse, Louisville and UCONN to your list. Consistently in the tournament and always competitive. Those three have certainly been better than UCLA and Indiana the past twenty years as well. 

But I agree with the Twolves as your pick. 

EDIT: Don't see why I'm getting downvoted for having an opinion but oh well. Guess that's why I don't comment on this subreddit. Wasn't trying to say Indiana and UCLA aren't blue bloods, but was merely trying to add a few to the list that I personally feel compare to them.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-01 17:30:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I would be able to assist a team in being first place...in the draft...lottery. 

I'm a 5'10" white guy that played tennis in high school and college. But I'm also a cigarette smoker with a bad right elbow. So. I'm probably worth less than a fingerless Danny Devi to.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Thank god for /r/The_Donald and all of you pedes! </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-28 00:50:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-27 23:38:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Built my whole computer from the ground up in 2013, haven't noticed a reason to upgrade until recently. Might upgrade either this summer or this holiday season.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-26 22:17:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Awesome. That sounds really cool. Thanks! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-26 20:57:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Sounds perfect for me then. Thanks!  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-26 19:27:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Awesome. I'll check out the Wiki! Thanks!  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-26 19:27:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thanks!  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-26 19:27:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> No worries. I had to sell it on account of the cost of my medications going up. I have more than enough to cover the next few months, just figured I'd buy a console with my refund.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Is it worth getting 2k17 if I don't play any online modes? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-26 18:41:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I've been hearing mixed things about 2k17 compared to 2k16 and I'm going to be buying an Xbox One soon. (Had to sell my PS4 to pay for rent a few months ago) is it worth the $60 for 17 or should I just buy a used copy of 16. 

What are the biggest differences between the two? Is MyLeague any different? Is MyCareer mode still cringey as all hell?  

Thanks in advance!  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-26 16:21:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> /r/JesusChristReddit </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
