<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject4934</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-10 05:47:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Middle Easterners are nowhere near the same level as those who came to the US and slaughtered natives. 

Like it's not even a close comparison. You're either really bad at keeping track of actual stats in Europe, or you failed history in school. The choice is yours as to which one it is, but if you plan on being part of the MAGA team, I'd suggest saying you don't know the factors of the outside world, because then you'd be on par with your leader.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-10 05:19:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Okay, year. 

But personally, having commented on the thread about Comey, I got a few replies that showed me the Trump supporter side of Reddit for a brief few minutes and genuinely thought they were sarcastic comments until checking their post history. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-10 05:00:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What an interesting day of politics it has been. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-10 04:51:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I've also heard he had a kid and simply left the spotlight, then when the kid didn't really need every waking moment he had time to come into Fantasy Factory. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-10 04:06:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Because if Reddit needs one thing, it's someone making jokes in the thread. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-10 04:02:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Wait what?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-10 04:01:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's been years since I've watched Fantasy Factory or Rob and Big but... Fuck this hurts man. 

Of course the dude was clearly unhealthy, but this is a sad, sad thing to read about. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-10 03:11:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  Maybe all the years of research as an immunologist has disqualified me from liking this show. In scientific literature we are taught to deliver succinct information carefully selecting fewest words to get the message across in a meaningful way. I feel like a smart show should be able to create impact and convey the intended meaning in a simplistic fashion.

You're either a troll, or a pretentious twat. Either way, if the show is not for you, then just leave. The fanbase sure as shit won't miss someone with opinions like this. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-10 02:09:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  8 years

hahahahahahahahahahahahahahahahaha. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-10 00:59:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Oh, I wasn't in the loop on knowing he streamed his other accounts. That's actually pretty funny, and I've heard from a few people that he is reformed. While I find it unlikely.. It'd be cool to see him turn it around.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-10 00:55:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Oh okay. Then shit, I should remove my /s and you should tack one on. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-10 00:54:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>   it's always there for easy access.

The fuck does this even mean? The only thing it'd be there for is another super sensitive part of the mouth to burn. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-10 00:53:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That intro reallyyyy hit a soft spot. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-10 00:49:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  can you guys at least save some of your top talent from the hammer.

So... It's okay for the best of the best to be abusive players? Ah okay, I agree. It sounds like a great idea to give players special treatment once they reach top 200...

^^^/s </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-10 00:47:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Okay, so then he grinds it out, gets to Challenger again, and banned. It's been happening to Tyler1 all year hasn't it?

And even if they enjoy that shit, there's no way he'll ever reach rank 1 again. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-10 00:39:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The proportions are either super out of whack, or [this guys] (https://gyazo.com/48094a6290646a2ed359973e26241baa) is fucking huuuuuuuuge. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-10 00:36:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  he's treating immigration as the problem that it actually is

For someone who seems to be up the MAGA tree.. You sure are out of date with your history of the US, aren't you? The country was built on immigration.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-10 00:35:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The subs you browse most definitely have a relation to your opinions. If you frequent TD, then you are a fan of his, therefore willing to defend. 

It'd be like how i browse /r/leagueoflegends , and earlier I was defending the game from people in /r/gaming , who also browsed /r/dota2 , a game that League competes with.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-10 00:24:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Ah, you browse T_D.. Well, time to ignore whatever else you have to say. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-10 00:23:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Okay wait... You want me to actually get into the scientific evidence of global warming and wind/solar vs coal?

I know you may not be used to it, but I want you to think very hard before I have to dig up 5 minutes of research.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-10 00:12:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Have you seen his opinions on global warming, the future of the power industry, and his plans for the wall?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-10 00:11:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Firing the person who is in charge of an investigation into you... 

That man child has way too much power for his level of corruption.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-10 00:06:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's been 4 fucking months. 

Please, for the sake of everyone outside the US, please get Trump out of office so I can stop hearing about how genuinely awful he is as a person, an American, and a president. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-09 23:01:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  The way Riot balances their game is by working on small batches of heroes at a time to make them viable

Apart from the tank update, I don't recall them usually focusing on specific groups.

in the end they do usually succeed but only by making that hero better than another at filling a specified role.

I'd love some examples of this, outside new Mao and maybe Malz way back when. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-09 22:58:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That thing about people talking about him AND TSM underperforming on the international stage..

I just realized they're not the same thing. Players have come and gone, but I've just woven Bjerg into the fabric of TSM. I don't think there's a midlaner out there that could replace him on the team that I'd be happy with. Of course there are better players, but he IS TSM in my eyes.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-09 22:55:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Ok, then to the other patches. Of course they're releasing content, but that's not all they do. There has never been a patch that was simply content to pay for. There are constant changes that need to be made to the game, and I'd imagine it's pretty expensive to do so, so making skins or whatever it is they release only makes sense. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-09 22:53:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Huh, my bad then. Pretty curious how you came out on top then. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-09 22:52:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  They are shit an keeping their community from being toxic,

Because it's on the developer to keep literally millions of players in check day to day. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-09 22:48:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  3) Many of the updates League of Legends gets are around new heroes or skins , essentially revenue generating content.

Ah, you mean like the Mid-Season update that just came out, completely changing a few champions and adding in new items/editing items, and changing the laning phase for an entire role. Those kind of updates?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-09 22:47:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> LoL is infinitely easier to get into when compared to most other top down games. 

It also doesn't help your case that you browse /r/Dota2 while talking shit about League. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-09 22:45:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I like how this has 40 more upvotes than the actual question, and while I agree with you about OP being lazy, it's hilarious that you didn't actually answer the question. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-09 22:39:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  The thunderstorm, the bloody hammer

 This is also fantastic foreshadowing for those who don't know much of the plot. There have been other moments like it but clearly they haven't been picked up on.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-09 22:26:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  but he needs to really start developing more as a character to match up to McShane

Shadow Moon as a character is never as excited or likable as Wednesday himself. Quite frankly he's been more of a character in the show than he is in the book. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> I rarely ever remember to use the Reddit search feature, but when I do, you better believe it'll tell me the servers are down. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-09 21:33:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-09 19:40:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Fuck... This looks wayyyy preachier than any season before it, and I really hope I'm wrong. The show has a good flow and chemistry among the characters, so I really hope this season doesn't go overboard on the "injustice and united power" thing this trailer seems to be going with. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-09 19:36:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  it is almost 300 cartoonishly over-stylized.

I'm pretty certain that is the aim. The show is about old gods and new gods. They can't aim for typical visuals and color correction. 

It may not be for everyone, but the visuals have pretty much nailed the feel of the book/show so far. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-09 19:34:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You really just censored the i in shit?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-09 19:23:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You're going to judge Jackie as a parent on the type of action she took against her kid one time? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-09 18:58:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> "I'm not a comic book guy, I've never been a comic book guy"

I reallyyy enjoyed this week's episode until the guys went on a shit talking rant about a topic they know nothing of.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-09 16:18:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So we're strawmanning now?

It;s gone from jogging vs longboarding, to half assed jogging with breaks vs longboarding on shitty roads with a backpack. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-09 13:07:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Given the interaction on the sub lately with murkah and chiz, along with making sure they're held accountable for fitness, AND chiz saying they'd pick up streaming soon enough, I don't think it's too crazy an idea.

Yeah, he tends to make a lot of plans, but he's not woody level when it comes to never making them work.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-09 13:05:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> There's just no reasonable way to make this argument. Running in non-stop cardio and doing it for an hour or two a day would leave you wrecked.

Longboarding, while it may take work to stay balanced and push yourself... It just can't be anywhere near the same level of workout as a run. 

+If you factor in the learning curve, and him being 40+, it's not like he'll be picking up incredible speeds going downhill or anything. it'll most likely be a casual thing. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-09 03:46:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Well yeah, but unlike his ability to play games, and his ability to work on trucks, his comedy isn't something he has worked for. He's just naturally gifted at "holy shit that's hilarious" moments. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-09 02:51:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah, League can have a weird affect on people sometimes. I have a guy on my friends who is pretty good, and will talk shit to you when you're down, but when he loses lane, it's somehow completely irrelevant and he'll find any other possible way to make himself out to be the winner in such form. 5-0 laner? At least he is pushing the lane to keep the 5-0 with him. 5-0 snowballs? Fucking team.. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-09 02:41:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>   the director is one of renown at this point.
 I don't know who's directing any of those other movies.

Ridley Scott is directing Alien Covenant, and has been some of the most memorable moments in cinema history under his belt. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-09 00:55:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> They are literally destroying your country, why don't you stand up and fucking march against it?!

He is setting a precedent for the rest of the world and I refuse to believe an entire nation is willing to let the world suffer because of the ego of one man. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-09 00:28:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I've always found his comedy to be, for the most part of course, completely unintentional. From lefty to Kyle, Subma-fucking-rine, burn the truck, grandma enema, most Wings moments aren't him peaking at his timing or a planned comedic bomb, but simply Wings being Wings. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-08 22:03:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> oh okay, thanks. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-08 21:47:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  No. NEW players don't get matched with smurfs.
 Smurfs get matched with Smurfs.

Um.. How exactly is this is a known thing, and how could that work? How does it determine it and whatnot? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-08 20:59:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I really don't see this working, simply because Wings is straight up devoted to beating a game the best way he can, with as little errors as possible. It's the one thing he's truly fantastic at. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-08 19:24:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What kinda rare are we talking about? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-08 19:23:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> They really took creative liberties to tell the story of murderer on trial.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-08 13:59:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Rewatching episode 1 and "You could be THE KING OF AMERICA'" reallyyyyyy stood out to me, simply because of how detail sensitive this show is. Seems like we're in for a rollercoaster. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-08 13:52:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I was soooo caught off by that. And it was even a lower body dick pic, just a close-up veigny dick. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-08 13:40:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Realistically just add an l to any word ending in w.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-08 13:35:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hey, I'm on the way to my bookstore now and have a quick question. You said you might feel cheated if having known the stories, but because I don't know them I'll be fine. Would you recommend this as an intro to Norse mythology or would you recommend any other books? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-08 04:43:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I guess I'll look into picking it up then. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-08 04:36:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What if I know none of the stories? Well, outside that of the wall around the city.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-08 04:31:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Teemo=Now has cancer.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Now that's it been out a while, how do people feel about Neil Geiman's "Norse Mythology"? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-08 04:21:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So I enjoyed American Gods, and with the show on now, I've been tempted to fall deeper into mythology, but I highly prefer Norse mythology. 

With that said, I'd rather not pick up a book to be disappointed. 

So apparently he retells old stories? Instead of the way he incorporated the world in American Gods, he simply does a book filled with short stories I guess?

Quite frankly I'm clueless on the matter, and would love to hear how you guys feel about it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-08 04:03:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Marvel movies are great, but they're not perfect. They're pretty bland outside 2-3 movies, and the story telling is formulaic. 

I'm not saying WW will be a better movie than any Marvel, but I'd put some faith in it looking way better than the average Marvel release. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-08 04:02:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Almost every WB trailer for a DC movie ever has been absolutely incredible. Go watch the Man of Steel trailers. The 3rd trailer might still be my favorite trailer of all time. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-08 04:01:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It definitely is, but it was written for the League of Legends World Championship. It's a great song that stands on it's own of course, and it's been used on other material, but he's not wrong in some sense, as it was specifically made for LoL. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-08 03:59:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That is... the basis to the movie. This is nitpicking to another degree. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-08 03:57:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [Damn do I love this shot] (https://i.gyazo.com/1d8981647968da06dac450267f7d0301.jpg)

Also really impressed they didn't spoil the villain for those unfamiliar with the character-enemies. Solid pacing on the trailer too. I can't contain my hype anymore, this movie looks really fucking good. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-08 03:47:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>   It wasn't even weird or different which I think most people can accept. It was.... cheesy. Felt out of place.

It's most definitely weird. It's a woman having sex with people until she swallows them whole through her vagina. I really don't understand how you find it cheesy, that's not what cheesy means at all, it's simply weird. It's also far from out of place. 

Shadow was talking to tvs, sucked into a limo, hung from a tree only to be saved by something we haven't been shown yet (in a massive explosion of blood and gore), and the whole fantasy land he keeps drifting off to. 

Quite frankly, I'm amazed that it's the vagina scene that you find out of place. The show as a whole is making a very clear point as to being insane, going so far as getting Wednesday himself to convince Shadow. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-08 03:41:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Well it'd be the right to do by saying "thanks, I work on it" instead of "oh yeah, it's great right?!" </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> You have 100 euro to spend tomorrow in Dublin. How do you spend it? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-08 02:06:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-08 01:23:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Can this actually be done? 

I watched Game of Thrones mid season 2, and by the end of it I wanted to pick up where the books left off but people said start from the beginning because of plots and developments that are different than the show.

Can manga be picked up after an episode or is it best to start at chapter 1? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-08 01:19:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If this is how you do all episodes, and only watch em once you're missing it. The music in this episode specifically gave me goosegumps.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-08 00:50:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> As an Irishman, these names you have for specific areas are quite adorable and catchy. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-07 23:39:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> And now I'll be sticking with op.gg </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-07 23:31:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What did you expect? If you're going to a movie with the intention of bringing your kids, can you not just sit through it like most kids movies? Or did you go in expecting a Moana, Zootopia level movie? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-07 23:29:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah, I have Tinnitus in my right ear, so during some of the action scenes I had to straight up plug my ear canal with my finger. It was definitely necessary though. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Why is /r/The_Donald mad about the new French president? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-07 22:44:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-07 21:30:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  you secretly concerned about how much money she'll have

It's not really a secret or a worry, it's more of a "are you sure you wanna spend this amount, instead of x amount less, leaving you with x amount more when the time comes?" </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-07 16:49:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Well fuck this took a turn. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-07 16:29:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>   the CGI was better than if they had a costume and make-up and let him do his thing?

Yes. While it definitely isn't perfect compared to today's standards, it is infinitely better than any kind of costume they could have made for a grown man. There was just no realistic way to use costume/special effects work to make him the scrawny, decrepit Gollum we know.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-07 16:24:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  from friends of mine

Ah, the age old "no proof but I know a guy" </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-07 15:49:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> "these farmers" 

Are you serious? Don't China host some of the biggest tech conglomerates on the planet? Talk about not only being a stereotypical douchebag, but believing we should lock them in their own country. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-07 15:44:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thai women man.. Never know what to expect behind the clothes and makeup. 

I'd still take the risk though. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-07 13:49:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I really need to give this show a third rewatching, god damn do I miss it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> DVG - Covered In Color (FULL EP STREAM) </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-07 02:34:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Is it better to play vs people during leveling, or just rushing vs bots? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-07 01:40:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So I'm leveling a smurf, and I'm curious about the fastest way to 30. Is it by playing full length game with 10 people, or playing a 20 minute or so game vs bots? Or, go out of the way and go 3v3/aram etc. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-06 18:45:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> There's no such thing as a noob champ. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-06 18:44:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's beautifully ironic how Woody custom built a pc like a month ago to stop any potential crashes, and all we've really seen from it is really, really stutter heavy audio/video. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What determines the level of player I go against in my first promo? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-06 18:11:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So I'm starting up a new account because I feel after years of playing and being around the same elo, now that I've started to climb quite drastically, I'm curious as to what rank I can get placed if I make an account to simply one trick.

I have a few questions though. How does the game determine the level of my first team? Do my normals effect it in any way? Can I play my draft pick games til 30 with someone from mid silver, and still have a clean slate for the type of player in my promo? Or will my first promo choose my tier of player?

Thanks for any guidance on this. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-06 07:34:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Render distance is a common term, and i have no idea what you expect from wasd. 

This post is both pretentious as fuck, and up before this week's episode, therefore breaking the rules. 

EDIT: The guy just deleted his account, damn. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-06 03:48:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Well it feels like I have to actually ask it, because by the looks of it, you're not critiquing this 11 year old dancer for the emotion on his face, and assuming he's pretentious because of it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-06 03:26:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Y'all are really in here calling an 11 year old pretentious because of how he emotes during his dance? For real? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-06 02:12:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Ah, they probably did, I just can't recall it exactly. My bad I guess. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-06 01:33:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  Tai chi is more of a spiritual thing, a form of meditation.

Pretty sure every type of martial art they talked shit about is somewhat a base for meditation, rather than combat, but that won't stop them. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-05 19:35:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So what you're now saying, is this was a good clip, but the two before it were not? So... you go back on the entire first comment you made? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-05 17:32:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Ah, you mean the comment with negative karma?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-05 16:01:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  People saying it's the best comic book scene ever filmed

I've made it all the way down to the bottom of the thread, and I don't think I've seen such a statement yet. People are excited about the movie, move on. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-05 15:59:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> But..Right now is probably the best it's been in a very, very long time. Rucka is on it and WW is his true love, so as bad as it's been in the past, I implore you to pick up anything Rebirth and onwards.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-05 15:55:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The scene sold the chemistry, the feel of the world they're aiming for, and I the music is very much Sherlock Holmes-esque.

Also..Man of Steel was a good movie ;-; </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-05 15:10:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Guess I'm making a Twitter account, thanks. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-05 04:54:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Anyone have proof of this? Strictly to look down upon Twitch for it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-05 04:29:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Really loving your interactions on the sub lately Chip, continue doing gods work. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-05 04:25:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I...I was so mad about the channel takeover, and now I'm reading this. My heart simply can't take this kind of switchup. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-05 04:19:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You should check the rest of the comment section on the two vids.

Sam dropped something like "I still talk about nerd stuff over on OnlyStupidAnswers" </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-05 02:34:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hahahahahahahahahahaha. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> With PKA being recorded tonight, and Chiz confirming a stream this week/next week. Can we get a warning as to when it's happening? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-05 01:22:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So according to Chiz, him and Kyle will be streaming/playing Battlegrounds at the end of the week, or the start of next week. I know it'll most likely be posted here when it goes live, but being in Europe, I'd have no business checking this sub at 2-3am, so if the hosts were to at least give the day it's happening, I'm sure it'll help a lot of viewers prep for the stream. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-05 00:41:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  this is a business decision to cash out on the popularity.

So are most empires of media these days, and even then, a lot of them are really, really good. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-05 00:40:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>   season 5 and 6?

AND 6?

I'm sorry, but in my book, the only season with actual bad writing was 5, and even then, if you remove Dorne, that season is just fine. At some point in the shows history there had to be a setup season, and 5 was it. 

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-05 00:38:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'd also like to believe that after 7 seasons, they have a pretty solid base for their dragon modelling/design structures, so the costs would be cut down drastically by 2019. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-05 00:29:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Since I've taken my rank seriously for the past few weeks, I've found myself at the mercy of OP.GG. While on the one hand, we have the typical "smurfs" that just want a lane, we also have someone who is actually smurfing and curbstomps the enemy whenever they get their pick. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-04 17:26:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This is eerily accurate to an Ahri I got a few days ago..

"Oh my god, I can't support. Let me mid please, I'm a one trick Ahri smurf".. I proceeded to look her up. She had a 2.4kda with a 49%winrate in like 150 games. 

What's even worse is that she got mid, lost lane, flamed the team, and acted like the "i'm a smurf" thing never even happened. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-04 01:53:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You can dislike the movies, that's fine, but what I'm saying is judging a person by their interest in a sole movie/book is fucking absurd.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Now that the Level 6-7 mastery has been out a while, could we get an S or S+ counter beside it? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-04 01:32:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-04 00:42:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Turtle waited til 47 minutes in to get his first kill, then got 3 kills within 1 minute. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-04 00:41:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [TSM fans right now] (https://gyazo.com/fa6dd8237ee27064931f0c6738bf16b0) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-04 00:20:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Weeks of fantastic PKA.. Amazing content on the sub lately, and now streams?

I feel blessed by the level of content we're at. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-04 00:11:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Of course he didn't. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-03 23:51:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  and your team isn't winning it through good plays

But... TSM wrapped the game up pretty well for a team that were just at nexus towers. They came back up, wiped out the enemy, got baron, and paced the push enough to actually end the game, unlike GAM minutes before. That's solid gameplay/shotcalling. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-03 23:46:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Doing the quick maths according to his Filmography on Wikipedia.. He is 5 million short of 6 billion dollars. That's not including budgets, but if anyone wants it just ask. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-03 23:41:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I was going to quote and reply to each sentence, until I realize the entire comment is ridiculous. 

Bay may not be your favorite director, but acting like he's a completely brainless ape who can't be involved in a good show/movie is fucking absurd. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-03 23:38:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> But how is that luck? The enemy made a mistake, and TSM took a huge leap back into the game because of it. That's just not luck. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-03 23:33:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> GAM over stayed their welcome, it's not luck, it's greedy shotcalling. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-03 23:31:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The return of Doublelift has never been so welcomed. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-03 22:57:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Well that's amazingly pretentious.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-03 18:24:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's not ideal, but it's most definitely a better situation than the past. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-03 15:38:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Seems like a dick thing to do. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-03 15:33:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Ok, I agree if that if I were to have gone in blind I may feel the same way, but I'm just trying to nudge you ahead if that makes sense. While there are flaws now, if you trust in how praised the book material is, you should at least try EP 2-3 to see if things start to fall into place. After all, most shows have a god awful pilot. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-03 15:31:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Watching this trailer was like watching the hearts of all Dark Tower readers break into a million pieces.

God this is truly a damn shame. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-03 04:41:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I feel like saying "with fans" is unfair. I'm ultimately a much bigger DC fan than I am Marvel, but damn do I love the Marvel movies.

I just don't want a the idea of a DC fan to be that of a toxic, anti-marvel neckbeard, considering I can't wait for Wonder Woman and Justice League, and would prefer it if I were to not be lumped in with a very obscure minority. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-03 03:00:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Well yeah, but it seems like that's a way to end a GoTG movie. They find out about him, and the shop warps away. Cutting to how they find out in IW will be tricky unless they're applied before. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-03 01:39:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I know he is, but what I'm saying is, I'm pretty sure the viewers who haven't read the books don't know that yet. Nothing he does makes him truly godly in this episode. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-03 01:31:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> There's just so much wrong with what you're saying..

Why was he played that extremely wooden and emotionless?

This sums up the character of Shadow. He is very much there as a witness for the reader/viewer. 

So the guys wife died suddenly but a few hours after getting that news he is on a plane with Ian McShane's character exchanging cool guy one liners while looking slightly bummed out.

You may not understand how grief works. It can be experienced quite a few different ways. Also no idea why suddenly is in bold. 

Off to the bar with Pablo Schreiber character (The Leprechaun), more cool guy one liners while the fact that Schreiber's character's coin trick is magic was way to much on the nose and lasted way to long. And of course you can't have two meatheads in one scene without using the opportunity to have a fist fight.

Straight up setting up the character of Leprechaun. 

Honestly, if this wouldn't be based on a popular book by a popular author judging by just this pilot I would assume cheap SyFi channel show that get canceled after half a season.

The show's visuals alone are enough reason to ignore your opinion on the matter, but nonetheless, I hope you'll continue watching the show as a lot of your complains seem to be because it's the pilot, and it was designed to leave a lot of questions. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-03 01:27:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [Just to be safe, it's all technically spoileres here] (#s "I'm not sure how many people actually know that Wednesday is Odin's day though, so a huge chunk of the audience may have no clue at all.") </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-03 01:25:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Well to be fair, at no point do they imply Technical Boy is a god. It's just a really trippy scene. I also appreciated the thumb faces more than blurred out, if that's the route you'd want.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-03 01:23:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Are you talking about the final shot? I actually really liked that scene. It sets up the awesome power of a certain character we'll see next episode. [Name] (#s "His wife") </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-03 01:13:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  What are you a DC shill,

Please don't make Marvel-DC into some politically focused Left vs Right scenario.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-03 01:12:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> But it also seems tricky to leave them out there and just show up in Infinity War, unless Thor drags them into the fold somehow. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-02 18:53:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm still waiting for him to work on an old car.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-02 05:42:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> As opposed to have Vikings slaughter each other, and have a body ripped in half, with a spine shot into the air... 

I just dont think it's reasonable to act like a native hanging is too out there. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-02 00:51:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> On one hand, I'd kill for some old SF hosts on this new ride, but on the other hand... I wonder if there are a a collection of people out there that simply need to be meshed together to become another set of people will hope to see in our sub boxes every day. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-02 00:44:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If I remember it correctly, that intro is vastly different from that scene in the books, and I'm pretty disappointed. I loved the terror vibe we got from the natives slaughtering the entire camp.

With that said.. I'm open to changes because it's set to be a long show. Here's hoping they don't sacrifice quality for quantity.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-02 00:42:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>   Shadow is intentionally and foolishly not asking pertinent questions just to keep mystery alive for the viewers

This was the same for readers as far as I remember. That being said.. The guy also did just get out of prison, find out his wife died, and then find out she was cheating on him. If I was in his shoes, I'd probably just go where the wind blew me at that point too. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-02 00:39:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That's exactly it. Reading it I had to do a few takes to fully imagine how it'd work.. Yep, they fucking killed it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-02 00:39:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You'll be glad you did if I must say so. It definitely tries more on setting up the vibe of the characters than it does show where the story is going. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Support mains of Reddit, what kind of clips do you keep in the "highlights" section of the new client? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-01 05:03:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So I've been playing lately and considering we have to play on the new client, I'm trying to take full use of all the new features.

With that said.. Finding clips that I'd consider for the 3 spots available to look back upon, none of them really satisfy me. With every other role, there's that INSANE play you can grab. With support, while you may be playing it like "holy shit this is huge".. with most champs it simply doesn't look that way, unless it's a Thresh, Nami, Rakan, Bard maybe..

So yeah, I'd love to talk about what clips you'd throw into those spots just so I can get some kind of idea, rather than being a picky asshole like I usually am. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-30 20:15:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I was watching it, then once I heard the "ahhhhh-ahh" as they pull into the city I had to check the date because I've heard that sound before.. What an odd post. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-30 18:15:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Could we get one for Championship Thresh?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-30 15:39:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  He's even managed to get the honors ribbons in league on some accounts over this year for being a friendly teammate

So what you're saying is he's still playing a game that he was permabanned on?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-30 14:37:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> No, I really appreciated it. Amid all the chaos, here is Groot, someone who is pivotal to the team, yet completely innocent in most cases and just doing what he can to help at times. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-30 05:11:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If anything, there seems to be a circle-jerk for talking shit about black and white films lately.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-30 03:31:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  or the smartest

Who in the JL is smarter than Batman? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-30 02:12:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> But why should it HAVE to be visible? 

Also, people have to readjust camera angle for a whole bunch of stuff, I really don't see why this is different.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-30 01:36:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Ok? Using this as an excuse is close to meaningless. A huge part of the laning phase is keeping the adc from getting cs.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-29 23:00:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Well I could go on to say it's even a mechanic that can simply be used but being realistic, a lot of this sub will talk down to anyone calling it a mechanic because it's used against them. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-29 21:31:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> There is a difference between a bug, and a design flaw.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-29 20:30:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  poorly made rubbish!

I'll agree it can be ham fisted, and I can agree it's not for everyone, but it's most definitely not a poorly made movie. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-29 18:54:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Oh you most definitely can. Just pimp certain products/services while you film. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-29 18:45:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  where the camera is block by the tower

That's just not true. You can move the camera to see it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-29 18:44:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Please don't blow this trap thing out of proportion. It's not a bug, it's just a flaw someone found while laning vs cait. Shit, they're called traps, why is it so wrong to not be able to see it when your camera is positioned a certain way? 

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-29 18:17:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm not sure what it is, but PKA has been absolutely fantastic for the past few weeks.

So glad to say I'm back in love with the show.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-29 17:09:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Because I'm average at everything else, so it doesn't bother me where I get after support. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> FYI: Role selection is bugged out. Always double check when choosing. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-29 17:04:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I've played 3 games today, and always chose Play Again. After doing so, I'd go to flick the main role to the right for support, which sounds obvious right? But then I'd notice while I have my mouse button pressed down, the role selection box is in the bottom right section of the client and I'd end up choosing mid.

Looking back, I realize this was probably something that happened last night too simply because I got mid after going my typical Support/Fill. 

TLDR: The Role Selection window may be displaced so pay attention to where you flick your mouse. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-29 13:44:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Not really. Superman died in BVS but thats not stopping him from coming back in the future. 

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-29 13:41:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It might be best if you sit down for this talk son.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-28 19:06:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Just a few notes:

This movie was funnier and more emotional than I ever expected. 

Baby groot was utilized perfectly. 

Also never once expected Bautista to be not just a main character, but legitimately one of my favorite parts of one of my favorite marvel movies. 

Solid Marvel movie with incredible visuals.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-28 14:18:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> For those wondering.. [Square ass head] ( https://i.ytimg.com/vi/ZfaY6Ym8T6E/hqdefault.jpg) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Given the amount of people on the planet, you could probably think of an activity or moment in life and someone is experiencing it right now. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-28 12:21:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-28 04:55:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Can I ask why it's a big offense? Here in EU it's basic terminology for talking shit. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-28 04:48:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>   based on the trailers

What exactly do you not like? It may simply be because I'm a big fan of the character, but I've loved the marketing so far for this. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> That one time Woody mentioned bringing Sark on as a guest... 3 years ago. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-28 03:08:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> INSANE Qtpie Vancouver Vlog #1 </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-27 23:53:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-27 23:13:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This is a topic that most would probably prefer for him to bring up on his own time. 

Often times a question will come by and people will say it's no right of ours to know, and I feel this is definitely near the top of that kind of list.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-27 18:36:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Ok that's fair enough to agree with.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-27 18:14:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm not quite sure the internet is ready for this. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-27 17:44:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  so all in all i dont think they spent more than six months to a year on this.

Well that's ridiculous, especially given that you talked about them needed concept work "and shit". Are you trying to say the build up and the actual creation of the game isn't included in their time frame because you're talking about actual in game, building the framework kinda stuff aren't you?

Oh that's fucking hilarious. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-27 16:30:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I thought I've been on the internet long enough to have seen it all.... Holy shit is this a rabbit hole I'm willing to fall down. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-27 16:26:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Wait, what do you mean you don't buy it? They have a 3 year rotation plan, I don't see what's not to buy. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-27 15:42:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So because the last 5 years of games have been poorly received, and were destroyed by loot boxes, that falls on the shoulders of the guys working on the game? 

I'm pretty sure there were some guys who were very happy with their finished product for the Campaign. Guys who liked the look of the map they made. Guys who designed the guns etc. 

Also, 5+ is implying Black Ops 2 and further back were bad games. I personally hold BO2 as one of the best there was. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-27 15:39:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>   now six months later they come out with their own?

See, this is just it. Sledgehammer have been working on this game for 3 years, not 6 fucking months. Activision have 3 seperate companies all release a game a year, and they rotate through a cycle. 

Sledgehammer gave us Advanced Warfare.

Treyarch gave us Black Ops 3. 

Infinity Ward gave us Infinite Warfare.

So now, 3 years after releasing Advanced Warfare, this is what they're giving us. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-27 04:38:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> They've already said there is an emphasis on a British intelligence agent, a french resistance fighter.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-27 04:37:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Supply drops can be a thing without ruining the game though. I said it earlier, but I'll say it here too. Overwatch is managing it just fine. Once the camos don't become over the top, and they stay away from selling weapons with varying stats we'll be fine. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-27 04:35:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  so they gonna give it minimum effort as always

I feel this is just an unfair thing to say. Activision are the global behemoth that can print their own money, but the companies like Sledgehammer, Treyarch, Infinity Ward.. As much as they put out disappointing games in the last few years, I find it very hard to believe the people working on the games actually aimed at the lowest effort, easiest release there is.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-27 00:08:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Ah okay. Still though, turns out a lot has been announced outside the trailer. Zombies too apparently. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-27 00:06:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> As long as they're completely cosmetic I'm completely fine with it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-27 00:05:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  you can trade in game items with other players.

Um, anyone able to fill me in? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-27 00:01:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's a mechanic we've never seen before, and damn do I fucking love it.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-26 23:58:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  just for coop campaign

Hold the fuck up, when was this confirmed? On the stream after the trailer?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-26 23:41:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> But there are those out there that are just fine paying 5 bucks for a new camo or look in game. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-26 22:02:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Dear god.. This episode really has me on the edge of trying to pick up a ps4 for Horizon Zero Dawn ;-; </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-26 21:49:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Oh I know, but it was the only analogy I could make in that moment. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-26 21:29:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Does it really matter though? I'm in Ireland and I still call it soccer. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-26 21:27:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Maybe compare it to Cod. It may have been because I was into following the scene at the time, but back around the time Cod was at it's peak, the pro scene was pretty huge and I knew most of the players. That is all still going today, but looking at the people that are lining up to play it.. The only guys I still know are the Optic guys. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-26 21:25:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Feel bad for Hauntzer lately. Wasn't that taken out of context completely? He was talking about Korean top laners playing in NA, and somehow it's now universally believed to be his opinion on every top laner in the pro scene..

EDIT: I'm not sure why I'm being downvoted, what I'm saying is the simple truth. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-26 21:24:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  Bengi was doubted by everyone but only kkoma saw the potential.

This sounds like the premise to a movie. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Call of Duty: WWII Trailer </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-26 20:08:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-26 19:59:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I really liked Assassins Creed 3 though.. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-26 19:58:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  ww2 themed trailer.

This answers your question. We've been asking for it for maybe 2-3 years now, and they're finally going back. If that doesn't get at least some hype I don't know what will. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-26 19:56:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Can't confirm.

Am a gamer. Do have sex with a girl.

Your maths doesn't check out, sorry. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-26 19:51:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Oh I agree completely. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-26 19:42:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Pre-ordering a Cod will change nothing for anyone else. The game is already a behemoth, and Activision is it's own money making machine. Waiting til launch will not change their approach to marketing at this point. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-26 19:41:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I genuinely hope this game is everything we've wanted, just so I can stop talked down to while defending the potential it has. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-26 19:37:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> They haven't ruined Overwatch or League of Legends. 

Micro transactions only ruin the experience when they sell actual guns that have increased stats.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-26 19:33:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> And here lies the flaw of creating a game. No matter what you do, there will be a reason not to do it.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-26 19:31:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Remember, circlejerk over what other people do with their money! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-26 17:38:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  Now all you love him because he sat on a bench and ate a sandwich.

Not even close to why people love him. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-26 14:09:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Wait, so are you saying the image on the right is the real one? 

Fuck, we haven't lost Bill to the LGBTQIASLFOSNFSAN have we?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-26 13:06:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  out there in the real world.

We're on Reddit though.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
