<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject136</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2010-09-16 23:49:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Didn't sound like an ass good sir.

I think cultural implications may have effected the way that I hurt myself more than whether or not I did. The first time I hurt myself intentionally that I know of was when I ground my fist into a wall repetitively, and I don't think that I've ever seen much of that in the media. So my first impulses to hurt myself stemmed from my own need for self destruction I would say; the ways I ended up hurting myself stemmed from the media most likely.

I believe that there is nothing wrong with the action of injuring yourself. The fact is, it's a sign of something else and that's the problem. If you fix up all those problems and still are cutting just because you're addicted, I really wouldn't see a problem besides the addiction itself. However, I find it very hard to believe that someone would hurt them self and not have an underlying problem besides addiction. I know that probably sounded pretty contradictory but I don't know how else to explain it. 

The reason I don't hurt myself right now despite my love for it is because I don't need it. I realize that unlike I did before. I have found other things to hold on to. The thing is, I cannot blame anyone who has yet to discover that. 

Sorry that was so long. Hope I explained that. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2010-09-16 23:37:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> thanks for the online diagnosis. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2010-09-16 00:22:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I go to therapy. I don't cut anymore. It's not about attention from my parents. I had hell with my parents over cutting. It was an outlet for my anxiety and depression which began in my early childhood. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2010-09-16 00:20:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> nope. i know people do that but i never thought cutting in a shape made much of a difference from cutting in a line. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2010-09-16 00:12:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I always think about this, being in your situation and all. I would never know how to treat my child, I would never know how to take care of anyone with the same problem as myself. I have a list of wrongs though, since my parents did do some things that were less than exemplary:
If your child is closed up, let her be. Prying is the most damaging thing I have experienced from my mother. I recall multiple accounts where I felt more guilt for not being able to vocalize what I felt, and she felt more guilty for worsening my conditioning. This circle of negative emotion sometimes led me to having a panic attack.
Also never deny a child's pain or issues. But clearly from your post you don't do that. 
Don't ask to see the cuts, don't send the kid to doctors once a week to check on the cuts. Unless you know your child is cutting to a point where they may cut too deep or they need hospitalization, it is rather stressful and shameful to be inspected once a week. Therapy is good.
Thank you for taking care of your daughter. Sorry I'm not much help. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2010-09-15 06:40:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yea, I actually started hurting myself without a razor and migrated to it. As in I hurt myself without knowing that I was doing something that was close to cutting. Then I slowly changed methods until I actually was cutting. I doubt I would have figured out that method if the media didn't glamorize that method, but I still hurt myself. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2010-09-15 06:13:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Oh I'm medicated. They just make me such a zombie. Topamax and Zoloft are the current owners of my brain. I guess it's better.

Now I'm absurdly curious about your past.. wanna elaborate a little? Sorry to keep bugging you : </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2010-09-15 06:03:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The cuts were made to provide me with something and those cuts happened to scar. 

Sorry I came off as sassy, I didn't mean to be. It was either my stupid humor, or just my inability to know how you'd react. I just deal with this misconception a lot.

I posted the AMA in hopes that people would come with open minds rather than jumping to the attention card. I don't show my scars, thus they aren't being used to stimulate a reaction in others.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
