<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject3726</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-15 21:24:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thanks for your reply. When you say 'lack of agitation' though - do you mean stirring? I always thought it was best *not* to stir caramel. Or is that only a rule if I am melting sugar on its own?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Does sugar ever dissolve in fat? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-15 20:45:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Firstly - I am sorry for posting so many questions at once (this is the last one for now) but I've only just discovered this sub and these are questions I've wanted some good advice on literally for YEARS. This sub is great. Anyway - caramel. I have had my own long and arduous journey with caramel which I will not go into - suffice to say I've got a handle on it now and caramel no longer scares me. But over the years I've struggled with many recipes that have told me to put butter and sugar into a pan and melt them together to 'make a caramel'. These are not random internet recipes, but proper recipes in books written by respected chefs. It never works. A while back I did some research and discovered that, according to scientific sources, sugar will not dissolve in fat. Is this true? And if so, WHY do so many recipes ask you to make caramel this way? This is a decades-old bugbear of mine.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-15 20:28:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thanks I will try that. Now I've just got to figure out what to do with this massive dish of salty whipped cream.... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-15 20:26:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thanks for the response. So I would add the milk *after* I whip the cream I'm thinking...? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> multi-function ovens - what's best for what? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-15 18:13:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> My new electric oven has 8 settings using a combination of conventional heating, fan, and grill (broiler in US). Anyone help me with a rough guide to which oven settings are best for which jobs? I use the oven for everything from roasting to baking. I have noticed that fan settings tend to create a hotter oven, and I'm not sure if this is a fault with the oven or if it's always the way. Any advice? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Double cream/ whipping cream - general cream confusion </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-15 18:03:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hi - first time posting here so apologies in advance if this isn't appropriate. 

My question is about the fat content of cream. I use Michel Roux Snr's recipes a lot (the man is a genius) but I find he is *very* heavy on the cream. I recently made his version of ham mousse, which called for 'whipping cream' - 800ml for 8 servings (see what I mean?). I was only able to get double cream (heavy cream in the US) and thought it was more or less the same thing. The mousse was not pleasant and tasted overwhelmingly of cream. Also after it was whipped the volume was huge and I ended up with enough mousse for 16. I have since found out there is a slight difference between whipping and double cream - but according to the internet this is only a few % fat content. Whipping cream, the internet tells me, is around 35% fat while double is 35 - 40%. I looked on my carton of double and the fat content was 48%. I find all this totally confusing. When following recipes should I adjust the amount of cream I use according to the fat content on the carton?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-14 10:42:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Ah OK sorry for patronising with stuff you already know! With Weerasethakul I would start with *Syndromes And A Century* or *Tropical Malady*. If you have never done Kiarostami you have a treat in store - I am jealous! Watch *Close Up*. I cried during that movie because I couldn't beleive I was watching something so beautiful. 

This is quite an interesting overview re politics in Kar Wai http://filmint.nu/?p=9206.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-14 01:55:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> They don't have that much in common to be honest - except the films you mention lean heavily on montage to tell their stories. Perhaps what's rocking your boat is simply what I would call an 'abstract narrative' approach to film making. Without more knowledge of what you have or haven't seen, it's difficult to make recommendations, but some obvious ones (forgive me if they're too obvious) would be Tarkovsky's *Mirror*, Resnais' *Hiroshima Mon Amour*, and maybe a Werner Herzog like *Kaspar Hausser*. In films such as *The Double Life Of Veronique* and *Three Colours: Blue* Kieslowski is a match for Kar Wai's supremely stylish poetics. 

If you want to go all the way into poetic abstraction try a Weerasethakul like *Tropical Malady* or even *Man With A Movie Camera* (pure montage). 

Two of the films you mention, *Spirit Of The Beehive* and *In The Mood For Love* contain deeply obscured political content - both having been made during the watch of censor-happy regimes. Is the intensity this can inspire what is grabbing you? If so you might look at Kiarostami, especially *Taste Of Cherry*.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-09 23:53:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Bergman - especially *Cries And Whispers* and the ensemble scenes in *Fanny And Alexander*. Also (as someone has mentioned already) Renoir's *The Rules Of The Game*. I recently saw *Summer Hours* by Olivier Assayas - some impressive blocking here in very tight interiors with groups of actors all moving at once.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-09 23:49:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yes! - this is the film that sprang to mind for me too! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-08 02:06:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Here in London, your small independent cinema audience can be just as annoying as the multiplex. Hipsters with an out-of-control sense of entitlement are just as likely to start texting or chatting to their friends during a film as some idiot down the multiplex who just doesn't know any better - in fact the former is *more* annoying because of this. Arrogance is more annoying than ignorance! If there's a film I *must* see at the cinema, I tend to favour the multiplex. I choose a week day matinee show. This, coupled with the fact that the type of films I like are never too popular there, usually provides a nice small and quiet audience.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-08 01:59:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I prefer to watch films in a cinema with a very quiet, very attentive audience. Unfortunately such audiences don't exist now, so I have stopped going to the cinema. A few years ago I worked as a film critic for a while and got to go to critics screenings. They were the best conditions to enjoy a film I have experienced - completely silent attentive audience. There *is* something special about watching a film with other people - it can be quite a different experience than watching alone. This is especially obvious in the case of comedy, but it applies elsewhere also. These days I only watch films alone at home, and that's a shame.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-07 21:52:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> For me, one of Kubrick's flaws (big Kubrick fan here BTW) was his occasional misfire in the casting department. It possibly was a result of arrogance on his part - the idea that he could take *any* actor and make them great. It happened with Ryan O'Neil in *Barry Lyndon*, and (just IMO) *Eyes Wide Shut* is another example. I found the 'acting competition' taking place between Cruise and Kidman irritating to say the least. *This is gonna be MY movie you SOB!*

Apart from that I enjoy *Eyes Wide Shut*, but I don't think it's one of Kubrick's 'great' films. Just my personal take  here (people are sensitive about Kubrick - I have learned elsewhere on this sub!) - but for me Kubrick excelled at 'trapped' narratives. It's when his story was limited to two or three locations that he could really fly.

 As a story teller, Kubrick leaned toward allegory - and yet, frustratingly, he was not a great allegorist! His most allegorical films (*Clockwork Orange* for example) are dull. I would suggest *Eyes Wide Shut* is such an allegorical work. He was, primarily, a visual artist who was at his best when able to mastermind an entire visual language for his audience - that is to say, when he could control and design the details of his world. The less control he has, the less powerful the result. Therefore, his 'multi-location' films like *Eyes Wide Shut*, while having much to admire and enjoy, are never going to work as well as something like *The Shining* or *2001*.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-07 21:30:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  It's not his best, that's probably Barry Lyndon

Say *what*? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-05 23:41:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Not really on topic, but for two years now every time *Birdman* comes up I ask the forum what that fiery commet in the sky was about. Nobody has ever answered me.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-05 23:37:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I remember this film vividly as I found it totally absorbing. I think it was a real 'zeitgeist' movie at the time, especially in France. It came at a time when France had just started to wake up to the social problems in its more diverse communities - usually exemplified by the troubled Parisian suburbs. It addressed an older generation's fear of disorder and a lack of respect in younger people, reinforced by the 'otherness' of ethnicity. It's worth remembering that France, while politically and ethically an extremely liberal country, can be culturally very conservative. 

The film was also extraordinary in the way it was developed. Based on a book written by a teacher describing his own experiences in a difficult school, the teacher ended up actually *starring* in the film, playing a version of himself (this is the main character). The younger actors were cast directly from similar real life schools, so basically there are almost *no* professional actors in the film. The authenticity this provides is a major feature of the film's success. 

The final scene, as I remember, was an optimistic attempt at a happy ending. It suggested that, despite everything, a positive future was possible for both the teacher and the pupils. 

If you enjoyed the movie definitely check out Cantet's other films because they are terrific, especially *Time Out* and *Human Resources*.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-04 10:10:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  there isn't any obvious through line to the films that you've listed

I see yes - maybe that makes it difficult. I just want to get inspired again and stop feeling like great cinema is in the past! Thanks for your reply anyway - I have not seen (or even heard of) the films you mention and I will definitely check them out.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-04 00:00:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hi - been inspired by similar posts like this to write my own version.

So I'm kind of a lapsed cineaste. I've basically lost my mojo when it comes to film, which was once a passionate interest for me. I guess I've become bitter and cynical, believing the best movies have already been made. 

Me: I'm a big fan of cinema from the 80s and 90s - my 'top films' list is very busy during that period, but then gradually slacks off, till there is probably about one film added a year since 2010. Last films that made my list (I don't have an *actual* list - I'm speaking figuratively!) were probably *Amour* (2012) *Martha Marcy May Marlene* (2011) and *Syndromes And A Century* (2006) (this is to give you an idea of what kind of film making I like). My favourite directors are French - Maurice Pialat and Agnes Varda. I love (or loved) French cinema. Also love Kiarostami, Kubrick, Haneke, Tarkovsky, Anderson ... you get the picture. In addition to my highbrow tastes, I have a fondness for American comedies from the Apatow stable, as well as Pixar movies. *Hate* the likes of Nolan and Inarritu - *hate* 'mind bending' movies. *Hate* Tarantino with a passion! 

My question: given my movie profile, what film makers/ movements/ countries am I missing? What amazing contemporary films have I lost touch with? What movies can relight my fire?? Help me TrueFilmers.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-03 23:39:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Definite:
Familia Rodante (Pablo Trapero 2004)

And possibly:
Summer Hours (Olivier Assayas 2008)
Hannah And Her Sisters (Woody Allen 1986)
Ordinary People (Robert Redford 1980) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-03 23:24:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thanks for your comment. Yes they are related thematically. It could easily be a case of artists working on similar themes which are, admittedly, pretty universal. I think it was the structure of the two narratives - strictly episodic, often describing one fabulous social event after another - along with the central character of the journalist and his would-be romance that got me thinking there might be more than coincidence.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-03 23:16:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I have heard that but I haven't read the book so can't confirm. It's just a more cohesive film - and by cohesive I don't mean comprehensible exactly, I mean that structurally it feels more of a united whole than the Tarkovsky, which reads as disjointed to me. It's worth seeing - apart from anything else George Clooney is superb in the leading role.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-03 16:07:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  Unless there was a similar post-war social "movement"(?) among aristocrats in Rome

Absolutely there was - I think the two periods are easily comparable. 1930 - 12 years after the end of the globally catastrophic Great War, 1960 - 15 years after the equally devastating second WW. It's something about a kind of societal search for meaning after events so terrible they would naturally lead a new generation to ask 'what's it all about'? I think the world was a uniquely unsettling place for these postwar generations. I interpret their hedonism as a form of depression - a cry for help.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-03 15:51:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm not sure I'm feeling the similarities as strongly as you. Both works are satirising the futility and dehumanising nature of warfare. Therefore they are sure to have much in common. Could you make a similar comparison with Kurt Vonnegut's *Slaughterhouse-five*? *MASH*? 

Hilarious as *Dr Strangelove* is, I think its creative ambitions fall short of those demonstrated by *Catch 22*. *Strangelove* is a brilliantly told joke, the point being to shine light on the ridiculousness of the cold war arms race. It's irreverent, almost immature (in a good way) in its tone; the schoolboy humour offset by the deadpan, drop dead visual cool of the thing. It's a while since I read *Catch 22*, but my memory of it is as an entirely weightier piece. Yes there is irreverent satire - but there's a whole lot more besides. Is there content I'm missing?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Was *La Dolce Vita* based on *Vile Bodies*? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-03 14:40:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Married to Fellini and especially his masterpieces *La Dolce Vita* (1960) and *8 1/2* (1963), I am greatly struck by the similarities between *La Dolce Vita* and Evelyn Waugh's *Vile Bodies* (1930) which I read for the first time recently. I am surprised further by the absence of reference to these similarities when searching the internet. 

Interviews with Fellini himself suggest the only inspiration for *La Dolce Vita* was Fellini's own experiences - that it's an autobiographical film. But the debauched, hedonistic milieu - the grandiose set pieces describing wild parties - the strict episodic structure - the central character of the gossip journalist who's romance with an aristocrat simply blows away into dust - the coldly observational tone that never quite tips over into satire.... Can anyone enlighten me? Is it simply a coincidence? Is this a well established cross-reference I have simply missed? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-03 14:17:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yes *2001* is definitely up there with the greats! I have a private thought on *Solaris* that I have never shared with anyone because it feels like *blasphemy*. Here goes - I think the Soderbergh version is *better* than the Tarkovsky. I'm nervous now - am I going to get arrested? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-03 09:58:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thanks for posting your article. 

I agree with you that *2001* is not cold and sterile. The scene where Bowman 'shuts down' HAL is arguably the most open hearted Kubrick has ever been. Of course it's quintessential Kubrick that this sentimental scene portrays the death of the villain of the piece. 

I too am a huge admirer of Tarkovsky. But I struggle with *Solaris* - it's the one Tarkovsky film I have seen that made no impact on me at all. Although very generally speaking I would rate Tarkovsky more highly than Kubrick as a film maker, for me personally, out of the two films you mention, *2001* is far and away the more successful. What I struggled with in *Solaris* was the world that Tarkovsky creates. Frankly I just didn't believe it. I completely missed any deeper meanings contained within the narrative, because I just didn't believe the action.

The space craft most of the film is shot on for example - it never seemed more to me than a series of disconnected studio sets. These individual settings bore no relation to each other and, to me, did not appear to be elements of a larger consistent world. 

Where Tarkovsky absolutely *floors* me with the sheer beauty of his film making is in his ability to create enchantment. For me this happens suddenly, and springs from the most ordinary, familiar settings. An ordinary kitchen - a half remembered garden - a hotel lobby. It's in these every day settings that Tarkovsky has the ability to create poetry - a sudden, breathtaking magic. A space ship is already fantastic, and so, for me, the enchantment has no foundation. 

In addition, I believe Tarkovsky was essentially a poet of his medium. As science fiction, *Solaris* does seem to require, on one level at least, an element of traditional narrative film making. Tarkovsky does not excel in this area, and so for me watching *Solaris* can feel like watching a poet trying to write a detective novel. 

These are very personal observations on *Solaris*. I know the film is held in the highest regard by film theorists far more qualified than me, and of course there are likely many aspects of this deeply complexed film I simply missed.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-02 14:30:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> For my two favourite directors - Maurice Pialat and Agnes Varda - casting non-actors in films was a big part of their creative identity. In France in general there is a tradition of this, sometimes leading to overnight stardom for the actor in question. One example that springs to mind was Beatrice Dalle in *Betty Blue*. One of the most extraordinary examples of this I've ever seen was Stefano Cassetti in the 2001 Cedric Kahn film *Roberto Succo*. Apparently Kahn saw Cassetti in a bar and asked him if he wanted to star in his movie. His performance is amazing! As far as I know it was his only engagement as an actor. Homayoun Ershadi in *Taste Of Cherry* is another great example. I think he was working as an architect before Kiarostami cast him..? Now that I start to think of it there are many examples of this kind of casting. 

I think in these cases the director must simply be working on pure instinct. There is perhaps also some kind of 'beginners naivety' at work. I think of it as similar to making mayonnaise. The first few times you do it it goes beautifully because you don't know what can go wrong. As soon as you realise how easily it can split, it splits. One of the greatest screen actors of our time, Sandrine Bonnaire, arguably gave her best performances in her first few films when she was still a teen. 

As for bad or mediocre actors who are great in a particular role, I can't think of examples of this. I don't think even a great director can transform a bad actor into a great one.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-29 20:32:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I do think *Sophie's Choice* is a very good movie. Film critics can be a little sniffy about it, and I gather this might be because it's a very literal adaptation from the book (I haven't read the book so I can't confirm). If you imagine the film without Streep, it's nowhere near as powerful. It's a great performance in a good film. Maybe for this reason it doesn't make it onto top 100 lists and the like (if you pay attention to those!). I adore *Kramer Vs Kramer*, but (just IMO) it's a beautiful chamber piece, and maybe lacks the cinematic ambition to be considered 'great'. I don't think *Adaptation* is a great film. 

If you're looking for more superb and compelling Streep performances there are many to choose from! Maybe a couple of less obvious options - *The French Lieutenant's Woman* and *Plenty* - both these films demonstrate what Meryl can do with some very sophisticated writing (Harold Pinter and David Hare respectively - both theatre writers). I think *Heartburn* introduced her fabulous comic ability to the world. I love her performance in *Lemony Snicket*, again she revealed and aspect of herself I hadn't seen before here. I think she's incredible in *The Devil Wears Prada*, even though that is not the best movie ever made. *Falling In Love* is another fascinating Meryl turn in a seldom raved about movie.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-28 21:31:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Meryl Streep is an absolutely phenomenal screen actress! The combination of technique, emotional depth, and beauty is unparalleled. She is, perhaps, a little over exposed these days. There is a danger - even for fans like myself - of Streep fatigue. I think too that despite an extraordinary career, she has failed to star in what you might think of as 'great' movies. Deniro had *Raging Bull* and *Taxi Driver* - Nicholson had *One Flew Over The Cuckoo's Nest* and *The Shining* - but what about Meryl? She has given truly great performances in very good movies (*Sophie's Choice*, *Out Of Africa*, *Silkwood*), and even the occasional great performance in terrible movies (*The Iron Lady*), but the history-making iconic Streep vehicle has eluded her. Maybe it is yet to come? I hope so! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-28 21:19:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You have to put it into historical context. Nobody had ever seen anything like *Citizen Kane* at the time. The technical innovations alone made it groundbreaking.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-28 21:17:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Mine is *Casablanca*.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-28 21:15:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Am I correct in thinking it was released the same year as *Psycho*? In some ways I think *Peeping Tom* is the superior film. Structurally it's more consistent and cohesive than *Psycho* which, while brilliant, suffers from a very clunky ending. As far as I can recall *Peeping Tom* has a terrific ending.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-28 00:07:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Bridesmaids </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-28 00:05:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> *Peeping Tom* is way underrated IMO </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-28 00:04:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I wouldn't watch La Dolce Vita or 8 1/2 first.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-28 00:01:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I enjoyed *7 Days In Havana* (2012).  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-25 10:49:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> **Welcome To New York**  Abel Ferrara (2014). Very disappointed with this movie that I've been keen to see since its release. Love Ferrara - love Depardieu - how exciting the prospect of a collaboration between these two. What went wrong? I'm not sure. Ferrara has never been afraid of slightly awkward action and dialogue. If a scene is semi improvised he doesn't mind if it *looks* semi improvised - and I mean semi improvised in the bad way, like an acting class improvisation where everyone's thinking 'what do I say now?'. In the past I've found this has contributed to Ferrara's persona as a kind of raw, underground, almost geurilla film maker - an impression he maintains even with his now very well established reputation. I greatly admire this about him. But in this film I found his trademark 'spontaneity' invasive. For me it backfired, leaving the whole thing utterly unconvincing. I felt like I was just watching a *bad movie*. Neither did I enjoy Depardieu in this film. He looked uncomfortable (as did most of the actors) and a little lost. I did not see a character - I never saw anything other than Gerard Depardieu starring in an Abel Ferrara movie. The promise of that partnership remained the most interesting thing about this film.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-24 18:45:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> For me *Vertigo* is maybe his most personal film. What I mean is that the 'blonde goddess' obsession was never so intense as it is here. The famous scene in the hotel room where Judy transforms into the other woman - the crazy green light - the music - it's a kind of cinematic orgasm, and the summation of something essential to Hitchcock as an artist. But as a whole I find the film overlong and uneven. I can never remember the story of *Vertigo*, even after seeing it a number of times. It feels like three different movies squashed into one. In terms of a brilliant and cohesive narrative film, I regard *Psycho* as Hitchcock's finest.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-24 18:10:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Sorry, but it is a relatively new technology. My point was about cinema's fascination with new technology.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-24 14:20:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yes I think HD is overrated. I am not a film maker, but it strikes me that film making is a highly technical activity. Occassionaly the technical challenges lead to some creative breakthrough, where a director and his/her team find a new way to tell the story and it works beautifully. The downside is that the industry can get too obsessed with technology, and the basics of narrative art get pushed into the background. 3D might be an example of this phenomenon. A film can be a staggering technological achievement, adored by industry insiders who can 'see' the technique, and can leave an audience completely cold. I'm sure HD has added a great deal to cinema on one level, but it's not why people go to the movies or watch them at home. I think cinema's constant striving for technological advancement goes back to its roots though. The very first moving pictures were enjoyed simply because of the illusion the technology created. It was a great novelty, and film will always be looking out for the next novelty.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-23 19:31:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I don't know - but what was that fiery commet in the sky thing about?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
