<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject4297</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-01 01:22:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It literally just says TFW is the problem mod </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-29 23:51:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Nope </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Output log says TFW mod is the cause of my life's problems. Wtf is TFW? Please help! </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-29 21:55:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-27 07:53:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I think your computers diagnostic systems are incorrect. I7's are beasts and can easily handle much larger than that. Ur specs are more than perfect for this game no need to worry. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-27 07:51:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Looking great for a first, nice job dude! I would work on detailing and cleaning/consolodatong industrial parks </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Please enjoy some of my older (But Still Awesome) Cities, im quite proud of how they turned out. Graphics arnt that great on my PC. If you enjoy plz check out my other most recent post :) </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-24 00:51:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-24 00:37:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Does not exist yet. I wanna see if people are interested first  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Looking for some Friends :) (read description) </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-23 18:27:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hey y'all. I am a fairly talented and experienced Cities Skylines player, and I am a former youtuber. I have been considering starting a channel back up to help beginner players learn how to make purdy cities but would love the support and feedback of my fellow reditors. Anyone out there interested in supporting my videos and learning some shit? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-22 04:11:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Perfect </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [Help] Trying to upgrade to 16GB of RAM but Im a Newbie and cant find a any compatible for about the $60 Standard. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-22 03:05:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I dont know how to tell if its compatible. Please help! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-21 02:41:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Nothing to enable </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Reinstalled game to fix crash issue. Game won't recognize subscribed mods. How do I get it to reinstall all of my subbed items? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-21 02:20:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> My fellow redditors, please, help! After a week long vaca I attempted to return to cities skylines to find it crashes everytime about 2-7 minutes after startup. I don't know why. More details in text. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-20 21:48:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It gives me no error message, just says it has stopped working. Varies in time after startup. I would delete and reinstall of I new how to ensure my mods/assets would stay. Please please help! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-20 19:29:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Can someone make a TLDR for me </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-20 16:56:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> No matter what I'm doing just stops working. No message besides the regular program has stopped working thing.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Help! Game crashes after about 5 minutes everytime I try to play it. I do not know what to do. I gotta get back to my city. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-20 15:23:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Help! Just downloaded the new DLC and now the game crashes everytime I open it. I dont know what to do, and if I reinstall the game all my 900+ assets will be unsubscribed! </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-20 05:18:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Please please help if ya can :) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [QUESTION] Getting my second amp. Suggestions? Right now I own some crap tiny fender one. I don't need different sounds because I have a g3 zoom pedal and I'm looking for something in the $150-$200 range. Thanks! </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-19 19:11:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [QUESTION] Im a beginner about to buy my second guitar after my fender bullet squier. After some research I don't understand why the fender Jaguar isn't very popular. If I like playing classic rock and srv style blues rock is there a reason I should stay away from it? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-17 04:41:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> I'm a beginer about to buy my second guitar after my squire. After doing some research, I still don't understand why fender jaguars aren't popular. Is there a reason I should stay away if I'm into rock and roll? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-17 03:57:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-16 16:36:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thanks man. I guess I'll wait it out.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-15 21:21:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Beautiful. Thanks!  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Clean Utopias VS. Realism: What do you guys like to build? DISCUSSION </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-15 21:20:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I prefer building the most perfectly clean balanced city I can. Always looks beutiful, never realistic. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Need a good map for nice small town... Suggestions? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-15 21:05:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I like tropical(ish) lush maps like rhinestone island but that map is huge. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Should I upgrade my RAM? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-15 05:04:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I am currently sporting dual 4gig ddr3 sodimm sticks o' ram on my alienware alpha. Should I upgrade to 16gigs? Thanks yall. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-12 21:09:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yep </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-11 04:43:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I only found one, under software drivers for the alienware alpha.. Mind sending me a link to the page?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-10 22:03:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I downloaded the driver from dell.. That was the only one </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-10 02:04:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> http://imgur.com/Qdqc6TD stays like this forever

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Hive mind interface not loading up, have yet to get it to work. Please help! </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-10 02:03:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hey yall. Got a new Alpha and upgraded to windows 10. Hivemind wont start up past the screen where I pick Console or Desktop. Ive tried deleting and reinstalling. Anyone know what to do? Please help! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> I suck </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-07 02:31:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> How do I make a hit? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Plopable path-like concrete? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-06 20:14:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Anyone know a concrete prop that looks like concrete path? It would look great as a paint brush type thing for industrial areas. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-04 04:50:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Ugh I tried I hate those guys.. Anyways thanks a lot man </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-04 03:34:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Pc. Haven't ventured into ranked much but I win more than most regular matches. Up for it?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Looking for a team player for doubles who is interested in getting better alongside myself and who plays often (ect time) thanks y'all :) </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-04 02:06:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-03 23:16:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I have no idea what to do </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-03 21:14:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> http://imgur.com/Qdqc6TD stays like this forever </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Advanced toolbar not working. Any ideas? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-03 21:02:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hey fellow city builders. I'm a big player and love the game. Everything works fine except advanced toolbar and other toolbar mods don't show up for me. I installed them and nothing changes. Any ideas? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-03 20:55:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I don't get an error it just never stops loading (I've left it for hours to test that) and both controllers and keyboards are responsive.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Hivemind stuck loading into console for first time. Help! </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-03 18:30:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hey yall. Got a new Alpha and upgraded to windows 10. Hivemind wont start up past the screen where I pick Console or Desktop. Ive tried deleting and reinstalling. Anyone know what to do? Please help! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> New addition to my gaming setup. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-29 21:50:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-23 17:21:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Can u make a mod collection for this? It looks amazing. Send me a msg if you do please!  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-20 08:33:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The fix is a special command that you input as a custom boot. Sadly I forget the command and I'm to tired to go find it for you but if u search for in on Google I found it on so forum. It def works. Gl </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Pics from my new Ultradense Nightlife Utopia, Erabath. Enjoy! </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-20 08:01:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-06 00:09:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> thx man
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Fox's Springdale City, Enjoy and tell me what you think! </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-05 23:40:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Black (darker) roads mod (?) </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-03 09:58:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What mod are people using to give roads a black pavement texture? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Xbox one or cheap pc? FO4 </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-27 23:34:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Shall I get fallout 4 on my xbox one or alienware alpha (8 gigs ram, 250gb ssd, i3 quad thread processor) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Fallout 4 Advice for a fellow sole survivor. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-27 22:42:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hey yall. Got fo4 for my birthday from my girlfriend on le xbox one and have become increasingly addicted.  However I recentlt bought the alienware alpha (i3 model) amd beefed it up and bit and cant decide whether or not I should drop $35 for a pc copy of fo4 (?).
Thanks reddit peoples! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
