<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject8599</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Trump signs revised travel ban in bid to overcome legal challenges </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-07 03:59:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Iraq dropped from list of affected countries with Syrian refugees no longer facing indefinite ban </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-06 17:57:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> 80% Skills and 20% luck </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-05 20:19:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-05 11:51:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Kern criticized Ankara's arrest of German-Turkish journalist Deniz Yucel, a correspondent for Die Welt newspaper, and many other journalists, academics and civil servants, and called for Yucel's immediate release. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-05 11:51:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Turkish Foreign Minister Mevlut Cavusoglu criticized German and Dutch restrictions on such gatherings as undemocratic, and said Turkey would press on with them in the run-up to the vote. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Crown jewels of football </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-05 10:55:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-05 06:44:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Lol </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-05 06:19:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> German and Turkish tensions are coming to a head over Turkey's continuation of state sponsored rallies within Germany. The gatherings are a means of encouraging Germany's Turkish population to back a vote supportive of a referendum that will boost President Tayyip Erdogan's powers. Austrian Chancellor Christian Kern called for an EU-wide ban on campaign appearances by Turkish politicians to prevent individual countries such as Germany from being undermined by Ankara. Additionally, Kern proposed that the EU end discussions with Turkey about EU membership and either completely cancel or restrict 4.5 billion euros in aid planned for Turkey through 2020. Turkish Foreign Minister Mevlut Cavusoglu criticized the restrictions on such rallies as undemocratic. Meanwhile, Kern stated in an interview that, "Turkey has moved further and further away from Europe in the past few years. Human rights and democratic values are being trampled. Press freedom is a foreign word." </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Austrian chancellor calls for EU-wide ban on Turkish campaigning </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-05 04:36:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-04 18:45:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Did he not? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-04 18:44:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So you are suggesting that it was waste of club money?
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Did Pogba really worth 100 Million Euros? Judge by yourself </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-04 18:38:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Impostor scams surpass ID theft among U.S. consumer complaints </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-03 19:28:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Ebola nurse's family want to sue Liberian hospital over her death </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-03 18:08:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-03 06:55:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah ,agreed </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Magic of true legends </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-03 03:33:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> U.S. jobless claims near 44-year low; rate hike expected this month </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-02 19:13:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-02 01:35:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The relative odds of conceiving sons or daughters have been baffling scientists for decades. The phenomenon was particularly mysterious to Charles Darwin, who meticulously studied the proportion of male and female offspring in a number of animals </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Why billionaires have more sons? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-02 01:30:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> SEC advisory committee to question Snap's transparency for investors </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-02 00:42:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> which one of them is great </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-01 19:58:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-01 05:55:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It is like first you commit a crime and then say sorry to the victim. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Trump shocks Congress with a speech that stuck to script </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-01 05:52:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-27 21:13:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The 9th U.S. Circuit Court of Appeals had suspended Trump's travel ban earlier this month while litigation over the measure proceeds. Trump has said a new executive order will be coming soon, and the Justice Department in a court filing asked the 9th Circuit to put litigation on hold, pending the new executive order. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-27 21:13:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> lol </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-27 21:11:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I think You got it wrong.C.R is king of football </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Appeals court will not put Trump travel ban case on hold </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-27 21:09:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The King of the Foootball </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-27 20:29:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Philippine government says armed forces made every effort to save 70-year-old but he was killed after ransom deadline passed </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-27 20:01:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-26 20:45:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Sanders, who spoke a day after Democrats chose Tom Perez, a veteran of former President Barack Obama's administration, as their new party chairman, said it was also crucial for progressives to do more to mobilize grassroots supporters to take on Republican President Donald Trump. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Democrats must overhaul party, attack big business, Sanders says </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-26 20:43:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Thousands of people have marched in Moscow to remember Russian opposition leader, Boris Nemtsov, who was shot dead outside the Kremlin in 2015 </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-26 16:29:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Iraqi forces aim to secure Mosul bridge, link up to east bank </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-26 14:46:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> In India, regional rival takes on Modi at his own game </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-26 07:15:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> I was just cleaning the roooooo... </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-26 06:10:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Malaysia declares airport safe for travel after nerve agent attack </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-26 05:19:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The controversial plan to fill a mine with nuclear waste </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-25 23:25:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> World Bank pledges $60 million to help fill Gambia's empty coffers </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-25 22:42:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Legend on Fire! </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-25 11:31:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Valencia beats the crap out of Real Madrid.. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-25 09:53:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> US President Donald Trump has vowed to start building a wall on the Mexican border "soon, way ahead of schedule", in a speech at a conservative event </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-24 21:55:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Redditor, this is insane </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-24 04:37:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-23 19:50:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> KHOU reported that a woman sitting nearby alerted a flight attendant, which led other passengers to also complain about the mans questions. When the Indian American boyfriend of the woman who alerted the attendant complained, a heated exchange followed. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> This is not Trumps America!: Passengers rejoice when man accused of racism is kicked off flight </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-23 19:13:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> President Donald Trump told about two dozen chief executives of major U.S. companies on Thursday he plans to bring many millions of jobs back to the United States </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-23 17:50:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Microplastics from tyres and textiles are a bigger source of marine pollution than the breakdown of larger plastic waste in some areas </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-23 02:35:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-21 20:38:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The advance into the province, which is almost entirely under the ultra-hardline group's control, is part of an operation to encircle and ultimately capture its de facto Syrian capital of Raqqa in the north of the country. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> U.S.-backed rebels enter Deir al-Zor province for first time: Kurdish military source </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-21 20:13:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Kraft Heinz drops Unilever takeover bid </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-19 19:12:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-19 18:57:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> In the meantime, the Soviets were sending scores of people  many ill-equipped and poorly trained  to carry out an emergency clean-up. The first team was instructed to bring the fires around the nuclear plant under control. It took them nine days and at least 28 people are known to have died as a result of exposure to radiation during that time. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Britain's justice secretary says Brexit is 'irrevocable' once triggered </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-19 14:27:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Iran's Zarif says use of chemical weapons in Syria cannot be condoned </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-19 14:08:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-19 12:42:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
