<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject8369</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-22 03:43:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> He has, fair, but he also mentioned Ivanka was on the call... that's a bit weird, you know the person running his company. Maybe she asked not trump himself, idk, the whole thing seems a bit concerning. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-22 00:10:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I agree, I think the OP has reduced both complex commentaries on society and the future of society to a black and white simplification.

 Neither writer was completely prescient, nor were they trying to be, they were exploring complex themes about society through the telling of a good story. 

After all, these were novels. For sure, the world of Huxley was hedonistic on the surface, with an underlying artificial and troubling class structure. 

Alternatively, Orwell pictured a surveillance/ propaganda state which also overwhelmed citizens with fake news on one hand and authoritarian enforcement on the other.   

Like the joke,  "history never repeats itself, it does however, occasionally rhyme", similarly I would use literature as a way to explore our existence rather than some blueprint or explicit warning.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-21 23:43:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> There are issues with sentencing and circumcision is a complex issue, but MRA has moved way beyond those issues and is cringy red pill stuff these days. Now do not get me wrong, the left/ feminist movements have some iffy proposals and ideas too. But the MRA movement got merged into some rapey dubious red pill stuff... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-21 23:40:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Funny things is that most PUA types on reddit are really wannabe be PUA... real PUA is probably doing PUA stuff, that is picking up women. 

It is the worst crowd really, people who aspire to use women and coupled with some red pill bull shit aspire to dominate women... really sad thing to aspire to be a grade A prick. 

Most of them feel that society does not offer them the respect that they deserve because they were born with a dick (for some its particularly their white dick). 

It Is a natural fit with the ~~alt right~~ neo nazi crowd who feel that they are also not respected and that brownpeople/jews/women/asians etc. are the reason people forgot about how awesome they are because they are aryan. 

Of course, they could go out and earn respect through hard work, education and being decent humans but thats too hard and their consitutions are far too delicate for competitive and challenging undertakings </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-21 22:20:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> btw, with regards to your previous comment, culture wars aside, how about the stink about the Clinton foundation? Trump has not even been sworn in yet and already is past anything the republicans even claimed the foundation may have been involved in. And the republicans keep decrying the media double standard. It is insane, it is either a massive cognitive disconnect or callous lying but its impressive nonetheless.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-21 21:47:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> way off topic but how does one get the "I voted" flare </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-21 21:44:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Was trump able to ring the President of Argentina just like that before? I am not so sure. Also, he is the President elect, it is not like you can just turn that off. Its why past Presidents had blind trusts, given the long reach and broad nature of the US presidency almost everything is a conflict of interest.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-21 21:39:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> As soon as he named pence they were going to fall in line, Pence will hold the real keys to the palace, and if trump epically disgraces himself, then they get Pence. Its works for them...  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-21 16:29:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> People don't want to pay $1000 for an air conditioner or $3000 for s phone and in many cases a robot is cheaper than a US employee. Moreover we have stricter employee safety and evirionmentak regulations, which is good because we don't want maimed employees or polluted air and streams.Moreover, everyone decries ttp and other trade agreements but they actually raise regulations and standards in Asia pacific nations (china excluded of course). Global trade has enabled a certain life in the West and people are not giving that up anytime soon, we just need to figure out a more equitable post globalization business model that also helps retrain those who lost out in the process. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-21 05:03:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Independents saw through what shit? What did the see tbrough the shit? That beneath his mysognist bigoted
exterior was a competent and visionary statesman? 

No, the problem that the media spent all their time on trumps despicable character and no time on his utter lack of policy proposals, experience or knowledge. So people ended up overlooking that he is a crook and despicable person and voted because they still believed his non existent policies would help them. No one explained to the rural voter that trump presidency would hurt them personally. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-21 04:53:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Not sure Americans want Foxconn style jobs... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-21 04:51:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Or billed to the secret service. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-21 04:50:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I love that it's too late for that... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-21 04:48:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I hope full hands on deck for midterms but we had trouble turning our people for presidential cycle so I will believe it when I see it. In the meanwhile, its pretty amazing how much damage trump can do I 2 years through executive orders alone... and he has both legislative chanmbers to help him. 

Set backs on climate change, environmental pollution, US geopolitical standing, the economy, and other issues can be hard to undue. For infants, we are still dealing with the sequale of bush era foreign policy. We are still dealing with the sequale of the 2008 crash, the deficits from bush tax cuts and Iraq war spending, etc... a lot can go wrong in 2 years that's not easily fixable. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-20 20:23:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah at the end of the day a dangerous and unqualified man was on the ballot and people couldn't be bothered to vote and of those who did many were willing to overlook his low dangerous flaws... oh and the media focused on how despicable his character was and missed the fact that he had few policy proposals, those that he did were not good for most Americans, and he has a huge knowledge deficiency. 

So yeah, we dun goofed, and we will all pay for this together for decades. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-20 20:20:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Or rather #fuckedtogether </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-20 15:32:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Means he is still thinking about it. Man needs to put together an executive branch and it's unclear if he has the people or knowledge to do that. He needs to try to heal a country. He needs to reassure foreign leaders. Needs to develop a legislative and executive agenda. But instead he is thinking of lame insults to throw at the cast of a broadway show... yeah shits not going to go well. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-20 15:29:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> No this is closer to South American or sub Saharan African dictatorships or the phillipines with dueterte. Maybe chechneye, or Ukraine, otherwise most former soviet republics as a whole have more professionl leaders. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-20 15:26:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> But depending on what he tweets the stock market could fall 500 pts... or you know cause riots in different parts of the world... Dutuerte is a great case study of the price the Phillapines pays everytime he shoots his mouth of but now magnify that effect a couple orders of magnitude to presidency of the United States. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-20 11:47:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Consequences but for people who did not choose this or have the vote. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-20 06:01:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hence heroin. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-20 05:58:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What about their kids? Did they deserve this too? And then we can get a whole other generation of people who had tean pregnancies and dropped out of school, no job prospects, bad education and plenty of heroin... how do you think they will vote or act? Or what about a gay or trans kid in Kentucky? Got to feel awfully lonely right now. Besides we are all going down together, the costs might tread water a bit longer but if the economy goes, if people are uninsured, if civil liberties are destroyed... we will all eventually pay the price. All that smugness and glee... the band is playing and the first class will go down with stearage, just a bit later, and yes some of the super rich might get a lifeboat...

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-20 05:22:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Um, he needs to start the process... has not even the intention. It's a part of the job... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-20 03:43:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> American fruit companies, like dole and Chiquita used to run Central American countries through proxy governments. It's a shorthand for corrupt business entities running a government through a tin pot dictatorship... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-20 00:03:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah so:

1) His children still run his company, not a blind trust

2) His children are 1/3 of the leadership of his transition team and his son in law is apparently calling shots on appointments.

3) We have no clue with whom Trump has business dealings because he runs an opaque private organization and has not released his tax returns. 

He could literally owe money or have shared investments with kremlin connected oligarchs, beijing connected Chinese businessmen, etc... and how people beleive that his own interests and his children's interests won't affect his decisions, consciously or unconsciously. Its a conflcit of interest and national security risk. 

Also, I am sure Pakistan loves the fact the Trump is meeting his Indian business partners. The entire situation is downright surreal. 

And all these people were screaming about the nefarious dealings of the Clinton foundation? The hypocrisy and the double standard is insane. God forbid hilary took money to help Haitian children... Trump is taking money to enrich himself and his own directly. 

Why do we think he will treat the federal government any differently than he treated his charity. He is already biliking them for use of his plane, and securing trump tower but the masses are caught up in the measly $400K he will save the government by not drawing a salary... which knowing Trump he might do anyway when all is said and done.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-19 23:34:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I mean they love Pence, they just need Trump to piss off rural south and midwest and then the knives will come out. 

"Et tu Pence" will be Trump's words as he boards the helicopter on the south lawn, hands outstretched in victory signs, the pelt on his head blowing wildly in the wind, and a mad nixonian gleam in his eye.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-19 23:29:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> But he is getting info from the government and picking cabinet and transition team positions... again problematic set up for quid pro quo and makes the trump campaign, administration and business look inertwined.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-19 23:26:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah, people who have been waiting for months for those tickets are ready to sell their firstborn for the privilege are not going spring for the tickets because Pence's feelings got hurt... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-19 23:24:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Libby did not get pardoned. But it is also though he was not acting alone. He was Assistant to the Vice President for National Security Affairs and Chief of Staff to the Vice President of the United States and Assistant to the President. It would be a stretch to think he acted on a whim alone. But he took the fall and Bush did not pardon him.

However, he was only convicted on perjury and obstruction of justice charges... when his offence and the intent in his offence, in my opinion, was far more serious. 

The point is Hilary showed poor judgement, outing Plame was, in my opinion, intentional harm to the US, silencing whistleblowers and possibly treasonous... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-19 22:52:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> ...things are either: makes Donnie feel good or makes Donnie feel hurt and sad. And he will fuck over and lie and cheat whomever he has to to make sure Donnie feels good. We have elected Eric Cartman but dumber... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-19 22:50:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Not only does he lack nuance, he cannot see beyond his own feelings and existence... in his mind the world literally revolves around him. 

Furthermore, his black or white approach is dangerous because he is also very prone to flattery, one meeting with Xi Jinping or Putin and he is going to do whatever they want as long as they flatter him and play up his ego. 

Finally, he has no sense of the bigger picture, no concept that institutions and principles are bigger than him... it is terrifying, he does not understand the concept of precedence... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-19 22:42:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> When diabetes might "go away"
1) Gestational diabetes, at risk for future development of diabetes, resolves after pregnancy
2) Diet and exercise controlled, losing weight and exercising can prevent progression and drive remission
3) Bariatric surgery when effective can fix type 2 diabetes in morbidly obese
4) Post pancreas transplant usually for type 1 diabetics, does not last very long as whatever autoimmune process knocked out the pancreas initially knocks out the new one eventually too, can last years though.
5) Post very bad pancreatitis, the pancreas can recover, although to knock out insulin production it has to be very bad pancreatitis o begin with. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-19 22:29:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Of all the things done by the bush administration, this was actually criminal and skirted actual on treasonous. Worse yet when people mention hilary's emails, and then complain that she is getting a double standard and being let off easy, I remember this as an example of a double standard and people getting off easy... Hilary's emails pale in comparison to this, Patreus' indiscretions are small compared to this, in the end Libby got jailed on some trivial charge and everyone else got off scott free.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-19 22:22:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> And studies suggest that even when done by a professional dedicated person med recs are still as often as 30% wrong. And its not just meds. Tests get duplicated because access to the previous one is lost, unnecessary interventions because previous lab/radiology tests and ekgs are inaccessible etc. Our health care system needs to enter the 21st century but with the upcoming administration the best we can hope is not to be set back a decade.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-19 18:12:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Drug drug interactions are a huge problem. As patients get older and given the us healthcare systems penchant for poly-pharmacy, this becomes a common and real danger. 

It's why we need a national health record system and why we need to make a medical home for patients healthcare information. Trying to figure out what medications a patient is prescribed, is actually taking, at what dose, why, and who manages the medication is very difficult. Often healthcare providers get it wrong at huge cost for the patient and system. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-19 17:43:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Sometimes whats left when you drain it is worse... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-19 17:21:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Let's not forget the bush administration comit treason by outing Valerie plame as a CIA agent to get back at her ambassador husband who wrote a white paper discrediting Powell's jewel in his Iraq wmd case that Iraq was trying to buy yellow cake from Nigeria...  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-19 15:18:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I love how the tea party yelled that they were honoring the founding fathers when really they stood against everything the founding fathers held dear.

Strict constructionism, mixing government and religion, anti science etc are all against what the founding fathers believed. Best of all the founding fathers were not some monolithic block but had disagreements with each other too... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-19 15:13:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Provided they are compliant to their meds and don't develop resistance, usually because of non compliance. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-19 15:12:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  No, it's not benign, there are still some long term issues but basically hiv is the virus, aids is the disease when the virus destroys enough T cells (immune cells) so that people become prone to aids defying illnesses, usually cancers or infections. Some tiny minority of people just never progress to aids and carry a low viral load but most need anti retrovirals to keep a low viral count and prevent progression to aids. Also modern anti retrovirals have fewer side effects than the originals but still have some health effects too. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-19 15:10:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  No, it's not benign, there are still some long term issues but basically hiv is the virus, aids is the disease when the virus destroys enough T cells (immune cells) so that people become prone to aids defying illnesses, usually cancers or infections. Some tiny minority of people just never progress to aids and carry a low viral load but most need anti retrovirals to keep a low viral count and prevent progression to aids. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-19 14:57:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Or just turning America into a banana republic... trump through cronyism and nepotism gives himself tax cuts and makes money hand over first. Meanwhile, his cabinet goes after marijuana, destroys civil liberties, starts wars (his NSA guy is a real hawk and gulliani might sec state), privatizes prisons... oh the merry place we will be. If people though Obama and Hilary were or would be hard on whistle blowers I am sure thin skinned trump and his authoritiarian cadre will be worse.
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-19 14:49:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Or maybe that was shown to be a misrepresented story? That nothing insidious or odious ever happened. But we also know this stuff because the Clinton foundation is a non profit with disclosures and also transparent. Trump has a private corporation run by his kids who also run his transition team and meet with foreign leaders, and which because it is private no one knows who it has deals with. And trump won't release his tax returns which would shed some light on it.
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-18 23:32:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Bannon self descibed father of the alt right, on the record anti-semite? #2 in the transition team... yup that is a problem, it is not hyperbole or name calling. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-18 23:30:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Also, the people running his business are running his transition team and joining him in official meetings with world leaders. 

Oh and because he runs a private s corp and has not released his tax returns, we have no clue who he owes money too and where he has monetary interests. After years of running banana republics, America has decided we want to be Panama or take your pick of Latin American dictatorship. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-18 23:24:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It is an incredible assumption that bernie would have done better... its an exercise in hypotheticals. 

At the end of the day there was a choice on november 8th, an incompetent rascist authoritarian and an unlikable and flawed but competent democratic candidate. 

People made the wrong choice, either to stay home or vote third party. Now we have this. We all own this, and we will all pay for this dearly in lost earnings, american geopolitical standing, erosion of civil liberties, erosion of our federal government... and its becoming clear that trump plans to mix his business with the federal government like we are some banana republic.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-18 21:46:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I do not think its some combination of he following:

1) they don't care about his transgressions, they want him to deliver on a campaign promise or destroy the federal government
2)  they do not trust the establishment anything, it is not that trump is faultless, it is that anything from any established institution is false.

A lot of them are alt right and authoritarian and want to pave the way for him to register muslims, build walls, deport illegals, roll back any safety net etc.

Or they are anarchist and want him to stay in power as long as possible to destroy as much as they can.

Or they are trolling the easy targets of upset redditors for whom a trump presidency poses a terrifying prospect for economic or social reasons. 

Or they sit in a non-descript building outside moscow practicing their english and paid $6 per hour by the GRU. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-18 21:08:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's worse than that. His company is not publicly traded and as such does not make disclosures or earning statements or have shareholder meetings. It's not a classic company but more of a holding company for trumps assets and wealth. And since he has not released any tax returns trump's business dealings are completely opaque. 

So not only is there risk for conflict of interest at the least and quid pro quo favors at the worst, but we have not clue who his business dealings are with. So foreign business entities could affect executive branch policy and this could be against us interests or even a security risk.

It's next order of magnitude concerning. What drives me crazy is any concern regarding the Clinton foundation which is a public charity with incredible transparency pales in comparison for this opaque and concerning mess. And trump never promised that he would put his assets in a blind trust so people knowingly voted for this.

After months of ctr accusations make you wonder if these pro trump accounts are fanatics, trolls or worse that we have been had and they are in fact trumps version of ctr or Putins paid posters... that maybe ctr was not so prevalent but the the ctr accusers and trump zealots are actually counter propagandists...  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-18 17:45:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> They are entirely not contradictory:

Headline A: trump told ford they should keep jobs in US

Headline B: trump takes credit for ford factory staying when ford kept it for reasons unrelated to trump or never planned to close it.

 More over these headlines give us no sense of the temporal relationship between them nor establish causality or relationships between the events. Also they are just headlines. 

If you are going to play free thinker, you must read carefully and critically, including posts by your brethren in this sub and the articles cited. 

Never let others connect the dots for you, that's how you get manipulated. Let them show you point a and point b, you draw the line. This post show you a part of point a and glimmer of point b and draws a circle with some commentary and opinion about the nyt thrown in. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-18 17:33:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> $400k vs potential billions from using insider government info, the appearance of or even actual potus backing for his empire through his kids running the show and then even the set up for pay to play... not to mention millions in tax cuts? That salary is picket change given the possibilities he has before him. It's also not exactly the line item bankrupting the fed giv. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-18 17:29:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Escaping the press pool is unprecedented, it's why for instance the press was there with bush on an uneventful September day reading books to little kids in 2011. 

This is different, this about conflicts of interest and nepotism with his fortune run by the people picking cabinet and transition team people. It's also people close to him still running his empire. The this is entirely unprecedented. 

Given his lack of tax returns we don't even know the extent of his empire or who he does business with and now the people who are 1/4 if his transition team and run his company are picking our future executive  branch leaders...

Do you not see the problem? Why candidates release tax returns? Why assets go in blind trusts? Why it's weird the kids who run his company are a large chunk of his transition team? 

All these people that decried Clinton foundation "corruption" but don't care about this? How is that not cognitive dissonance? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-18 17:20:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I think you missed the entire point of the article. It's not about his children, it's his children managing his business empire and transition team. His empire is not in a blind trust and the people running it are making decisions about his administration and interacting with him daily. It's a set up for corruption and quid pro quo politics and conflict of interest. It's unprecedented... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-17 02:41:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> How about effective ambassador to China under Obama respected by dems and republicans and also the Chinese... who speaks multiple languages including I think Chinese... the man was good enough for Obama, more than good enough for trump and miles ahead of any of the other people in trumps cabinet... huntsman for sec state all the way. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-17 02:36:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That huff po writer who wrote an article throwing a hissy fit that nate silver was purposely skewing his model to trump to make it look like more of a horse race probably feels mighty stupid right now: https://www.google.com/amp/m.huffpost.com/us/entry/us_581e1c33e4b0d9ce6fbc6f7f/amp
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-17 01:42:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Will it follow you if you move? Or are you stuck in one state? What about people moving into the state? What if everyone turns 65 moves to states that have it?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-16 19:37:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> http://mobile.nytimes.com/2016/11/16/us/politics/trump-transition.html

Or you think the nyt has not done any fact checking?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-16 05:23:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> r/the_donald is literally either trolls, contrarian teenagers, stormfront lite, or people who have trouble accepting the complexity of modern life and government and want an authoritarian to at least superficially organize it... similiar to r/conspiracy but more right wing and slightly less into random shit like UFOs and 9/11 denial... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-16 04:57:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> To be fair, with trump I get the gist of his half baked rhetoric... even sometimes follow the premise of his point.

With Palin it is like a coked out parrot having a stroke...  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-16 04:54:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> cocaine is a hell of a drug... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-16 04:46:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Why would you want to work in that administration? It is a positive feedback loop, senior people don't want to suffer trumps unpredictable whims and inexperience or risk tanking their careers. Junior staffers don't want to work for the sub par people who end up leading those departments and so on. Also given the utter lack of preparation and mess no one wants to struggle and risk everything to get that administration off the ground. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-16 04:38:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> He literally though that, I think he was genuinely confused why 3 decades in politics hilary had not done everything she advocated. I think he imagined that if she asked for it, then it would be so. 

When asked about policies he would say things like "we are going to bring jobs back". When pushed he would say the same thing, like he thought it was a policy to bring jobs back, that obama simply needed to get some smart people together, ask them to bring jobs back, and they would order something and jobs would come back... like it was simply obama not realizing we need more good paying jobs in America.

I think he thought it would be like his hotels, smart people finance, design, and build them and they periodically ask trump which door or curtain he prefers and he chooses one and then at the end of the day he sticks his name on it... and decides who he will rip off and not pay. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-16 04:16:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Apparently, trump's people are having trouble finding people to staff the executive branch and have little or no idea how many positions or who to fill them with... they need thousands of high-level positions filled and lack the contacts to do it. Also, if you are a young aspiring graduate with skills and prospects are you going to risk your career working in this department? when trumps kids, or worse yet gulliani, or bannon, or thiel might be your department head? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-16 04:03:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Also if enough obama staffers stay on and obama looks over trumps shoulder make we get 4 more years obama... Maybe that was the plan all along, this deplorable transition team is just a front, its reall all 54q^3 dimensional chess. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-16 03:57:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Globalization has been destructive and has hurt many people. Like with any change there are winner and losers. Rural communities, blue collar communities got hit hard when intellectual capital became more valuable than labor. Even modern manufacturing jobs require advanced skills. Now it is fair that we did little to help these people but then again their own elected small government republicans led the charge... because they did not want retraining, the wanted to do the same thing, get paid unrealistically for it, and make sure no one else got to live life any differently then they though right based on their religion and morality. 

And the line the was fed to these communities was that you do not have to change to face these changes. They were told America is great, the greatest in fact and so are you, simply by virtue of being American. And that post cold war industrial boom mixed with heady days of the 90s, that is the norm. It is just the politicians standing in the way of companies that is holding the economy back.

And when that line grew thin they trumped up wedge issues like guns/religion/abortion. And then they depicted the other... women, minorities, illegals. The system they were told favors the other, that is why they suffer.

But no one can deliver on that promise or entitlement... so along comes a demagogue who no longer plays to wedge issues, or blows dog whistles. He promises to roll back the privileges of these others, hold back the international competition, cut taxes, and unleash the corporations. And they vote for him. 

It is all lies, they have been had and while they figure that out, the other they so despise will be hurt, and so will they...

I do not hold these trump supporters so innocent, they either did not care or wanted trumps mysogony/racism/anti-intellecutalism because they wanted what they felt was due to them the rest of the country or world be dammed. 

Agricultural subsidies, mining subsidies, gun laws that make no sense in cities, unde influence religion in our government... we already cater to these dying communities too much. They need to adapt like the rest of us. 

To be fair though we all failed, so we will pay this price together in the worst possible protracted way as this trainwreck of an administration grinds the machinery of government to the ground. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Trump Surprised by Extent of Scope of Presidential Duties </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-16 03:34:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-15 03:09:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Not even public corporations or conventional private corporations  but private corporations like his that are really mechanisms for personal wealth holdings. His companies product is trump himself. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-15 03:07:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Bannon is really a temporizing influence /s </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-15 03:04:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Still does not make it less established  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-15 01:24:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's also a function of delegitimizating institutions and experts and putting up fake experts or people with no credentials as falsely equivalent opinions. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-14 05:37:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I mean same can be said of the trump campaign and rascist dog whistles that were so loud they just passed into rascist/fascist/sexist/red pill megaphone territory. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-14 05:33:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Well if you run for president that's kind of part of the deal... or as a citizen this current planned arrangement does not strike you as concerning?


 If the Clinton foundation was accused of pay to play and allowing foreign money to influence us governmental and political decisions, then this set up is an order of magnitude more concerning... 

Especially, considering his empire being private corporations is completely opaque and he never released his tax returns.

His financial well being might already be dependent on Russian and Chinese money. Not to mention his kids are already a major part of his transition team. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-14 05:28:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So we can have pence instead??pence is worse. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-14 05:27:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> His kids are part of the transition leadership... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-14 05:26:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That are a 1/4 of his transition team </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-13 23:01:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This time the president is chaotic evil/neutral, while the VP is lawful evil. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-13 21:55:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> the most entrenched is pence... gulliani is scary, and the trump children are problematic too... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-13 21:52:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Well stein is also clueless and underinformed, with no policy substance or realistic understanding economy, so keep wearing that chip on your shoulder with pride. 

But to be honest a not an insubstantial portion of the population has been wound up with cries of American exceptionalism and are demanding an authoritarian to return them to dominance in the country... without any change or adaptation on their part to the modern socioeconomic equation. They want a return to when they had no competition, america dominated world markets, and they did not have to deal with gay people, women in charge, minorities, etc, and they picked a guy who promised to strong arm those changes for them democracy or facts be damned. 

Sorry but coal is not coming back, neither is manufacturing and their kids are still going to do heroin... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-13 16:57:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> sure, ok, one of the experts in finance in the Senate it to be disqualified from future advancement because she might have thought she was part native american and has not advanced native american issues when they are a tiny part of her mass constituency? Meanwhile, on the other side of the aisle all sorts of political and personal transgressions are overlooked.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-13 16:17:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Or palin sec interior?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-13 16:17:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So is his entire transition team </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-13 16:15:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Compared to pence? Very moderate. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-13 16:14:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> He is a physically big plug but looking at trumps transition team by far not the only plug and not even the worst plug. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-13 08:55:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  Never ceases to amaze... real conspiracies like fossil fuel companies undermining climate change policy, Russia meddling in US elections, a branch of the FBI leaking things to sway an election, etc.. they dismiss. 

Some guy on 4chan posts 1 + 1 = 5, and they take that as evidence that naturally a Clinton-Soros pedo ring taught them math wrong by telling them 1 + 1 = 2. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-13 06:27:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> And the smear campaign starts, we keep hobbling our candidates before they even run. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-13 05:36:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It was trillions on the kn the ground fighting not the r and d. But we did recycle some armored vehicles to militarized police departments... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-13 05:34:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Or used that bush tax cut money for a real post 2008 stimulus package... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-13 02:44:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Maine's governor is horrible... about time... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-13 02:23:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> They had less time with Obama and he had less of a political history. Also if that is the bar, to be as squeaky clean as Obama, we will dismiss a lot of qualified candidates. Obama literally has an antiseptic past and no one hacked his emails either.  I am sorry but a part of this narrative is that we let the republican pundit class and slander machine create the narrative and facts of this elections and the rest of the media lapped it up. Furthermore, it is insane that somehow the fact that trump is a hugely flawed human being was completely overlooked.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-13 01:49:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> still went trump </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-13 01:41:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Kim Jong Un has a new soul mate. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-13 01:36:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> In an industrial society like 1918 able bodied men were valuable on average if you look at their future productivity. Also people maimed and injured are a long term cost. 55,000 able bodied men is the workforce of a large town... that is a huge expenditure, especially as they had been raised, so capital was sunk and there was no return yet. 

If we take modern numbers, a person has on average say low-ball $6-8 million lifetime productivity, that is 330-450 million in productivity, not to mention the lost productivity of their offspring less the costs of their training. Unlikely that those few miles would produce anything near that for a long time.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-13 01:33:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Cheney/ Libby Plame, torture and Iraq Cheney/ Rumsfield.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-13 01:32:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> we let the republican slander machine erode at her for years and let them supplant reality with this some fact-free version of it, and if you think they wont do it to all future liberal or opposition candidates you are mistaken.

 Its important we take a stand against the fact that we allowed and stood by while this happened. Hilary had her flaws but was not what she was projected to be. 

Unless we take a stand against sensationalist media coverage, false equivalency,  and a rejection of expert opinion we are screwed... this extends to issues too. 

We cannot get acceptance of climate change which is backed by an insane scientific consensus let alone anything actually controversial. That is a big part of this election too. Boring, fact-driven, nuanced approaches and candidates need to be ok again... until then we will vacillate between demagogues and  strong men.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-13 01:24:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Sure but somehow the republicans come together and vote as a block time and time again. If mccain after being belittled by trump in the most personal way or ryan after literally deeming trump a despicable human being could swallow their pride and back him, the large majority of establishment republicans are going to fall in line. Its also not an insubstantial portion of the republican primary electorate that supports him so they also cannot toe the line against trump too much either.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-13 00:48:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You kind of made it sound like more of a thing than it is... no corroboration or anything beyond pure speculation. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-12 23:51:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What might? He has 2 chambers of republicans and soon the court to back him up... what levers of power do we have? The whole federal government is lost or threatened to be lost. We can impotently scream from the sidelines, stall stuff in lower courts, yell in the streets and then watch this agenda unfold before our eyes... explain to me what is supposed to check or balance this government we now have? The outlook is profoundly bleak. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-12 16:03:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> But given that states have open borders there is the concern that straw purchases make there way into urban centers... so while I agree many liberals gun polices are emotion driven, all sensible policy is completely blocked by the NRA. 

We need sensible legislation that takes into account urban and rural needs and both sides need to remove the emotion and hyperbole from the discussion. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-12 15:27:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So it's ok to risk the future of the country because Hilary was not exciting?? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-12 03:41:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Pence has both houses, what are people going to do? We have no levers to stop him or the stooges he puts on the court. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> US launches cruise missle strikes at Houthi radar sites </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-13 08:15:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Chinese fishing vessel rams and sinks South Korean coast guard vessel </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-13 07:54:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
