<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject8902</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> My new baby </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-10-28 01:46:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Just purchased a Focus </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-10-26 02:19:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Purchased a 2012 focus today, think I got an okay deal. Take delivery Tuesday. Really excited to have a new car. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-10-23 19:26:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yes, not denying that person is horrible  but wanting to deny people rights makes me horrible as well. 

And obviously not everyone in prison is awful, some just got unlucky with drug possession charges or other infractions.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-10-23 03:01:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I love seeing the belugas at Georgia Aquarium, but it seems evident at this point that they shouldn't be housed in the Georgia Aquarium.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> GDOT delays road projects due to federal funding crisis </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-10-23 00:18:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-10-21 18:03:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You're making broad assumptions, yes some parents don't give a damn, but it's hard for a single mom working 2 jobs to devote time to their children's education, and in some of the poorer neighborhoods that's what's happening. 

I know from experience. I grew up in a small town, but it my mother wasn't able to help with my studies because of exactly the situation I described.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-10-21 03:15:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Charter schools can definitely be better, they get the more affluent members of society, who generally are better performing students.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> There's a reason she got caught </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-10-21 02:59:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-10-20 22:27:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I definitely understand a parent wanting to send their children to the best school they can afford, but the problem with charter schools is that the public schools then get neglected. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-10-19 04:49:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It always sucks when you're the only sober one at a party.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-10-18 16:45:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Android device manager, or the ios equivalent.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-10-18 16:45:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I don't technically own it yet, but I know my house will be the most expensive thing I will ever own.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-10-18 01:12:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Wall, he would work great in the Hawks system. Great defender and passer, and definitely capable of scoring.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-10-18 00:23:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I do feel Joe Johnsons contract was worse though. Way too much money at his age. He was on the decline when he signed it in Atlanta.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-10-17 20:31:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I can see what he is saying, but I do think he has it backwards. A contract is rewarded on what a player is capable of and what the team thinks a player will accomplish, and in order to do that, the team looks at the past and what the player has done.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-10-17 20:25:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Anthony Davis, assuming he stays healthy. The numbers he's capable of putting up on a nightly basis are insane. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-10-17 19:13:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That's really cool. I live in Woodstock and didn't know there was one here. Will probably go there instead of driving all the way to Burt's  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-10-17 17:04:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Best one I know of is Burt's in Dawsonville. It's quite a ride though. 

Maybe someone else knows of a decent one closer.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-10-16 19:22:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I don't think The Hunger Games setting fits in with theme parks. It was dystopian science fiction, what rides and shows would it have? I can't imagine a show centered around killing your countrymen for food in a theme park.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-10-16 01:52:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That I was unaware of since I'm not in his state.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-10-16 01:16:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I think it helps his popularity in that he has stayed true to his principles during his entire campaign. He has released no negative ads or attacks on his opponents. He's also not accepted big money from corporations or even small donors. 

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-10-16 00:34:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Assuming it's not embellished that was an incredibly nice gesture of you, and who knows, you may have helped spark a child's interest in science.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-10-15 21:47:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Were there any injuries?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-10-14 22:29:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Did you try Blue Ridge Georgia? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-10-14 20:34:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The ones I'm in are Woodstock Online Yard Sale and the Marietta/Kennesaw/Woodstock Online YardSale groups.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-10-14 18:25:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I have bought things from the local group in Woodstock many times. Like it a lot better than Craigslist since it's all local and well moderated.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-10-14 18:01:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I don't disagree. I love my 15 minute commute  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-10-14 17:52:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I know there's a lot of yard sale groups on Facebook that are basically local smaller versions of Craigslist. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-10-14 17:50:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Could have been anything. Road ragers aren't exactly known for being reasonable and making logical decisions.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-10-14 17:39:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I don't see how road rage necessarily correlates with a lot of traffic. It was probably a small infraction, like cutting this person off that set this person off. Road ragers aren't exactly reasonable people  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-10-14 17:23:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I do think this article is correct in that bernie does not have a lot of foreign policy experience. I think that concern would be alleviated I if he chooses an experienced vice president and secretary of state.

I do think it's great that he stood by his principles though and didn't succumb to personal attacks. That makes him look like a good man who is true to himself.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-10-14 17:19:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> TIL, thank you.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-10-14 16:50:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Are the jobs really low paying? You would think treating the screeners well would be important considering the importance of their responsibilities.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Atlanta has one of America's lowest average commutes according to Waze </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-10-14 15:47:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Reed lays out plan to combat uptick in crime </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-10-14 04:39:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-10-13 19:45:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The people perpetrating this scam deserve to be ruined financially and thrown under the fucking jail. I absolutely hate it when someone takes advantage of an uneducated, poor person.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-10-13 18:57:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What does the classification First Nation refer to? Legitimately curious.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-10-13 05:06:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I don't know where you got that it's been a holiday for hundreds of years. It wasn't made a holiday in the US until 1937.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-10-13 04:49:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> http://dictionary.reference.com/browse/indigenous you do realize the word indigenous is just another word for native don't you?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-10-13 04:37:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That's part of the reason I would support a holiday. An incredibly important man kind of lost to history.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-10-13 04:09:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I would definitely support Jonas Salk receiving a holiday.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-10-13 04:08:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That still doesn't mean we have to celebrate it. We have evolved and understanding that many of the deeds done in the past were brutal and unacceptable in a civilized society.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-10-13 04:07:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Source?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-10-13 04:06:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I did not expect them to be this bad. I normally stay in the smaller subreddits and there are significantly less trolls and assholes.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-10-13 04:04:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I thought that was July 4th or memorial day weekend.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-10-13 03:57:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> How does Columbus day benefit anyone in anyway? At least this way we're acknowledging them as opposed to celebrating someone who committed many atrocities.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-10-13 03:17:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Wonder who was behind this. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-10-13 03:13:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> God you're right. Why are we trying to respect cultures and not celebrate people who committed atrocities?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-10-13 02:53:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Ben Carson the one who said a Muslim shouldn't be president, which flies in the face of the Constitution he claims to want to defend. The one who is anti vaccine and denies climate change even though he is an educated doctor. 

No thank you.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-10-13 02:25:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Because Hilary would be so much better for minorities, or even trump. Not the guy that has made an effort to meet with black activists.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-10-13 02:25:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That would be a great way to handle this, and I think it's a good idea. 

Indigenous people's day is still progress though. A lot better than celebrating Columbus.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-10-13 01:58:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> http://www.understandingprejudice.org/nativeiq/columbus.htm A well sourced article stating Columbus' treatment of the Native population. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-10-13 01:51:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I think it's hard to say "Heritage, not hate" when the heritage is predicated on hate. The history they're so proud of consists of seceding in order to fight to keep the right to own people considered lesser, and a 100 years later the south fought the progress of the Civil Rights movement. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-10-13 01:25:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I think him committing genocide outweighs that. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-10-13 01:16:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I think it's more that Presidents are still worthy of admiration regardless of some of their bad qualities. George Washington was still a general in the Revolutionary War regardless of the fact that he owned slave, Jefferson was still one of the authors of our Declaration of Independence.

Columbus didn't even do what it is we celebrate him for. Our continent had been discovered by the vikings centuries before Columbus was born, and there's the fact that Columbus committed atrocities as bad as anyone throughout history. He maimed and tortured the people that were on the continent first, sold them into slavery and raped the women. He is definitely not a man worthy of admiration, and he is definitely not worthy of a national holiday. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Alaska Renames Columbus Day 'Indigenous Peoples Day' </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-10-13 00:35:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-10-12 22:38:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Any wrecker service will be able to jump you off. Won't be cheap though.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-10-12 22:11:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I definitely think their statement shoots that argument in the foot.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-10-12 21:02:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Now that I think about it there's also a doubletree literally across the street from that Hampton. They're pretty nice too. Stayed there last year  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Georgia Confederate group issues statement on MLK memorial at Stone Mountain </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-10-12 18:56:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Employees file lawsuit against Here to Serve restaurant group </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-10-09 02:48:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> A first Democratic call in DeKalb for Lee May to resign </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-10-08 22:12:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Here to Serve employees still unpaid, Atlanta restaurant industry steps up with plans for aid </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-10-08 05:54:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> City Hall hires executive director for new homeless nonprofit </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-10-07 16:44:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Event Horizon - Nostalgia Critic </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-10-07 02:13:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Man is forced down from MARTA skywalk in Inman Park </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-10-05 20:03:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Atlantic Station retail core sold </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-10-02 16:07:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The Return of Flux Night </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-10-01 13:58:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Here Is The Nexus 6P In All Its Glory, Front And Back </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-09-23 03:14:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Augusta has an important role in protecting country against cybercrime. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-09-22 20:50:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> 'Mega load' expected to stall metro Atlanta traffic Tuesday </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-09-22 18:35:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Question about tolls. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-09-20 02:00:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> My girlfriend and I are coming to Orlando for vacation next week. We will be coming down from Atlanta taking 75. How much should I prepare to pay for tolls? Do I need to bring cash and coins? 

Thanks Orlando redditors. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Lamborghini driver killed in DeKalb when car flips, catches fire </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-09-19 16:25:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Reed: Those involved in fire station photo scandal could be fired </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-09-18 15:24:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Georgia workers least happy in the country </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-09-17 00:08:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Important feedback </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-09-16 03:28:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Gwinnett sheriff compares all protesters of police violence to terrorists. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-09-15 22:31:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> TIL There is a Brewery in Woodstock </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-09-15 00:41:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Know I'm probably going to get down voted to oblivion, but I found out there was a brewery a few miles from my house and thought that was cool. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Georgia police shooting sparks 'Justice for Caroline Small' </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-09-13 19:10:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> 2 more women kidnapped, assaulted at East Point townhouse complex </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-09-09 21:57:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Kidnapped, slain DeKalb couples estate sues police, parole board </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-09-03 04:38:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Huawei Watch Pre-Orders Are Live </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-09-02 17:57:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Huawei Watch Pre-Orders Are Live </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-09-02 17:56:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Ruling could pave way for Atlanta annexation </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-09-02 17:45:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Man stabbed in northwest Atlanta during argument over loud music </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-08-31 15:04:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Multiple Sources Now Indicate That Android Wear Will Launch For iOS Soon </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-08-28 18:37:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Raptors HQ interview with former Hawk DeMarre Carroll </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-08-25 03:07:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> MARTA trains and buses will be free on the last day of Dragon Con, Monday, September 7th. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-08-22 01:51:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Al Horford Q A with Sports Illustrated </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-08-21 23:23:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Atlanta Hawks at the bottom of best dressed teams look. Personally I like the new uniforms though. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-08-21 02:32:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Atlanta 17th Sexiest City according to Playboy Magazine </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-08-20 00:08:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Atlanta Theater tops Nation in Straight Outta Compton Ticket Sales. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-08-19 18:21:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Shot Atlanta father quoted scripture after violent home invasion </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-08-19 15:49:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Wow, that ending was anticlimactic. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-08-19 03:04:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The final mission to get to Rais was intense, but when you finally got there it was just quick time events. So disappointed. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Roy Barnes: Its time to pardon Leo Frank </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-08-18 14:46:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Roy Barnes: Its time to pardon Leo Frank </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-08-18 14:42:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Spotted at the Woodstock Starbucks </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-08-14 17:02:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Atlanta Hawks Dennis Schroder on cover of NBA 2K16 Germany </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-08-05 15:11:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> No cell phone use equals a discount at The Melting Pot </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-29 14:42:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Mega-Load, Part 2, to cause traffic delays Thursday evening </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-29 14:14:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Kasim Reed willing to spend public money for new Hawks arena </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-24 23:02:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Kasim Reed willing to spend public money on new Hawks arena </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-24 23:01:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Atlanta Hawks build new basketball court in College Park. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-23 22:04:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Of Georgians registered for medical marijuana, two-thirds are children </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-15 19:41:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Reversible toll lanes coming to 575 and 75 </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-14 16:23:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Archer Comic Con spoofing video. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-11 19:10:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Ellen Pao, interim CEO of Reddit, has resigned </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-10 23:27:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Atlanta Hawks officially announce signing of Justin Holiday </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-10 01:49:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Smoke stops MARTA trains headed south to Atlanta airport </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-07 19:11:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Thank You, Atlanta | By DeMarre Carroll </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-07 16:02:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Atlantas efforts on paid family leave draw approval from White House </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-07 04:18:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Possible health risk at Clayton County Animal Control facility </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-06 16:08:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> DeMarre Carroll says Hawks had to choose between him and Paul Millsap </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-06 03:59:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> DeMarre Carroll says Hawks had to choose between him and Paul Millsap </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-05 22:20:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Firefighters Rescue Puppy from 75ft Well </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-05 18:27:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> 16 Year Old Girl Killed in Own Home by Gunfire in College Park </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-05 16:40:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> http://www.ajc.com/news/news/crime-law/college-park-girl-believed-killed-by-celebratory-j/nmrt4/ </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Atlanta as a free agent destination. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-26 18:41:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> How much do you think the Hawks have helped themselves this postseason in regards to picking up the big named free agents this offseason? Even if we get swept in the ECF, which unfortunately appears to be likely, we've still went to the ECF and were closer to the Finals than most teams.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
