<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject6752</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [Discussion] Modmyi sure knows how to troll us hard :( </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-01 02:11:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Discord Group and a quick intro </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-31 23:57:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hey guys!

As mentioned by the founder of this sub /u/suicidalstreet, I'm one of the mods who will make sure everything runs smoothly here ;)

Just wanted to say hi, and introduce myself. I barely host any car meetings, but I love to join clubs, so if anything, let me know! Invite me! My PSN is bloodbrother1318 (one thing though, I don't have a mic **:(** )


**Now, for easier communication between us when meeting**, I have setup a Discord group. To join just click/tap this guy right here --- [\_()_/](https://discord.gg/0ubKkxt4YE4PTGBN)

I might also setup a Telegram group, but I don't know how many of you guys are interested in it. Let me know!
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> IE keeps opening with a weird link that redirects to a random yet sketchy website. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-30 16:08:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hey guys :)

I'm having a bit of a problem here. I hope that you can help.

Whenever I am using another app like Chrome or playing a game, IE opens automatically with this website http://click.cpvredirect.com/ and then this website redirects me to a random website. Is a different website each time this happens.

I have tried following the steps listed in this video: https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=EXA4i7eEZHw   however that didn't help at all.

I scanned my computer with a free trial of Avast Internet Security, and iObit's Advance System Care 9 and Anitvirus and none of them could detect an issue with my computer. I also tried Avast's Web Toolbar Removal tool but nothing out of the ordinary of what I use comes up. 

How can I get rid of this malware?

Any input is appreciated :) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> So, I thought I was going to get my first week in advance ($400) in the mail. Interesting. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-29 23:03:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> TIL that the Wallet/Passbook card that sticks to the LS of your iPhone when you are near a store or something along those lines appear in the NC of the AW and it stays at the bottom just like in the iPhone </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-29 22:56:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Click this link and sign up for it please :) </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-29 22:53:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> https://www.quikly.com/1351-dominos/t/o9WHwDb-lnk

This is a contest to get gift card for Dominos, run by Dominos </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [Release] New build of iOS 9.3 released for 26 devices </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-28 18:54:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> I'm almost 18 and I stutter. I'm thinking on applying for a job on T-Mo [NY] </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-27 22:35:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hey guys, can you help me out with this doubt.

I have a light to mild stutter. However, I still get my point across whether is by changing words (while making no sense in terms of 'spoken grammar') or by pointing to things or just by pausing and starting up again. Even with this impediment, I have worked at two places, once in a summer camp, and once as an office assistant in my High School. 

Does my speech impediment and my work history minimizes my chances of landing a job as a Retail Sales Associate or any job at a T-Mo store?

Thanks in advance! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [Discussion] Apple stopped signing some 9.3 builds for select iPads, iPhones and iPods. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-25 00:29:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [NEWS] Optional update coming soon with fixes </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-24 21:02:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Are the BestBuy's Open Box Apple Watch good? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-22 23:46:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm thinking of picking up a 42mm AWS from Best Buy, but one that's already used. Has anyone bought from them? How is the condition of those devices (the one I'm aiming at says is "excellent", I don't want to get any surprises)? 

Thanks in advance! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [NEWS] iOS 9.3 is released! </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-21 19:57:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [GTA Online] Oh, so you keep killing me while minding my own business? I hope you have money to afford killing me. [X-Post from /r/pettyrevenge] </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-21 18:00:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The game in question is GTA Online, where you have to basically play as your own character online, with 29 other people max with you, in the same city.

Once in a while, I encounter people having this jet: http://gta.wikia.com/wiki/Hydra and basically killing everyone with it, and since the jet is fast, no missile can take it down if the player knows what she/he is doing. And as you might have guessed it, a player killed me with the jet. Multiple times. I got a little frustrated as I am minding my own business so I, with my friend, decide to buy the most expensive car in the game, which costs about $2 million. The reason for such is that if another player destroy your car, they pay 1-2% of what the car costs. So we got in our car (2 cars in total) and waited for the Hydra to come. He killed us about 30 times each or more so enjoy losing more than 1 million dollars a-hole! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [MISC] COC on Twitter: "We're looking into the account switch issue. In the meantime, you may want to try this: (see tweet)" </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-21 15:22:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [MISC] Update March 2016 - known issues: supr.cl/KnownIssues_Ma </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-21 14:26:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Anyone else think Yachts should be used as a Heist planner room? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-19 18:17:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I know the fact that some setups require us to go back to the Planner room to finish the mission, like Fleeca Job- Scope Out, but I think R* can allow us to leave the Yacht's vehicles on the shore (and probably marked in our radars) so we can finish the mission. 

When the Setup/Finale starts, we can take the Yacht's vehicle to go to the shore where we will be met with our cars. If R* plans to make things hard for us, they could disable access to the Yacht's helicopter so we don't do things fast and easier. 

Anyone else agrees? I especially think this should be a feature exclusively to the Aquarius yacht as this one has 4 seasharks so everyone has a boat for themselves. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [C++] Where can I get better in this language? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-17 13:58:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hello Reddit,

I'm a freshman in college and I am pursuing a CS degree. I started up working towards my major by taking [CSCI 271](http://johnjay.jjay.cuny.edu/bulletins/undergraduatebulletin20142015.pdf#page=211).

Now I'm pretty good at math, computers, solving problems and etc, but my one big problem is that I get distracted. A lot. In class, I end up using my phone more than paying attention to the codes in the board, and I messed up real bad in my first test (I got a 78/100). This, plus a combination of my professor not knowing how to explain in an interactive manner that can help students. Is mostly my fault either way.

Now, I know a few terms of C++, I know where to put them, but I don't know what is their function to the program, or what do they mean. I do my homework too, but I have no idea what the f*** I do in it (although I get a perfect score on them)

Is there a website, guide, where I can see several topics, and get quizzes, lessons and pretty much everything that has to do with C++? 

Right now, we are at "Control Functions (Switch)" March 17. if that helps. Syllabus here: http://imgur.com/jYlCWcw


Thank you so much for your help guys! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [Release] iOS 9.3 Beta 7 released! </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-14 22:47:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [Meta] A quick update about the new Telegram group. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-14 17:27:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hey guys,

[I made this group three months ago, the post can be found by clicking this sentence](https://www.reddit.com/r/jailbreak/comments/3vp3pm/meta_a_modapproved_rjailbreak_telegram_group_chat/)

Since then, we have had good laughs and a nice time helping others out. A bot was even made to simplify our lives. The bot, made by /u/ARX8X , currently checks Pangu and Taig servers for jailbreak release, it check this sub, Twitter, it gets us the ipsw download links and among other thing. Example here: [Image 1](http://i.imgur.com/y2Odgkh.png) , [Image 2](http://i.imgur.com/1Jb39uO.png) , and original comment by the creator: https://www.reddit.com/r/jailbreak/comments/49yd7z/releasepangu_releases_ios91_untether_for_64_bit/d0vuvpb?context=3

However, the admins of the new group made yesterday (which is found [here](https://www.reddit.com/r/jailbreak/comments/4aag3r/discussion_telegram_now_has_supergroups_with_up/)), blatantly took /u/ARX8X 's bot without permission, which we believe is a selfish, and bad move. Our conclusion narrows down to the admins as there were no members of the group created first, in the new chat. 

**So what are asking for?** We ask to not support this types of moves and for us, joining in and interacting with the bot, tells us that you are supporting it. We know that you didn't know that before, but now you do. We are okay of having different ways to get quick support, like making a group on Discord, but can we please not steal someone else's work? Hell, I'm not even the creator of the bot and I'm mad about this. Is like taking a developer's tweak and putting it on a pirate repo. The purpose of this community, is to be together, not to harm each other by stealing someone's else work.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> How do I upgrade my group to a supergroup on iOS or Telegram for OS X (not desktop)? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-14 15:33:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What the hell is going on lately? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-12 22:08:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm experiencing glitches in GTA lately. I know they are doing server sides fixes/additions as changing the icons to the radio stations, but, they keep breaking another things. 

I got four videos to show you, captured from my PS4 and if I keep experiencing issues, I will post them here. I'm just mad about the first one, and the second one (this one keeps happening to me in my cars, and somebody else's car)

**First one:** [Here is the video](https://youtu.be/NrB16CWrJuI)

I tried to do Piracy Prevention by myself, when this other VIP comes to my yacht, to "invade it". As you can see, he was on "Super-Passive Mode", he had a gun and everything, but he couldn't hit me, nor I could hit him. And as you might have guessed if you didn't watch the video, he got my Yacht, and left in my Helicopter (which was also on "Passive Mode"). What kind of glitch is this?

**Second one:** [Here is the video](https://youtu.be/N6nbKSE_r4w)

This happened on my second character, but I still experience this with my first character. Why the fuck wouldn't the car run? I mean I understand she was jamming to Pop music, but after I turned it off, she still wouldn't accelerate the car. This happens on my firts character on the Osiris and Zentorno where my character will turn on the car, but won't accelerate at all. This annoys me because I have missed many opportunities to chase a bounty down, or escape from the cops/players. What the hell R*?

**Third one:** [This is a graphical glitch/bug, doesn't annoy me, but I will share it nonetheless](https://youtu.be/mYM0RAt-oU8)

This is the second time it happens. The first one I was driving the car and I got into the water and the game puts all of us in the middle of the road with the cops. We didn't swim out of the car or anything like that. We just teleported. 

**Fourth one:** [I think I broke GTAO with this one...](https://youtu.be/cfYmhVSv0HI)

After finishing a Heist Setup, we respawned at the Host's house. When I tried to go out, this happened, and now, all of a sudden the house, becomes my house (it changed style to match my house in Eclipse and everything). Well, at least I know what's behind that door :p

Anyone else seen weird glitches lately? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [NEWS] Pangu will release JB for Apple TV 4 in one week </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-11 18:06:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> I don't know where to ask this, but since I live in NYC, I will give it ago here. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-11 02:18:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hey guys!

A little backstory, on August, I lost my green card on the JFK airport. I didn't try hard enough to see if the officials from the airport recovered it, so when I decided to try hard enough it was too late (I'm so stupid, I know **:(** ) I also had my passport expire in the Dominican Republic and renewed it right away, so when I came back from DR, I had two passports, stapled together. USCIS says my Permanent Resident Visa is still valid as long as I have both passports when traveling. 

So in January, I moved/rearranged my whole house in hopes that I can find it, and I didn't and since I was too late to be helped by JFK, I decided to pay the fee to replace. No biggie. I get scheduled to my biometrics appoinment, everything is done. I'm just waiting for the card to arrive and it will take 9 months at most to get it back. 

Now, I wanted to apply for my Learner Permit, and tried to apply with my passport, however, since my Visa stamp is on the old passport, my application was automatically declined as I need it on my new passport. I do really want to apply to get my permit and "upgrade" to the senior license as it will open many opportunities to apply to more jobs, like being a valet. What should I do in this case? I was told by the DMV office that I could go to the USCIS office to get my new passport stamped but I looked online and I don't find anything helpful. What should I do? What offices in NYC can I visit to get help? 

Just a note, I'm 17, 18 in a month. I don't know if that matters, but I'm trying to give as much allowed info I can in order to get help.

Thank you guys in advance :) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [Release] iOS 9.3 Beta 6 is released! </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-07 18:52:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> I just got an old Nexus 4. Any interesting things I can do with it? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-07 17:32:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I use iOS as my main device, but I always felt the burn to have both platforms alongside, so I got a Nexus 4. However, I don't know what to do with it. I rooted it, installed a custom ROM and that's all I've done. There were more things I have done when Android was my main device when I had my Galaxy Nexus, but I just don't remember what they were.


What interesting things I should try out? I bought a SIM adapter so I can use it as my main device for at least a day, but that will be about it (at least what I have planned) and I plan to develop on Android when I learn Java in college. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> I got a Nexus 4. What interesting things I can do with it? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-07 03:15:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> iPhone 6S beats other Android flagships in Speed test. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-05 19:51:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Students, what apps do you have on your Watch to boost your productivity? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-05 00:40:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Just wondering which apps you guys use for school/college. I personally use iStudiez and PCal, but I'm on the market of more helpful apps. What do you guys use? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> If you could add **and** delete/replace one thing on the game, what would it be and why? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-02 17:45:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I would add a tool that would allow players to create Contact Missions and Heists, so that R* reviews them and puts them in the game (decreasing their effort in creating Missions).

I wouldn't delete anything actually. I would change the LSPD system. They are annoying. Maybe R* could decrease their way of going at the player?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Anyone else think Heists and Contact Missions are an Idiot Magnet? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-29 19:30:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> **EDIT: This post was downvoted, as well as my comment before people misinterpreted the point of the post. My point wasn't to talk about the Kuruma and how "I abuse of it" as I was accused for by other people in this sub. I don't the Kuruma a lot, but I just use it where I see that it is necessary. In this situations a low level invites me to a Heist, I go without armored car to see how they perform. If they suck, I get out of the Heist, let them invite me again and use the Kuruma to help out, but they still don't follow instructions nor advices like doing things **outside** the car like going to an objective or taking a shortcut. I'm not trying to be a little bitchy ass boss, but I'm just trying to help out so they don't die and do the mission. Several people here turned against the post because I use the Kuruma without seeing why I use it. So before commenting see why I use the Kuruma in the situation below. This also goes to /u/majoroutage , /u/Skellicious , /u/Solaratov , /u/IggyWon , and /u/_Woodrow_ 
This is just how I play, helping others out and thinking about them so we can progress forward, if you maybe see how I play (or play with the people I described below), I'm sure you will change your mindset.**


I can't believe I could be the only one matched with complete fucktards on the game. I know you are a low level, I realize that and know what you feel as I have been there but God damn, can you follow instructions/advices at least? This shit don't make sense. This is going to be a long read. Here is my experience:

**The Flecca Job**

This should be the easiest one right? Eh, no. I can't believe how people fail this one. Heck, even me being a low level and doing it for the first time knew what to do and thought with my brain.

*Flecca Job - Kuruma*

The easiest way I like to do this is to take my Kuruma and kill the gang guarding the Kuruma we need to take. When we get out of the Host's apartment, I tell them to get in my Kuruma, because we can kill the gang faster, and I also say and repeat, to stay in my car until all of them are dead. **They still get out of my Kuruma to kill the gang and they end up dying, at least twice. WTF? Is it hard to understand it?**

*Flecca Job Finale* 

After drilling the safe (or whatever that is called), we are supposed to get on the car. **Why the fuck do you get out of the banks, to kill the cops? Just why? Lester told you at least twice the car is armored. Tf?**

**The Prison Break**

*Plane*

**"Um, don't get out my Kuruma until all of the Vagos, well, the enemies are gone okay guys?" *Everyone gets on my Kuruma* "All right, here we go, don't get out of my car and shoot from the inside" *Everyone gets off my car and dies the second they try to get to cover* -_-*

*Bus*

**"Guys, I got the bus, go to the dirt and don't follow me so we lose the cops faster" *Oh sure, that's the first thing we going to do* "Get away from me" *Psych, we like you, let's make this harder and lose the cops together while I keep shooting at them* -___-**

*Prison Break- Finale*

I also don't have complaints, unless the Prisioner doesn't listen to me when I tell him to get to cover or the Demolition destroys Helis and cars near the Plane on Sandy Shores.

**The Humane Labs Raid**

*Valkeryie*

Oh damn, this one is just plain stupid to do. Hope in a Kuruma and go all the way to the Heli itself. Kill the people around the Heli inside the Kuruma and get out of there with the Heli. Yep, that's the way to do it. Unless, another player do the stuff their way, which, ends up in them being dead. At least twice until the player realizes getting on the Kuruma is the way to go. 

*Deliver EMP*

Agent 14 tells you to kill them silently, heck, he even tells you he gave you weapons with silencer. Why the fuck do you take out a RPG, or an Assault Riffle without silencer? What the hell?


**Series A**

*Bikers*

Same thing as *Deliver EMP* why the fuck you use something without silencer when the game tells you to not alert them?

**Pac Standard**

*Vans*

I'm always the Navigator. I know where the Vans are and if I get confused, I use the Tracking app. One of the driver honks at me to get on their car so I tell them via voice, that I can go and do it, but I will need the driver to just drive around and not crash any vans. Well, that can't work out as the driver will crash into me when i'm taking the picture of the van's plate, or he will shoot at the other driver and crash into everything, making the mission fail. If we ever get the van we need, the other players keep following me. TF?

*Hack*

I always like to go ahead and kill the rival crew the others come to decrease our chances of dying. Well, I tell these people not to follow me and yet they do so no one goes and get the vans, making us lose time and a few tries along with it as they die trying to get on my car (I set my car access to No-one once in a while).

*Convoy*

This one is easy, if you are patient that is. The first thing I say is not to take the truck and drive it away, as it will make the mission more difficult by having enemies on foot and car and the Heli. If we wait, we can knock out everything without being too pressured by the enemies. And guess what people do, the opposite of what I say/planned. Great.

*Bikes*

Same as always: **"Get on my Kuruma and knock this out." *Nope, I'm going on my car and die* Really?**

*Finale*

First thing people can't do right is the simplest thing ever. Crowd Control. In every finale I do for randoms, the NOOSE gets called, making things harder and the Host didn't put the Heist so that we can use our Player Saved Outfit. I tell the Hacker or Demo (depending on which role I'm doing, either Demo or Hacker) and tell them to stay on the bank while I go to the bikes, but, Mr. Super Man don't listen. Well, either way, I open the way to the bikes, almost dying, but IDC. When we are at the bikes, I repeat like 5 times to not get on the bike and follow me (describing my character as it stands out from the others who wear the same thing). Well, all of them left on the bike and wait for me on the entrance of where the bikes were. I try to get them out of the bike by holding triangle and quickly destorying the bike, but the others see what I did and decide to play with me. Cool. We almost lose a million dollars in there until we get the Kuruma. Now on the way to the canyon on the Kuruma, the players jump out of the car, when I say the opposite. Losing more money as the host goes downhill without his parachute. 


This is my personal story with Heist. I think I'm cursed with randoms. What is the experience you guys have with randoms?

TL;DR: People being stupid and being jackasses on Heist and missions. What's your story?




 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [USA-NY] [H] 2014 Asus X550CA [W] Verified Paypal, or GW </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-26 22:39:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hello there!

This is my first time posting here, so if I didn't do something right, let me know please :)

Up for sale is an Asus Notebook bought on November 2014 but it wasn't used as much in the house and I'm looking to get a Mac for college. 

The only problem/defect of the laptop is that the plastic is broken at the top left of the keyboard/base. I might not described it correctly in words, so I will leave this album here to explain the issue better: http://imgur.com/a/5RjYP

Other than that, it is in a great condition, no flaws on the screen, nothing abnormal. 

This laptop packs the following: 

**3rd Gen Intel Core i3-3217U processor (With 3MB L3 Cache and 1.8 GHz processor speed and it also features smart 4-way processing performance for HD quality computing. 
Intel HD graphics provide extra graphics power for the laptop when needed); 4GB DDR3 Memory (expandable to 6GB oficially, but people have this same Notebook with 8GB with no issues); 15.6" display, 500GB of hard drive (Actually two separate drives adding up to 500GB, one 250GB and the other, well, 250GB too. Both drives have 5400 rpm); Intel HD Graphics 4000, 1.0MP webcam, digital media reader (I haven't tested this to see if it works); 1 USB 3.0 port and 2 2.0 ports; 802.11n Wi-Fi and 10/100/1000 Mpbs Ethernet (RJ-45) connector)**

That was a wall of text :( But every thing I could say about the note book is in there. A better way to see the features/specs are here, on ASUS' website: https://www.asus.com/Notebooks/X550CA/specifications/

The laptop is on Windows 10 64-bit, but I could go to W8 or W8.1 when requested :) 

Also, depending on the buyer, I might give you access to Office 365 (one of the activation codes my school provides) and McAfee (my cable router provides this). The reason I say might, is that both software reveals my name and email address so when you purchase, I will need to see your history here on the sub to trust you with both, my name and email. 

Moving on! TIMESTAMPS: http://imgur.com/a/USfFZ      I just have two pics, and if you need more let me know and they will be uploaded ASAP. 

My asking price is $370 + shipping. 
.
Any questions please let me know :) 
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [NEWS] Routine PSN maintenance Tues 3/1, 9:30pm - 11:30pm PST. Log in prior to retain online play/app access </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-23 21:01:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Oh, so you keep killing me while minding my own business? I hope you have money to afford killing me. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-22 19:01:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The game in question is GTA Online, where you have to basically play as your own character online, with 29 other people max with you, in the same city. 

Once in a while, I encounter people having this jet: http://gta.wikia.com/wiki/Hydra and basically killing everyone with it, and since the jet is fast, no missile can take it down if the player knows what she/he is doing. And as you might have guessed it, a player killed me with the jet. Multiple times. I got a little frustrated as I am minding my own business so I, with my friend, decide to buy the most expensive car in the game, which costs about $2 million. The reason for such is that if another player destroy your car, they pay 1-2% of what the car costs. So we got in our car (2 cars in total) and waited for the Hydra to come. He killed us about 30 times each or more so enjoy losing more than 1 million dollars a-hole! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What is the name of the law in question? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-22 18:31:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hello /rAskNYC!

I wan to know the name of the law that has the following effect on minors:

The law require people under 18 to have a person over 18 to sign for a legal document, like School sports permission, electronic device repairs/replacement, medical form and among other things Apple. The reason I ask is because Apple has given me replacement for my Apple Watch and iPhone without having someone with me to sign the document, but when I wanted a replacement for my iPad, they wouldn't let me sign it unless I have someone over 18 with me.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Apple Watch 42mm Leather Loop Band Raffle! </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-21 04:56:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [x-post from /r/scams] Am I going to get scammed? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-10 19:05:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Link: Original link: https://www.np.reddit.com/r/Scams/comments/453xe1/am_i_going_to_get_scammed_if_i_proceed_with_this/

Text:
Hey guys! I just want to know if this is a scam or not. Any help/inout is appreciated. I posted a listing of my laptop on NY Craigslist. Shortly after, I received a text, from a NY phone, asking for the condition of the computer. I answered their text, and the "buyer" proceeded to ask where I was located, question which I answered (I just said city and state). The buyer then asks me if I can take $130 more than I asked for so i can ship it to Miami. I proceeded to ask why he/she is offering more, and he told me is for shipping purposes so I can send it to Miami. He/she stated that the computer will be sent outside of the country for his "friend" after he receives it. Anyways, the buyer proceeded to ask if I can request the money to his paypal, which seems strange to me, so I stopped answering. Is this a scam? If I request money, Paypal won't have my back so I'm having second thoughts about all of this. I reversed search the phone number and nothing comes up, neither something appears for the Paypal email provided. Should I keep ignoring the texts? Or this is safe? I can provide screenshots if requested via PM so I don't break the rules. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Am I going to get scammed if I proceed with this? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-10 18:44:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hey guys!

I just want to know if this is a scam or not. Any help/inout is appreciated.

I posted a listing of my laptop on NY Craigslist. Shortly after, I received a text, from a NY phone, asking for the condition of the computer. I answered their text, and the "buyer" proceeded to ask where I was located, question which I answered (I just said city and state). The buyer then asks me if I can take $130 more than I asked for so i can ship it to Miami. I proceeded to ask why he/she is offering more, and he told me is for shipping purposes so I can send it to Miami. He/she stated that the computer will be sent outside of the country for his "friend" after he receives it. 

Anyways, the buyer proceeded to ask if I can request the money to his paypal, which seems strange to me, so I stopped answering. 

Is this a scam? If I request money, Paypal won't have my back so I'm having second thoughts about all of this. I reversed search the phone number and nothing comes up, neither something appears for the Paypal email provided. Should I keep ignoring the texts? Or this is safe?

I can provide screenshots if requested via PM so I don't break the rules. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [Question] Does No PLS Recovery prevent remote wiping via iCloud? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-09 23:56:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Title ^ 

Thanks in advance </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [Request] Can a developer update this tweak please? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-06 01:27:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Yacht spawning somewhere else after switching sessions </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-05 17:46:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hello Redditors!

I bought a yacht about two days ago, and the initial location was in the East side of "Terminal/Bucanner Way". Shortly after I get on it, I decided to move it to Vespucci Beach, paying the $25k fee. After a Heist/switching session/closing the game and opening it again, the Yacht goes back to the Terminal or to the East of LSIA, which means I have to pay the $25k fee in order to move it to Vespucci again.

Anyway I can stop my Yacht from moving? I hate paying $25k just because my Yacht wants to move on its own. Thanks for your help! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [NEWS] iOS 9.2 is no longer signed by Apple. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-04 19:13:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Was the Pac Standard Glitch fixed? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-28 16:44:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Sorry if this isn't the right place to post this.

I believe the glitch doesn't work anymore as the game detected the Host (one of my friends) left the game/Heist so I want to confirm it. We tried twice already and I don't know if we did something wrong, or is patched already. 

Here is how the game went:

Host was Demolition, I was Hacker, and two random guys were Crowd Control. I carried all the money, so I stayed in the bank while the "runners" went to the bike and destroy it so the checkpoint is set where the bikes are. Everything was successful (with a couple of tries). After we spawned, bikes were destroyed again, as I had a Kuruma in the apartment right behind where the bikes are. So, we destroyed it, we took the Kuruma and we got to the place where the Dinghy is. Afterwards, I made sure the Host was last to enter (as the random guys took a long time to get on the boat.... I think they don't read directions) and it happened. I was driving the Dinghy and as soon as the front of the boat passed the bridge, the Host closed the game and the glitch seemed to work as the minimap and the destination circle disappear so I stopped driving. **However**, the minimap appeared as well as the destination circle and we got the message that the Host/Demolition Team left. 

Was the glitch patched? There was no update at all so we thought the glitch still worked (before the new Sultan update that came out today). Can someone please confirm if it was patched or not? We are on PS4. 

Thanks in advance! 

TL;DR: Friend and I did the Pac Standard Heist, and my friend was the Host. The purpose was to do the glitch. The game detected that the Host left the game twice already and we made sure the Host was last to get on the boat. Host closed the game as soon as the front of the boat passed the bridge. Is glitched still working? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Watch OS 2.2 Beta 2 released for developers! </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-25 22:41:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [Question] Cydia can't restart the Springboard. This happened after installing Flame. After uninstalling Flame, the same problem persists. What can I do to fix it? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-25 18:34:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [NEWS] iOS 9.2.1 is released! </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-19 19:01:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Some pics of the bands sold by Baoxing Trading, these don't feel so cheap at all! </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-17 23:29:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [NEWS] [UPDATE] PlayStation on Twitter: "PS4 system software update 3.15 is coming tonight  its a minor update designed to improve system performance." </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-13 06:04:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [NEWS] PlayStation on Twitter: "PSN update: check your email starting this week for details on extensions for PS Plus, PS Now, and video rentals for active accounts" </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-12 18:31:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> There is a petition asking Apple to keep the headphones 3.5mm jack. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-09 00:48:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Random </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-07 17:35:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Testing </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Hello RDADS! </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-07 16:31:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I want to join the RDAD crew on GTA 5 however, I can't find it. I believe I need to be a friend of someone in the crew so I can see it. Is anyone willing to add me? I play GTA 5 on the PS4. My username is bloodbrother1318.

Thank you :)  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> John Legere on Twitter: "If you have questions about #BingeOn that werent answered already, dont worry  Ill be doing a twitter Q A around Noon PT. #AskJohn" </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-07 15:54:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [NEWS] Maintenance inbound! The Attack boost is over but the Resource boost has been extended: supr.cl/22MM6BJ </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-07 13:48:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Every single time. Is like the game doesn't want me to do so </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-31 06:52:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [PSA] Many GTA players know this, but if you don't, you can get a free car, specifically the Elegy RH8. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-27 17:44:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hey guys! Just a tip for the beginners of the game (or for those who didn't know this). You can get a Elegy RH8 for free. Here is the car's info: http://www.ign.com/wikis/gta-5/Annis_Elegy_RH8

In order to get this car for free, you will need two things (or one, or none, depending if you have the materials):

- A garage or a house
- Have your Steam, PSN, or Xbox Gamertag connected to Rockstar's Social Club

If you are new to the game, here is a list of properties you can have. I recommend aiming for a high-end house (apartment) so you can do your Heists: http://www.ign.com/wikis/gta-5/Properties_(GTA_Online)

If you got your house (or garage), then connect your gamertag with Rockstar's Social Club here: http://socialclub.rockstargames.com/

If you got those things, then go to the Internet on your player's phone (or computer in the Heist planning room) and click on "Travel and Transport" and click on the third link. Then go to the red bar under the yellow car and hit it once. Afterwards, you will see the Elegy RH8 and it should be **free**. If it is not, wait a few minutes. Choose your color, and get it
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [NEWS] Maintenance Break inbound! </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-23 14:55:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [HIMB] Improvements after a month-- Anything I should improve? I'm open to negative and positive feedback </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-20 22:33:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Anyone on PS4 willing to help me on Heist setups? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-17 23:57:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm having a hard time finding players that would join my Heist Setup for Prisiob Break. Are you guys willing to help me? I will help you out if you need players for missions or whatever. My username is bloodbrother1318

Thanks in advance!  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [Question] Can someone confirm this for me? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-17 02:32:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Have you guys been recently to the Poconos? How's service over there? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-16 15:02:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hello guys!

I've been invited to the Poconos and we will be going by Christmas time. I was there 2 (or 3) years ago and I remember service on an iPhone 5 sucked in there. No roaming, nothing at all. Only AT T, Sprint (and I think also Verizon worked, I don't remember) worked and their MVNOs. 

Does T-Mobile works there now? Is it only band 12 phones that work there? I will be going with my brother who has an iPhone 6 on MetroPCS so I want to know if I will be the only one to have a signal on my iPhone 6S (T-Mobile) or not. 

If it helps:

Device: iPhone 6S
Plan: Simple Choice 2 lines for $100


Thanks in advance!
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [Update] Auxo 3 compatible with iOS 9 </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-12 18:38:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [NEWS] Maintenance break is over </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-10 18:22:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [NEWS] Another maintenance break inbound. SC is increasing capacity numbers </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-10 17:29:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [MISC] SC updated some of CoC's images/design, see for yourself. I personally like it. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-10 16:35:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> I can't access my rewards in any way now... </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-10 03:03:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hey guys, I hope you guys help me on this issue as I will be visitibg Gamestop often.

2 weeks ago, I went to the store and got myself a PS4 BO3 bundle. I didn't have my card on me, but lucklily, my info popped up on the computer. The employee didn't offer me a "Pro" reward card, so I didn't even ask for it as I wasn't thinking about that anyways. 

A few days later, I kept saying people got items using their points, so I wondered how many points I had and I was this close to getting the points I needed to get something that I liked: https://pbs.twimg.com/media/B1NFMTTCYAMkSOX.jpg
so I decided to buy some more games, remotes, etc for my PS4. 

So today, I went to trade in some games and remote with my 18-years old cousin (as I can't trade them due to age). At the end, the employee helping me offered me a "Pro" Rewards Card and explained me the benefits of it (how it will help with the trade, etc,etc) so I used the credit to upgrade my Basic card. Everything worked as expected, I got 10% more on my trades, and I got out of the store. When I got home, I tried activating the card from Safari on my iPhone, it said: **"Sorry, we couldn't validate your information. Please try again."** so I thought it was a problem with the browser so I went to the Gamestop app, and it sent me to Safari so I switched to my laptop where I tried again and the same message appeared. Now my card isn't active, now I can't see my points, and I basically have an extra "useless" card on my wallet. What should I do now? Sorry for the long post :/

**TL;DR: I upgraded my Basic card and now I can't activate the Pro card for some reason. What should I do?**

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Upgraded from the fat PS3 made in 2007, here is what I think. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-09 16:06:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I got my BO3 PS4 bundle 2 weeks ago, and here is what I think about the PS4 at this point after upgrading from my fat 60GB PS3. Worth to mention that I have the latest PS4 revision (the one with mechanical buttons)

*CONS:**

* I still can't save 2 Wi-Fi networks :( I saw that many people requested it on their forums (and pretty much anywhere else) and Sony didn't bring that feature to the PS4. I 'm still positive that future SW updates will bring this feature. I see myself playing online with my iPhone's Hostpot, then switching to the public Wi-Fi (I'm paying for subscription) near my house so I can download things/keep the PS4 connected to the internet and is annoying setting up both networks again and again.

* **This sounds like an issue I only had. I fixed it by factory resetting the system. Special thanks to /u/Matt4045, /u/supabloo , /u/workworkwork1234 for their insight in this issue so I could get it fixed.** ~~The PS Dynamic home screen lags while an application is **running** (it doesn't when no application is running). I've tried switching to a static theme, but nothing helps. The PS3 I had could go into the XMB just fine, without lagging. If I want to change a song on Spotify while playing BO3, I have to wait like 15-ish seconds so the UI can be fluid and then changes to the next screen, where I have to wait more so the animations complete. (I know I can do it from my phone, but sometimes my phone is unavailable for me to use to change songs) I was told to rebuild database, however, that helps, for some time, then the lag comes back.~~ 

* The DS4....... Sony, couldn't you put more battery to the DS4? I played longer on my DS3 but I see myself charging the DS4 at least once a day and I hate being tethered to the console. 

**PROS:**

* This thing is silent, I don't hear anything from it at all. My PS3 will make so much sound, it would affect my mom's sleep at night and she will tell me to turn it off. She doesn't even notice my PS4 at all (unless I forget to lower the speaker sound and I get a call (or make one) in GTA V, or the lady in BO3 tells me my scorestreak is ready)

* Performance in games is super duper great. I enjoy using my console even more due to the graphics and things that I wish I could do with the PS3. The PS4 really exceeded my expectations.

* The DS4 is a huge improvement over the DS3. In the DS3, I could feel/see the latency between pressing my buttons and my character on the screen but I can't see it here on the DS4/PS4. 

**Things I wish I could do/ Things I want**

These are not hardware wise, but I wish I could:

* Delete some apps from my home screen. I don't use 40% of them so I wish I could hide them in "Library". I feel this will help reduce lag.

* Re-organize the menu on the "Notification" screen. I mostly go there to check download and that's pretty much it.

* Re-organize the PS menu (where you hold the PS button on the remote).

* Lower the volume of the system/remote when I have it connected to my headphone via the headphone's volume control.

* I wish the Playstation Store was a standalone application and not a "internet browser bookmark** (At least how I feel it/see it)

* I wish I could install my Blu-Ray games on my PS4, and that the system asks for it every 3 days or so to verify that I still have it. I don't see the point of having 48GBs of Black Ops 3 in my hard drive if I still need the disc to play it **Quick question about this: why does BO3 takes so much space as it was downloaded from PS-Store?**

* I wish I could activate 2 systems per account like the PS3


**Summary-- TL;DR**

I'm pretty much happy with the change. Sony could improve somethings via SW updates, so I can't wait to see what Sony brings us in future updates. Via SW updates, Sony can also fix several annoyances people have with the PS4. The PS4 is definitely better than the PS3. If you got the latest model of the PS3, I still recommend to upgrade anyways, it is worth it. I chose this long to upgrade my system as I was waiting to see what manufacturer problems the PS4 can bring, and at this point, there isn't pretty much any problems. 

**If I said anything that could be easily fixed, please let me know. Thanks in advance :)** </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [Discussion] Is it me, or the $1 million jailbreak was given/sold to Apple since they patch all this Safari related "bugs"? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-09 01:54:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> I've run out of ideas for my research paper.. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-06 22:28:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hello guys, 

I'm writing a research paper in which I talk about stuttering. The whole paper is good, however, the solution I proposed wasn't well accepted by my professor. 

In my paper, I put that raising awareness could help us (at least how I see it), so I have to look for something that's not about raising awareness. What solutions do you guys have/had in mind for stutter that I could talk about? 

Here is the link to my first draft: https://drive.google.com/open?id=1GAhmBl40WN4nQ-jzG17bO-G2_3cCBGpSFLZrqmCjP0Q

I will of course, share my final draft with you guys :) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [META] A mod-approved /r/jailbreak Telegram group chat </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-06 21:06:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> **Is worth to mention that this is not an official chat from the moderators, I am working on the chat independently. I just did it so you guys have quick support. A message from a moderator: /u/ibbignerd "To make this very clear, this is an independent project and has nothing to do officially with /r/jailbreak or the moderation team. While we support users coming up with new projects, this is different from being officially supported."** 

Hello guys, I messaged the mods of this sub asking if they could do a Telegram group chat, and their response was that I could do it so let's see how this will work out :)

Joining is easy, and here are the steps:

1) Download the Telegram app || [LINK](http://telegram.org)

2) Register your account using your phone number (You can sign up using a Google Voice number if you want)

**NOTE:** If you do not want anyone else to see your phone number, don't add them as a contact. Only your personal contacts in Telegram can see your phone number.

**3) If you would like to remain anonymous, do not put your real name in when it asks you for your name. Whatever you put in this field is what everyone else in the chat room will see. Put your Reddit username or something along those lines so you remain anonymous.**

4) After you're done setting up your account, go to Settings and register a "Public Username." This will associate a username with your account that can be searchable by others. Your username will then be what you have chosen and it will be after the @ symbol (just like Instagram)

5) Finally, to join the chat, click this link: telegram.com/rjailbreak

6) Change your notification settings for the group. As the chat grows, it could create chaos in your device.

I hope you guys like this and if I don't see positive feelings towards the chat, I will delete as it will be sort of like unnecessary then. The same rules will apply, but we can work it out as the chat grows :)

Cheers!

We are a supergroup btw :)

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [Discussion] Please don't fall for these fake jailbreaks.. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-05 21:00:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I saw a thread just now (but I can't find it now so I could link you guys to it), that said that the OP lost his iOS 9.0.x jailbreak for a 9.1 and 9.2 jailbreak. Just so you know, if you see a jailbreak for 9.1 or 9.2 is fake. If you still doubt it see the sidebar - [Sidebar](http://imgur.com/gStYGSq) just in case.

I believe these people do these fake jailbreak because they can advertise via these methods and get money. Or a Youtuber can promote it on his channel so he/she gets views (which equals to money if they monetize their video). Jailbreak is free in every way (unless a Youtuber posts a tutorial of it), just remember that

Remember to follow closely each jailbreak team on their website or Twitter so you get reliable info and a good jailbreak:

**Pangu**: [Website](http://pangu.io) || [Twitter](https://twitter.com/PanguTeam) || **Note: Pangu's website domain is "io" not "net" so don't fall for this one (which is fake by the way) [Fake one, "net" domain"](http://pangu9.net/)**

**Taig**: [Website](http://www.taig.com/en/) || [Twitter](https://twitter.com/taig_jailbreak)

**Last thing, if the sub isn't talking about that jailbreak then is fake. Period*

I recommend turning on Push Notification for those two accounts so you know when they are about to release a jailbreak or something along those  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [Discussion] Just wanted to make sure, is this a hardware issue and not a software issue? (See video) </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-05 00:36:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [News] Maintenance Break for iOS users due to the campaign. SC is disabling it </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-04 18:10:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [HWYA] Just a quick question. If I drop a lightning spell in the marked area, will it hit both ADs? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-04 16:32:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> I have good speeds (according to this) yet my "connection" is slow. YouTube and about everything else is slow. What gives? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-04 02:07:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [Request] This app but for iPhone. Maybe it could be activated via an Activator function. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-03 02:47:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [MISC] CoC and its brothers gets featured on the App Store for their RED update. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-01 23:00:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Just wanted to share a campaign of a tracker that works with iPhone. It is $1 with free shipping. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-01 22:21:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [Discussion] Looking into starting fresh with your jailbreak? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-01 03:27:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I have seen myself in the situation where i wanted to start from scratch on my jailbreak. I didn't try Impactor as you guys have said that it doesn't work so I tried an alternative that should be done via my phone. 

If you uninstall **Cydia Substrate**, all your tweaks and libraries will be uninstalled too at the same time. So I went ahead and did that and now I have a "fresh jailbroken" iPhone 6S. 

If you get an error like in this thread: https://redd.it/3r53k0
Fix it following this steps: https://www.reddit.com/r/jailbreak/comments/3r53k0/help_i_accidentally_unistalled_substrate_and_all/cwkyqhd

 "Fixed it!
I tried following /u/jayreddin 's advice, to close Cydia from the task switcher and I opened it again. I saw as an opportunity to install Substrate again (without respringing from the previous unistall). I resprung and everything is good again.
Thank you /u/jayreddin" 

Hope I helped in any way! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [MISC] I didn't see a post of the update supporting "RED" so here is some screenshots of it. It removes the Halloween theme. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-11-30 23:26:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [PS4] I have like two days trying to get Online but I can't. How can I fix this? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-11-29 17:41:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> I suck at CoD, what can I do? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-11-29 00:27:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> In every match I play I get 4/10+ (K/D) and I can't get any better. I have a terrible aim and I want to improve that. In local matchs I could get my kills but online, I'm a free kill for the enemy team. What can I do to get better? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> 15% off in iTunes Gift Cards. Available until tomorrow (Nov 26th) at 11:59PM PST </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-11-25 20:19:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> How do I get 14GBs of Hostpot as announced in the Uncarrier X? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-11-23 13:50:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> On the event, it was announced that all unlimited lines will get a bump from 7GBs of Hostpot, to 14. I am still getting 7GBs. What should I do to upgrade? Is it free?

http://imgur.com/JQh2HCv </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What happens when you sharpen a pencil? An Apple Pencil to be exact. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-11-21 21:19:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Doesn't matter which Chipotle I apply to, I get rejected. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-11-21 17:22:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I live in NYC and I have applied for almost all the Chipotle in Manhattan. Some of them just flat out send me an email rejecting my application. Some of them say to go for an interview, they see me, and they say that they are going to call me or email me in regards to their desicion. One day later, my application is rejected.

The only time that I have felt that I would get the job is when I applied to the 8th Ave and 52nd Street Chipotle. I went for an interview three times. Thee third one was to see the back of the restaurant and how things work. Afterwards, I was told that I would receive a call in 24hrs. I didn't so I waited another day before I called. I called and they put me in hold then the manager told me that I was rejected. No reason given and hanged up.

 I don't apply in the Bronx (another  because they are full already and I don't apply on Queens nor Brooklyn because they are far away from where I live (Bronx).

Should I keep applying to the same stores or should I just give up? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Despite my stutter, I made my first unboxing video. I actually plan to keep uploading videos, and stuttering won't hold me back :) </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-11-21 05:16:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> John "roasted" Sprint following their cut in Twitter </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-11-18 20:47:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This is what he said: 
"This may be a surprise to some, but I love @sprints new err rinse-and-repeat promotion announced this morning! Why do I love it? Marcelo repeatedly said there are no gimmicks, but lets look at the fine print shall we? They added @TMobile to their cut your bill in half promotion, and heres the great news - it applies to almost 0% of @TMobile customers! "

Then he followed to list ten things in which T-Mo is better than Sprint:

"10. @TMobile customers get Unlimited video streaming w/ their plans. Not on @Sprint. #SprintCountdown #halfoffthetruth

9. @TMobile customers get Unlimited music streaming w/ their plans. Not on @Sprint. #SprintCountdown #halfoffthetruth

8. @TMobile customers get #DataStash (unused data rolls forward). Not on @Sprint. #SprintCountdown #halfoffthetruth

7. @TMobile customers get tethering included in their plans. Not on @Sprint's new 50% off offer. #SprintCountdown #halfoffthetruth

6. @TMobile customers use their phone in Mexico   Canada just like they do in the US. Not on @Sprint. #SprintCountdown #halfoffthetruth

5. @TMobile customers get unlimited data and text in 140 countries. Not on @Sprint. #SprintCountdown #halfoffthetruth

4. @TMobile customers don't have activation fees. @sprint charges $36 per line! #SprintCountdown #halfoffthetruth

3. @TMobile customers get America's Fastest 4G LTE network. @Sprint's get America's slowest (@Ookla). #SprintCountdown #halfoffthetruth

2. @TMobile customers get 4G LTE in 500+ cities. Not on @Sprint. #Spark...I mean #LTEplus #SprintCountdown #halfoffthetruth

1. @TMobile customers get access to whatever plan they want. On @sprint, you have to leave and come back take advantage! #SprintCountdown"

TL;DR: John roasted Sprint on Twitter. That's all you need to know :p

PS: I hope this is better than the last time I did something similar here: https://www.reddit.com/r/tmobile/comments/3shpe7/john_will_finally_talk_after_the_price_increase/ </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [Discussion] For those of you who use Twitter, what are some good accounts to follow? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-11-18 18:57:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I have some developers like Unlimapps, CP Digital, and the developer of Preference Loader (can't get the name now). What are some other developers I could follow? Thanks in advance </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [REQUEST] Make a tweak that would make the iPhone wake up when a notification comes while its paired on the watch </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-11-17 16:31:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If you have an Apple Watch, you would know that when the screen is locked, the phone stays "chill" (the screen doesn't light up, nothing) when a notification comes in, while the watch tells you. 

If you turn off Bluetooth, the phone will alert you (since the Watch can't) or when you take off your Watch, the phone will alert you. 

The tweak that I am requesting makes the watch alert you of the notification as well as the phone while the phone is locked.

There is a tweak already that does this feature, but it is when the phone is unlocked. When the phone is unlocked, the watch doesn't alert you of the notification but the phone does.

TL;DR: A tweak that will make the phone light up when a notification comes in on while its locked and paired with an Apple Watch </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [ASK] Since CoC is down, what happens to boost, wars, and barracks (making a troop) and spell factory? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-11-17 03:50:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Title ^ </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [Glitch] So, I'm still attacking even though I'm not. Go me! </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-11-17 02:38:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> A CoC player... </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-11-17 00:40:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hello there, I recently upgraded to Headquarters lvl 5 and I can join a force. I actually rushed a little so I could get help on the game. I play CoC and I understand that better compared to this. I just don't know what to do here. Any force willing to take me to guide me to success? Here is my base http://imgur.com/a/e7nUT </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Why does the iPhone take "ages" to narrow down the GPS to a single location? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-11-16 16:58:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> All right, so I have an i6S, and I often look up my family on Find My Friends so I know where are they if they don't pick up the phone or to meet them up, however, I see my phone is in a different address for about 20 seconds and then moves to my location (address) afterwards. While my phone is at "that address" the radius is bigger then it becomes smaller or it dissapears completely. The same thing happen with my family members' iPhone (2 iPhone 6 and an iPhone 5S). 

Is this due to Wi-Fi? We have 3 iPad Mini Retina and I can get the iPads' location right away but I have to wait for the iPhones, and the iPhones have the Wi-Fi off. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [ASK] How does the Global Chat works? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-11-16 16:16:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I have two devices (iPhone 6S and iPad Mini 2) right next to each other, but they have different accounts (both are mine). They both on different clans. However, when I text in Global Chat from the iPhone, the iPad doesn't see it and viceversa. Is a whole different chat. How does that work? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> WTF Trump? Excuse you, T-Mo is better than any company (at least for me) </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-11-16 02:56:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [Request] Can someone make a tweak that will eliminate the transition from an app to another when "3D Touching"? (See vid) </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-11-16 00:56:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [Recruiting] G8Way | TH7+ | Clan Level: 6 | Farming/Warring </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-11-15 23:03:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> We are a clan that cares about team. If you are rushed, we can help you out. We donate strong troops (but of course, we expect you to donate too). We war twice a week so you can get loots to upgrade your stuff. If you don't want to be in war, just say it (we ask who doesn't want to be in war before searching). We are active! We have won over 50 wars! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> This is funny yet sad at the same time. [x-post from /r/funny] </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-11-15 06:01:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Can somebody shed some light in this? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-11-13 03:35:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> All right, so I signed for T-Mobile because I thought that the unlimited data will help me for college (and it does, but the only downside is that there is no service in some areas of the campus). I got the 2 unlimited lines for $100 (I'm with my mom on the line).

Later on, I discovered that my college gives discounts, so I signed up for that, and I got approved for it. That was two bill statements ago (2 months). The next month came in super low so I thought the discount was in effect, and I thought that could save me economically. However, this bill statement came in higher than usual ($189) since I got an iPhone 6S on JOD ($26/month) but that didn't add up to the amount I owed last month ($127). I was expecting my bill to come in at $153 with my discount, and that didn't happen as you can see. 

I contacted T-Force on Twitter and i get told the following:

And I quote; "I do see that there is a corporate indicator on the account. However, the rate plan that you are in is one of our already discounted promotional rate plans that the monthly discounts do not apply to. *TripR" 

Is there a specific requirements to get discounts? If I knew this would happen, I wouldn't have bought the iPhone 6S, and instead I would have fixed my water damaged iPhone 6. Should I contact somebody else rather than T-Force (611 maybe?)

TL;DR: Signed up for 2 unlimited lines for $100, I applied for discount and I got approved. Now I have been told by T-Force that the discount doesn't apply on my line. What gives? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Facebook released another app for iOS. Have you guys tried it yet? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-11-11 20:59:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> This was my favorite part of the whole Uncarrier X event. This was just funny  </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-11-11 01:04:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Let's see who gets it right... </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-11-10 02:32:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So I want you guys just to predict what Uncarrier X will be about tomorrow. Anything goes! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [HIMB] Anything I should improve? I'm open to negative and positive feedback </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-11-08 17:20:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [ASK] Just wondering, how many of you guys use real $$ on the game? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-11-08 16:20:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Title ^ </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [Question] Any Apple employee here that jailbreak their phones? What do you get told at job? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-11-08 14:08:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Title ^ 

I just want to see how Apple employees handle jailbreak (reactions) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [Update] Paragon is updated with support for iOS 9. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-11-08 04:33:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [Request] Can someone do this please? (See video) </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-11-07 01:25:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> I broke Minecraft's sky (y-axis) limit on the PS3! Does this work in other versions? Please try it. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-11-06 23:08:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [Discussion] I moderate a Jailbreak community on Google Plus, and it has come to my attention that you can install Cydia without a computer. Just in case, this is FAKE! Beware! No one knows what malware gets installed there. One of the members sent me this video, see for yourself and judge </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-11-06 17:11:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [USA-NY] [H] Guitar Hero Live for iOS devices [W] Paypal, Google Wallet or cash </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-11-05 03:43:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hello /r/hardwareswap !

Looking forward to my first sale here!

I have a Guitar Hero Live that I don't want anymore (I sucked at it lol) so I want to sell it to someone who will make good use of it. It is on perfect condition, zero scratches, nothing. It has new batteries (Double AA).

I live in NYC and I can ship it (if you pay for it, I will have to pay too much for it as the neck of the guitar can't be removed so it can't be placed on the box) or we can meet up. Looking to sell it for $85. Any questions let me know!

Pics: http://imgur.com/a/uKMFJ </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Quick question, what happened to the T-Mo employees that were here on Reddit? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-11-04 20:03:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I was reading the side bar and I noticed that there were four T-Mo employee that aren't active anymore (their username starts with 't_mo') What happened to them?

**EDIT:**

I'm talking about these users:

/u/tmo_AmandaC
/u/tmo_JessicaB
/u/tmo_JoshuaJ
/u/tmo_DonA
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [Tutorial][Discussion] Tweaks that will help you in case your phone gets stolen or you lose it. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-11-04 18:53:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hello /r/jailbreak!

So I wrote this tutorial to help you out in case your phone is lost or gets stolen. I believe this will help you get your device back and it will be hard for someone to turn it off thus leaving your phone "untrackable" via Find My iPhone. 

Please visit this link as I will show you pictures of I how I have things set up here: 

http://imgur.com/a/u45fH

The tweaks I will use for this tutorial are **BioProtect,** (BioLockDown will do fine if you use that) **Polus, IfFound2** (it works good on iOS 9) **and iGotYa.** (Image 1 from the Imgur link located above)

So let's jump into the steps:

1-) Install the tweaks I mentioned above.

2-) Turn on Find My iPhone (if it is off) and turn on the last option (Image 2). This will help you a lot tracking your device you will know where it will be when the phone turns off due to battery. The option can be found in iCloud - Find My iPhone.

* 2A-) There is also an app that is like Find My iPhone and is better (although I recommend keeping Find My iPhone on as it will enable Activation Lock). The app was brought to my attention by /u/_SarahB_ . The app is called Cylay and it can be found on the ModMyi repo. The app features:

* sounding unstoppable alarms
* sending messages to your phone
* fake shutdown mode
* Take a picture front/rear cam
* Taking Screenshots from the website cylay.com
* Call history
* Erase ALL data
* reboot/shutdown
* LIVE streaming front/rear cam or audio alone

and more! I will definitely keep it. 

3-) Now let's setup **BioProtect** (or BioLockDown if you use that). With this tweak you can block access to apps with your fingerprint. The tweak also blocks someone from turning off the phone without a registered fingerprint so go ahead and turn that on (Image 3). The option is in **Settings - BioProtect - Power Off Protection** Now the device can't be turn off without your finger.

4-) Now let's setup **Polus**. I believe this is an important piece because anyone can make the device "untrackable" by turning on Airplane Mode, so let's avoid that. So I will go to **Settings - Polus - Top Shelf**. If you take a look at Image 4, I blocked access to Airplane Mode, Wi-Fi, Bluetooth (I did that so I can keep my watch connected and ring it from there just in case) and DND (this is also important) in the lockscreen. I had the option to disable the flipswitch or to hide it so I chose to hide it and it looks like this (Image 5). After unlocking the device, the switches will appear again.

5-) Now let's talk about **IfFound 2** (Image 6). As I said, this works on iOS 9 but you have to get it from another repo since the BigBoss one will not let you download it yet. This will put your info in the lockscreen so whoever has your phone can call a number you set so the device can go into your hands again.  Take a look at Image 7, it will talk by itself.

6-) The tweak I will talk about in this step is **iGotYa**. This tweak will help you identify whoever has your phone and the location of the phone. As you can see on Image 8, I have it set it up so the tweak sends me an email with the photo (taken from the front face camera) and the location of the phone. Apart from the email iGotYa sends, iGotYa also sends a SMS from your number to the number of your choice with the location of your phone. I recommend putting your iCloud email (if you don't use it as much) and turn off notifications for the email so the person wouldn't know the device is taking pictures of him/her.

7-) I want to add one more tweak that I will be using in combination with the other ones. I didn't about this tweak until it was presented to me by /u/lanouille974. This tweak is called PickPocket by our moderator /u/Ziph0n . The tweak will make your device activate a sound that will ring endlessly if the passcode is entered incorrectly. This also works for TouchID. It will also make the device ring endlessly if some tries to turn it off (a passcode is required to turn off the device, the password can be edited from PickPocket's settings). To stop it the sound, simply unlock your device. Please note that this is in an alpha state, but I believe this tweak is almost ready for a full release. The tweak can be found at http://repo.ziph0n.com/    Nice work on this one /u/Ziph0n !

I hope this tutorial helps you and if you have question or suggestions, don't hesistate to leave a comment. I take positive and negative feedbacks ;)

Also, if you take this tutorial and use it in your website, please **CREDIT ME**. Thank you! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> When it comes to stuttering, what names come up to your head? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-11-03 16:05:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I am doing a research paper on stuttering since this is a topic that really affects me. The assignment that I am doing now will be doing a "mock interview" of a person who studied/researched stuttering and is working to find a cure for it (sort of like a doctor or a professor). So I want to know if you guys know anyone who has done research and has a website where I could get his/her findings? 

Thanks in advance, I just don't know where to look. I've tried 'Googling' but I didn't get anything. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Bruno Mars is the artist to be presented at the Uncarrier X concert </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-11-03 15:29:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [Discussion] What are your favorite fonts? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-11-02 22:51:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Also, what's the repo for the fonts? It starts with a "d" but I don't remember the rest </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Another #Uncarrier move is coming according to John! </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-11-02 15:02:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Should I get PHP? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-11-02 05:54:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I got an iPhone 6S (JOD) about 12 days ago. I'm a little paranoid of losing my phone to a thief or lose it in the streets. Should I get PHP for my phone? What will it cover and how much do I have to pay for the deductible? Will it affects the JOD lease? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [Discussion] That annoying alert that says "Problem parsing dependecy" has a temporary fix </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-11-02 01:40:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [Help] I accidentally unistalled Substrate and all my tweaks got unistalled with it. However, Cydia is stuck in this screen. what should I do? hard reset and hope for it to boot up? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-11-02 00:24:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [Question] How do I reset all my tweak's settings? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-11-01 22:40:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I want to sort of start from scratch with them. Reinstalling them brings the settings back. Thanks in advance  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Just wanted to let you guys know, Apple will fix/replace your screen if and only if... </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-11-01 05:26:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hey guys, just wanted to let you guys know that Apple will change your screen for free if you meet the following conditions:

1. Your screen has only one harline crack. ONLY ONE. Maybe they will take two (if connected). If you have more than one try your luck.
2. The iDevice you have does NOT have a POINT OF IMPACT. Meaning, if it has a dent, Apple will know you dropped it and this will be counted as an accidental damage and you have to pay. 
3. You are still on warranty. This is important. If you are out of warranty you have to pay. 

My friend had his iPhone 6 screen replaced because he had a hairline crack. I went with him to the store and the repair was under my name (the device is my friend's but the repair was under my account) and everything was free. They took two hours to replace it though but it was worth it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Where do I check which band I'm connected to on my iPhone? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-11-01 00:36:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Title ^ </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [HELP] Siri is triggering herself when I press the home button to wake up the phone on my 6S </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-10-31 22:41:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hello jailbreakers,

I have a little issue. Siri is triggering herself when I press the home button to wake my iPhone 6S. I'm sure this happened after jailbreaking the phone. I'm sure she is not being triggered by someone saying "Hey Siri" because there is different behaviors when she starts depending on how you invoke her. I previously installed VirtualHome and I had the action to put my finger on the sensor for a short time to trigger her but I got rid of VirtualHome and it keeps happening. What should I do? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [Question] Something that is like iCaughtU that works for iOS 9? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-10-31 07:36:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Title  

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Did John just deny the Uncarrier "leaks"/rumors claiming that video streaming will not count against your data? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-10-29 20:18:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [Update] Pangu Untether 1.2 (from 1.1) Changelog inside </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-10-27 14:18:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [Discussion][Update] OneHandWizard is updated for iOS 9. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-10-26 15:38:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> John will send a message to one of the other carriers (AT T or Verizon). This is going to be fun  </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-10-26 14:01:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [Question] Can Activator turn on Wi-Fi and connect to a specific network (public one) when SIM card is ejected? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-10-24 01:15:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So I have always been scared of losing my phone or have it stolen. Things happen so I want to be ready for it. I already have tweaks for my iPhone 6S that will make it hard for a thief (or person who finds my phone) to make my device offline (so I can track it and get it back), like BioProtect, Polus, and etc. 

However, there is an effective solution to make my device unusuable, and that is ejecting my SIM card. So I want to know if Activator could make the phone connect to a specific Wi-Fi network  so it is still online on FMI. Is this possible? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [Discussion] What is the most complete theme out there? (That has UI change, icons, CC, etc) </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-10-23 17:33:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I have been looking around and I am getting a bit tired of Gunnii already. Any themes you guys use that's "complete"? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [Discussion] 3G Unrestrictor is updated for iOS 9! </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-10-23 15:12:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> This keeps happening even though I have good internet connection (I'm in an Apple Store, lol). Is this because I am jailbroken? Can an employee help me even though I am jailbroken? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-10-23 00:14:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [Discussion] Pangu9 installed WWDC on the phone to jailbreak, however after the JB was done both apps (Pangu and WWDC) were deleted from my phone and the WWDC stayed on my AW. Did this happen to anyone else? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-10-22 21:46:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [Discussion] Just a friendly reminder that iOS 9.1 patched jailbreak exploits, so if you are going to restore, grab the iOS 9.0.2 update from ipsw.me (linked). iTunes will force you to restore to iOS 9.1. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-10-22 02:18:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [Discussion] Just jailbroke my new i6S. Which tweaks you guys are using for this amazing device? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-10-22 00:13:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Title ^ 

Also, the iPhone 6S was lightning quick when Cydia was preparing the file systems. My iPhone 6 would take 1-2 mins in this and my iPhone 4 an eternity. Something wrong happened or is just that this thing is blazing fast?

EDIT: I don't understand, why am I being downvoted? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> T-Mo Sales Associate made a mistake even though I told him that I didn't want something. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-10-21 19:53:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So I went in to get an iPhone 6S, I told the associate that I would like my phone financed, via EIP. After he said "Okay" I paid and everything. Now I see that my phone is not through EIP but in JOD (something I didn't wanted so I can keep my device). I'm not sure this happened because my mom has an iPhone 6 through EIP. What gives?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What do I need to finance a phone on my line at a store? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-10-21 15:17:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I went into a store yesterday and my college ID wasn't valid, they said I needed a passport or a state ID. I don't have a state ID yet, and I have a passport, but is not a US passport. Will they take that or I will need something American based? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> I just won a Guitar Hero Live pack from John Legere! </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-10-20 20:05:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Planning on getting a phone since my i6 damaged. Which way should I go? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-10-20 18:04:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I have an iPhone 6 16GBs that has water damage. Now I am debating whether I upgrade to the 6s or get an i6 64GBs. What do you think I should do? If I get the 6S it will be 16GBs. What can I do with the iPhone 6 that damaged? Sell it by parts? (Everything is fine with it, is just that the Motherboard is fried. Screen, button, everything else is working like it should) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [Release] Pangu9 Mac version, app made by me. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-10-20 15:11:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [Discussion] Steps to take so you can avoid the BLoD. Found this on RedmondPie </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-10-18 06:35:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Any way to change the sounds of the watch? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-10-16 18:42:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I really hate the messages notification sound on the watch. It sounds like I have a portable oven/microwave that tells me when the food is heated up and I hate that. The other notification sounds are good, but I want to change the Messages one. How can I do this? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [Discussion] After Karen's post about Pangu9, I want to make a mega-thread of tweaks that causes your device to reboot upon installation. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-10-16 00:39:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> As Karen stated here: https://www.reddit.com/r/jailbreak/comments/3owd3h/discussion_stability_of_pangus_ios_90x_untether/  your device could get the "BLoD" when you reboot it, so if you are jailbroken, try to avoid tweaks that makes you reboot. Also try to avoid "soft resetting" your device (Home+Power) until all of this is sorted out.

As far as I know, *Winterboard* forces to Reboot in order to complete its install. Any more tweaks you guys know about that forces you to reboot when installing or changing its setting? 

When I find more tweaks I will edit the post (or comment on the post) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> iPhone 6 error 53 </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-10-14 20:16:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> When restoring my phone, I got this error. I googled it and I found out that this is due to me changing the touch ID button/sensor, but I didn't. Now my phone is useless, what can I do in this case? Phone is still on warranty </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> How can Apple do this? They upgraded the BT chip with iOS 9? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-10-09 23:02:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Any way to fix this little scratch in the screen? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-10-07 22:40:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Possible way to downgrade AW as told by an Apple Rep. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-10-05 00:52:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So I sent my iOS 9 iPhone for service and I got an iOS 8.3 one as a return, so I jailbroke it and my watch was on Watch OS 2. So I figured that I could talk to Apple so they can downgrade my watch (as I have read here and other websites). The chat rep I talked to, wouldn't let me send my watch for service so what he said is that to downgrade I should have a backup of Watch OS 1, which will downgrade the watch when I restore the backup.

Would that work? I know it doesn't work on iDevices (as the backup will restore on the version you are in, it won't downgrade it) but in the AW could be different. Could somebody try this? 

PS: I can't try it, I don't have a Watch OS 1 backup, and my Watch is now taking dust (I won't give up jailbreak, I rely on it)

Is there any other way to downgrade the watch? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Siri's birthday is today! (Oct. 4) </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-10-04 06:39:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [Discussion][News] So an Apple Watch jailbreak was possible based off this. Credits go to Taig and Pangu for finding this exploit. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-09-28 02:36:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Watch OS 2 seems to be released! </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-09-21 19:00:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> 4G LTE Booster </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-09-21 18:19:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I got one of those at my apartment because I usally get 1-2 bars of LTE on my home and my phone always switch to 4G due to the lack of LTE signal. However, on 4G, my data won't work at all. Music won't load or will load at 2G speeds as well as websites. After installing the booster I still get 1-2 bars of LTE on my iPhone 6. What gives? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Sleep Tracker </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-09-20 02:00:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What app do you guys use to track your sleep? 

I have used Lark on the phone to track my sleep (which it does a great job) however Lark on the Apple Watch doesn't do that (as far as I know).  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> AppleCare+ </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-09-18 23:20:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What is the timeframe to buy Apple Care+? I bought a 2month old watch from Swappa, and it doesn't have AppleCare+. Also, can Apple exchange my AW to a black one from Silver?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [NYC-USA] Anyone willing to trade this for a black Apple Watch 42MM? This is the 42MM </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-09-18 01:02:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [Discussion] Apple fixes yet one more jailbreak exploit. Credits awarded to Pangu and Taig </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-09-17 01:49:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> How's performance on Watch OS2? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-09-10 23:55:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I noticed how on WatchOS 1 the watch will lag here and then and stutter on some animations. 

Has this been improved in WatchOS 2? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [Question] Is it possible to replace Siri by Cortana when Cortana is released on iOS? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-08-19 05:03:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hello, I have a question. So I have seen in the past that it was possible to invoke Google Now when the home button is pressed for about 2 seconds, replacing Siri. Will this be possible so Cortana is fully accessible when pressing the home button for about 2 seconds? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
