<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject5873</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-17 16:27:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I have posted an update that is linked at the bottom of this </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-17 15:55:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Shelby GT500 - Eleanor </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Never buy a mattress off of Craigslist - 2 </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-17 15:50:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [Part 1](https://www.reddit.com/r/nosleep/comments/5uf78g/never_buy_a_mattress_off_of_craigslist/) \ [Related](https://www.reddit.com/r/nosleep/comments/5v4wrk/ill_never_go_downtown_again/)

I added this to the first post but Ill put it here as well. It is the note and picture  the only thing I have that the police didnt take [proof](http://imgur.com/u4iBUyk)

So like I said in my first post I unblocked Brians number and tried to get in touch with him again but it said it was disconnected. Of course I gave the number to the police to try and track but I have yet to hear any news from them, which is incredibly discouraging. They say you only have 48 hours to find a missing person and I am approaching that number very quickly. I cant I just cant lose my family. My wife is the sweetest, most loving and wonderful mother to our beautiful, vibrant daughter. I remember when she was born and  sorry. I have been thinking a lot about that night. I guess it is the only thing pushing me on. *I have to find my family!*

One of the comments mentioned checking my car for a tracking device. Dont know why I didnt think of it before so I went out last night before I went to work and after a few minutes of checking I did find something under the rear bumper, on my exhaust pipe. I dont know if it is a tracking device or what but I turned it in to the police on my way to work. Why didnt they think to check my car? Anyway I didnt really feel like working much. I was distracted and exhausted. My boss told me to take a few nights off, paid, to clear my head. I couldnt believe it, not because it is out of the ordinary but he is just a hardass most of the time I didnt think he had a soft spot on him. I took full advantage of it by heading back up to the storage site to see if I could find anything. 

Like I mentioned in my first post I work two jobs, one being warehouse stocking overnight and during the day I work for a home security company called Vivint installing and servicing home systems. One of the neat things we offer is a camera that you can access from anywhere in the world and watch a live stream. Most people use it as a nanny cam or to see what their pets do while they are gone but I had a great idea. Id set one up on the roof and then I could watch it from my work laptop to see if anyone is moving mattresses around. If I could get a visual on the guy we could catch him! So I headed up to the site and climbed up the backside of one of the buildings that had the humidity controlled units.

According to the receptionist they only have 24 of these units and since they are selling a ton of mattresses I figured that is a unit they would need to have. There were cameras all over the place so I couldnt get a perfect angle or see the whole row of units but I was able to place it in such a way that I could see about two thirds of them. Not ideal but better than nothing. The camera is tiny so I wasnt worried about anyone finding it and I know it can run for over 6 months on a fresh battery. 

Since I dont have anywhere to sleep at home I decided Id just recline the seat in my car and try to snooze a little while keeping an eye on the footage. Now I know a lot of you are probably thinking There is no way Brian is ever coming back to that place. And while I agree with you, what else can I do? I have to have hope, to believe they are still alive and unhurt. It is the only thing keeping me going. I am sure you can understand that. 

I must have actually fallen asleep because a train horn startled me and I jerked up, knocking the laptop off of my lap. The train was moving pretty slowly, even slower than most around here and there was a van and a few cars waiting at the crossing. It took a moment to remember where I was and rub the sleep out of my eyes. It was 3AM. I rewound the footage in triple speed to see if anyone had shown up during the hour and a half that I was laying there and only twenty minutes before a 15-passenger van showed up just inside the frame of the camera. It was hard to tell but I am pretty sure it was the receptionist that was there the day we came to buy the mattress. Two guys were hauling mattresses out of the back of the van and into one of the units. I started to get excited. I had him. I found him! Then I got sick to my stomach. From inside of the unit came five women, most of them older but one was pretty young. I couldnt see their faces because of the distance from the camera but I could see that they were chained together and gagged with something. One of the guys gave something to the receptionist lady, most likely money, and they piled into the van and drove off. 

Wait, I thought, didnt I just see a van? I looked up and the train was gone, the cars that were waiting now far off in the distance. I turned on my car and took off after the fading tail-lights, praying Id be able to catch up and hope they hadnt already turned off somewhere. I grabbed my phone and called the police, telling them everything that transpired and where I was/direction I was heading. They told me to pull over and to stop following but screw that - I floored it even more and tried to close the distance. 

Pretty soon I heard sirens from several different directions but I had lost sight of the van, or maybe never had sight of it. When I finally caught up to the taillights I was chasing they belonged to a Corolla or something. About that time my phone went off. It was the police, they had found the van! I drove my way over, only a few blocks east of where I was, hoping for good news. 

When I got there they had two men in cuffs in the back of a squad car which left soon after. Five women were laying on gurneys being tended to by medical staff, but none were my wife or daughter. I was relieved, happy, thankful that they were safe, but also devastated. Where was my family? After interrogation or whatever of the men and the women that were saved it was determined that they would have been sold as slaves  human trafficking. The police are still looking for my family, of course, but they arent acting very positive about the whole thing. 

I just left my day job because my boss caught me still watching footage of the unit and told me to just go home. I know it sounds stupid but what else can I do? I cant eat or sleep or even think without feeling the need to vomit. My family, slaves. Sold to some freak that will do God knows what to them? My eleven month old daughter. So beautiful, so innocent. Daddy is going to find you!

----------------

**UPDATE**

So far no one has come back to that unit other than police. I watched them drag everything out, sick to my stomach. I watched their cars drive off full of evidence. Everyone seems to have vanished that was connected to this aside from the two guys that were arrested. They havent given up any information from what the station is telling me. I dont know why but I started to browse Craigslist again to see if any new ads were put up similar to the one I had responded to. I didnt find anything but I did remember a few stories Id heard about the Deep Web/Dark Web and how human trafficking goes down on those sites. 

I dove head first into that awful area of cyberspace trying to find anything that could help me find my family. The things I found only made me that much sicker and more worried about my family. Who could do such things to fellow human beings? I know we are in a sick, confused world but oh  I will just stop there. I dont want to upset anyone by the things I saw. After an hour of searching I was about to give up when I found something hosted by BMK. I had seen it before and passed it by but looking at it again jogged my memory. The only reason it stood out to me at all is because of the CL ad. Brian had called himself the Mattress King. It is a pretty standard claim, to be fair, but I didnt think I could pass up an opportunity even if it wasnt him. 

I responded to it with an old e-mail I hadnt used since probably high school and got a response almost immediately. $5000 cash for a female. $4000 for a male. Discounts for age. An address to meet at and a time.

When I plugged the address in I was surprised to see how close it was to the storage facility. One of your comments was right, they kept operations close. Obviously I dont have the cash but I have a gun. What mid-westerner doesnt? I am on my way right now. I dont want to be late.

----------

**FINAL UPDATE**

So as I said I like being early and I figured my old pal Brian would be late to this arrangement. I got there an hour ahead of time to scope out the place and find a good spot to take him out. 

I found a nice loft where I could overlook the big, open factory floor. I parked my car a ways away at a thrift store parking lot and walked to it with a guitar case - hiding my .22. I guessed they would probably have a few people out front waiting for me to come in and Brian inside with the lineup of women. Fortunately I guessed correctly. 

A total of six armed people showed up, four taking position somewhere outside. Brian and the receptionist stood inside with twenty women. My heart skipped a beat when I saw my wife among them. I almost cried out right then and there but I stifled it in time. 

I took careful aim and busted Brian's knee with the first shot. I'm assuming he went into shock because he dropped and laid there moaning for the entirety of my visit. My next shot took out the receptionist as she ran. 

The girls started screaming right away, obviously not knowing what was going on. A guy from outside came in but I was already back outside on my way down. I have never been happier than right then about my grandad forcing me to go hunting every year and "earn my dinner". It was paying off! It was then that I called the police. 

I waited until sirens were nearing before I shot the next two guards in the leg. Suffer for your sins. I made my way inside and used one of the guards handguns to finish Brian and the other guy with him after I let him see my face. I don't think my wife even noticed me until I put my hand on her face. 

I'm not sure where the last one ran off to but he didn't bother us as I unlocked the women and hugged my wife. *Where's my baby? Is she ok?*

She just shook her head. We cried, oblivious to the police filtering in.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-17 04:24:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thank you so much for your kind words. People like you are the only thing helping me thru this right now. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-17 04:23:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Just be thankful it DIDN'T happen to you. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-17 04:21:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Uh Ya sorry. It's fixed. I'm a bit out of it at the moment.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-17 02:21:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Not yet :( </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-17 01:36:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The police didn't find anything inside of it, thank God.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-17 00:07:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Good thing it isn't Brian... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-17 00:05:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Ya sorry, thanks.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-16 22:01:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Another Beta user? Don't do it, just don't. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-16 20:44:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You must have me confused with someone else. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-16 20:37:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You have to understand that when you have a baby you can't just wait around forever. It was time for her to eat and she needed to be home. Sometimes you have to drop whatever it is you are doing to accommodate them and yea it can be a bit of an inconvenience but they can't help it.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-16 20:16:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> One of the most beautiful stories I have ever read on here. Thank you for sharing you and your grandmother's story with us. I hope I hear a fllm score by you one day. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-16 19:55:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> As a father I know that had to be impossibly hard to make. I understand why you made it, and I can't condemn you for it. I would have done the same thing.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-16 19:28:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The police took the mattress for evidence so if they find something I am sure they'll let me know.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-16 19:22:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What does that mean? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-16 18:27:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It was new, not used, and it is all I could afford. I never wanted to be in this type of financial position but life happens and sometimes things get tough. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-16 17:49:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I thought of that as well but I've been in contact with my carrier to see if she made any calls or texts that day and none were to or from anyone other than contacts. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-16 17:47:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Can't wait to hear more from you. You write well for a "redneck stripper".  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-16 17:37:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Ah yes, I must have glazed over that detail. Thanks for pointing it out! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-16 17:35:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> My man. Stick to the horrible people of the world. There a lot more of them than you think. Don't become one yourself. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-16 16:43:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What amazes me is that if it was such an obvious camera for you to spot in one day how did no one else notice it? Either way, glad you were able to catch the creep and put a stop to his invasion of peoples privacy. I'll keep my eyes peeled for these bears. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-16 16:19:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> No the only information he had was my phone number, not even my last name. I am unsure of how he found out where we live but Google doesn't even bring up our current address.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Never buy a mattress off of Craigslist </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-16 15:21:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> My wife and I have had the same mattress since we have been married. It is lumpy, dips horribly in the middle, and isnt large enough now that our daughter sleeps on it with us. I know, thats dangerous and not recommended at all. But when you go six straight months without more than an hour of sleep at a time you eventually cave in. With that being said I am always on the look-out for a good deal on a king size mattress and yesterday I found one. $125 for a *new set*, and not a cheap one either. Incredible, right? I thought so too so I called the guy up and asked if it was still available (you know how sometimes they advertise something really cheap because it doesnt exist). To my surprise it was so I set up for my wife and daughter to go out and take a look at 5PM. I would have rather just gone myself instead of dragging my cranky daughter all the way into Downtown but my wife is pretty particular about the firmness of the mattress so I had to make sure it was comfortable for her. 

Brian, the guy selling the mattress, said to call when we were on our way so he would know when to meet us at the storage site. I called but it went to voicemail so I left one and also texted him to let him know we are on our way. The whole drive there my wife and I are chatting happily about how great it will be to finally have a new mattress and have our own space in the bed once again. My daughter likes to sleep at a bit of a diagonal so that her hands are touching mommies shoulder and her feet are touching my leg. It is very sweet and cute but also incredibly uncomfortable because I have to sleep on the knifes edge of the bed in order to not crush anyone (dads out there I am sure you can relate). Fortunately the traffic isnt too bad yet so we make it right on time. I HATE being late to appointments. It is just so unprofessional and inconsiderate, you know?

I get out of the car and unstrap my daughter so that she can enjoy the cool breeze and point to all the new things she sees while we wait for Brian to arrive. After about fifteen minutes I walk into the office of the storage facility and ask to see if Brian maybe works there or if the receptionist knows anything about him. She told me that he works for a home staging company for when people try to sell their homes. That is why we can buy the mattress so cheap! It is unpackaged and set up so they cant resell it in a store. She assured me he was a great guy and was probably just running late due to traffic. I was glad I talked to her because I was still having a few doubts about why the mattress was such a good deal but his line of work made a lot of sense. My daughter and I walked around some more, singing songs and feeling the brick wall of the building and the nylon threads of the American flag swaying in the breeze. She is a very happy, sweet girl and loves to feel new things so I didnt notice how much time had passed until my wife popped out of the car and asked what was going on. Forty minutes had passed! This guy was ridiculously late. I handed off my daughter so that I could call him up and see what the deal was. 

*This is Brian.*

*Yea, hi, this is Steven. We had a 5PM meeting to look at a mattress. Where are you at, bud?*

*Oh yea ok I am thirty minutes away, Ill be there soon.*

Now as you know I hate being late. I also hate when others are late. *Seriously? It is 5:35PM and we agreed to 5PM, Brian. Dont bother, we are leaving.*

*I told you to call me when you were leaving so that I knew you were coming, this is the first time you are calling me so now I am coming.*

WHAT?!

*Look, Brian. I called you when we left our house and I left you a voicemail. I texted you to let you know we were on the highway. We agreed to 5PM and you stood us up. I dragged my daughter and wife out here for no reason and now we have to fight traffic to get back home. Thank you for wasting our time.*

I hung up before he could get another word in. I was furious. Who sets a time to meet but then doesnt show up until the person calls? Clearly this guy wasnt a real businessman. He called me right back but I ignored it. We needed dinner and showers, we had routines to follow or this baby was going to be up all night. He texted me right after trying to justify his reasoning, telling me I was foolish for not wanting to wait around to save so much money on a $1000 mattress. Obviously this guy didnt have kids. I added his number to my spam list so that I wouldnt get any more calls or texts from him and apologized to my wife for wasting our evening. I work two jobs to make enough for the bills and we dont have much time together as a family. I feel like a bit of a failure but my wife always reassures me, thanking me for working so hard. Still, I cant shake the sadness I feel when I come home late and barely get to spend any time with them so I was extra frustrated with Brian for wasting one of my only free evenings.

Of course traffic was awful heading back out of downtown and there were two car accidents because why not add insult to injury? My daughter was starting to get fussy so I was singing all her favorite songs and making silly faces to keep her occupied. It took over an hour to get home but once we hit the driveway everything was forgotten and we all smiled. Home at last! We went through our normal routine of dinner and bath time and instead of turning on the television I just played with my daughter until she was ready for bed. It was a nice change of pace. I cant believe how big she is getting! 

------------------------

The alarm went off far too early for my liking but I got up and did my best to crawl out of the dip in the bed without arousing anyone else. Got dressed, packed a lunch, ate a quick breakfast and I was off to work. The day was pretty uneventful which was nice because I couldnt keep my eyes open easily. Normally I get a few calls from my wife during the day and at least one picture showing our daughter doing something silly or new but I didnt get any of that today. I knew they had a few plans to go to the petting zoo and story time at the library so I didnt think much of it although I did miss my daily picture. Wednesday is always a special day because it food pantry day (at first we were just embarrassed but we try to make the best of it by guessing what dessert they will give us)! The generosity of people in our area is so amazing. They donate all organic foods, even organic meat. I usually make it home before my wife is done at the pantry so I tidy up the house and get ready to go out and grab all of the bags full of food. 

I kicked off my work boots and put my lunch bag away, cleaning up a few dishes in the sink and washing down my daughters high-chair tray. As I headed into the bedroom to change into more comfortable clothes I stopped dead in my tracks. There, in place of our small, lumpy bed was the king sized mattress on a simple bedframe. It even had sheets on it, nice ones. A few tears gathered at eat eye because I realized why my wife never called me today. She was busy surprising me with a new bed! She must have found Brians ad on Craigslist and went up to meet him on her own while I was at work. What a wonderful woman she is! On the bed was a small, white card. I rushed over to it, flopping onto the bed and taking the card in my hand to read.

Dear Steven,

I hope you like the mattress. Dont worry about payment, I already took what I needed.


-Brian

What the hell?! I sprang up off of the bed and went to my phone, calling my wife. No answer. No problem, she is probably wrapping up at the food pantry or driving home. She never answers when she is driving. 

I waited fifteen more minutes before calling again. She is never this late from coming home. 4:15 at the latest and it was already 4:30. I called again, straight to voicemail. I tried not to panic, tried to let my imagination run wild but I couldnt help it. Was she in an accident? Is she stuck in traffic? Please answer! After another twenty minutes and no response from her I drove over to the food pantry and found the managing volunteer just before they closed up for the night. 

*Hey Terry, was my wife here today?*

*Oh, hi Steven, no she never came today. I was a bit surprised myself but I thought maybe you finally found a better job and didnt need to come anymore.*

I drove home much faster than the law or safety would dictate praying that her car would be in the driveway, but it wasn't. I tried calling one more time with no luck. Sprinting around the house I searched for anything strange or missing. That is when I noticed the picture frame on our nightstand. The picture was torn down one side, leaving just me.

Tears started flowing down my face, coating my phone as I dialed 9-1-1.


-------------------

**Just a quick update/answer of various questions from the comments:**


First, thank you all for your concern. The local police and I are doing everything we can to try and locate my family. I will let you know as soon as I hear anything positive or negative regarding the case.

Secondly, I understand that CL can be shady. I have dealt many times with buying and selling without ever having an issue for many years. Please understand I am in a difficult financial position right now which is why I even looked around for a mattress on CL. We go to a food pantry every week, so yes times are tough. I can only do what I can do. 

So far we are unsure of how Brian found our home or got in. There was no signs of a forced entry and no record of anyone calling or texting my wife/her calling or texting anyone over the course of the day outside of actual contacts saved to her phone. She received no e-mails either. Our neighbors did not notice a moving truck or anything similar come by during the day but obviously something had to have come by. Still no idea about that either.

-----------------

**UPDATE 2**

The police have put out my wife and daughters picture to try and get the word out. I went up to the storage facility to try and talk to the receptionist but it was a new woman today. She looked up storage units owned by a Brian and there was not a single unit. Can you believe that? Over 1400 units and not a single Brian. I mean, it's a common name! I feel like something is getting covered up so I'm coming back later to snoop around on my own.

I also unblocked the number and tried to call but all I get is a disconnected number message. The police are trying to track it to a house or business but they aren't telling me much, which worries me more than anything else. 

Oh and since so many have mentioned my family being in the mattress: the police took the mattress as evidence. They checked it inside and out for clues. They are *not* inside it. 

For those asking for some proof, since the police took most of it I only had a chance to snap a pic of the note and torn [picture](http://imgur.com/u4iBUyk)

[Part 2](https://www.reddit.com/r/nosleep/comments/5umhqn/never_buy_a_mattress_off_of_craigslist_2/) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-16 04:10:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What a fascinating ability! Have you ever tried to learn more such as when or how? I certainly hope you can figure out how to stop your daughter from launching a nuke or whatever it is she does in the future. I sure hope my daughter is a zero :/ </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-16 03:27:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Well he did ask for it. I can't let him down, can I? That would be quite rude of me. 

- Dr. Zero  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-16 02:39:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> General Talbot was the man we encountered and killed when we first went into Site 2. He was way in over his head trying to get in good with Dr. Feldman. Lot of good it did him, eh? 

- Dr. Zero  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-16 02:23:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You could think of it that way, sure. Or part 12 of the Experiments series. Either way I hope you like my *work*.

- Dr. Zero  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-16 00:47:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> RUN!  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-15 23:15:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Well now that I have eternity at my disposal I'm sure I'll find something to do. 

- Dr. Zero </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-15 22:07:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Human 1 is Patient Zero.

Human 2 is Patient 314.

Human 3 is General Talbot.

Human 4 is Dr. Feldman.

Hopefully this clarifies. I'd hate to be confused as Dr. Feldman. 

- Dr. Zero </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-15 21:39:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> My dear, sweet friend. Please don't run. I just have a few questions for you.

- Dr. Zero </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Patient 314 - Final </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-15 15:16:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> **Chapter 1** | [1](https://www.reddit.com/r/nosleep/comments/5ppwqe/you_must_die_in_order_to_live/) | [2]( https://www.reddit.com/r/nosleep/comments/5px61m/helpers/) | [3]( https://www.reddit.com/r/nosleep/comments/5rvtzd/my_doctor_is_the_cure/) | [4]( https://www.reddit.com/r/nosleep/comments/5sgofu/patient_314/) | [5]( https://www.reddit.com/r/nosleep/comments/5snx09/patient_314_day_2/) | [6]( https://www.reddit.com/r/nosleep/comments/5svb9k/patient_314_day_3/) | [7]( https://www.reddit.com/r/nosleep/comments/5t2ncl/patient_314_day_4/) | [8]( https://www.reddit.com/r/nosleep/comments/5t9rkp/patient_314_day_5/) | [9]( https://www.reddit.com/r/nosleep/comments/5thx2n/patient_313/) | [10]( https://www.reddit.com/r/nosleep/comments/5tsyl6/patient_zero/) | [11]( https://www.reddit.com/r/nosleep/comments/5u0d4q/site_2/) | [12]( https://www.reddit.com/r/nosleep/comments/5u7lf7/patient_314_final/)

**Chapter 2** | [13](https://www.reddit.com/r/nosleep/comments/5u9s1m/hide_seek_with_dr_feldman/) | [14](https://www.reddit.com/r/nosleep/comments/5vt6ud/patient_zero_origins/) | [15](https://www.reddit.com/r/nosleep/comments/5w0734/thanksgiving_with_dr_feldman/) | [16](https://www.reddit.com/r/nosleep/comments/5wotm6/patient_11/) | [17](https://www.reddit.com/r/nosleep/comments/5x4373/patient_98_the_surgeon/) | [18](https://www.reddit.com/r/nosleep/comments/5y1fk7/patient_314_has_a_name/) | [19](https://www.reddit.com/r/nosleep/comments/5yhiy6/patient_314_has_a_name_part_2/)

-----------

Site 2 Test Facility

Dr. Feldman

*2/12/2017  8:44PM*

Dr. Feldman personal entry  logging

The look on Patient 314s face when his ability didnt work on me. There is no greater rush than power. I was unsure if the neural disruptor would work considering our tests were cut so short at Site 1 but very pleased with the outcome. I felt a tug somewhere in my neck but only briefly. It is possible that 314 didnt have enough strength to overcome the device. More testing will determine the true extent of the device. Tomorrow begins a new chapter in his testing. 

-------------------

*2/13/2017  6:15AM*

Experiment one  logging...

Breakfast delivered.

**Dr.** - Good morning, Patient 314. I very much look forward to working with you. For the next few days we are going to focus on that beautiful brain of yours. Youll be given Faceless to kill as you please in order to keep your strength up however your tests will not involve killing. Are you familiar with Star Wars, 314?

**314** - The movies or the government projects? [Eats slowly, deliberately, warily]

**Dr.** - The movies.  [314 nods] Good. The Jedi have certain abilities they like to use to get their way. In a similar fashion you should be able to as well. With practice and careful tutelage, of course. When you are done eating I will ask you to take a seat in the chair. Once in the chair a cerebral cap will lower down and fit over your head. Dont be alarmed by it  it is only there to help map your brain activity.

Three Faceless enter the room, one holding a chair. 

**Dr.** - You may kill two of them in whatever manner you choose. The third will subject itself to your directions. These directions must be spoken internally only. Understood?

314 finishes his last forkful of hashbrowns and nods slowly. Setting the plate down he moves slowly to the first Faceless, snapping its neck. The second is dispatched similarly. Once in the chair and the cerebral cap strapped on he looks to the Observation window. Readings are taken, compared, logged.

**Dr.** - Good. Now give it a command to do something out of the ordinary.

Patient 314 turns back to the remaining Faceless. The cerebral cap begins reading his internal monologue. 

*I dont want to do this. I cant help this man. How can I get out of this? I should play along for a while, come up with a plan. How? He killed Zero. Im alone. Alone. Ive always been alone. I figured this disease out on my own. I can do this. Focus.*

314 looks up, into the blank stare of the Faceless. 

*If I can control this I can get to Feldman. I can kill him. Hurt him. Make him suffer. Why couldnt I kill him earlier? Was I too weak? Focus. Focus.*

The Faceless seems to contort slightly, pinching and pulling of the skin where its mouth should be. A thin crease forms in what looks to be a smile.

**Dr.** - Oh most excellent. A smile on a Faceless! You are more twisted than I am, 314. You may kill it now.

The Faceless crumples as if no bones were present in its body. Readings taken, compared, logged.

Experiment one complete.

----------------

*2/13/2017  9:20PM*

Dr. Feldman personal entry  logging

The speed in which Patient 314 learns and performs is astonishing. I wouldnt believe it unless I saw it with my own two eyes. It helped to be able to hear his thought process  such focus! A lifetime of isolation and suffering honed his resolve far beyond anything I have seen in previous Patients. 314 has shown considerable command over mental coercion in the first three experiments. In addition, several gaps in my understanding of his ability have been filled. After review of the data collected by the cerebral cap I now have pinpointed several neural paths that only his brain seems to take. Tomorrow we will attempt to perfect mental coercion and begin reading minds. If I am correct that will give me enough data to complete mapping his neural paths and design an algorithm to match it. 

------------------

*2/14/2017  6:15AM*

Experiment four  logging

Breakfast delivered.

**Dr.** - Good morning, 314. Please have a seat in the chair once again and we may begin. 

314 sits and eats, the cap descending down onto his head as the last bite is swallowed.

**Dr.** - You progressed very well yesterday, so well in fact, that I think you are ready to begin pulling from their minds instead of pushing into their minds. Try to ascertain what the Faceless are thinking. I have programmed them to think of several things, each one for twenty seconds before thinking of the next. 

A Faceless walks in with a chair and sits three feet from Patient 314. The blank stare gives nothing away. 

*What are you thinking? What stupid, pointless thought does he have flashing across your brain right now? Focus. Where did I push thoughts yesterday? Yes, ok. What are they saying? Focus! How can you read the mind of a doctor if you cant read the mind of a blank-faced zombie? FOCUS! Animal. Four-legs. White? Wooden. Paint. I must have run out of time, new thought.

**314** - The first was an animal, maybe a white shaggy dog.

*Brass. Its large. Focus! Hinges.*

**314** - A door.

*Fast. Powerful. Click-click-clack. What is that? A sound? A game? Typing!*

**314** - A computer.

**Dr.** - Good, keep going.

*Red. Short. Heat. Inferno. Water. Dog. This makes no sense what is this? Focus! Metal dome. A siren.*

**314** - A fire hydrant.

**Dr.** - An excellent first attempt, 314. Of course people dont think at such a slow rate under normal conditions so the next test will be 10 seconds per thought and each thought will be more involved. Now Id like you to push a thought into the Faceless head so that it kills itself.

314 looks from the Dr. to the Faceless. *Stop breathing* The gentle rise and fall of its chest ceases. A tremor slowly builds in its body, muscles give out from a lack of oxygen. The Faceless drops in a heap to the floor, the last thought still lingering in its mind long after. 

---------------

*2/14/2017  11:12PM*

Dr. Feldman personal entry  logging

The mapping is complete. By the end of the day Patient 314 was able to successfully determine 90% of thoughts at one second intervals. Even with this accelerated testing he never seemed to wear down. Of course, more testing would be preferable but my timetable has changed. With a complete neural map I should be able to stop both incoming and outgoing information from my brain with the disruptor. Tomorrow Ill put it to the test, as well as testing whether or not I can duplicate his ability. 

-----------------

*2/15/2017  6:15AM*

Dr. Feldman opens the door to Observation Room 1 and closes it behind him. Patient 314 watches warily from his cot as the doctor sits down in the chair he has grown to hate as much as the cell.

**Dr.** - Good morning, Patient 314. I apologize for a lack of breakfast this morning but I did not see much point in it. Today is a big day for us. Id like for you to try and read my thoughts.

A moment passes before 314 grimaces in pain.

**314** - I cant.

**Dr.** - I see. If you would please, push a thought into my mind. Tell me to hurt myself in some way.

Another moment goes by. Sweat forms on 314s brow and pain flashes across his visage.

**Dr.** - Good, the device is working. You see, by watching and mapping how your brain works when you push and pull thoughts I was able to create a means of breaking that connection.  I was fairly certain the device would work but the real test is right now.

**314** - Oh? And that is what exac

314 can no longer move. Fear fills his eyes like a spooked doe in the open field. Dr. Feldman stands up slowly and walks up to 314, placing his hands on each side of the teenagers head. Memories, thoughts and ideas, the very structure of Patient 314 flows into the man that looked like Dr. Feldman. 

Patient Zero lets go of his head and steps back, the body tipping back lifelessly. He stares at the body he now mimics and smiles as a Faceless walks into the room.

**Zero** - Ah, just in time. Dispose of the boy. I have a [plane to catch.](https://www.reddit.com/r/nosleep/comments/5u9s1m/hide_seek_with_dr_feldman/) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-15 13:46:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Zero - Because with you he could unlock the secret to escaping death. While I absorbed information you absorbed life! If he could harness that and manipulate it in the right way it would enable everlasting life. Not to mention the nifty tricks you can do with your mind. He hit the jackpot when he found you and your mother.

This is from the previous update when Patient Zero and 314 are talking. 

- Dr. Feldman </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-15 13:46:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Mindless drones don't enjoy sex. It is just another action to perform. It would feel the same to him as brushing teeth or doing laundry.

- Dr. Feldman </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-15 09:01:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> He killed four with his hands and two with his mind. I just glossed over the unimportant part.

- Dr. Feldman  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-15 03:40:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Make sure you read the stories BEFORE even downloading the app. Please trust me.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-15 01:20:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Just read the dad's tapes because of the new post. I'll look into the others </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-15 01:19:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'll check it out!  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-15 01:19:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'll have to find those. I've heard others talk about borrasca </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-15 01:18:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Those ones are incredible </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-14 22:39:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That's cute.

- Dr. Feldman  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-14 20:49:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You shall be Patient 315. Thank you for volunteering for the cause. I shall send for you once I am done with 314. Fair enough?

- Dr. Feldman </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-14 20:31:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Some things in life are simple pleasures. And pleasure is very much worth the trouble.

- Dr. Feldman </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-14 20:01:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I suppose that would be possible, however very time consuming. Do you have any idea how much information is on the internet? Not only that but the amount of contradictory information. It would take a lifetime to upload it all, process it properly, and then Patient Zero would be dead before it could apply anything.

- Dr. Feldman </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-14 19:17:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Now, now, no need for such things. I may just find an ability in you that strikes my fancy.

- Dr. Feldman </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-14 19:16:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Are you Donald Trump? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-14 19:06:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Are you an orphan or extremely obese? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-14 18:49:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I do see myself as something of a hero. Thank you kind person.

- Dr. Feldman </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-14 17:43:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Dang. Alien babies up in that belly. I sure hope they don't eat their way out.. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Site 2 </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-14 15:05:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [Previous](https://www.reddit.com/r/nosleep/comments/5tsyl6/patient_zero/)

*2/12/2017  3:17AM*

Zeros personal log - 

Patient 314 is sleeping. I have reviewed all of the mental memory from Feldman  we are just under eight hours away from Site 2. According to the Phase 3 time table we should make it there before they are in full swing. These fuckers are quick. Task forces are already being reassigned to the new site and the data dump that Feldman did is being uploaded. Until that is complete they wont have any real security features online that can contain us once we are in. My hope is that we can get there before the upload is complete. 

-----------------

*2/12/2017  6:42AM*

Patient 314 awakens.

**Zero** - Eat this, you will need your strength.

**314** - Thanks. So what is the plan? Why do you even need me if you have all of Feldmans memory? 

314 begins eating. 

**Zero** - Having all of the knowledge, schematics, access codes, those are all important. But you are the weapon. I know *about* the abilities of the other Patients but I cant **do** them. Feldman didnt get very far with your mom or you on *how* you do what you do which means I cant do what you do either. What I did know is that I couldnt trust any of the remaining Patients to help me do this except for you. 

**314** - Wait, what do you mean get far with my mom? He took my mom? 

**Zero** - Your mother was Patient 313. She had the same mental ability you have. That is how he even knew about you in the first place. 

**314** - So... that wasnt a clone, was it? [Zero shakes his head] I killed my mom

**Zero** - Im very sorry. But that is how I knew youd help me stop this bastard. 

314 buries his head in his hands, entire body heaving with silent sobs. I put a hand on his shoulder before walking away towards the other end of the train car.

----------------

*2/12/2017  7:09AM*

314 looks up, eyes bright red and puffy. 

**314** - Whats the plan?

I smile.

------------------

*2/12/2017  11:10AM*

The train glides to a stop inside of what looks to be an abandoned warehouse. 314 and I exit the train and are greeted with nothing but a metal staircase leading down. 

**Zero** - Alright, follow me. If we cross paths with anyone let me do the talking.

314 nods and we begin the descent downward, feet echoing loudly in the narrow stairwell. After ten flights we arrive at the concrete landing. I approach the large steel door and place my hand onto the palm reader while staring into the retinal scanner.

**System** - Dr. Feldman recognized, access granted.

The airlock releases in a quiet hiss, massive bolts sliding into the walls, ceiling, and floor  light filters out into the dim landing as the door opens. 

-------------

*2/12/2017  11:32AM*

Site 2 Security Channel  logging

Motion detection active.

Video surveillance active.

Video-transcription software complete.

Facial recognition software incomplete. 51%

Voice recognition software incomplete. 34%

Thermal recognition software incomplete. 18%

Cognitive recognition software incomplete. 2%

Defense systems offline. 

Two humans enter through Train Entrance 3. One (Human 1) walks with purpose, the other (Human 2) follows. Couple moves to floor C. Another human (Human 3) approaches from the east.

**Human 3** - Ah, Dr. Feldman, it is good to see you. Im glad youve finally made it over here to Site 2. 

**Human 1** - Kill him.

Human 3 drops to the floor. Dr. Feldman and Human 2 drag the body into the closest room, then continue south towards the offices. They stop in front of the office of Dr. Feldman. He palms his way into the office and Human 2 follows inside. The door closes.

------------------

*2/12/2017  11:44AM*

**Zero** - Shit, he isnt in here. He must be wandering around overseeing the progress of everything gearing up. I am going to access his computer and try to absorb anything else he may have on there that wasnt in his mind. Stand guard while I am linked up. Ill be vulnerable while it is going.

**314** - What do I do if Feldmans clone tries to come in?

**Zero** - Knock him out. We may need him still. 

------------------

*2/12/2017  1:39PM*

Site 2 Security Channel  logging

Motion detection active.

Video surveillance active.

Video-transcription software complete.

Facial recognition software incomplete. 98%

Voice recognition software incomplete. 71%

Thermal recognition software incomplete. 37%

Cognitive recognition software incomplete. 12%

Defense systems offline.


Human 4 is entering the loft. Loft has stopped on floor C. Human 4 proceeds towards the offices. 
Facial recognition software complete.
Searching 

Human 1 is Patient Zero.

Human 2 is Patient 314.

Human 3 is General Talbot.

Human 4 is Dr. Feldman. 


Dr. Feldman approaches his office.

-----------------

*2/12/2017  1:41PM*

The clone of Dr. Feldman walks in to see 314 directly in front of him and falters mid step. 314 focuses on breaking his knees, knowing Zero told him to keep him alive. Confusion creeps across 314s face when nothing seems to happen. In an instant the clone is lunging forward, fist outstretched. 314 tries to move out of the way but takes a glancing blow to the cheek and the lunging body follows, crashing into each other and falling to the floor. An object, blurred by the nearness and the sped, crosses 314s vision. Then black.

------------

*2/12/2017  5:06PM*

**Dr.** - I see you are finally waking up. Let me be the first to welcome you to Site 2.

**314** - Site 2? Wha.. what? Uhmmm [rolls over gingerly, holding the side of his head] 

Patient 314 slowly brings his head up to look around. Four walls, one observation screen, one cot.

**Dr.** - I must thank you. In coming here I can pick up where we left off at Site 1. I wasnt quite finished with your testing, you know.

**314** - Zero. What happened to Zero?

**Dr.** - Ah, Zero. You can thank him for making all of this a reality. Without his ability this facility would probably not exist. It was unfortunate to have to kill him, especially in such a vulnerable state. He didnt even look up when I wrapped my hands around his throat. 

314 trembles with rage. Tears stain his face. 

**314** - I wont help you. I wont!

Dr. Feldman takes out his phone and presses a few buttons. A blinding light and horrible screech fills Observation Room 1. It seems to go on forever.

**Dr.** - Oh I think you will. Without a kill youll be in the same sad, pathetic state you were just a few weeks ago. Any passing fart will send your weak heart into convulsions. Do you want to be like that again, 314?

**314** - I lived my whole life like that. Ill suffer it if it means you dont get what you want.

**Dr.** - Hmm. Be that as it may, if you dont mind please feel the nape of your neck for me. [314s hand slowly moves to the back of his head] Do you feel that slight bump? That is the Z implant. If I press a button it is activated. If you try to take it out it is activated. Do you know what it does, 314? It gives me complete access to your mind. You are my little zombie pet, hence the Z. I can make you do *anything*. Anything, 314. So I dare say that you will help me whether you want to or not. I was able to test on your mother for quite a while before her lack of will became a roadblock. But you see, now I know that your ability is hereditary. You will be my factory, impregnating thousands of women so that I can test on all of your special offspring. Oh yes, I will get what I want.

A faceless walks into the [room.](https://www.reddit.com/r/nosleep/comments/5u7lf7/patient_314_final/)

[](https://www.facebook.com/aaron.writes.1) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-14 08:09:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> My apologies for being exacting in my research. 

- Dr. Feldman  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-14 08:02:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Upon review of the footage this has been corrected. I must have miscounted the bodies. Thank you for pointing out the error. 

- Dr. Feldman 

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-14 00:20:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I hope I never need this warning. But thank you.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-13 16:00:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I was wondering why police arrived the next day instead of in three minutes. Very good! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Patient Zero </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-13 14:54:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [Related](https://www.reddit.com/r/nosleep/comments/5thx2n/patient_313/)

Mt. Whitney Psychiatric Ward 

Containment Protocol - Facility Lock down 

*2/11/2017 - 11:12PM*

ALL CHANNELS OPEN - logging. ..

**Security channel** - Sub-Ob 3 breach. All units to central loft. All units to central loft. Patient 3 is active. Patient 3 is active! All units to central loft. 

**Chief Security Advisor** - P3 Unit to the fore. Stand ready. Units one thru four flanking position. Weapons ready. 

[Central loft comes to rest and doors open]

------------

Dr. Feldman personal log

*2/11/2017 - 11:13PM*

Patient 3 is not in the loft. It is coming for me. It's not alone. 

[Dr is rifling thru papers, searching]

[Massive data dump onto unknown server]

Office should hold but just in case... initiate Phase 3 on my command...

[Groan of metal can be heard]

--------------

*2/11/2017 - 11:13PM*

**Chief Security Advisor** - Where is it?  FUCK! This wouldn't happen if we had video in Sub-Op. Security to operations this is CSA do you have a visual on Patient 3?

**Operations** - Negative, CSA. Thermal scan in progress... Heat signature outside Dr. Feldman's office. 

**CSA** - En route. Units with me, protect Feldman at all costs. 

-----------

*2/11/2017 - 11:14*

[Metal screams in anguish, audibly twisting and conforming against its will]

**CSA** - P3 Unit forward. Engage. All units backup formation. 

[Weapons crackle and sizzle, men screaming]

**CSA** - ALL UNITS ON ME! TIGHT CIRCLE, PATIENT ZERO IS PRESENT!! PATIENT ZERO IS PRE..

[Weapons open fire in all directions]

----------

[A single tentacle breaks thru, bits of metal still attached to its suckers]

**Dr.** - Access code Kite Bravo Six Zero Field Six One Hippo Tango

**Security Channel** - Phase 3 confirmed. 

[The tentacle pulls back. Inhuman shrieks mixing with human screams fill the compound]

**P3 UNIT** - Patient 3 neutralized. Patient zero at large. All remaining units to Feldman's office. Office hull is breached. 

[A deep groan issues thought-out the compound. Generators begin whirring]

-------------

[Dr. Feldman's body lies facedown behind his desk. Blood spills out from his head at both temples]

*P3 UNIT* - Feldman is dead. All personal be advised, Patient Zero has assumed his form. I repeat, Feldman is dead. Open fire immediately upon contact with Dr. Feldman. 

-----------

*2/11/2017 - 11:16PM*

Patient 314s observation room opens. Dr. Feldman walks in.

**Dr.** - Sorry to disturb you at this late hour, 314. If you would please follow me.

**314** - Follow you where? 

**Dr.** - Ill explain on the way. Come along now.

---------------

*2/11/2017  11:21PM*

[All data received at Site 2. Phase 3 in progress.]

Water floods the facility, filling every square inch of every room. All power is diverted to the coils, 1,000,000 volts cooking anything left alive. Set charges begin to go off. Floor by floor the facility collapses onto itself. 

-------------

*2/12/2017  12:04AM*

Patient 314 watches from the back of a high-speed railcar. The mountain seems to shudder slightly. 

**Zero** - As I was saying, I am not Dr. Feldman. In there I was referred to as Patient Zero just as you are Patient 314. I was the first, the reason all of this is even happening. 

**314** - So who are you really? How did you know how to get out of there?

**Zero** - Who I am is not important, young man. What I can do is the important thing. Dr. Feldman and I were colleagues once, doing research for our joint thesis on the human potential. I was trying to find out more about myself, my ability. He was trying to make himself better.

**314** - And what is your ability?

**Zero** - To put it in basic terms I absorb information and I never forget anything. The downside is that whatever information source I absorb is destroyed in the process. If I read a book the pages are wiped clean. If I take someones memory they die. I was careless with it early on in my life before I understood the need for such caution and it caught up with me. Dr. Feldman was a brilliant man. He figured out there was something special about me during our short time together as researchers. What I didnt know was that he was already working for Mt. Whitney Research.

**314** - But you look like him, too. So you shape shift?

**Zero** - The reason a living thing dies when I absorb their information is because I take ALL of it, down to the DNA that dictates how they look. We went for a weekend camping trip to take a break from our thesis but it was a set-up. I was locked away in that mountain ever since. He figured out how to extract the information I had absorbed and built almost everything off of that information. He designed an implant that mimicked my ability. It absorbed information down without destroying it. With each new Patient he was able to put together one puzzle piece at a time of the full human potential. You might have been the last piece.

**314** - Me? Why?

**Zero** - Because with you he could unlock the secret to escaping death. While I absorbed *information* you absorbed *life*! If he could harness that and manipulate it in the right way it would enable everlasting life. Not to mention the nifty tricks you can do with your mind. He hit the jackpot when he found you and your mother. 

**314** - Mom [314 looks out the window at the rapidly fading mountain] Why did you save me?

**Zero** - Because Feldman activated Phase 3. All his research was transferred to Site 2. His clone is probably already at work trying to locate the next Patient. [Were going to stop it.](https://www.reddit.com/r/nosleep/comments/5u0d4q/site_2/)

[](https://www.facebook.com/aaron.writes.1) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-12 10:14:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Excellent summation of information. I will not fill in gaps however I will confirm your conclusion. 

- Dr. Feldman  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-12 10:11:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So glad for you! Please try to enjoy the life you have. You've been thru hell, literally, and a second chance at life.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-12 10:02:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I will start by stating a disclaimer: there is only so much I can divulge and my answers will most likely be too vague for your liking. Now to "answer" your questions. 

1. We observe our patients with a system of implants that detect a great multitude of reactions occurring in the body. We try our best to create a baseline with which to compare to, in this case the coefficient of 1.3.

2. The disease is singular to Patient 314. At this time there is still much to learn and uncover. The hereditary link between Patient 313 and 314 is specific to the mental abilities. 

3. We understand the way in which their mental capabilities manifest but not how to manifest them. Therefore we can block the means of their power from leaving the confines of the observation room. 

4. Almost every one of our patients are unique in their abilities or reasoning for being under observation. Patient 313 was our first telekinetic. I am able to theorize about 314 because of the months I had previously with 313.

I hope this is sufficient for you. 

- Dr. Feldman  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Patient 313 </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-11 23:19:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [Day 5](https://www.reddit.com/r/nosleep/comments/5t9rkp/patient_314_day_5/)


Mt. Whitney Psychiatric Ward

 

Dr. Feldman

 

*9/13/2016  5:15AM*

 

Observations from experiment six  logging

 

Patient 313 continues to decline. She has not slept the past three nights and still refuses to eat. Today we will be forced to run an IV and tube feed her to regain her strength based on our interactions in the coming hour. She must remain alive. It is hard to judge whether she is refusing to use her mental capabilities or if she is too weak to use them effectively. 

 

Experiment three showed such promise. It seems like a lifetime ago when I was excited about her test results. Today we will repeat experiment five again in hopes of determining whether or not multiple subjects can be terminated. 

 

---------------------

 

*9/13/2016  6:15AM*

 

Experiment seven  logging

 

Breakfast delivered. Patient 313 makes no indications of getting up. 

 

**Dr.** - 313, please eat. You need your strength.

 

**313** - Dont act like you care about me. 

 

**Dr.** - You know that I [313 interrupts]

 

**313** - You abducted me from my home, my son left all alone, locked up in a room defenseless. You keep me isolated in a small room with nothing but news and hospital food to eat. You are a monster, *Doctor*.

 

**Dr.** - You dont like the food?  Ill look into that. And like I have said before, your son is safe and being watched after. He doesnt even know that [313 interrupts again]

 

**313** - That you replaced me with one of your fucking clones? No of course, that makes it all better. MY SON NEEDS HIS MOTHER. NOT A DAMNED CLONE!

 

The lights begin to flicker. A small crack forms in the center of the observation window as Patient 313 moves deliberately towards it. Fifteen Faceless rush into the room to apprehend Patient 313. Twelve are killed before a needle finds a home in her neck. The crack has become a massive spider web in the glass. She is taken to a maximum security cell where a feeding tube and IV are administered.

 

She is kept in an induced coma for seven days while her body is replenished with nutrients and back in balance. Drug Z is implanted.

 

--------------

 

*9/20/2016  8:07AM*

 

Medical evaluation of Patient 313  logging

 

313s eyes fluttered open as the last of the IV fluid left her system. She slowly turned her neck one way, then the other.

 

**Dr.** - Good morning. Dont try to sit up yet. It will take most of the day for the grogginess to fade completely. There is some food next to you when you are ready.

 

**313** - What did you do? 

 

**Dr.** - You were malnourished and in a very agitated state when we last spoke. It was necessary to remove you from the observation room while we made the necessary improvements to it. I dont think youll be cracking the observation window any time soon. Nor do I think you should try.

 

**313** - Ill do whatever the hell I want. Kill me if you dont like it.

 

**Dr.** - I have better options that killing you but I certainly hope it doesnt come to that. You are special, 313. We can learn a lot from you. 

 

**313** - Youll get nothing else from me you bastard. I promise you that!

 

Patient 313 begins sitting up, slapping the meal tray away and pulling tubing out of her arms.

 

**Dr.** - I see. It was a pleasure working with you.

 

Dr. Feldman activates Drug Z. The change in Patient 313 is immediate. 

 

----------------

 

*11/1/2016  10:30AM*

 

Observations from experiment twenty eight  logging

 

This will be the last observation log for Patient 313Z. She has done as much as she can in her current state of mind. There is only so far a controlled mind can go when testing mental capabilities. Below is a summary of her accomplishments:

 

* Able to kill up to six individuals at once

* Able to push thoughts into an individuals mind

* Able to block out pain up to a pain threshold of a gunshot wound

* Able to learn at a heightened rate

 

Tomorrow we will do a full medical screen for genetic markers and scan for matches. Once the scan is complete the full autopsy can be scheduled.

 

------------------

 

*11/2/2016  6:45AM*

 

Patient 313Z medical summary  logging

 

We found some very interesting things, very interesting indeed. Patient 313Z has a marker we have never seen before which may attribute to her ability. Much more testing needs to be done to determine if this is the case but preliminary research indicates the marker determines higher brain functions. Her autopsy is postponed until all research is complete.

 

--------------

 

*2/5/2017  8:57PM*

 

Patient 313Z medical summary  logging

 

We found a match to Patient 313Z. Mobilizing a task force for immediate transport.

 

----------------

 

*2/8/2017  4:14PM*

 

Patient 313Z sent to observation room 1.

-------------------

 

 

*2/8/2017  4:17PM*

 

Patient 313Z sent to autopsy [room 1.](https://www.reddit.com/r/nosleep/comments/5tsyl6/patient_zero/)

[](https://www.facebook.com/aaron.writes.1) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-11 18:33:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If I understand the situation correctly comments were made about two separate areas of the log. I was answering one question and another was then asked about a different area. I confused the two and here we are. 

That being said, your comment is spot on (both of them) so I applaud you working your way thru it. I must be under more stress than I realized. 

- Dr. Feldman  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-11 17:49:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Ah yes I see where the confusion has occurred. I misspoke when I talked with Patient 314 about 313. I will add an addendum to the log in an attempt to clear up any future confusion. 

I told 314 that he killed 313 "yesterday" when in reality it was two days before. Thank you for catching that and bringing it to my attention! 

- Dr. Feldman  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-11 16:39:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I stuffed the knife straight down her throat until I felt it connect with the vertebrae. Running back (amazing how trivial this seems to most but it was my first time doing so) to the last of them I made their cries stop quickly. Pickle was last. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-11 16:07:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It is not every day I get complimented on my research. Thank you very much, Lauren. I've got my eye on you. 

- Dr. Feldman  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-11 16:01:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I am envisioning a man in a crowded room furiously masturbating in order to have enough ability to kill them all. That would be rather inconvenient wouldn't you agree? Comical, though. 

- Dr. Feldman  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-11 15:23:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> *2/10/2017  6:15AM*

Experiment five  logging

Breakfast delivered. 314 appears contemplative and relaxed while he eats. 

Sixteen subjects enter the room just as Dr. Feldman begins to speak.

**Dr.** - Good morning, 314. Today we will attempt to verify a few theories I have. *In front of you is a mixture of Faceless and clones of your Father, Mother, and myself.* Each one is holding a different weapon. Those without a weapon you will kill with your bare hands, except the very last which must be killed with your mind. On my mark move to the first subject. Please wait thirty seconds between each kill. Proceed.

I italicized the detail you missed. 

- Dr. Feldman  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-11 05:44:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The future. 

- Dr. Feldman  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-11 05:31:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> My wife would never go. And never let's me either </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Patient 314 - Day 5 </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-10 21:38:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [Day 4](https://www.reddit.com/r/nosleep/comments/5t2ncl/patient_314_day_4/)

Mt. Whitney Psychiatric Ward

Patient 314 Personal Log

*2/9/2017  10:23PM*

I guess I need to eat my words a bit. He said today would be fun and it WAS! Sure, yeah it started out kind of slow but shooting a gun was invigorating, mesmerizing even. The power inside of that tiny little weapon is astounding. I wouldn't mind taking it up as a hobby someday but who needs a gun when you can visualize severing the spinal cord and it actually happens? Well I guess I dont know if the spinal cord severed but the dad-clone died so whatever I did to it killed it. How did he know I could do that? I guess since I am patient 314 that means there were 313 before me but the real question is where they *like* me or were they all different? Like, different abilities and stuff? I am going to ask some questions tomorrow. 

------------------

Dr. Feldman

*2/9/2017  10:59PM*

Observations from experiment four  logging

Patient 314 has shown more promise in four days than any other patient in a months time. I do not think that we have seen anywhere close to his maximum potential. 314 is also becoming a bit more interactive  this can only be taken in a positive way. Only two other patients have reacted positively once testing began. He appears to be settling in to his routine nicely. 

As I theorized, an isolated kill is very static, and only fluctuates with emotional connection. This is important for a great many applications where emotion must be removed from a situation. When multiple beings are killed there is a multiplier factor of 1.3. This is possibly linked to adrenaline or a similar effect to runners high  more testing will be done to determine the exact cause. 

It should also be noted that the method of killing plays a factor. Patient 314 gained more from killing with the knife than he did with the pistol. He does seem to favor using his hands when killing. This might tie in with the emotion aspect. 

Most exciting of all is having another patient with the mental ability. Patient 313 was a complete failure in the testing environment however the discovery of her mental abilities led us to Patient 314 so I shouldnt be too hard on her. Where she failed he has succeeded! Autopsy on the Faceless that 314 failed to kill showed some damage to the neck similar to whiplash and minor internal bleeding on the brain. Autopsy on the clone showed a cleanly severed spinal cord. If we can somehow find a way to translate that result without the personal/emotional connection I am getting ahead of myself. 

Tomorrow will be interesting. 

-----------------

*2/10/2017  6:15AM*

Experiment five  logging

Breakfast delivered. 314 appears contemplative and relaxed while he eats. 

Sixteen subjects enter the room just as Dr. Feldman begins to speak.

**Dr.** - Good morning, 314. Today we will attempt to verify a few theories I have. In front of you is a mixture of Faceless and clones of your Father, Mother, and myself. Each one is holding a different weapon. Those without a weapon you will kill with your bare hands, except the very last which must be killed with your mind. On my mark move to the first subject. Please wait thirty seconds between each kill. Proceed.

Readings are taken, compared, logged. 

314 moves to the first subject. When he finds himself in front of the last he locks eyes with the subject. Blood seeps slowly out of the mouth, nostrils, eyes, and ears of the subject as it crumples to the clean, white floor.

Readings are taken, compared, logged.

A powerful strobe lashes out, blindingly bright, accompanied by a thunderclap of sound.

Readings are taken, compared, logged.

**Dr.** - Wonderful, simply marvelous! Sixteen more are coming in now. This time I would like for you to try and mentally kill the first subject AND the last subject. Proceed.

314 approaches the first subject. Sweat begins beading on his forehead. His breathing grows harsher.

**Dr.** - 314, enough. Use your hands and move on to the next. 

314 moves down the line with more violent intent. When he steps in front of the final subject the neck twists swiftly in a full 360 degrees. 314s hands never left his sides. 

**Dr.** - Perfect, thank you 314. I am sure you need some rest so Ill have a snack brought and we can resume at 8.

**314** - How did you know I could do that? You know, with my mind?

**Dr.** - I suppose you deserve a few answers. Patient 313 had similar mental capabilities. Once an ability is discovered in one Patient we check every Patient for those abilities as well.

**314** - Are there other Patients here? Can I meet them? Can I meet 313?

**Dr.** - Youve already met Patient 313.

Dr. Feldman walks away and a tray with sliced meats and cheeses is brought it. 314 eats in silence.

------------------

*2/10/2017  8:00AM*

Experiment five, continued  logging

**Dr.** - How are you feeling, 314? Have you had any headaches or eye strain?

**314** - Not yet, no. Was that an issue with 313?

**Dr.** - It was, among others. We are going to continue the testing now if that is ok.

Three clones of Dr. Feldman enter the observation room. 

**Dr.** - If you would, please try to kill each one mentally.

**314** - [mumbles] Like this world needs more crazy doctors running around

Patient 314 stays on his cot but focuses on the first clone. His knuckles turn white as his grip tightens on the edge of the cot, then the clone crumples to the floor. Readings are taken, compared, logged.
314s neck bulges and strains as the second clone drops to the floor, twitching slightly twice. A large vein is standing out on 314s forehead and gleams with sweat. Readings are taken, compared, logged.
A guttural yell escapes the lips of Patient 314. His concentration has forced him to stop breathing, his head vibrating back and forth.

**Dr.** - Breathe. Recollect yourself. Then try again.

Patient 314 leans back, drawing in a large breath. Again. Again. The color in his hands and face start to return to normal. He locks eyes with the last clone  twenty seconds later it drops lifelessly to the floor. Readings are taken, compared, logged.

**Dr.** - I believe we have found your threshold. There will be one more test today but it can wait until just before dinner. A second channel has been added to your television. Please try to rest.

----------------

*2/10/2017  11:15AM*

Lunch delivered. Patient 314 awakened by the sound of the tray. Television mode is activated while 314 eats.

-------------------

*2/10/2017  4:00PM*

Experiment five, continued  logging

Six Faceless enter the room.

**Dr.** - This is the last test of the day. I would like you to kill four with your hands. Then try to kill the remaining two at the same time with your mind.

**314** - Are you kidding? At the same time? How am I going to do that?! 

**Dr.** - How do you kill one? You visualize the action and carry out the action with your mind. Try to visualize them both.

314 sighs and closes his eyes. He rubs his temples for a minute before looking up at the Faceless. Breathing is slow and even. Eventually two thuds resonate through the room. Readings are taken, compared, logged.

**Dr.** -  [whispers] Yes 
[to 314] How do you feel?

**314** - Tired. Could I meet 313 again?

**Dr.** - I am afraid that isnt possible anymore. You killed her yesterday. 

[ADDENDUM TO LOG] - Patient 314 killed her two days before. See Day 3.

---------------

*2/10/2017  5:15PM*

Dinner is delivered. A comedy movie is playing on the television. 

Experiment [5 complete.](https://www.reddit.com/r/nosleep/comments/5thx2n/patient_313/)

[](https://www.facebook.com/aaron.writes.1) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Patient 314 - Day 4 </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-09 21:37:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [Day 3](https://www.reddit.com/r/nosleep/comments/5svb9k/patient_314_day_3/)

Mt. Whitney Psychiatric Ward

Patient 314 Personal Log

*2/8/2017  8:17PM*

I feel like I am being conditioned, like I am a bad dog in obedience school. To a degree I understand what Dr. Feldman is doing and why but I hate not being in control of the experiments. I felt like I was getting closer to a cure on my own! I didnt need this beady-eyed prick force-feeding me little kids and raping my eyes with blinding lights. Eff it. At least he said today was the last day for all of the back and forth shit. Tomorrow would be fun, he said. Id like to say I dont trust him but what choice to I have? It is going to happen one way or another. What I dont get is how they have clone tech. Like, I know it wasnt my mom but at the same time it was impossible not to think it was her. Her voice, expressions, everything was perfect. Then that smug bastard throws a clone of himself in here. Probably testing me to see how much I hate him. A lot, man. A whole effing lot.

------------------------

Dr. Feldman

*2/8/2017  10:00PM*

Observations from experiment three  logging

Patient 314 has stabilized. There was concern at first due to the nature of our testing, of course, but his resolve is incredibly high. This is most likely caused by the extreme isolation he has already endured. Testing has determined that size or age of the individual is not a factor in the amount of strength 314 gains from each kill, but rather emotional bonds. It is still undetermined whether positive emotions or negative emotions such as love and calm versus hate and fear change the amount but we will revisit that at a later date. A most interesting note - the highest amount of strength gain did not come from killing me but actually his mother. Very much looking forward to testing my theory on why that was.

By the end of the day we determined the amount of sensory stimulation needed to bring 314 down to his zero point: the point where he does not hurt from sensations but is not above normal human ability. We also determined that 314 actually goes slightly beyond the normal levels of human strength, speed, and agility after killing, thus enabling the next kill to be easier.

Tomorrow will be an exciting day. 

--------------------

*2/9/2017  6:15AM*

Experiment four  logging

Breakfast delivered. 314 eats hungrily. Readings are taken, compared, logged.

Six individuals enter the room. Each one is faceless and naked.

**Dr.** - Good morning, 314. Before you is the first round of tests for the day. If you would please kill one, then wait until my signal, kill two and wait for my signal, then the last three. I also need you to be consistent in your actions.

**314** - Why dont they have faces?

**Dr.** - We are trying to eliminate any emotion behind the acts today.

**314** - How do they see?

**Dr.** - One day I will explain everything, but for now please kill the first individual.

314 studies Dr. Feldmans face for a moment before walking over to the first. He stops an inch away, almost nose to nose (if it had a nose).

**314** - It isnt breathing. Strange.

314 snaps the neck and steps back. Readings are taken, compared, logged.

**Dr.** - Proceed.

314 moves in front of the next, quickly snapping the neck of one and then two.  Readings are taken, compared, logged.

**Dr.** - Proceed.

314 snaps all three necks almost too quickly to see. Readings are taken, compared, logged.

**Dr.** - Thank you, 314. Ill return once the results for this test have been analyzed. Relax and enjoy some news.

The observation window switched to television mode and news is displayed. A blurb about the President, unseasonable weather patterns, a ISIS terrorist attack at Mayo Clinic, a Yellow Fever outbreak.

-------------------

*2/9/2017  9:27AM*

Experiment four, continued  logging

**Dr.** - Have you ever fired a gun before, 314?

**314** - My doorbell used to send me into shock. You think a gun firing six inches from my ear would be pleasant for me?

**Dr.** - Of course, a silly question indeed. Six more individuals will be entering your room. One has a gun. Please take the gun and kill them all.

Readings are taken, compared, logged. Six of the faceless come in, the last holding a gun outstretched toward 314, handle out. 314 takes the gun, slides his hands over it, studies it. The first shot misses however each subsequent shot hits the target. 314 is smiling. Readings are taken, compared, logged.

**Dr.** - Excellent, thank you. How did it feel to use a gun?

**314** - Different. Powerful. Surprisingly cold, like the gun is trying to steal all of my warmth.

Six more of the faceless come in, each one grabbing a deceased test subject and carry them out. They return, the last holding a large hunting knife.

**Dr.** - Please, again, this time with the knife.

314 takes the knife and sprints from the first to the last, knife flashing out. Each drop lifeless with a slit across the throat. Readings are taken, compared, logged.

**Dr.** - Did that feel different to you? The knife?

**314** - It did. I could almost feel the heartbeat when I ran the edge across their throat, the warmth of blood on my hand.

314 glances down at his hands to find them devoid of any blood.

**Dr.** - Interesting, yes yes quite marvelous. [Slowly walks off talking to himself]

----------------------

*2/9/2017  11:15AM* 

Lunch delivered. There is also the most recent issue of Time magazine. 314 eats and reads.

----------------

*2/9/2017  4:00PM*

Experiment four, continued  logging

One of the faceless enters 314s room.

**Dr.** - Good afternoon, 314. This test will be a little different. Id like for you to kill the subject with your mind. 

**314** - My what? Mind? How the hell am I supposed to do that?

**Dr.** - I dont know, maybe you cant. But please humor me and try.

314 stares at Dr. Feldman, eyes narrowed, and then focuses attention on the Faceless. Nothing happens. Two minutes pass. Still nothing. Readings are taken, compared, logged.

**Dr.** - May I ask what you are thinking?

**314** - I am thinking this is the most retarded test Ive ever heard of.

**Dr.** - Have you truly tried to kill the subject? Focused intently just as if you had a gun or a knife in your hand.

**314** - Sure, yea. Ok. 

314 focuses on the Faceless. Eyes close. 314s vitals slow. The Faceless twitches momentarily. Then nothing. 314s brow is glistening lightly with sweat. The Faceless leaves the room. Readings are taken, compared, logged.

**Dr.** - Thank you 314. You may rest now. Dinner will be by shortly.

--------------

*2/9/2017  5:15PM*

Dinner delivered. 314 takes the dinner and sits down to eat. A man enters.

Confusion crosses 314s face momentarily, then recognition, then a smile. 

The man drops dead. He looked just like his father.

Experiment 4 [complete.](https://www.reddit.com/r/nosleep/comments/5t9rkp/patient_314_day_5/)

[](https://www.facebook.com/aaron.writes.1) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Patient 314 - Day 3 </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-08 21:34:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [Day 2](https://www.reddit.com/r/nosleep/comments/5snx09/patient_314_day_2/)

Mt. Whitney Psychiatric Ward

Dr. Feldman

*2/8/2017  5:30AM*

Observations from experiment one and two  logging

Patient 314 can be manipulated into submission with extreme sensory input and enhanced by the taking of life. Still unsure of the cause, whether it is life force, chemical reaction in the brain, or simply a deranged perception. If it is life force or a chemical reaction we can control it and perfect it. If 314 has created this illusion it wont be so easy to control. Maybe even impossible to control. Today we attempt to measure how much a life is worth.

--------------

*2/8/2017  6:15AM*

Experiment preparation  logging

Breakfast delivered. 314 eats in silence. Immediately following the meal another child is presented. 314 watches the child warily for several minutes, glancing at the observation window occasionally.

**314** - Who are you?

Child does not respond. 314 circles the child, then casually snaps its neck.

Readings are taken, compared, logged.

Light intensity increased by 180, white noise volume 8.

Readings are taken, compared, logged. Light and noise discontinued.

----------------

*2/8/2017  8:15AM*

A child is introduced to the room. 314 looks up from the floor.

**314** - Didnt I just kill you?!

314 grabs child by the neck and strangles it to death.

Readings are taken, compared, logged.

Light increased by 180, white noise volume 6.

Readings are taken, compared, logged. Light and noise discontinued. 

-------------------

*2/8/2017  10:15AM*

The final child is introduced to the room. 314 screams in what seems to be rage. 314 grabs the child by the face, pressing one thumb into each eyeball. 314 repeats *Just die* over and over until being overcome by sobs.

Readings are taken, compared, logged. 

Light increased by 180, white noise volume 5.

Readings are taken, compared, logged. Light and noise discontinued. 

------------------

*2/8/2017  11:15AM*

Lunch is brought to 314 but shows no desire to eat. The food is removed at 11:45AM.

------------------

*2/8/2017  12:15PM*

A woman is introduced to the room. 314 does not seem to notice. 

**Dr.** - Please, 314, only a few more before this stage of testing is over. 

**314** - Why did the little girl look the same? Why are they all the same? WHAT DO YOU WANT?!

 314 pounds on the glass.

**Dr.** - Kill her.

314 spins and lunges in one fluid motion and snaps her neck cleanly.

Readings are taken, compared, logged.

Light intensity increased by 180, white noise volume 8.

Readings are taken, compared, logged. Light and noise discontinued.

--------------

*2/8/2017  2:15PM*

A woman is introduced to the room.

**314** - Who are you? 

**Woman** - I am Test 3.2. Please kill me.

**314** - Why do you want me to kill you?

**Test 3.2** - So that you can be cured.

**314** - But dont you want to live? To experience life outside of these walls?

**Test 3.2** - I live only to be killed. Please kill me.

**314** - Why do you look just like the last woman?

**Test 3.2** - Please kill me.

314 begins striking Test 3.2 in the face and chest. 314 screams in pain due to a broken bone in the hand. While clutching the hand to his chest 314 kicks Test 3.2 until she drops. He stomps repeatedly. 
An orderly and a nurse enter the room, pulling 314 away from the crushed skull to treat his hand. The body is removed and floor cleaned.

Readings are taken, compared, logged.

Light intensity increased by 180, white noise volume 6.

Readings are taken, compared, logged. Light and noise discontinued.

-------------

*2/8/2017  4:15PM*

The final woman is introduced to the room.

**314** - Mom?

**Woman** - Oh [Removed] I thought Id never see you again. Are you ok? What is this place?

**314** - Some kind of lab or something. They are experimenting on me. I.. Ive done bad things, mom.

**Woman** - Hush now everything is alright. Mommies here. [She holds 314 close, stroking his hair]

**314** - I think I broke m..

**Dr.** - Kill her, 314. 

**314** - Wait, what? Kill my mom? No, no way! Are you kiddi..

**Dr.** - Kill her.

**Woman** - Who are you? What are you doing to my son?

**Dr.** - Kill her now.

314 is shocked with 50,000 volts. He is shaking his head, tears in his eyes. The woman is striding toward the glass. She pounds on it, then moves to the wall where she entered the room, pounding on it.

**314** - I love you, mom.

She crumples to the ground, neck broken.

Readings are taken, compared, logged.

Light intensity increased by 180, white noise volume 10.

Readings are taken, compared, logged. Light and noise discontinued.

--------------------

*2/8/2017  5:15PM*

Dinner is brought to 314. 

**Dr.** - Please, eat. You need your strength.

**314** - Screw you.

**Dr.** - Oh come now. I thought we were past all of that nonsense. There is only one more test today and then youll be moving on to the next phase in testing. I promise youll enjoy it much, much better. Now eat your dinner and Ill bring you your dessert soon.

314 slowly eats the food. As soon as the last bite is eaten Dr. Feldman enters the room holding a plate with a large slice of carrot cake. Dr. Feldman sits next to 314, offering him the cake. 314 begins eating. 

After two bites 314 takes the fork and jams it into the throat of Dr. Feldman. Blood spurts out all over the carrot cake and 314s face.

[Clap, clap, clap] Dr. Feldman can be seen just beyond the observation glass. 

Readings are taken, compared, logged.

The observation glass switches to television mode, displaying CCTV footage with timestamp matching the present time. The footage is of 314s home. His mother passes by one camera, emerges on another in 314s room. She sits and cries.

314 takes a bite of carrot cake.

Readings are taken, compared, logged.

Experiment 3 [complete.](https://www.reddit.com/r/nosleep/comments/5t2ncl/patient_314_day_4/)

[](https://www.facebook.com/aaron.writes.1) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Patient 314 - Day 2 </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-07 21:32:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [Day 1](https://www.reddit.com/r/nosleep/comments/5sgofu/patient_314/)

Mt. Whitney Psychiatric Ward

Dr. Feldman

*2/7/2017  6:15AM*

Experiment preparation  logging

Patient 314 receives breakfast, eating rapidly.

**Dr.** - Good morning, 314. How did you sleep?

**314** - Mind if I finish eating first? It is rude to interrupt a meal.

**Dr.** - Of course. Ill skip the pleasantries and explain what we are aiming to do here. All you need to do is listen.

314 continues eating however his eyes never break from Dr. Feldman

**Dr.** - We want to perfect your cure, 314. Right now we know only rudimentary ideas about how your disease works but that is going to change. Dr. Ramsus quite frankly didnt appreciate the opportunity he had. He squandered his chance at placing his name in the forefront of the medical community. I, however, will not let that chance get by me. Now I am going to ask you a few questions about the circumstances of your disease. All you need to do is nod yes or no.

314 has finished his meal.

**Dr.** - Any amount of sensory stimuli would cause heart palpitations and mental anguish, correct?

314 affirms.

**Dr.** - Until the car accident you had never witnessed a reversal of the condition, correct?

314 affirms.

**Dr.** - Your first experiment involved your estranged father and his new family in which you attempted to recreate the effects of the car accident, correct?

314 smiles, then affirms.

**Dr.** - Tell me about the outcome of that experiment please.

**314** - It worked, at least for a while. My experiments were interrupted so I cant be sure about any quantitative or qualitative statistics. I *believe* that a personal connection, positive or negative, enhances the experience. When I killed my father I felt much more strength flow through me than when I killed his skank or kids. Of course I also thought it could be tied directly to the size of the individual, or their vigor. Again, I was interrupted before conclusions could be made.

**Dr.** - Do not fret. Together we will pinpoint the exact range with many testing variables. Did intercourse with Vanessa give you strength or was it simply the euphoria of orgasm?

**314** - It was my first time. I have nothing to compare it to so I cant answer that. Are we almost done? Im bored.

**Dr.** - One more question: If you are never cured completely will you kill forever in order to have a normal life?

314 affirms.

**Dr.** - Wonderful, thank you for your cooperation. Your room records everything you say and do and we would like to know your thoughts throughout the process of these upcoming tests. If you say Journal Entry, start and Journal Entry, end your words will be logged separately. Lunch will be served [looks at watch] in approximately four hours. After lunch your first experiment begins.

--------------

*2/7/2017  11:00AM*

Lunch delivered. 314 eats in silence. Still no change in demeanor and monitors not detecting a heart episode yet.

----------------

*2/7/2017  12:07PM*

314 has begun to exploring his room. 314 appears to be exceptionally patient and thorough in exploration. Discovery of observation glass doubling as a television has ended the exploration. 314 is now sitting on the cot watching world news  it is the only available program.

-------------------

*2/7/2017  2:15PM*

Automatic light intensity program initiated. Television volume increased by four. 314 appears to be slightly agitated. 

------------------

*2/7/2017  3:15PM*

Light intensity increased. Television volume increased by four. 314 begins pacing, continues for two minutes, then resumes exploration of the room.

------------------

*2/7/2017  4:15PM*

Light intensity increased. Television volume increased by four. 314 is now face down on the cot, blanket draped over his head. Monitors show one small instance of heart palpitation.

--------------

*2/7/2017  5:15PM*

Light intensity increased. Television volume increased by four. Dinner is presented to 314. The sound of the metal tray sliding on the concrete floor creates a heart episode. 314 slowly makes his way to the food and eats even slower. Three more episodes occur during the meal. The last episode is stronger.

-------------

*2/7/2017  6:13PM*

314 appears to be anticipating the increases. Dr. Feldman watches his reaction and the monitors when the increases occur. A massive heart episode causes 314s body to twitch and shiver. 

Experiment 1 complete. Light intensity reduced to normal. Television off, observation window now opaque.

**Dr.** - I am sorry for the discomfort. Before any real testing could begin we had to first bring you back to a baseline. I didnt know if more sensory information would speed up the process  now we know it does. 

**314** - Screw you!

**Dr.** - Now, now, now, any good scientist knows the need and importance of a baseline. How else can we draw any real conclusions? Please, [A small child enters the room of 314] believe me when I say that we want to cure you AND understand your disease properly. Now, you know what to do.

314 launches at the small child, grabbing the hair with both hands and twisting forcefully. The child drops lifelessly to the floor. 314 stares down for a moment, then returns to his cot. 

**Dr.** - Better?

**314** - Who was she?

Experiment 2 [complete.](https://www.reddit.com/r/nosleep/comments/5svb9k/patient_314_day_3/)

[](https://www.facebook.com/aaron.writes.1) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Patient 314 </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-06 21:26:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [Related](https://www.reddit.com/r/nosleep/comments/5rvtzd/my_doctor_is_the_cure/)

Mt. Whitney Psychiatric Ward

Dr. Feldman

*2/6/2017  4:12AM*


Transfer of [REMOVED] from Mayo Research Clinic, completed.

Admittance of [REMOVED] into Ward 11, completed. 

[REMOVED] assigned to PID# 314

48 hour initial observation of 314 has begun.

-----------------


*2/6/2017  9:01AM*

First contact interview between Dr. Feldman and 314  logging

Patient 314 is laying on the cot with eyes closed.

**Dr.** - I trust the flight was not too rough. How are you feeling this morning?

**314** - Screw you.

**Dr.** - Are the lights too bright? I can have them dimmed more if you prefer. 

**314** - Screw you.

**Dr.** - I see. Command, please increase lumens by eighty, thank you. Ill be back in an hour.
Patient 314 spits on the observation window and resumes laying on the cot with eyes closed.

---------------------------

*2/6/2017  10:04AM*

Follow-up interview between Dr. Feldman and 314  logging

No change in patient 314.

**Dr.** - I would like to discuss what you did to Dr. Ramsus and his colleagues. Will you please explain what caused you to act so destructively towards your doctor?

**314** - He promised to cure me fourteen years ago. I was just making sure he kept his promise.

**Dr.** - How can he keep his promise if he is dead? Are you suggesting that you are cured?

**314** - For now.

**Dr.** - Please elaborate. 

**314** - Screw you.

**Dr.** - We cant help you if you dont explain why you did what you did and what you mean by him curing you. Please, elaborate.

**314** - Do you even know what is wrong with me? 

**Dr.** - You suffer from a unique condition in which your senses overload your brain causing massive heart trauma, which has now been called [REMOVED] Disease. Additionally, you suffer from mental instability and delusion (in this case Cotard Delusion) possibly caused by a lifetime of extreme stress, mental, and physical anguish. Furthermore, you are now labeled as schizophrenic and/or bi-polar.

**314** - So, no?

**Dr.** - Lets move on for a moment and talk about what happened at the clinic. What drove you to do that to Dr. Ramsus and his staff?

**314** - Each person cured me a little longer. It isnt rocket science, doc. And you are wasting time brightening my room. Ive got a few weeks before they wear off.

**Dr.** - I suppose we will have to wait and see, wont we? Command, please increase lumens by one hundred and initiate noise program. Thank you. Ill return in an hour.


Patient 314 shows no noticeable signs of distress.

--------------------------------

*2/6/2017  11:09AM*

Second follow-up interview between Dr. Feldman and 314  logging

**Dr.** - Command, please discontinue noise program. I am going to read to you the transcript issued to us by security at the clinic. Please interrupt at any time if a detail is incorrect or if youd like to explain. Ill pause periodically to ask questions as well. [Dr. Feldman begins reading] Patient was lead to Observation Room 1 where Dr. Ramsus and twelve staff members waited to perform testing and observations based upon the recent change in physical ability. The patient sat down in the chair which was centered in the room and surrounded by equipment, monitors, and staff. Dr. Ramsus began asking several questions when the patient grabbed a scalpel and surgical drill. The patient proceeded to stab nearby staff with the scalpel while placing the drill to the head of Dr. Ramsus and 

**314** - I had already drilled through his eye before I ever stabbed a staff member.

**Dr.** - Noted. Patient then threw scalpels and other surgical items at staff while chasing down each one with the drill. The room was put on lockdown while security rushed to the scene. At one point two nurses tackled the patient from behind however the patient bit and ripped out the throat of one nurse while jamming the drill into the stomach of the other. By the time security could get a Taser on the patient Dr. Ramsus and ten of his staff were dead. The remaining two were critically injured and died in transit to Surgery. [Dr. Feldman looks up from his clipboard] Before this incidence you could not even leave your room without extreme cardiac distress. How were you able to murder thirteen people within 90 seconds?

**314** - When they lose their life I gain mine. 

**Dr.** - So you are saying that you steal their life force?

**314** - I have no idea how it works. I just know that when I cause their death my issues fade.

**Dr.** - Hmm.. Is this fading permanent or temporary?

**314** - Well Im not sure. My experiments were interrupted.

**Dr.** - Dont worry, we will get to the bottom of your disease together. How did you discover this phenomenon?

**314** - By accident, really. I caused a massive car accident a while ago. Immediately I felt different. From there I began my experiments and here I am.

**Dr.** - Was your father and his family part of your experiments?

**314** - Yes.

**Dr.** - Thank you. Your lunch will be brought to you shortly. Ill be back this evening to discuss your daily schedule of testing. Get some rest. Command, please reduce lumens by one hundred and eighty. Thank you.


[Day 2](https://www.reddit.com/r/nosleep/comments/5snx09/patient_314_day_2/)

[](https://www.facebook.com/aaron.writes.1) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> We only have armpits to be picked up </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-06 02:12:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> My doctor IS the cure </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-03 20:04:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [Previous](https://www.reddit.com/r/nosleep/comments/5px61m/helpers/)

My mother was astonished when she came home. The entire house was clean, sparkling. Every curtain was drawn back to let in the bright sunlight. It had been so long since this house was brightened by anything other than incandescent bulbs. Dinner was laid out on the table for her and I to enjoy. She walked over to me weeping joyful tears. 

*Hunnie, what is all of this? Are you.. are you.. better?*

*I just woke up and felt different. Momma, Im cured.* Of course I couldnt tell her the truth.

*Oh sweetie, oh my baby!* She stood behind my chair, hugging me tight and covering my head in tears.

We ate together, her staring at me between bites, still unable to comprehend the sudden and drastic change in me. It was so nice to see her smile again. She has a pretty smile. I offered to clear the table and wash the dishes but she had a better idea. We hopped in the car and went for ice cream! This was the first time I had ridden in a car that wasnt heading toward a hospital. I ordered a PB Blizzard Blast, extra-large, and she bought a waffle cone with two scoops of butter pecan. Do you remember the first time you ate ice cream? Do you remember the cold filling your mouth and stinging your teeth a little but immediately washing away with wonderful flavors dancing along your tongue? I do.

I made my momma promise not to say anything to anyone yet, not even my doctors. The next morning was my scheduled in-home visit and I wanted them to see it for themselves when they came. We stayed up late playing card games and watching classic movies that I had missed out on. I was starting to wear down a little bit after the third movie. Maybe it was because it was so late but I didnt want to chance it. 

*Momma, Im going to go the bed. I cant keep my eyes open anymore.*

She kissed my forehead - *Ok, sweetie, good night.*

----------------

I woke up the next morning refreshed but still a little worn down. I was unsure of whether the effects were not permanent or if I just pushed myself too far with my new found lifestyle but I would find out soon enough. I laid in bed for a while contemplating this when a wonderful smell made its way into my nostrils. I got dressed and was greeted with omelets and coffee. How could I have never enjoyed coffee before? Seriously, it is amazing. My first sip hit me the way Mario must feel whenever he gets a mushroom or power-up. Dark, rich, and hot. My mouth burned but I didnt care  I let it sit on my tongue for a while just savoring it. I drank three cups along with my eggs and a slice of toast while waiting for Dr. Ramsus to show up. 

He was shocked to say the least when I answered the door on my own two feet with no signs of heart agitation. I led him into the kitchen and pulled out his chair, offering him some coffee.

*No, thanks. Coffee and I dont mix. I suppose I dont know what to say. When did this change occur?*

*I woke up yesterday morning feeling different. I suppose strength would be the right word, I felt strength in my body.*

*Can you describe what you feel? What differences you perceive?*

He asked me a lot of questions that I did my best to answer and then took a few blood samples to take back to the lab for testing. He also did a quick physical  listened to my chest, blood pressure, looked in my mouth and ears. When I led him to the front door we shook hands and he promised to get in contact with me as soon as he had a look at my test results. I thanked him and he left. 

I figured I had two days before he would want me to come in for more extensive testing so I began to plan. I still felt a little weak, although eating a big meal helped some, and an excessively loud action scene in a movie I was watching set my heart off to the races so I knew I wasnt cured completely. I would need more deserving [helpers](https://www.reddit.com/r/nosleep/comments/5px61m/helpers/).

It was a nice day and I wanted to enjoy the sun on my skin so I went for a walk thru the neighborhood. Kids were out playing, the mailman tending his route, and a woman dog-walker trying to keep control of the ten or so dogs she had out in front of her. She was on the same side of the street as I was and I caught up to her pretty quickly, seeing how her dogs kept taking off in different directions. As I passed I recognized her  a friend of my older sister  and a constant source of teasing when I was younger. My, my, my she had matured nicely.  She did a double-take when she saw me. We chatted for a bit while we walked and I explained the miraculous change. She was majoring in human anatomy at the local university so she was **very** interested in the whole thing. I invited her over later that night to talk more about it and she agreed. I watched her butt sway back and forth as she walked away down another street. 

-------------

Vanessa rang the bell (something I used to despise hearing) and I let her in. She was gorgeous, radiant. Her hair flowed easily around her shoulders and neck and her eyes twinkled whenever she smiled. She was wearing yoga pants and a loose, flowy shirt that looked like it was 80s fashion. I led her to my room and we sat across from each other on my bed. She asked me all kinds of questions and it was a lot of fun making up the answers. Instead of answering one of her questions I leaned in and quickly kissed her on the lips. It was my first kiss! I knew I didnt have anything to lose so why know, you know? She was kind of startled by it but she kissed me back. Oh it was heavenly. What a day! My first taste of coffee, my first kiss, and later, my first orgasm. Ill spare you the details but I am sure you can remember the first time you experienced it. What a rush! I am not sure if I enjoyed having sex with her or killing her more but both were incredibly satisfying. 

--------------

The next day I got a job walking dogs (because clearly Vanessa no longer could) and I used the opportunity to learn my neighborhood better. Who lived where, who had pets, kids, etc. One of the dogs was especially unruly and disobedient so I decided he would be my test subject of the evening. Late that night I snuck into the backyard where the dog lived and found my new helper snoozing. We did some experiments and then I went home, a huge smile on my face. It was great to know that animals could give me strength, too, although not quite as much. Armed with new knowledge about my disease I laid out my plan for Dr. Ramsus and the others that have failed me thus far in my life. I cant wait to show them everything I have [discovered!](https://www.reddit.com/r/nosleep/comments/5sgofu/patient_314/)

[](https://www.facebook.com/aaron.writes.1) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The Builders </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-02 19:57:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I always thought my family was crazy. Family members disappearing, a curse on us or our house or our land, murderous ancestors doing whatever it took to keep things quiet. That is why I changed my name and moved as far away as I could. I was tired of the stares, the murmurs, and people crossing the street so that they wouldnt be on the same side as me. It wasnt me they were afraid of per se, but my last name. One word that tied me to a bunch of lunatics who instilled fear and hatred. 

From what I could piece together it started about two hundred years ago when my family first moved into the area. They were builders, not farmers, and they wanted a fresh start. I think a lot of people did back then. So they moved south to a settlement that was just coming to life in the hopes of helping create a solid future. And things went well, for a while. They built a town hall, church, courthouse, jail, saloon, and pharmacy. It was beautiful, and no other town had anything like it for miles and miles, so people started coming to stay. Soon families and even whole towns were moving in to this bright and beautiful paradise. Ive seen drawings and pictures  it truly was ahead of its time as far as design and architecture. 

Once everything was well established my family started putting their efforts into building their own home. By this time the patriarch of the family was mayor and so he decided a mayoral mansion should be built on a wooded hill overlooking the city square. Not only was it beautiful land but very defensible. Two sides were high cliff faces and the other two were heavily wooded with the river (and city water supply) cutting across. The only way to approach the home easily was across a wide drawbridge that was flanked by two short guard towers. My family is from Ireland but youd be able to guess that if you saw the mansion. It was modeled very much like an Irish stronghold. I never understood why they felt it was necessary to be able to withstand a full-scale military attack but I do now.

Fast forward to my youth  I am seven or eight years old, an only child and one of seventeen young children living in the family estate. It was great fun then. Innocent and pure. No knowledge of my family history. We kept mostly to the estate grounds (we were told it was to keep us safe but in fact it was to keep us isolated and unaware of the hatred now extended to our family) and that didnt bother us. There was plenty to do and explore and have fun with. I went hunting and fishing, learned to ride horses, tended a small vegetable garden, and did lots of rambunctious kid things. 

One day all the kids decided to play hide and seek and I was excited because I was finally allowed to play it with them. Everyone seemed to know of a good hiding spot already but since I hadnt played before I was a bit clueless. I took off running and could hear the counter getting closer to zero but still no hiding spot. Just before time ran out I darted sideways down another hallway, then another and another, and scrambled up the steps of a narrow stone staircase. It wasnt a great spot but at least it was pretty far away. Maybe Id get lucky. I climbed onto the bannister and crouched behind the statue that sat atop it, hoping I was narrow enough to not be seen from the base of the stairs. Once my breathing slowed and my initial excitement wore off I started to look around at where I was and listen for incoming steps. There was no door at the top of the steps which I thought was weird and the stone was very different from anything else I had seen around the mansion but my young mind didnt think too much of these things. I wish I had. 

After a few minutes of waiting and hearing no one around I got bored and made my way back to home base to see if I won the game. As soon as I turned the corner of the last hallway I walked right into my mother. She grabbed me, crying and yelling, scolding me but kissing my face all over somehow all at the same time. 

*Whats wrong, mom?*

*What do you mean, Whats wrong? Youve been gone for three days! WHERE THE HELL HAVE YOU BEEN?!*

She broke out into huge sobs while hugging me tighter than any other time I can remember. Needless to say that was the last time I was allowed to play hide and seek. I couldnt explain it, didnt really understand the implications at the time. I was young and it was easily forgettable I suppose. Looking back on it now I dont see how I could have ever disbelieved all of the stories and legends about my family. Apparently on several different occasions kids have gone missing in our estate never to be seen again. It first happened right after the mansion was built. One of the grandkids had friends over and they went hunting for rabbits but none ever came back. The only thing they ever found was a shoe with the foot still in it. Another time the entire town came for the annual costume ball. Sometime during the event an amorous couple wandered off to have some fun but never came back. The town suspected foul play because the man was a favorite in the upcoming election and both were from prominent families. Not sure what happened but it looks like people were silenced or killed to keep things status quo.

Like I said, I didnt pay too much attention to the stories. I hated living cooped up on the estate, I hated the looks cast at me when I did manage to go to town. I am not sure if it was the death of my father or reading the U.S. Forest Service stories that jogged my memory but the stone staircase jumped to the front of my mind. I cant seem to get it out, actually, which is why I am even sharing this with you. My father was the youngest sibling and the last surviving member until now, which leaves me as the sole heir to the estate. I think it is time I investigate these stories. My plane is boarding so I will conclude this for now. Ill post an update when I have some answers.

[UPDATE](https://www.reddit.com/r/nosleep/comments/5wwufx/the_builders_part_2/) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Small value cash investment question </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-31 23:43:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> My wife and I had our first child (now almost eleven months old) and we received about $600 in cash at baby showers for her. We decided to save it for her instead of using it on items and opened a savings account. I'm trying to find the best investment to use it in for her. We found a 48 month,  1.8% CD we could put it in but is that our best option? Any advice would be much appreciated!  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> They want You to feel Safe - Part 2 </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-31 19:25:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [Part 1](https://www.reddit.com/r/nosleep/comments/5r2pm4/they_want_you_to_think_you_are_safe/)

Woke up this morning feeling exceptionally refreshed considering the situation I have found myself in. It is amazingly quiet in this house. Although my house is in a tiny stretch of homes on the far end of town I still have some pretty noisy neighbors. I bought my house out here, far from pretty much everything, for the peace and quiet. Of course I couldnt find that, usually keeping me up with their extremely annoying Mexican music blasting from their backyard patio or drunken fights after the music is finally turned off but I didnt hear them once last night. In fact, I dont recall hearing anything at all. A siren blaring or kids playing or the family of birds that live in the nearest tree. After a few minutes in bed thinking about this revelation and what exactly I was going to do financially I dragged myself out and found my way to the new, ultra-modern kitchen to get some coffee. Normally this could be done with my eyes closed, still half-asleep but with an entirely new layout to the kitchen (whole house, really) I needed my head up, eyes opened, and that is when I took my first look out the kitchen window.

The sun was just peeking up over the house next door. Odd, considering my neighbor on that side is on a downslope and usually I could see right over their roof. I rubbed my eyes and tried to knock out all of the sleep from my mind before looking again. Yes, it was not the same house. Walking over to the small bay window I took in a startling sight  every house was different. Every house that I could see was a NoSleep house! 

I ran to the front door and fumbled with all of the new, huge deadbolts, pressing my palm to the door to finally open it to the brisk morning air. Pulling my robe a little tighter around my body I stepped out and gasped. The entire neighborhood, *OVERNIGHT*, had changed. How could that even be possible? I couldnt even hear the salesman standing right next to me over the machinery being used to take care of my home yesterday yet I didnt hear a single thing from inside my home. I had to be dreaming. Nightmaring. A few others were stepping out into the morning sun on their new porches to survey the changes as well, one waving when she saw me. I waved back and began walking over.

*Morning! What a surprise, eh?*

*Yeah, hey thanks for the referral. We got a huge discount because of it.*

*Uh, yeah, sure. So you called the number on the flier as well?*

*Flier, what flier? We saw that salesman talking to you and asked him what was going on once you went back to work. He explained the situation providing protection against the fracking earthquakes, tornadoes, and other natural disasters we get so often around here. Plus being in a flood plain and all that. We never would have known if you didnt take the initiative and have them come out.*

*Yeah, great. Glad to help Hey I gotta get ready for work so Ill see you around.*

She called out a good-bye to my back as I made my way inside and shut the door. My mind was swimming and my stomach growling. I tried to reason things out over breakfast but nothing really made sense. Why did that guy lie to everyone about the houses? Taking out the business card and rotating it a few times in my hands  why the hell is this thing blank?

*Abra kadabra POOF!... Open Sesame!... Bazinga!... Be revealed*

Well that didnt work. I guess it isnt voice-activated like everything else in the house. I finished up my breakfast and got ready for work. 

-----------------------


Not very productive today. Who could be? All I am thinking about is the crazy new sub-division I am living in. At least I hadnt seen any of the cars parked out front but they could be in the garages. How much money did we just get suckered into giving away? A phone call from a client would snap me out of my revere from time to time but mostly alternated between checking the clock and pondering the implications of my new situation and how I would get out of it. 

**RING RING RING** It was the number I called to order the house. The disconnected number.

*Hello?*

An automated message spoke back - *Please return home, there has been an emergency. Your employee has been notified of your absence. Good bye.* 

As soon as the line went dead my boss knocked on my glass door and stepped in. He asked if everything was alright and I just shrugged, probably looking confused and a little scared. *Just call when you get it all cleared up and let me know if I can help with anything* he said. What else could I do? I went home.

Something was clearly wrong the moment I turned off of the highway and made the left-hand turn onto my street. Was it darker somehow? It felt darker. There were no clouds passing overhead. It was darker, and quiet. Not that I am usually home at 2 PM but I figured at least a few kids would be running around or the retired guy down the street would be out making his perfect lawn slightly more perfect. I eased up on the accelerator and cruised past each new, solid, powerful fortress of a home looking for any kind of movement or hint of life. Every shutter was drawn. On every home. Except mine of course. My garage door glided up just seconds before my front bumper collided with it and closed seconds after my rear bumper cleared the threshold.

I sprinted through the house and over to my control chair, hitting the lock-down button and watched as each door and window went through a series of changes. Secondary barriers slid into place, thick steel shutters slammed shut, a gentle whirring of locking mechanisms all around me. Within thirty seconds it was done and silence filled the room. I turned on the TV and changed the input to show the surveillance footage while I poured myself a drink. I still dont understand why I was following this insanity. An emergency? What emergency? How did they get me out of work? Why did my boss even take them seriously? I called in sick a few months ago and had to jump through flaming hoops just to get it approved as an absence. 

I got up and poured myself another drink and decided to at least enjoy this extra time as best as I could. Drink in hand, recliner kicked way back, 75 inches of 4K resolution the only light in the room. I watched. And I slept.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> They want you to Think you are Safe </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-30 19:54:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Like most of you in this sub I have had strange situations in my life. Unexplained, frightening, paranormal even. And like you I search here for answers. A few days ago a flier was left on my door, rubber banded on just like a new Chinese restaurant menu or church worship service begging for new attendants. I didnt think much of it and tossed it down with the rest of the mail I grabbed on my way in my home from work. I kicked off my boots, put away my lunch bag, unloaded my pockets of keys, wallet, phone, Chap Stick, work badge and changed into my lounge-wear. Once settled in my favorite chair I leaned over and grabbed the stack of mail, already having forgotten the flier. Bills, bills, junk mail, illegible letter from my grandmother, bills, and lastly the flier.

I dug through it all, made a halfhearted attempt at deciphering what my grandmother was trying to tell me, double-checked the amounts of the auto-payed bills before ripping them up and then pulled the rubber band off of the flier (I LOVE Chinese food). What I saw shocked me and I just sat there, staring, not really reading but just staring for a moment. It was an ad for homes, cars, and what appeared to be an all-in-one phone defense system tailor-made to secure a person from the spooks and haunts of r/NoSleep.

After reading over it a few times I laughed and called the number on the bottom, thinking it would be a hoax, and was even more shocked when a pleasant-voiced woman greeted me. *Welcome to NoSleep, Inc.* she said. *Would you like to place an order?* I stammered for a second and hung up.

Now I understand that we are supposed to suspend all disbelief, every story is true, and I am sure that most are. But there are some that just couldnt be, right? I try and try but my skeptical nature wont allow it every time so of course I called the number expecting a joke recording about how dumb I was for calling the number or whatever. Now I was intrigued, excited, but still very skeptical. I called back. A different person answered this time with the same greeting. Again I was shocked. I was expecting the same kindly voice of the first woman. I asked a few questions about the house and how much it was, playing along with the guy on the other end of the line. Damn this thing was pricey... but what do you expect when it is made up of things youve never end heard of before. Still, it sounded silly and, although elaborate, very much a hoax. So I did what anyone would do, I ordered a house.

I was too stupid to take a picture but I did transcribe the flier and post it online the next day because I knew you would all get a kick out of it, maybe even get a message from the creator asking for feedback or something. It was removed. Quickly. I did get it posted to another area so you could see it  [enjoy.]( https://www.reddit.com/r/thelongsleep/comments/5qj9q9/nosleep_inc/) Now fast forward to today when I get a call at work from my neighbor asking me why my current house is being bulldozed. What. The. Actual. Fuck. Took my lunch break to drive home only to see I had no home. Just a massive pile of timber, shingles, and crap heaping up towards the sky where my home used to be. Machine equipment everywhere and parked down the street is a semi with a huge house on a special trailer. As I made my way toward the closest man in an orange vest a car pulled up next to me, a VERY nice car that kind of looked like a Lexus, and a suit got out. In his hand was my invoice. 

---------------------------------------------------

I am now sitting in my new living room in my new chair trying to figure out what the hell just happened. Somehow within twelve hours my house was completely demolished, hauled off, land cleared and leveled, and a new house placed. I tried to call the number again but it was disconnected. Attached to my invoice was a blank business card and I am playing with it now as I type this out. Sometimes it feels smooth and sometimes I can feel indents in it but I cant seem to get those indents to become visible. Ill keep you updated on any progress I make. 

At least the chair is comfy..


[Part 2](https://www.reddit.com/r/nosleep/comments/5r9yoy/they_want_you_to_feel_safe_part_2/) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> NoSleep, Inc. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-27 20:53:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Are you afraid of all things that go bump in the night? Do you live alone? Does your family consist of psychopathic killers? Is your town rampant with indescribable creatures from your worst nightmares? Look no further, friend! We have a state-of-the-art, top-of-the-line catalogue to prepare you for whatever you already are or may encounter in the future.

First up is the NoOneIsHome Home  this massive structure comes pre-constructed and is fully customizable. With over thirty different styles and sizes you can have your dream home as well as your safe home. Floor plans range from 2-6 bedrooms and 1-6 bathrooms. Basements are available upon request and every home has a contingency room. Outer walls are constructed with a blend of poured concrete and nano-titanium and coated with lead and silver for supreme strength and invulnerability. The entire house is equipped with anti-phasing technology to disallow unwanted creepies from passing right through your walls. Each window is built out of shatterproof glass and equipped with steel emergency shutters. Likewise, your doors are twelve inch thick solid steel attached to maintenance-free hinges molded directly into the outer wall. Voice and active retinal scans are available as well as a smartphone app to manage your home with. Control your lights, temperature, doors and windows right from your phone! Your new roof is especially marvelous, being practical and indestructible. It is constructed of huge sheets of solar panels that are rated to withstand 350,000 lbs. of force per square inch. Nothing is getting in through that  except solar energy! In optimal weather conditions your roof can keep you off the grid for up to 45 days while you wait out the apocalypse from your comfortable couch.

Of course, you want to feel safe and protected 24/7 but you cant be in your fabulous home all the time. When you drive to and from work or to the grocery store, why not hop in a NotJustForPopesMobile. Have a crazed ex-military sniper in your neighborhood hell-bent on wiping out everyone because they all look like Charlie? No problem! This four-door sedan can withstand 50 caliber rounds, tank rounds, and drone strikes. Patent-pending technology that magnetizes the car to the ground so no one can move you where you dont want to go or flip your car with a bomb. Powerful chainsaws, flamethrowers, and other weapons are built into the frame, trunk, and front bumper to ward off zombies or other supernatural contenders. But dont worry. This car is also stylish, using a Lexus IS form to blend in and turn heads at the same time.

Scenario: You are a beautiful young woman, walking home from the local pub. It is a nice night out and only a few block away so what is the harm? BAM! A horrible drunk attacks you, trying to get inside that sweet, virgin treasurebox. What do you do? The NoThankYou is a smartphone that is equipped with a one million volt taser which activates when it senses danger. Thanks to our research and development team the phone syncs to your body and reads all of your vitals, muscle activity, even decoding your major senses for feedback. It will trigger automatically when you are in danger, creating a field around your body that zaps that horny bastard right to the ground. A distress call is made whenever the taser is activated with a safe word and a danger word that you merely need to think of. Once that is triggered we will know if you are OK or not! The phone is also connects to your home and your car. Batman isnt the only one who can summon his vehicles directly to his side!

CALL TODAY FOR MORE DETAILS! 1-800-NO-SLEEP </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> NoSleep, Inc. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-27 16:13:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Alex Smith is even worse at dodgeball that he is at football </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-27 13:19:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Helpers </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-24 17:46:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [Previous](https://www.reddit.com/r/nosleep/comments/5ppwqe/you_must_die_in_order_to_live/)

I knew I should feel horrible. I should be full of remorse and regret and guilt for being the cause of such a terrible accident. But I didnt. I felt alive! I felt genuine happiness. For the first time I was able to enjoy the sensations of life without pain or anxiety. I heard things without repercussion, felt the air ruffle my hair, and watched a bird land outside my bedroom window (which was open for the first time ever). Although it didnt last very long it was the greatest few hours Id ever had and I needed it back. Over the course of the next twenty four hours I tested the effects the car accident had on me. 

* For three hours only extreme sensations caused me to die

* The remaining twenty one hours slowly tapered back to a more normal response from my body, however I noticed slightly less sensitivity by the end of the day
What caused it? Was it an overload of information? The massive amount of heat, burning flesh, screeching tires and crunching metal, BOOM of the engine and screams of those inside and those running to douse the flames, the sirens of eight emergency vehicles coming on the scene? I couldnt say for sure but I was about to find out. 

I had never seen my father in person, just a few old pictures my mom kept for some reason. He had been in contact a few times to try and visit, make himself feel better about leaving us. Last time he called was about a year ago and he really wanted me to meet his new wife and kids. Yea sure Id love to meet the family that was good enough for you. But that was then, and this is now. Now I had a reason to see him - *Look at me, dad, Im better! You can finally teach me how to play catch.*

**Me** *Hey, uh, dad?*

**Him** *wow.. I cant believe you are calling here. Is everything ok?* I could practically see the tears welling up at the corners of his eyes.

**Me** *Yea yea everything is fine, dad, more than fine. I am better! I can do things like go outside now.*

**Him** *How, how is that possible? What did the doctors say?*

**Me** *It is easier if I just showed you. Want to bring Vikki and the kids over tomorrow for lunch? Ill make something for us.*

**Him** *Yea, of course, lunch. Ill take the day off of work and bring everyone by. We just got a puppy, Pickle. Want me to bring him, too?* The tremble is his voice was almost too much for me to take. He was just so happy.

**Me** *Sure cant wait to see you, dad.*

With that I hung up the phone and slowly made my way through the house, getting it ready for them tomorrow. Mom would be home soon from work and I had a lot of work to do. I wanted everything to be perfect for my first visit with my dad.

I had to get up at 5AM to ensure that the house was ready and lunch made in time for their visit but I made it just in time. Just as I laid out the last fork I heard a knock at the door. My heart was racing and I wasnt even being effected by any outside stimulus. I was nervous, excited, ready. Pausing at the door for a minute to regain my composure and let my heart settle down I slowly opened the door and let them in. All the excitement of five kids and a puppy hit me hard and I had to catch my breath after several deaths all in a row. Dad looked at me with sad eyes, knowing what pain and agony I just went through and realizing that I wasnt actually cured of anything. 

*Dont worry dad. It isnt as bad as it used to be and I am in the middle of an experiment that relieves my condition. Ill show you.*

Once they were all in I ushered them over to the table and they took their seats. I asked dad to say Grace and then we dug in to some delicious pancakes and eggs (It is all I really know how to make). Halfway through my second pancake I reached out and grabbed the knife for some more butter but instead plunged it deep into my fathers neck. The cold metal and warm blood would normally send my body into spasms and my heart would race, stop, race, stop. But not this time. I felt strength and a calming of my nerves just like the after the accident. His new wife screamed at the top of her lungs and tried to get up but only succeeded in crashing into one of her brats. I pulled the knife out of his neck with blood pumping out all over my arm and moved slowly around the table to his wife as she scrambled to get away. Kicking her in the face once, twice, then bending down and ramming the knife into her pleading eyes with all my force. She stopped moving immediately. Pickle was barking and whining, going from snapping its teeth at me and licking the blood off of the ground.

I turned, aglow with renewed vigor and life, towards the closest child. We had a huge bottle of extra strength superglue that I had coated the chairs with just before they arrived and it was doing its job. I reached out and snapped the neck of the closest and sprang away down the hall after the oldest. Her legs were long enough to reach the ground from a sitting position and she ran, hunched over towards the front door. I caught her by the hair and flung her backwards. She landed on her back, face covered in tears, mouth split wide in a scream. I stuffed the knife straight down her throat until I felt it connect with the vertebrae. Running back (amazing how trivial this seems to most but it was my first time doing so) to the last of them I made their cries stop quickly. Pickle was last. I honestly didnt know if an animal life would benefit me or not and I am still not quite sure. I was so high, so full of their life essence that I couldnt tell one way or the other. 

My body was strong, agile, not a single sensation caused my heart to race or stop. My experiment was a success!

I spent the rest of the afternoon cleaning up the mess and enjoying my new found freedoms. It wasnt until the next morning when I had my first relapse, which was minor in comparison to what it used to be, and even now as I type this with my actual hands I have yet to fall back into the state I once was. It is possible that either the violence of the death or the close connection I had to the persons dying caused it to be that much more medicinal. Of course, I have much more experimenting to do before I know whether it is permanently cured or not. Fortunately I have many [doctors who can help me.](https://www.reddit.com/r/nosleep/comments/5rvtzd/my_doctor_is_the_cure/)


[Narrated](https://youtu.be/GhzP843qpCs)

[](https://www.facebook.com/aaron.writes.1) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> You must die in order to live </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-23 17:47:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Have you ever wondered what it feels like to die? Is it painful when your body lets go of its last stores of energy? Are you aware that you are dying or do you think it will pass? Maybe you are one of the many that have thought it great to never be *able* to die. Like a superhero. Saving beautiful women from horrible men and little children from burning houses. Oh yes, that would be nice.

Now lets imagine you are walking up some stairs. The damned elevator is broken again and you have to trudge up five flights to get to your office building. Step up, step up, step up. After two flights you are a little winded perhaps, maybe you take your phone out and check e-mails to save time. That is when your foot catches the stop of a riser and for a split second you panic. Your heart races, your blood flowing fiercely through your body which causes your body temperature rises significantly and you break out into a sweat. In the next moment your foot finds the step and your panic recedes although you feel a little sheepish and hope no one witnessed the miscue. A few stairs later and your face is no longer flushed with the excess blood, your heart has returned to a normal rhythm, and all is right with the world. You may tread a little more carefully for the next minute or so, maybe even putting your phone back into your pocket or purse, and you forget about that moment in time.

These are all normal responses for a normal human being. Your body senses danger, your balance is thrown off and your mind knows the great distance you could fall should you go backwards. All normal. But what if I told you that **everything** caused your body to react that way. Every properly executed step. Every change in the winds direction. Every noise your ears perceive and every flash of color taken in by your retinas. What if your body could not differential between normal interactions with the world around you and emergency situations? I suppose, then, you would be me. 

My mother told me once that all I ever did was cry for the first few years of life. She couldnt understand it, the doctors couldnt understand it. Pain, the doctors told her. He is always in pain. There was nothing they could do because they couldnt find the cause. The only indication they had was my heart  it constantly revved up like I was in pain and then stopped very briefly before resuming a normal beat. She had raised four children already and knew exactly what each needed based on their cry, except for mine. It didnt take long for her to stop taking me places and pretty soon I was left alone in a dark room with the door closed and a primitive baby monitor keeping me company. 

I was small and weak, physically and mentally. Going outside for even a moment was enough to send me into shock. But I survived. I kept on going. As I grew up and my capacity for communication increased I was able to relate more of what I was going through with my mother and doctors. Unfortunately it was far too late for any real help or hope. The debt of constant hospital visits and specialists crippled my mother. My father only lasted a few weeks before giving up and leaving us. I told my mom to stop looking for a cure and focus on my brothers and sister, and thankfully she did.

I spent the next fifteen years by myself for the most part, except for those my laptop connected me to. School was out of the question so I enrolled in online learning that was an at-your-own-pace style. It was hard considering just touching the mouse or clacking on the keyboard sent my heart racing and stopping suddenly, mind crashing into mental walls of anguish and blinding light overtaking all of my senses. It is hard to describe but it was as if I tasted more than I could handle, heard more than I could process, smell so much I became clogged, felt every molecule colliding with my body, see so clearly the spectrum of visible light separated for me for a split second. It was so overwhelming every time. But I kept going. I survived. The episodes slowly grew worse, longer, harder to handle. I had to do something but I no longer had doctor visits or specialists calling the house or coming by to see if they could figure things out. I was on my own armed with the internet and a determination to prevail. 

Fast forward to today as I speak this aloud for my computer to transcribe. I have my answer, my cure. Death. As you are probably aware there is some very taboo stuff on the internet and as a person who literally spends his every waking moment online I have stumbled across a lot of it. I began studying death more deeply some time ago and it intrigued me. Something about it seemed so familiar but I wasnt sure why. I studied what death was, how people died, what religions thought about it, what people with near-death experiences describe. It slowly became clear to me that I was dying. With every touch, sound, blink of an eye I died. And came back. Again and again and again. Eventually my heart wont be able to take the constant trauma and I will die for good unless I can find enough *helpers*.

As I said I found a cure, but it isnt an easy one to obtain and I happened upon it by accident. Yesterday I was determined to make another attempt at outside for research and to see the world. This would make my fourth visit that I can remember to the world outside of my home. Wearing special sunglasses that block out almost all of the light and noise-cancelling headphones I took it very slow, my powerchair cruising at the slowest speed. I had died twelve times by the time I made it to the end of my driveway. Glancing up ever so slightly to one side and the next I made sure the road was clear and began the slow crossing. As I crossed the yellow line in the middle of the road I heard the loudest sound Id ever witnessed, dying for twentieth time. When I came back to myself I could feel the heat of the car crash a ways down the road, hear the screams of those inside the car and those running to help. I died nine more times trying to get away as fast as I could before the car exploded. 

Seven people died that day because of me. Four in the car and three who attempted to rescue them from the car before it blew. I could feel the blast on my neck as I powered away at a brisk 3 miles per hour. But I didnt die. Not that time. In fact I made it all the way back inside my home before I succumbed to another instance of my malady, caused by the high-pitched sirens of emergency vehicles arriving on the scene. 

I was filled with fear, filled with hope. It was time to [experiment..](https://www.reddit.com/r/nosleep/comments/5px61m/helpers/)

[Narrated](https://youtu.be/L8e5ZEMl_LU)

[](https://www.facebook.com/aaron.writes.1) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Going out with a bang </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-20 22:01:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [Before](https://www.reddit.com/r/nosleep/comments/5ozbf4/oh_so_many_shanes/)

I am writing this from my prison cell, formerly my office. Not quite sure why I still have access to a computer or anything really but I am assuming it is because in a short time Ill be lowered back down into the chamber for another go at fixing me and they figured it will be a successful conversion. This isnt the way that I had planned to fix things. Nor is it the way I hoped to die. But die I surely will.

I will try to clear up any confusion or missing details that I have purposefully (in case someone from the hospital found these posts online) left out of my other reports in case my plan doesnt work and you need to finish what I started. From what I can gather it looks like this hospital was founded with a very strict, special set of goals in order to promote health. Their mission statement and vision is to be lifelong partners for a healthier future. That sounds amazing, awesome. Thank you for caring so much! Unfortunately, the founders were a bit crazy and took *lifelong* a bit too far. I also dont think I agree with their definition of *healthier* either. As far as I can tell I am housing the memories and abilities of every single Shane that has worked there before me. The same goes for everyone else here with their originally hired employee. Looking back through the records of all the employees (yes, I broke in to HR one night) there are very few people that were hired with different names than the first employee. I am guessing that it makes it much easier to convert them without them knowing what is going on. I was one of only twenty nine total employees that did not have the same name already as the previous person. The most likely cause of this is that you just cant find a lot of Biomed Technicians so they have to take what they can get. The other instances of miss-matched names were positions like mine that werent very mainstream or common. 
	
Now you might be saying, OK, sure that is weird but it isnt really that bad right? Well, yes and no. It is great to be gifted with decades of knowledge and ability that you didnt have to learn. BUT having your family and friends killed and removed from existence is pretty awful and that is just what was happening. You cant have a person one day be Aaron and the next day be Shane without outside people growing suspicious. And that is why I have to stop them. 

As I said I had access to virtually every room in the hospital and now I am privy to lots of knowledge that I never used to have. Using that knowledge, I roamed the hospital looking for the ingredients I would need and took them home in my lunch bag so I didnt arouse suspicion. Over the past week I built a very powerful bomb in case I couldnt find a way to reverse what was happening here on an individual basis. I didnt know that the therapist would be connected to the hospital but I didnt want to take any chances so I swallowed the bomb before going to the appointment. On my phone I have a universal remote app that I programmed the bomb timer to. Ill activate it once I know for sure I am on my way to the chamber. My hope is that the bomb will be powerful enough to take out the chamber and whatever mechanisms/technologies are at play deep in that floor. In doing so maybe everyone will snap out of whatever trance this is. 

Please keep an eye out on the news for any bombings at a hospital or any weird circumstances. Dont let this continue..
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Oh so many Shanes </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-19 22:01:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [Before](https://www.reddit.com/r/nosleep/comments/5oqaju/to_be_shane_or_not_to_be_shane/)

I am sitting in bed with every light out, curtains drawn tight, and my phone screen as dim as it will go while still being visible in an attempt to ease the pounding in my head. I know I cant write it all down, there was just too much, but I will try to recount as best as I can the experience I had at the therapists office last evening. I did not expect to get in on the same day that I called the office but the doctor had a large block of time available so I took it. There must be a lull in the crazy people in my area right now. Dr. Tzilcammo was not a local, didnt even attend a college in this country, and had zero ties to my company. That is why I picked him in the first place. The second reason was because he specialized in dream interpretation and hypnotism. Most of his clients are soldiers with severe PTSD (there is a major military base nearby) and other similar mental situations. 

Fast forward to me lying down onto the couch and getting into the swing of things with the doc, I didnt give any background information or reasons why, just that I felt like I had amnesia or some kind of block on a large portion of my memories and I needed to free them. He asked a few questions, trying to probe into the situation but I didnt give him much. I dont recall what happened after that but I am assuming it was watching a pendant swing back and forth or counting down from a number and snapping of fingers. What I do know is that one minute I am lying down in his office and then I am not. I will do my best to describe what I saw and felt:

*I am at work, laying down on the floor of the workshop in the middle of a repair on what looks like VERY old equipment. As I am working I notice that my hands look different. Bigger. Wedding ring on the left hand. Nails jagged and dirty. My body looks different as well. A bit of a beer gut, strange clothing Id never wear, and from what I can tell at least a foot shorter than I am. What the hell is going on?*

***Shane, how much longer on that Zoll defib?***
*I found myself responding back although in a husky, old voice:* ***Eh, dont know bub. Looks like the paddle is busted.***

 **BAM**

*I am transported to a familiar hallway, walking from the shop to the warehouse where the door is  where I ceased to be. This body is extremely tall and lean, stickly and awkward. I duck to make it through the doorway and find myself toward the back of the pack. I am witnessing a burial (that is what I am calling it when someone gets lowered into that chamber). I dont recognize anyone in the room but I recognize the process very well.*

**BAM**

*Another body, this time recognizable. It is Shanes body. The man I replaced. The man I am now. He is talking to my boss about a new job opportunity that just opened up closer to home. He/I seem so excited. My boss does not.*

***What do you mean, another job, Shane? Dont you like it here at LMH?***

***Oh yea I mean it is great and all, but it is such a long drive. I barely see my kids you know?*** *(Shit, he had a family! I didnt see any of that on Facebook..)*

***I know but youll never find a better job than here, Shane. We are a family here. We are the best.***

**BAM**

*I am back in my body. My shoulders, now my waist is breaking through from the watery hole. The door that I am standing on finishes its ascent with a soft thud and the chains are removed from my wrists.*
***Welcome back, Shane***

The doctor brought me out of the trance, my eyes fluttering open but squeezing shut once again. Even in a dim therapy office at dusk the light was too much for my eyes. They watered and burned. When was this migraine going to go away? It was pulsing behind each eye and burning down my neck. I struggled to get into a sitting position and found my body and the couch drenched in sweat. Cracking my eyes open I sought out the doctor.

*So, did I say anything?* I asked.

*Oh yes. Yes, you said quite a bit. I dare say you said too much, Aaron.*

Through the watering eyes and the pain shooting out of them I didnt see it at first. Dr. Tzilcammo had a small pistol pointed at my chest.
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> To be Shane, or not to be Shane </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-18 17:23:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [Previous](https://wh.reddit.com/r/nosleep/comments/5ode3u/hi_im_shane/)

*I am going to give you a piece of my mind* 

*It is on the tip of my tongue*

*In the back of my mind*

Expressions that we use often but take for granted. At least I know I did, until now. I am still struggling with it all but things are becoming a little clearer. A little more focused. Someone has taken a piece of my mind and I want it back.

I wear glasses normally, not because I need them for every situation but it helps my eyes to focus. I have a strange condition where one eye is near-sighted and one eye is far-sighted. Without glasses my brain allows one eye to take over depending on the situation, which is great because it means I can always see, however it also means that during that time my other eye is unfocused and therefore slowly weakening. As with any muscle you must continue to use it in order for it to be strong and agile. Thus my need for glasses. They dont help me see much better but they help me focus both eyes at the same time and keep them strong. I bring this up only because of a comment that was made about light bending /u/AlphonseLermontant. I believe that my rare condition is the reason I am stuck somewhere in between my true self and my fake self, the person they want me to be. 

In order to test this theory I pretended to lose my glasses and borrowed a pair from a coworker while trying to read the cafeteria menu. Of course I couldnt see well from her pair (she is quite old and had a VERY strong prescription) but I did steal a glance at my badge while feigning to decipher the daily special. It was blurry and I was seeing in triplicate BUT I could make out two letters. R and O. My heart fluttered and my stomach filled with butterflies. It was true what you all had said. My badge didnt say Shane but Aaron. I must have let out more excitement than I wanted to because a few people around me looked over at me in a funny way like I was crazy for being that happy about tomato bisque with rye toast. Briskly walking out without even ordering food I went off to one of my hiding spots that I know about but cant remember how I know about it to contemplate this new discovery. Thinking is very hard to do at the moment. I have a massive migraine, my eyes burn from a lack of sleep, my brain feels split in two. Ever play charades or Catch Phrase and you KNOW what the person is trying to get you to say but you just cant find the right word. It is on the tip of your tongue but it just wont leap off. That is what I feel with every memory I try to bring up.

I lost track of time in that closet. Maybe I fell asleep, maybe I didnt, I am not sure. My boss found me as I was walking out and got on me about my production the last few days. Blah blah blah. I told her I wasnt feeling well and that I was sorry. Id get some rest and double my efforts tomorrow, promise. Of course I had no desire to do either but she didnt have to know that. I probably wouldnt be working here much longer anyway. On my way home, and I use that term very loosely, I stopped by a Target and faked my way into another prescription. I think that whole *Is this better.. or this* is a bunch of bullcrap anyway so I just answered as willy-nilly as I could while still being able to see clearly enough. With a new pair of cheap glasses in hand I searched my place for any clues or changes that I could not decipher before. I found a couple, always regarding my name. I am fairly confident now that my theory was correct and at least one part of it is fixed: they did something to my brain to **make me see certain things differently**. Obviously they planted new memories and other things into my head as well as altering my old memories to fit what they wanted and I dont know how I can fix that but at least I know about it. 

They say that knowing is half the battle so that is something, right? I spent the rest of the night trying to force my way into those memories, the real ones. They are there, way in the back, muffled and blurry. I am trapped somewhere between everything being on the tip of my tongue and being in the back of my mind. 

I am going to see a therapist about being hypnotized so that they can help me unlock those memories, kind of like repressed memories. That always works in the movies, right? Ill report back with anything I may find out after my appointment.
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Bards need love, too </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-17 23:10:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Hi, I'm Shane </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-16 21:52:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [Before](https://www.reddit.com/r/nosleep/comments/5m8yjo/my_name_is_not_shane/) | [After](https://www.reddit.com/r/nosleep/comments/5oqaju/to_be_shane_or_not_to_be_shane/)

Hows it going, everyone? I decided to come on here because it looks like I may have posted on here before but I dont really remember doing it. I was checking my e-mail and saw some replies that lead me here but I dont even remember making an account. Of course curiosity got the best of me and after a few hours of reading the top r/nosleep posts and comments I figured maybe you as a community could help. Other posters seem to think so, anyway.

Every day I get up and do the same routine. Put on deodorant, get dressed, make a lunch for work, eat breakfast, warm up the car, gather up my phone and badge and keys and glasses and head to work. I listen to the same radio station, listening to the same stupid arguments about why our team is good or bad or how awful the refs were during the game. I park in the same parking spot, sit down and watch the same daily YouTube channel until it is time to clock in, say hi to all the same people from my office to the timeclock, and then go about my day. I repair things that I dont remember ever learning about almost like it is second nature to me. I eat lunch at the same time every day. With exactly fourteen minutes left to go in my shift I start to pack everything up, go take a crap in the bathroom, and clock out after washing my hands. When I get home I unpack my lunch, change into comfortable clothes, go through the mail, and relax with a beer and Netflix. Sometimes I go dancing on the weekends at a few of the cool bars around town.

I feel a satisfaction from it all, a sense of purpose and direction. But I dont know why. Or how.

I didnt take a crap today. Weird how that was what really stuck out to me but it was. No crapping. As I wandered (I never wander) around my new home (my old one burned down, but I didnt remember that) I looked at all the pictures and knick-knacks. Staring back at me are faces I dont recognize aside from a vagueness, a nagging feeling in the back of my head that says I should but dont. Written on the backs of them are names and dates and locations. *Shane, Lisa, Owen  Grand Canyon 94* Bowling trophies and a diploma from the local university, a huge new TV and surround sound decorate the rest of the house. It is very impersonal. I cant imagine I am this boring.

I found a box of DVDs and popped one in. Bourne Identity. Good movie. Maybe it was only good because I can relate so much to it. Afterwards I tried calling a few numbers in my phone. There were only five numbers so I decided to just call all. My sister, Lisa. Brother Owen. Parents. Lauren, girlfriend. Dave, boss. Of the five only two numbers were active. 

Dave sounded cheerful when he answered. I lied and said I was just testing out the reception of my new phone. Lauren practically jumped through the phone when I called and said she would be on her way over in a little while. I guess that is a good thing, maybe Ill get some answers. Anyway I finally feel the urge to take a crap so Ill log back in after Lauren leaves and hopefully have some answers.

-------------

**UPDATE:**

Everything seemed to go well with Lauren. We laughed and talked and went out for some Indian food. It seemed natural, normal, yet so hollow. Even the sex afterwards. Oh sure it was amazing, but somehow artificial. Like I didn't deserve it. Does that make sense? The weirdest thing was that when I went to pay for dinner I signed the check with [this](http://imgur.com/a/kAflx). That doesn't look like it fits my name at all.. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> My name is not Shane - Final </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-15 02:23:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [Part 1](https://www.reddit.com/r/nosleep/comments/5m8yjo/my_name_is_not_shane/) | [Part 2](https://www.reddit.com/r/nosleep/comments/5n7mg8/my_name_is_not_shane_part_2/) | [Part 3](https://wh.reddit.com/r/nosleep/comments/5ngp58/my_name_is_not_shane_part_3/)

We ran. We stumbled. We ran some more. Blindly, without regard for direction or purpose. My lungs burned, my legs wobbly, and my face covered with sweat from sprinting up several flights of steps and across many yards of empty hallways. That was when I realized I never once heard someone chasing. I reached a hand out to Lauren to steady her and after a second to catch our breath I led her to my most secret hiding place. It was an unmarked room that only three people could open. We hunkered down and regained our composures and our breath. I hadn't run like that since high school! 

Fortunately I keep snacks in my hiding places so that I don't need to bring them around. Much less suspicious that way, you see. Anyway, I reached up to the back of the top shelf and brought down a box of frosted mini wheat and a box of Ritz Bitz crackers. We ate as silently as we could, to nervous to enjoy the sustenance. 

After a while we chanced a few whispers:

*What do we do?*

*Gotta wait. Listen for any pursuit or search party*

*Maybe security will think it was just a vandal. Maybe no one saw our faces*

*Do you know who even called out back there? I didn't recognize the voice*

*No I haven't even worked here a week yet..*

*What was that? Shhhhh*

--------

We practically broke our necks craning our ears toward the door in hopes of knowing what might be just outside. No other sounds were heard. Hours passed by but nothing seemed to be happening out side of our hiding spot. Lauren needed to pee and the bathroom was literally across the hall. She cracked the door, waited. Cracked a little more, waited. All clear. She darted across into the bathroom to relieve the building pressure in her bladder, a pressure I was starting to feel as well. 

My head snapped up and dizziness overtook me for a moment. Shit, did I fall asleep? How long? SHIT, WHERE IS LAUREN? Maybe I just dozed for a moment and she will be coming right back. I waited, counting seconds in my head. Five minutes passed. Ten.

The door screams as I open it. God, you are a loud bastard! I peek my head out and look both ways like a little kid crossing the street. I step out. Cross the hall to the bathroom door. Crack it open. *Lauren?* No answer. I step in and check all the stalls. It's empty. They got her. At this point I just stopped caring and ran out and down the hall toward the basement. If she was alive she'd be there. Maybe I still had time. 

Rounding the last corner of another completely empty hall I skidded to a halt. Hundreds of employees gathered in a circle, filing the entire warehouse and spilling out of the entrance and into the hallway. No one turned around and I stepped back behind the corner. There was a fire escape of the far side of the warehouse I could get to from outside and maybe see what was going on invisibly. Making my way out into the cold and around the hospital made me realize just how exhausted I was. It had been over a day since I had slept. Finally I got to the door and badged it open, pulling it open just enough to get my lean frame in. For once I was thankful for the fire code of two separate doors. The inner door had a window so I could see in without needing to open it. 

They had her. Standing on the door, hands chained together in front of her. I couldn't hear what they were saying but the president took a key out that matched a key being held by the HR director. The keys were attached to a chain hanging down almost to the ground from her hands and pressed into the holes in the door. A pale light emitted from the crease around the door as it slowly dropped down into the floor with Lauren chained to it. I could see her mouth split as wide as it could go and her entire body straining against the chains as she screamed. Still, she descended. The pale light moved and sloshed like water in a jacuzzi. Oh God they are going to drown her!

I watched in horror as her eyes slid past the edge of the floor. Then the top of her head. The light showed water just below her head. Then two facilties workers brought a metal cover over and set it onto the hole in the floor, sealing off the light. 

My mind raced but in all the wrong directions. What could I do. There were police in there. I couldn't call 911. I had to get her out and fast. Making my way back to my hideout, I sat and sobbed. It all flooded out. I couldn't help it. My body heaved and shuddered. Again, I fell asleep. 

When I awoke Lauren was staring down at me, a smile on her beautiful face. *Hi Shane*

-CRACK-

She must have hit me hard because when my mind regained it's abilities I was chained and surrounded by my coworkers. She called me Shane. I'm not Shane! The keys went in. I slowly descended into a frigid liquid. She knew my real name. Why? Why?! The lid was placed over my head. All light was sealed off. 

I'm not sure how long I was in there. And I'm not sure what I was babbling about this whole time to you all about. 

My name ***IS*** Shane.
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> My name is not Shane - Part 3 </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-12 03:32:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [Part 1](https://www.reddit.com/r/nosleep/comments/5m8yjo/my_name_is_not_shane/) | [Part 2](https://www.reddit.com/r/nosleep/comments/5n7mg8/my_name_is_not_shane_part_2/) | [Part 3](https://wh.reddit.com/r/nosleep/comments/5ngp58/my_name_is_not_shane_part_3/) | [Part 4](https://www.reddit.com/r/nosleep/comments/5o16dg/my_name_is_not_shane_final/)

Today something new happened, something I only now realize I've seen just once before. A body was carted, covered and zipped up in a silver bag, down the basement hallway past my workshop and into the morgue. I say it was new because up until right now as I type this out I  thought it was. But I'll get back to that. 

Moments after the faceless body bag was pushed slowly into a huge steel room I've never been in and hope to never be in I saw my first new face since working here. She was stunning, breathtaking even. I fulfilled every clich in that moment. My heart raced, my mouth hung open, and I'm pretty sure I had a semi. Her eyes mirrored every color that she passed. Her posture perfect yet not aggressive. Petite. And lips like Angelina Jolie. Describing her fills me with shame knowing I paid so much attention yet can barely stammer out a few ugly words. 

She stopped, held out her hand. *"Hi, I'm Lauren."*

*"Nice to meet --"*   ***"SHANE! This bed isn't fixing itself."***

*"Thanks boss. Thanks. I'll be right there. So yeah, nice to meet you."*

I must have looked like a kicked puppy because he apologized once I stepped into the workshop and closed the door. 

Lauren worked in food services, taking patients orders and delivering the food. I saw her often because I went from room to room fixing things and she went room to room filing bellies and lightening dark rooms with her eyes and smile. We talked a bit and something magical happened. She used my real name. I wasn't Shane to her. Do you know what it feels like to hear your name for the first time? It's impossible to describe but I took every chance to talk to her, just to hear her say it. We actually have a lot in common. Dancing, sports, same strange obsession with eating hot peppers. And by the end of the day exchanged numbers, planning on going out to dance tonight. If that goes well I hope to ask her over on Sunday to watch the game. 

During one of our three hundred conversations (I know, I know, pathetic) I drummed up the courage to ask her about the person she replaced. She didn't know much, except that her name was Lauren also. 

God, it felt so good to hear my name. I could listen to her say it for hours. Anyway, back to the body bag. This morning I thought it was the first time I'd seen one and just attributed it to a great hospital staff and modern medicine. But now I remember seeing a body rolled past me once before but I didn't realize what was happening at the time. It was my first day at work. Now that I think about it, it was the same two people pushing the body down the hallway. Weird.

Oh yeah, Lauren is calling! Gotta go get ready. 

She said my name again when I answered. I think I'm in love. 


We danced to a few songs, drinks in hand, never spilling a drop, smiling and grinding a bit. A weird song neither of us knew came on next so we took the opportunity to get some water and talk some more. 

"How come everyone at work calls you Shane?"

Her question caught me off guard, not because it was a difficult question to answer (or maybe it was) but because I never thought anyone would ask it. And everything came flooding out of my mouth. I told her about the employee I replaced and his name somehow passing on to me, about how much I hated it, about the door I found and the two dead bodies I'd seen. About them coming on first days and how she was the first new employee I'd seen in five months. My mind finally caught up with my mouth and I firmly placed my hand over it. 

*"I'm sorry, I talk fast when I'm nervous"*, I mumbled. 

*"You know what I think? I think we need to get into the morgue and look at that body."*

*"What, when?"* I asked. 

*"Tonight."*

That last word caused my drink to reverse course, spewing from the sides of my mouth. 

She laughed a melodious laugh, tossed a few napkins at me and got up, shaking her cute butt to the beat of the newest song. Sheepishly, I cleaned the corners of my mouth and bounced up behind her in an attempt to get close once again... and close we got. A few songs later and she suggested we head back to my place to plan our break-in. 

I'm writing this from my bed, her hair tickling my arm. It was some plan. 

-------------

**UPDATE:**

I am exhausted and scared. After a short nap Lauren and I got dressed for work, only we were going in seven hours early. Her plan was simple and flawless, or so I thought after a few drinks and an orgasm. A word to the wise, never trust your brain after sex. Anyway, the hospital is usually a ghost town after about 5PM in the basement because that is where all of the maintenance, facilities, cleaning type of workers have their offices and of course that is where the morgue. 

We came in through a door that doesn't need badge access but isn't a main entrance either so as not to be spotted and crept down to the basement. I had been here before at this time answering an on-call from the ICU department and it didn't seem creepy or frightening then but it certainly did now. The quiet was tangible, pressing against me with each step. Coincidentally the door that I found and the morgue are in the same large warehouse so I took Lauren over to it and showed her. 

Squatting down to get a good look with her I noticed the door was slightly damp and one of the plugs was missing from the two central holes that a handle probably fits into. While she ran her fingers over the door's seam I searched the immediate area for the plug, praying it wasn't me who lost it when I first discovered the door. I almost let out a whoop when I found it and pushed it back into it's home but when I did some liquid forced its way up and out of the hole. There was no noticeable scent to it, or strange feel or texture. It seemed to just be water. I guess the strangest thing about it was that ONLY the door was damp, not even a tiny portion of the surrounding floor. 

Instead of wasting too much time with a door I couldn't open we made our way over to the huge steel door that lead into the morgue. As I have said before, I have a lot of master keys and a few master codes to keypad doors. Fortunately one of them was the right one and after a few tries I was able to get the door open. We stepped inside of a small, chilly chamber just big enough for four people. In the center was a sleek steel table about eight feet long. On the left and right of the entrance were matching steel work tables, covered in gleaming surgical tools. 

Drills. Saws. Hundreds of scalpels of all shapes and sizes. Steel bowls and bins. Forceps. An industrial sink with huge over-head handles like in a restaurant. 

On the far wall was what we came in here for. Four steel doors with bodies behind them. 

I took a deep breath, shivered a bit from the cold air entering my lungs, and stepped across the room. One hand on the handle and one hand gripping Lauren, I pulled. Empty.

We locked eyes for a second, relief on both of our faces. I am not sure what we thought we would find in the first one but apparently both of our imaginations were running wild. I gripped the next one and pulled. Empty. The third, empty. The fourth, not empty. 

SHIT.

Another deep breath and I grabbed the sliding tray with both hands. It slide out easily on well maintained rollers and so did the Taco Bell we had on the way to the hospital. Staring up at us was Lauren. The old Lauren. The one that was replaced.

I couldn't breath, I couldn't think. I slammed the tray back in, shutting the door. Shit, vomit everywhere. Never eat Taco Bell. Never never. I leaped two steps over to one of the sinks and grabbed the over-head handle. The water stream was powerful and freezing cold. It blasted the vomit toward the drain underneath the center table easily and after a few seconds the floor looked brand new. 

*"Hello?"*

We ran.
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> My name is not Shane - Part 2 </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-10 21:55:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [Part 1](https://www.reddit.com/r/nosleep/comments/5m8yjo/my_name_is_not_shane/) | [Part 2](https://www.reddit.com/r/nosleep/comments/5n7mg8/my_name_is_not_shane_part_2/) | [Part 3](https://wh.reddit.com/r/nosleep/comments/5ngp58/my_name_is_not_shane_part_3/) | [Part 4](https://www.reddit.com/r/nosleep/comments/5o16dg/my_name_is_not_shane_final/)


Sorry about the delay. I was out of state at my brothers wedding. So. Much. Fun! I never realized I enjoyed dancing so much. I don't think I have ever been to a club or really ever danced at a wedding or party, either. Definitely going out this weekend to keep the party alive. During the reception I was talking to a few buddies and they were excited about the Super Bowl and how big their party was going to be, yada yada. That was when I realized that I had never thrown one myself. Or even been to one. Weird. I was in a pretty good mood heading back in to work until I clocked in and had my first "hello" from a co-worker. God, I hate that name so much. Shane. Shane. At least the time-clock knows what my name really is.

As I cruised around the hospital from repair request to the next my mind wandered back to that door I had found and I started to plan how I could get a fair amount of alone time with it to investigate. A few of our machines make a permanent home down in the basement but as long as we own them they need to be maintained so I decided I'd volunteer to take the lot of them on and get them calibrated for the year. All I needed was some tools and our calibration system to take down to them and I can work on them all day. My boss agreed quickly, probably because he doesn't want to do it, and so the next day I gathered up what I needed and headed down.

Once in the basement I laid out all of my calibration equipment and tools in a neat row and positioned all of the equipment that needed to be worked on around me in a circle, one so that I could access each one rather easily and two so that I could be mostly blocked from all views while I messed with the door that I placed strategically inside with me. I was about halfway through the first machine when I took a break to check out the real reason I was down there. Grabbing my mini Maglite and soft bristled brush I went to work trying to find a real seam or gap that I could wiggle a screwdriver into. As I worked it became increasingly more obvious that this was not supposed to be found. I'll do my best to describe my findings now.

The door is 16 inches by 16 inches perfectly square and 1/4th of an inch lower than the floor around it. It is perfectly level and has two small holes drilled into the middle nine inches apart. I couldn't see the holes before because they were filled in with some type of soft putty insert that matches the color of the floor, like a temporary plug. The holes are only an inch or so deep from what I can tell with the Maglite. The outer seam is also filled with that putty but more like caulking in this case and the seam is only 1/8th of an inch thick. This door is designed well! So well that it pushes my curiosity further and further into skepticism and fear. I have read enough r/nosleep and SCP articles to know when I am in too deep but somehow I am driven forward. Call it blind stupidity.

I could probably have finished up all of the equipment down there in one day but I knew that I needed to find the handle that lifted up that door so I took my time instead and split it up into two days. When I came in the next day an idea came to me. Maybe I could make my own handle. We have a huge parts room that rivals any hardware store. Surely I could cobble together something that fit the threads and be able to lift it up so I went and grabbed a few different sized bolts and washers to see what I could fabricate.

All of the first batch were too big but on the next visit I hit pay dirt with an eye-hook screw. Using an old power cable I threaded through both of the eye-hooks I had my handle. Giving it a tug was futile, however. Even getting into a deep squat and using my entire body I couldn't even feel the door give one bit. The cord snapped, I lost my balance and tumbled back into the equipment I had circled around, making a massive crash. Several people ran to the noise and fortunately I had enough time to get my eye-hooks out before anyone noticed.

*"Are you OK, Shane?! What happened?"*

Holding back a low growl I responded with a lame "I tripped" excuse and went back to work on one of the pieces of equipment.

*"Oh Shane, always being so clumsy! Do you remember the time Shane.."* Everyone walked out shaking their head and laughing and sharing stories of my clumsiness. The only problem is that I had never done any of the things that they talked about. Not a single one.

----------

UPDATE:

The episode today at work really freaked me out. I tried to distract myself by driving around, going into some stores but nothing could take my mind off of it so I went home and made some calls. First I called the hospital that Shane took a new job at to see if I could speak to him. The guy I spoke to said there weren't any Shane's working in Biomed. I asked a few questions, maybe he is in maintenance or something but still no Shane. With shaking hands I called a few more hospitals in search of Shane, then more, then all in the entire metro. No one had a Shane.

For some reason I called the first hospital back and asked to speak to the hiring manager this time. What he told me made my blood go cold. Yes, they hired Shane, but he never showed up to work.

I hopped onto Facebook next in hopes of finding a recent post by Shane and alleviate my fears. Shane hasn't made a post or picture or status for YEARS! Looking back thru his history he stopped posting a few months after joining my hospital. What is even more disturbing is that his only friends are coworkers. He used to have friends but must have removed them all. His last post had comments from other people, family it looks like based on last name, and a few school buddies. All of them appeared worried about something.

It didn't take long to dig thru his old posts because of the rarity of them so I started looking at my coworkers pages. After a few people I noticed a trend and after several hours of checking I have condoned that every single person that I work with is ONLY friends with coworkers. Not a single extra friend out of every person I could find. God, just typing that out makes me sick and cold inside.

Anyway, while I was out I decided to finally get a new TV so I picked up a 60 inch 4K Samsung for my football party this Sunday. I'm going to have everyone over for each game our team is still in the playoffs. I'd keep blabbing on but I'm off to go dancing. I'll update my progress with the door tomorrow.
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> My name is not Shane </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-05 21:48:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [Part 1](https://www.reddit.com/r/nosleep/comments/5m8yjo/my_name_is_not_shane/) | [Part 2](https://www.reddit.com/r/nosleep/comments/5n7mg8/my_name_is_not_shane_part_2/) | [Part 3](https://wh.reddit.com/r/nosleep/comments/5ngp58/my_name_is_not_shane_part_3/) | [Part 4](https://www.reddit.com/r/nosleep/comments/5o16dg/my_name_is_not_shane_final/)

My name is not Shane.

I just wanted to clarify that right now. Four months ago I began my career as a Biomedical Technician at a local hospital. It wasn't the best paying job and it was not as close as my last job to home but it was a start. Getting a foot in the door is the hardest part from what I understand. Anyway, my co-worker was really nice and the rest of the staff at the hospital seemed kind enough. Always waving and smiling. And never learning my name.

I attributed it to being new at first but even people I saw every day never remembered it. They could remember the once-a-week contractor just fine, but me? Nope.

Normally this wouldn't bother me because I have a hard time remembering peoples names as well and I have been known to say the wrong name from time to time. It started to bother me, however, when I had every single name memorized and NO ONE had mine. Petty? Maybe. But try it for a few months and tell me it doesn't get ridiculously annoying and belittling. What was even more strange is that everyone called me the same wrong name....

Shane.

After a month I was "let loose" from the training label and started to move a little more freely around the hospital instead of having to follow my co-worker around like a lost puppy. A part of our job is to do repairs on all of the equipment so I have the master code to all keypad locks and a few keys that will open basically any door in the hospital. In my down-time I'd wander around and explore, opening up random closets in search for lost equipment and to better understand the layout of the hospital (and to find a great hideout when I wanted to just sit and watch YouTube videos).

A few months of poking around and I had peeked into just about every room I could find but one day as I was looking thru some old equipment in the basement storage for a missing ECG machine I found a door. There was no key, no keypad, no lock, virtually no seams either. And it was on the floor. Once I cleared the clutter away I squatted down to inspect it.

Was it a drain? No, that didn't make any sense. Was it access to a sub-basement? Shouldn't even be one, all of our plumbing is here and our boilers are outside.

Just as I started to run my fingers along the very faint crease my body cringes from the sound I hate most.

"Shane? Shaaaaaaneee."

"Ya over here, and it's NOT Shane. Did you find the ECG?"

"Sure did, let's test it to make sure it still works."

Days went by but I couldn't get that strange "door" out of my head so I let myself into our records room that has all of the blueprints and schematics for the hospital hoping to find an answer. None. Not one damn mention of anything being underneath the basement storage. No electrical. No plumbing. Nothing. Undeterred, I make it a point to keep digging when I have time. I even made a daily alarm on my phone.

The next day during lunch my co-worker and I were talking about football and how we couldn't wait for the season to start. Our team was going to be very good this year, you know. Apparently the guy that I replaced was a huge football fan. Tailgated every Sunday, had huge parties for the Superbowl, that kind of thing. I had never heard anyone talk about him before so I asked what happened. It seemed like a sour subject because my co-worker just mumbled a bit about him not giving any notice and taking another job downtown at the school hospital. [Oddly enough I had applied for the same job but after making it to the final three candidates I was knocked out. Lack of experience, they said.]

"Sorry he skipped out on you like that. What was his name?"

"Shane."

------

UPDATE: Thanks to a vigilant helper my past has been resurrected. In my attempts to figure out what has happened to me /who I am it seems other powers are at work to stop me. Somehow this post was deleted but a good samaritan recovered it for me and I can now read it. I'll continue working on being able to read the others as well. Thank you all for your continued help in my identity crisis!  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What is the best r/nosleep? Why? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-04 21:50:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What did you do with your day off, today? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-03 02:02:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Anxious friends of Reddit, how do you cope? Is there anything other people can do to help? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-30 02:48:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> "The Dreaded Ocho" - what type of behavior is this? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-29 17:53:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> ELI5: Why do your hands smell horrible after touching stair railings but not after touching other metal objects? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-29 16:16:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> I legit have the cutest kid in the world </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-28 18:07:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> If you could only eat one food for the rest of your life, what would you choose and why? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-27 19:48:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Does stress actually turn your hair gray? What else causes the change? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-27 00:05:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> ELI5 how Linux works. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-24 16:59:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Why is it my daughter can crawl around all day without issue but I crawl around for an hour to play and I get dry skin and pressure sores? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-24 03:44:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What is the most orgasmic non-sexual activity you do? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-23 01:25:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Why does my hair hurt? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-20 00:30:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Wearing a beanie all day and my hair gets matted down. When I run my fingers thru it it hurts, or maybe a better term would be sensitive. Why is this?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Hacking my Panasonic smart tv? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-17 21:37:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hey guys, I have a smart tv that is up to date but not really compatible with videos anymore. Some sites I can watch but others I can't. I was wondering if there is a way to jailbreak or hack my tv so that I can put a different browser on it and have full functionality again. Thanks for any insight!  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> I'm done </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-09 14:28:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This game is just ridiculous now. The latest update is just awful and I am sick of all of the spoofers, alt account losers that wreck this game. I tried to take it all in stride but today was the straw that broke the camels back.

It was a pretty cold morning so I had my jacket and whatnot but my hands were freezing. Still, I decided to take a few level four gyms and collect my meager coins. I head to the first one and take it. Moving on the second I notice a dude in a car just watching me like I'm some sexy college girl. He sees me looking so he leaves. I am thinking, weird but whatever. Once I am done with the second gym I move on to the third and he is sitting there as well. I begin taking the gym but error out (freaking stupid game). It is cold so I give up and go to collect but behold the creeper has taken both gyms. Now this is the frustrating part about it.. THEY ARE THE SAME TEAM AS ME!!! The dude literally waited until I took out Valor and then took me out to place an Instinct in to collect coins. THEN he took himself out and put his other Mystic account in. WTF?!

Done. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Brees or Newton </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-27 18:57:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Standard 1 QB league on ESPN. Who should I start? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> a18916546 - Add me so I can add you! </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-13 14:20:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Comment with yours and I'll get you back :D </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> My phone is dying (Galaxy S5) </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-27 16:00:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Alright so I have purchased a spare battery, try to switch them every day or two and give them a day off before charging back up. I am still seeing very fast total battery capacity loss but that is somewhat to be expected. 

What I was NOT expecting is that my phone is basically a POS now. It lags even outside of the game, and when playing PoGo it is good half the time and awful the other half. Today I missed about half of my stops because it was hanging up so badly which I have never witnessed. Gyms are almost unusable.

Anyone else experiencing this? Is it specific to my phone?

Thoughts, methods of extending my phone life, comments, etc

Thanks! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Lenexa Mystic players </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-26 18:46:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hey all,
Looking to band up with a few players to build some lvl 10 gyms and hold them. I have three gyms right near me that are hotly contested but I think with the right group we can hold them pretty easily. If interested let me know. Or if you need another player to help out your area let me know as well. Cheers. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Vulpix Nest/Spawns </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-23 22:08:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hey all! I am in Lenexa and I have only found one Vulpix thus far (lvl 25). Any idea on a consistent location to find them? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
