<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject7048</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-06 02:02:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That's awesome

I don't know why but I feel privileged right now
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-05 20:28:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> wtf </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-01 23:35:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That was a joke </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Tried backdooring on Urf but couldn't damage the Nexus. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-01 23:14:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The enemy team had 2 inhibitors down and I tp'ed on a ward to backdoor them with Caitlyn, but I couldn't damage the nexus. I was hitting like crazy and critting, but the nexus took no damage. At least we won right after, Kassadin did the same but he could damage it. 
Wtf is this bug?
It's not an 1st april joke too

And this is a post corresponding to pi (314159) so yeah better everyone start voting up that shit because there won't be another one </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-01 13:39:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The only me is me. Are you sure the only you is you? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-01 05:19:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Wow, lets troll at Reddit Community. 
I bet you have an fake vvortic account and type 'JOEL SKYPE" in every twitch chat. 
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-01 04:39:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I don't see how that Lee sin combo would work really, because it's actually forcing people to enter the Bard's skill which is not the idea AND it doesn't add too much to the board. Now if you actually can have two people compounding their skills to perform a certain objective, than that's a thing. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-31 23:46:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Well they don't actually NEED to start ulting from that far. 
Let's have an example:
The enemy team is doing dragon and you are blued side. Sion and Bard already have the strategy to make the play, so Sion ults and Bard throw his E at the wall, making a surprise engage and maybe even stealing the dragon itself. The rest of his team could either follow the engage by the Magical Journey or flank by the river while all happens.
Just imagine the possibilities. :) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Can we make Sion enter Bard's E while ulting? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-31 23:19:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Of course his ultimate time would keep counting while he's in the middle of the Magical Journey, but if it could be used wisely, then Bard would have even more playmaking chances and a really cool "surprise" for enemy teams.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-13 10:21:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Its only 5-8 seconds. I think the spell idea is good, just would need some tweaks. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-13 09:50:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I don't see how this would be so op. It has its weaknesses. If thr guy uses it and misses all skills then it would be a complete waste. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-13 09:39:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Well the enemy team would be well aware about the fact that she would be able to do that, and also that would be a spell switched over ignite or heal, it's a big trade. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-13 09:35:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Well isn't this the purpouse of spells? Make a situationaly op one with a good cooldown like maybe 200 sec. He wouldn't be spamming it. Just helping to make a good play. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Make a Summoner Spell that can be able to halve your non-ultimate skills Colldowns for 8 seconds </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-13 09:30:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> *Title
Basically having another kind of offensive summoner which is not ignite would be nice.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-10 01:05:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Amazing Mitis!
No, WE have to thank you. Certainly one of the biggest artists of EM out there that deserves WAY more attention. 
I really want to know what to throw at the master bus! I generally come up with 2 Maximus, one for the Comp and the other for the Gain and some EQ.
If you want to hear how you inspired me, please visit my soundcloud (Tulio Ricci) if it's not asking much. It would be a dream.
Getting at Born Records is my motivation!!

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-09 19:45:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Joe, I've been waiting for this AMA for a long time since you are one of my biggest inspirations to produce music. I hope you can answer to my questions, sorry for the long list.

1. How much is Mitis itself working to have a better engagement with his fans?

2. What kind of programs do you use to forge your awesome plucks and also your beautiful piano?

3. What inspires you to write your songs? 

4. Do you plan making tours in other countries in the future?

5. Any tips for a good mastering?

6. Do you believe you can grow your audience with your own music style to most of the Spinning Records artists in terms of popularity?

7. What was the biggest challenge for the Living Color EP?

Thank you for everything you've done for us.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Low Volume on DJ Sona </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-25 21:10:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Is that only me who thought Dj Sona's volume way too low? Even if I drag the music to the max the song still gets drowned by the effects and everything else. Please Riot raise it a bit so we don't have to turn the other bars down just so we can hear it!
Thanks. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-11-30 18:30:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> And now with his 2.0 version incoming, guess will become unplayable for sure. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-11-13 22:50:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Couldn't Riot just implement an Saturation Adjustment option in game so each player could choose how they want the map to look? Like in a scale of 0 to 10, 0 is the actual SR map and 10 is a high saturated one. That would be awesome and would solve the problem, just don't know if its actually handable.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
