<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject4129</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-22 02:34:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Based on? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-22 02:34:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Who said they're face? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-22 02:28:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> New day need to look convincing as champions if the record will be made otherwise it will mean nothing. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-22 02:18:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> No </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-22 02:13:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Would make zero sense. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-22 02:11:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hoping for the new day to go over clean for once. They looked really weak last night. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-22 02:05:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Would you rather have had 15 mins of goldberg vs lesnar?? Lol </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-22 02:03:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Would love Goldberg to have a title run, I know he doesn't need it but whatever. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-22 02:01:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What disaster??? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Plan B - Suzanne (Lyrics) </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-12 14:19:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Celph Titled - Windows 98 (Ft. Majik Most) </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-26 17:39:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Can't access the web app </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-25 15:45:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Dr. Octagon - A Visit to the Gynecologyst </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-21 13:15:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Any good deals happening in the UK? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-04 15:23:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Need me some cheap dvd/blu ray purchases for Halloween month! But most of the ones I find are for the US </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> (NSFW) picked up these nasties at a DVD market in Germany </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-04 15:09:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Need catching up </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-04 11:45:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So I'm spending time with my grandparents here in Germany and have been unable to watch any wwe programming since backlash. 

Can anyone bring me up to speed with what's been going on? I know sasha just won her title back. And rusev lost the us title to reigns. What's been the stand out highlight thus far and which show has been putting on better shows?.

Appreciate any replies  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Viktor Vaughn - R.A.P G.A.M.E. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-10 16:50:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> American Alpha out for Backlash </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-07 04:08:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> WTF? why? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What do you want from Smackdown today? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-07 01:53:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Seeing as Backlash is this Sunday... How would you book this Smackdown show? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Canibus - Levitibus </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-27 12:06:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Why does this creep me out so much? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-21 22:16:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Dr.Octagon - Real Raw </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-28 18:36:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> KMD Shirt came today! </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-25 23:01:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> New Edition of Yu-Gi-Oh Cards </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-24 23:52:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Does anyone know this instrumental and who produced it? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-22 13:46:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=TliBlVozmjU

I know its been used before but i can never find the beat no matter how much a look online. Any help appreciated. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Reading Between The Rhymes: The Skits of MF DOOM </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-13 13:40:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Whitewash - Buckethead [Experimental Rock] </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-11 20:55:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The Number 9 Shirt </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-11 16:20:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Madvillain - Accordion | Bar for Bar Breakdown </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-09 10:54:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Crystal Palace improve offer for Christian Benteke, worth up to 31.5 million </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-04 16:41:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Any place to get Viktor Vaughn T-Shirts? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-04 14:53:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Been looking around for a while and have yet come across any Viktor Vaughn t-shirts, unless im blind as hell but if anyone knows a place (preferably in the UK) where i can purchase Viktor Vaughn t-shirts that would be of great appreciation.

also, happy 4th of July to most of you! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Thomas Prime - Spirited Beginning [Jazz-Hop] </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-25 19:17:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Whatever happened to Relentless Inferno? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-31 20:48:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> When and why did they stop making them?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Where can i find the full video for this? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-27 15:59:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Can only find the audio version, im sure there is an actual video of DOOM performing [this] (https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=7bfMQteuzLE).  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> An issue i had purchasing a Vinyl </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-24 17:38:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Sorry if this isn't the correct place to post but i figured this fits the criteria.

So i purchased my first vinyl a few days ago and it was a mixtape that i made (called Sadevillain) but when i purchased this vinyl i noticed the cover had "Sadevillain" spelled wrong (this was my fault and will make sense in a moment)

A little backstory, i created this mixtape and uploaded it onto Datpiff (a mixtape hosting site) and i was dumb enough to not only misspell the title but to misspell the actual front cover. When the tape blew up i noticed the error and immediately fixed it (reuploaded the tape with the correct spelling) 

Fast forward a month or so and i find out that this mixtape is being sold as a vinyl, to which i thought "holy shit! my mixtape is on vinyl!!" so i immediately went to purchase it (the mixtape they advertised had the correct spelling) i thought nothing of it until i open the package up and to my horror it had the old cover with the misspelled name.

I contacted the company that i bought it from and they told me to contact the distributor, as they are the ones who deal with the printing... my question is, how do i know who distributed it and where can i find out? 

any help is appreciated


TL;DR: My mixtape got a vinyl release, wrong cover was used and i wanted to get the updated cover (as advertised) printing on the sleeve instead.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Top 3 Best/Worst Kevin Smith Movies? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-15 09:46:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> He's been getting a lot of stick recently with his recent trailer "Yoga Hosers" so i thought it would be cool to see what you guys think of his best and worst movies are...

Here are mine:

Best:
1: Clerks
2: Mallrats
3: Dogma

Worst:
1: Cop Out
2: Tusk
3: Zack and Miri

EDIT: Clerks (1994) is my favourite not Clerks 2 which is how it looks on the post.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> King Geedorah - Fazers </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-11 19:50:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Nerve (2016 Movie) Official Trailer  Watcher or Player? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-11 19:12:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> PingPong - Between Moral and Fashion </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-11 18:45:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Professional football club West Brom unveil their new kit for 2016/17 </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-09 14:53:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> realistic injuries? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-08 13:37:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> im looking for some realistic injury sliders, im currently playing on no sliders and i feel as if the injuries are non existent, im Liverpool atm (in real life we have had a bunch on injuries this season) and the onl injury i have had was sakho being out for 9 days (im in January atm) 

I used to have IF on 70 and IS on 30...

any suggestions?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Quasimoto - Low Class Conspiracy Instrumental </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-04 23:09:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Rush - The Trees </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-02 01:23:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Starting XI Prediction for Thursday? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-01 16:05:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Im going to be doing two predictions... What i would want and what i think Klopp will do:

Klopp XI:
http://lineupbuilder.com/?sk=sy326

My XI:
http://lineupbuilder.com/?sk=sy327 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What shitty movie had the best soundtrack? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-01 12:12:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Viktor Vaughn - Fall Back Titty Fat </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-24 17:03:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> NAS performing N.Y. State of Mind at MBL Cave. Crowd really active. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-23 23:58:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Rapper "Desiigner" performs an exorcism while dabbing live in NYC </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-15 18:17:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Hello Friends ... (Kanye West,Adele) - [3:38] </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-15 17:45:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Is Deadpool in the movie a true reflection of his comic book character? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-15 13:12:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I personally dont read comics and know very little about these sort of things as im not a massive fan of superhero movies in general. I decided to give Deadpool a go because it was rated R and it peaked my curiosity/interest. Although i didn't think it was an amazing movie i did enjoy it quite a bit, and will definitely check out the sequel. 

As for Deadpool himself, how accurate is his representation? I know they didn't add his Schizophrenia, which is weird because it would be a good reason for his constant 4th wall breaks (which i thought were pretty bizarre). I remember people telling me he was a badass, but this movie (IMO) made him feel like a bit of a joke, which i guess was the intention with the constant jokes but is that what hes like in the comics? is there anything else they missed out?
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> MF DOOM - Rock co. Kane Flow (Remix) </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-13 18:04:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Anyway to change the samples speed/time midway? without it affecting the whole thing? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-13 16:27:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> im making a mix and at the end of the first verse i need the acapella to speed up, just for that section. is there anyway to do that?

heres an idea of what i [mean] (http://www.youtube.com/watch?v=I_wWbcWfxZA nohtml5=False)

instead of the whole temp changing BPM i just need a section of the a Capella to speed up.

Thanks :)

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Kanye West x Adele - Friends (Remix/Mashup) </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-09 20:35:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> SADEVILLAIN - SADEVILLAIN EP (MF DOOM x Sade Mashup) </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-09 17:00:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> NXT Takeover Blackpool: Fans chanting to Bayley "Heeeeey Hey Bayleeyy" </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-07 14:13:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> My "FULL" remix of Ghostwhirl, check it out! </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-04 01:03:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Young Thug - Tattoos </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-30 15:13:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> JMT - I Against I </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-29 20:14:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Downloading 1 file at a time??? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-13 16:52:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Is it possible to download 1 file at a time?

Lets say i was downlaoding a whole series... is it possible to download 1 episode at a time WTHOUT manually having to select 1 episode to download and to turn every other episode off? instead of downloading the whole season in 1 go it would be awesome if it will automatically queue each episode to download separately.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [NOIR-HIP HOP] RA The Rugged Man vs Marcella Puppini - "The Greatest" </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-09 14:36:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Players overall should be based on form every 3 months. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-07 14:57:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Does anyone else find it ridiculous that any players that is under 30 will always go up and will never go down? how many times have we seen promising players get downgraded due to poor form? look at Falcao, he went from like 88 to 83 and hes under 30, if this was 3 years ago and i played a career mode with liverpool... Sterling would be rated about 85* right now, i just find it stupid how players overalls never decrease unless they are getting old. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Anyone seen The Plague Dogs? (1982) </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-07 08:47:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Traumatized me as a child, the earliest memory i have of me being severely upset and depressed from a movie. 

Criminally underrated imo, never really gets mentioned even though i hold it in the same bracket as "Watership Down" </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Nate Diaz walking out to my 2Pac remix "Dont Make Enemies With Me Pt.2" </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-06 16:30:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> SADEVILLAIN Artwork _ Credit to @Marcoso__ </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-01 23:41:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Good beer to get in the UK that isn't generic? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-28 01:08:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So i live in the UK (South of England to be precise) and i always see people drink beer or post beer of a brand that i have never seen before (with pretty cool names and designs) all i see here in Tescos, Asdas, Morrisons etc is just your typical Fosters, Strongbow, Carling, Magners etc... Im enjoying Corona Extra atm (im stil getting familar with the beer taste and Corona is hitting the spot for me atm)

Any suggestions?

Price cant be too high, but i wouldn't mind paying a bit extra for some real good stuff.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> (Mixtape) ...SADEVILLIAN EP (Prod by Seanh) </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-27 22:10:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> I Present To You... SADEVILLIAN. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-27 17:31:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> (Remix) SADEVILLIAN - Hot Pants/Ghostwhirl (SNIPPET) </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-23 02:36:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [Remix] SADEVILLIAN - Gazzillion Grand (Snippet) </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-21 22:09:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> MF DOOM Ghostwirl Acapella? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-21 15:26:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Can anyone hook me up with his Ghostwhirl acapella? I'm making a SADEVILLIAN mixtape and i know there is a Ghostwhirl pella out there but i cant find it.

any help greatly appreciated </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Would anyone be interested in a SADEVILLIAN mixtape?? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-19 21:35:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Posted a couple of DOOM mixes which involve samples of Sade, the response was pretty good and someone came up with the idea of making a SADEVILLIAN mixtape, im down with the idea but i just wanted to know if more people would be interested in listening to it? im not a very skilled producer and im still learning the ropes with production but i feel like it would be a dope idea to put out a remix tape of SADEVILLIAN (Sade   DOOM) (consisting of about 4-5 tracks worth 2-3 skits/intro/outro)

Im currently working on the 3rd track and i might upload a snippet of it for you if you want to hear it. Another thing i wanted to add is if there is anyone who is a skilled graphic designer or knows any graphic designer that can make a SADEVILLIAN mixtape cover please hit me up!

Leave me your suggestions on how you guys would like the mixtape to go and if you have an cartoon sampled that you know of that uses the words "Doom, "Villian" "Metal Face" "Mask" or anything let me know aswell. 

Thanks for reading  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Very confused with this... </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-16 18:50:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So i'm a big fan of impractical jokers and downloaded all the shows online because im from the UK as they didn't show a lot on Sky+ TV.

Now the thing that im confused about is that Season 5 just premiered in the US, and in the uk they have just started premiering Season 4, but its labeled as Season 7? and season 8 is premiering next week? why is it called Season 8? can someone explain this?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Am i missing something? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-16 02:17:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Checkout my new DOOM mix! x MF DOOM ft. Sade - Jezebel (Seanh Remix) </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-14 03:55:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What word sounds like it should have a completely different meaning? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-10 00:25:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> My remix of MF DOOM's "Air" featuring Sade. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-04 12:35:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Drums... </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-23 17:11:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> TIFU: Left my flash drive in a college pc, forgot to bring it with me after class </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-20 14:28:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Let my memory stick in college </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-20 14:09:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> So when is Evac coming back to Ps4? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-11 17:49:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> EDIT* I mean "Exodus"

Completely forgot that map existed until i saw someone stream it, heard they took it out of the cycle of PS4 due to glitches or something, when is it returning?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> ELI5: Why "Jesus" isn't a popular name in the US like it is in Hispanic countries. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-07 23:55:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Never! And i mean never! say the word "Bnag" </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-03 23:56:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's bang out of order. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Dudes gets a kiss on the "cheek" if he chugs these beers at Hooters, things get uncomfortable. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-03 23:42:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What a fucking subreddit </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-02 22:18:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This would a great subreddit if it weren't for fucking OP </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Treadmill Exercises? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-02 18:01:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I got a treadmill for Christmas and would love if someone could give me a steady daily routine (or every other day, would prefer daily)

info about me: Male (18 y/o)/5'8/11.7 stone (164lbs)

im very out of shape and would love to lose some fat as i feel very flabby and what not, im not the type of person that has always been like this, i was very fit when i was younger but since i left school and started college, none of my mates in college played football/soccer (which is how i stayed fit) and that led to me gaining weight.

any daily treadmill routine for someone like me would be great, thanks!
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> So... its that time of the year again. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-02 02:12:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So as cliche as it sounds, I'm going to try to lose weight this year. For Christmas my parents got me a treadmill (don't worry, i asked for it)

I'm an 18 year old male, 5'8 and weight 11.7 stone (164lbs) and feel very out of shape and flabby. What i would like to know is, whats the best stuff to do on a treadmill? i plan on doing it daily or at least every other day (i go on the treadmill at night in my garage because i like the quiet) and just did my first run on it and created my own little thing, which consisted of:

4.5kmh walk for 4.5 mins
11kmh sprint for 30 secs
4.5kmh walk for 4.5 mins
11kmh sprint for 30 secs
4.5kmh walk for 4.5 mins
11kmh sprint for 30 secs

2 min rest and another

4.5kmh walk for 4.5 mins
11kmh sprint for 30 secs
4.5kmh walk for 4.5 mins
11kmh sprint for 30 secs
4.5kmh walk for 4.5 mins
11kmh sprint for 30 secs

What i noticed is that my ankles tense up a bit for some reason and makes it kind of uncomfortable, not sure if thats normal or what.

again i have no idea what im doing, if thats the right routine but for my first run and just wanted to get a feel of the treadmill and do my own thing

i have my diet under control so no need to wrry about that

any advice is greatly appreciated :D </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Can't Activate Windows 10 </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-01 14:43:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So i got a new PC for Christmas as my old one was corrupted. I went about setting up my new PC by installing Windows 7 and then going on to get the free update to Windows 10. I went about installing windows 7 but the product key did not work (legit copy of windows 7) so i had to resort to finding an online key which did work. Upon installing windows 7 i went to install Windows 10, everything went smoothly until i entered the product key, i had to go through multiple ones online to find one that worked and when it does it says "Windows cannot activate right now" i have tried multiple keys and they all work, but all come up with the same error message.

Any help?

img: https://gyazo.com/679e41963e5baf688252603371d45b77 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Cant join anyone! </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-25 20:21:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So... this is taking the piss now

Since i got the game i haven't been able to join anyone, it keeps saying "lobby not joinable" another issue is that half of my friends playing on BO3 wont shop up in the party thing (when i press triangle on the ps4) i have looked online and apparently this is a wide spread issues, so well done treyarch, i cant even play with my friends!

also my NAT used to be moderated (which didn't fix it) and now all of a sudden its strict, which is the first time its been strict since ive been playing cod (cod4) WTF is going on?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Best Youtubers To Watch? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-22 01:55:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I used to watch loads of YouTubers back in the day during MW2, WaW and BO2 and most of the people i watched that i admired don't upload COD videos anymore. I was wondering which YouTubers you guys watch? im not a fan of those view whoring YouTubers (Ali-A, Prestige Is Key, TmArtn etc...) I prefer the likes of Chris Smoove (used to love his MW2 stuff) Thunder, and WingsOfRedemption. Are there any guys that you watch? i like watching people play the game in their own unique way and dont just rush about a lot dropping 80+ kills every game.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Fuck Combine! </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-18 15:29:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> AMA Request: Stewards who work/have worked at football/soccer stadiums </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-10 13:18:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> My Questions:

1) Whats the craziest game you have stewarded at? and what made it so crazy?

2) Does it get boring looking at the fans for 90mins?

3) Have you ever been hurled abuse at? 

4) How do you get into Stewarding and what qualifications are required?

Thanks! 
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Dessa - Dixons Girl - (Alternative Hip Hop/Noir) </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-11-28 01:29:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Name your top 5 Akira Kurosawa Movies </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-11-21 12:58:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> About 2 weeks ago i wanted to watch Kurosawa's entire filmography as i know he was one of the most influential directors that inspired the likes of Star Wars and Spaghetti Westerns. 

I've seen 9 of his movies:
Sanshiro Sugata,
The Men Who Tread on the Tiger's Tail,
Rashomon,
Ikiru,
Seven Samurai,
I Live In Fear,
Throne Of Blood,
The Hidden Fortress,
Yojimbo,
Sanjuro

My top 5 currently:

1) Seven Samurai
2)Throne Of Blood
3)The Hidden Fortress
4)Rashomon
5)Sanjuro </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> ELI5: How does one become injury prone? And why do people suffer injures more frequently than others? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-11-16 18:43:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> For example, i'm a big fan of football/soccer and there are lots of players that are just more likely to get injured, Daniel Sturridge is a player that plays for m favorite team (Liverpool) and hes incredibly prone to injury, (thigh injury) so i'm just wondering how some people just get unlucky with long term injuries than people who almost never get inured.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The Word: "BNAG" </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-11-12 00:08:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Is bang out of order.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What infomercial product is actually worth purchasing? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-11-11 17:50:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What was the shortest phase/fad you guys went through in your life? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-11-10 22:49:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> First attempt at color restoration, tell me what you think! </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-11-06 14:52:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Shyheim - On   On (Explicit) [Hip-Hop] </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-11-03 23:16:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> ELI5: Why does wet hair look dry underwater? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-10-16 16:50:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Why aren't daughters often named after their mothers like how sons are to their fathers? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-10-14 22:32:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm not sure if i ever recall seeing any women/girl being named "Jennifer III" or "Jackie Jr" but it's extremely common for boys to be called after their dad (especially in the USA) so why is that? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Does anyone else think that WWE need more gimmicks? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-10-05 18:19:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I mean.

I haven't been heavily into wrestling since 09, and i feel what made WWE so fun to watch was all the over the top gimmicks they had. Hulk Hogan, Ultimate Warrior, The Undertaker, Mankind, Kane (Demon), Big Boss Man, etc. And now there aren't really anymore of these gimmicks around, apart from the few that are still here (Taker, Kane etc.) i enjoyed seeing dumb wrestler come out with their over the top gimmicks and attires. I'ts just a bit tedious to watch now. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> M/18/5'8/163lb - Muscle Tone? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-09-20 16:11:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So this is my first post on this Subreddit.

I'm 18 years old and weigh about 11.7 stone (give or take a pound) i wouldn't consider myself fat or overweight (even though technically my BMI is just in the region of being overweight) but i'm very unfit and really out of shape. 

The problem is, is that i don't live near a gym and even if i did i don't exactly have the money for a membership. So i've been thinking of doing DDP yoga along with a 7 Minute Beginner Workout in which i've been doing for about 4 days now (muscles are sore atm, good thing right?) is this the correct way to go about it? As far as my diet goes, i eat 3 meals a day, don't drink sodas (only water, coffee and tea) but occasionally have a low carb monster or something slightly unhealthy here and there (homemade cheeseburger, homemade chips, etc..) i'm not looking to get ripped i just want to have some form of muscle tone to my physique.

Thanks for reading! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Eminem - The Rebirth (Hosted   Mixed by Seanh) </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-08-28 21:46:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> BSOD issues </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-08-26 00:37:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So, My PC has been crashing and playing up for about a year now and i have tried every possible issue on how to resolve it (apart from buying new hardware) the issue i have is that my PC keeps running into BSOD's and i'm getting sick and tired of it, on other occasions my PC will just freeze and my monitor will switch off and will display a no signal. i have reinstalled my drivers, updated them, refreshed my whole PC (about 10 times) reinstalled windows (about 10 times)

i have run a memory diagnostic on my RAM individually and it came up with 0 errors on both occasions. 

here is a dump on the blue screens.
http://imgur.com/KFo4JWJ

any help is greatly appreicated </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Do your worst Reddit. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-08-22 19:18:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> PC keeps crashing, don't know the issue. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-10 14:57:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Specs: http://imgur.com/qrjGwFg

So i've been having this issue for about a year now and before i buy new hardware i want to make 100% sure its not a software issue.

What happens is my PC will crash sporadically throughout the day, some days it will not crash at all, other days it will crash 5-10 times a day. When my PC crashes i will sometimes just randomly freeze (need to hold power button to force restart) or i will get a blue screen with various different messages (usually MEMORY_MANAGEMENT or SYSTEM_THREAD_EXCEPTION, and sometimes other random ones), and other times my monitor will just switch off and will receive no signal (i connected my TV to my pc to see if its my monitor thats faulty or my PC, and when it randomly switched off my TV switched off aswell) i have update all of my drivers and updated every windows update i have. i have also ran several scans on CMD Prompt (SFC /SCANNOW, CHKDSK) and nothing, aswell as memory diagnostic and it says my memory is fine. I also checked inside my PC and there doesn't seem to be any issues with it. 

Now, the weird thing is, 4 weeks ago i deleted some partitions, and my PC was running fine, 0 issues what so ever, then i checked Slimdrivers to see if i needed any updates and i had about 12 to do, ever since i updated them i have had several issues, (it crashed about 10 minutes after the reboot) so i decided to do a system restore to before the updates, and it still crashed, several times :/

I'm running out of ideas and i dont want to spend 80 - 200 on new RAM when it says my ram is fine. 

any help is hugely appreciated.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> 2Pac ft. Coldplay - All I Know (Seanh Remix) </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-09 14:17:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Apathy   Celph Titled - No Place Like Chrome </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-25 23:42:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Need help finding a movie </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-31 23:42:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I was about 5/6 years old (born in 1997) and i remember watching a movie over a friends house with his parents. all i remember was being frightened by it and constantly looking away, the only scene i remember was a scene that involved two kids that were trying to enter a room (i think it was a sci-fi alien kind of movie) and they turned out to be aliens (or robots) that took the form of two children. i've been trying to track down this film ever since and never got round to finding it, theres another scene that i remember (not sure if its the same movie, i should expect so) and i think it was the ending, there was a guy ( i think he was black) that was fighting someone and he ended up getting killed by either a propeller blade from a helicopter or something similar.

i know its vague but this is honestly all i can remember, any help would be appreciated </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Back When Real Hip-Hop Was Appreciated </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-08 13:17:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The Original CPR dummy was created by using the face module of a girl that drowned in Paris </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-22 00:35:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> (Mind Blown) K-Rino - Surface Dwellers (LYRICS) </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-07 17:23:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
