<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject388</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-10-30 04:57:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I don't know what she talks about in her sessions, but I will definitely call her therapist and raise my concerns tomorrow, that's a great idea. I probably should've thought of that but I've been a little overwhelmed by everything that's been happening.

I'm not an artist, and I don't understand that world, but I'm worried that working in that world would make her miss it even more. I'll talk to her about this though and see how she feels. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-10-30 04:53:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Even if a reversal isn't viable, kids are unfortunately not off the table. My parents agreed to pay for the procedure (I wasn't in the best financial situation at the time and had just had a pregnancy scare with Claire), but only on the condition that I freeze some samples in case we changed our minds. Claire knows about this, too. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-10-30 04:49:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This is a great idea, I'll bring this up to her - I'm sure some of our non-CF friends would love an evening off </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-10-30 04:47:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I don't think she's manipulating me. She's never said "give me children or I'm leaving". She just let me know its important to her - which is weird, because it never has been before. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> My (30M) formerly CF wife (28F) has been diagnosed with depression. Since then, she's decided that she wants to be a SAHM and is pressuring me to have my vasectomy reversed. Advice wanted. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-10-30 04:27:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> 6 years ago, I met the most amazing woman I've never known. Let's call her Claire.

She was adventurous, intelligent, and incredibly talented (she's a violinist). We've been together since we met and married one year. 5 years and 10 months of that time has been absolutely blissful. Starting a couple of months ago, she started to develop aches and pains when she practiced for a long period of time. After I poked and prodded her for a while, she went to the doctor and was diagnosed with rheumatoid arthritis. She stopped giving lessons a couple of weeks ago, and then she had to give up her chair in the orchestra she played in, and then she stopped playing altogether.

Since she stopped playing, she's become very depressed (and this isn't a self diagnosis - she goes to a therapist weekly now and she's on antidepressants). There were whole days when she was at her lowest when she didn't leave the house. She's told me that she feels like she doesn't have purpose anymore, and I hate that. Then, after she started the antidepressants, she decided that her calling in life was to raise children.

We've both been CF since we met. After our wedding, we got all the "when are the kids coming bingos", and she hated them more than I did. Now she's totally changed her mind, and has told me that it's really important to her that I have my vasectomy reversed. She's brought it up once or twice every day for the past week.

I hate kids, but if I honestly thought it would help her, I would become a dad. I don't, though. I think she lost something really important to her and is looking to fill a void that can't be filled. I've tried talking to her about this and she broke down crying about how I wouldn't "give her children". I just don't think it would help. I think she's be just as depressed, but we'd have a kid to take care of on top of it.

I don't know how to help her. If having a kid is really what she needs, I don't want to keep her from that - but I don't think she's in the right place to make this kind of decision. A year ago she hated kids and now she thinks she needs them. I don't know what to do.

Before anyone says "divorce her bruh", I'm absolutely not willing to consider that. This woman is the love of my life, and I'm not willing to leave her when she's already hurting. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-08-26 15:31:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Or just give the kid some candy and don't be a twat about it.

Okay, tiny rant over. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
