<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject6666</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> O M G ROASTED </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-18 16:25:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Found Corsair's new website </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-18 04:21:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> cant receive text messages </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-16 21:34:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I can send messages fine, and yes they receive it, but when they text back, I can't receive it. stock messaging app gives error "cannot start conversation" and textra sends fine but doesn't receive as I said before. 

running running resurrection remix Rom v5.6.7 android marshmallow. CM13 based Rom. currently have an outage and can't test different texting apps because low data. any suggestions? the apn is correct.

edit: just went to fulmics 6.0 and its working fine, miss the smoothness of aosp but a working phone  a not working phone </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> can send text messages, can call and can receive calls. cannot receive messages </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-16 20:21:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> lg g3 d852 with Resurrection remix v5.6.7 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> I find any chest size a good size </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-15 16:26:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I find any chest size a good size, though a little something is nice.
My last partner was incredibly flat, and they kind of felt bad for me, because as I said before, I prefer a little something.
During the first time we had sex, they were super sensitive about everything. So I told them to take it easy. They wanted to try to give me a paizuri (breast job, for those people who still have their dignity). Ever received a paizuri from a person that's flat as a chess board?
Put human skin on a xylophone then run your dick on it, you'll feel the same experience.
Anyway, I told them I wasn't really feeling it, and they were sad about it, then I felt bad about it. I just told them to use their mouth and it'll be fine.
Later, they tell me:
"Don't worry Shaku! If I'm anything like my mom, I'll start to grow boobs once I hit 12 years old!"
Then I just laughed at them. I told them this:
"Haha! That's not gonna happen. Boys don't develop breast like girls do." </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> oh and i support feminism </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-13 20:14:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hey my grandmother died at around 61 and my grandfather is 81 now so yeah not all women live longer than men. It just kinda pisses me off that you decided to categorize every women that they live longer. I mean you don't know that now do you. What if a woman have cancer and she have about just a few months to live? I'm just saying. Oh and I support feminism cause hey, suppressed women exists too okay.

comments section from this video

https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=cXNCyrkkgLc </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [Music] Flyleaf - Cassie (Acoustic) </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-12 19:58:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Play At Your Own Risk! The Hidden Truth Behind Pokmon GO! </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-11 18:50:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Frankie Mish - Dicks Out For Harambe </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-09 20:27:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> there's literally a deep web forum about penis enhancement </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-08 04:28:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> thundersplv36.onion </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> 12GB update </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-29 18:15:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> thoughts </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-29 03:39:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> wake up sheeple </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-28 03:12:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> u r being used </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> i love this phones camera so much </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-19 06:00:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> kinda hot idk </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-09 20:40:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> she looks lkinda hot however bad in the sack probabnly hint ps im the best atsex ive ever met i feel sorry for all the emotional wreck retarded people who will never experience the insane incredible orgasms my tongue and penis can give women over and over and over and over and over again... haha oh well I hate you </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Flyleaf - Fully Alive [Rock] </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-06 22:09:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What you listening to right now? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-06 20:30:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Flyleaf's self titled album is so good

[This song in particular](https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=-d3RYW0YoEk) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Edgy? Of course I am edgy! </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-27 03:36:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Don't watch the new Ghostbusters </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-24 14:01:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Hard Rock and Metal discussion </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-22 16:40:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What's songs you like? My favourite artists would probably be three days grace and metallica </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> How do you think performance will be with AMD CPUs? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-20 03:27:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Dolphin doesn't like them </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> ... </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-19 23:00:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Fuck off Imgur </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-19 16:41:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> 60FPS Battlefield 1 Gameplay from M3RKMUS1C </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-13 00:28:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Portable charger and LG G3 </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-10 06:16:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This portable power bank I've been looking at, 

http://www.amazon.ca/dp/B010L43UAQ/

Has a review that's worrying me. Cherry picked 

The input charging rate for this is 2A (actually, I got 1.94A - close enough). And if you are trying to charge with any lesser USB power source (like a laughable 900mA, or 0.9A) or a typical USB Data Synch/Charging cable, which inherently has amperage limits due to the data transfer capability, you **WILL** have problems.

What does this mean for me? I have the standard charging cable. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What's "HDMI Scaling" </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-10 02:33:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> GPUOpen AOFX? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-09 04:41:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I want to see this Ambient Occlusion utilized in games, from [the picture from AMD](http://32ipi028l5q82yhj72224m8j.wpengine.netdna-cdn.com/wp-content/uploads/2015/11/aofx_screenshot.jpg) it looks like it will be a very good looking AO. 

Thoughts? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> My mom won't let me go out in public for the summer </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-06 15:35:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I was at a clothing store with my mother today. I was browsing the shirts in the big and tall section while slowly sipping my Diet Mountain Dew looking for the ever elusive 5XL shirt. When passing by the rack full of shirts too small for any average man such as myself to wear when out of the corner of my Gunnar glasses I saw a shelf full of head-wear that peaked my interest. I approached the shelf wiping the leftover Dorito dust from my all night long Overwatch marathon onto my 6th #FeelTheBern shirt when I saw it. The perfect hat to adorn my head, the one piece of fabric that could define my personality while also covering that embarrassing shine poking through right above my hair-tie.

[This hat](http://i.imgur.com/xQ8fnW1.jpg) felt perfect for me, and the moment that I put it on I could tell, this was the hat for me, the hat that I could never take off and would complete my entire aura of high fashion. Within the first 69 seconds of looking at m'self in the mirror I noticed a fine lady was looking at me from the other side of the store, smiling with the biggest grin I have ever seen. The smile was akin only to those I have only seen on Jennifer Lawrence's perfect face on television while laughing and flirting with Thor's ugly younger brother. It was unmistakable, this woman was flirting with me, the way she shook her breasts up and down while smiling and trying to cover it up like she was shy or embarrassed about it. I tipped m'fedora in her direction and she swooned so hard she fell right to the ground, her grin still visible from ear to ear. [This hat...](http://i.imgur.com/xQ8fnW1.jpg) had turned me into a total pussy slayer, buffing m'romance skill by a value of 1337. 

Then m'mom came back, took m'newly found superpower off m'head and she told me to "Stop acting like a fucking neckbeard" and dragged me out by the scruff beneath m'chin that I have not had time to attend to since I got m'GTX 1080 and m'copy of Overwatch. She drove me back home and instantly locked me in my room with some new clothes she picked out and a treadmill. "I'll let you out when you can wear normal sized clothes and interact with people in a way that doesn't make them laugh at you for being a dumbass."

M'mother hates me now all because I instantly became a woman's wet dream. She won't let me go near a hat again, not even m'blue "Make Donald Drumpf Again" hat with an MLG sticker on the back. M'mom has ruined m'chances with the ladies forever and only unlocks and opens the door to m'room to give me a kale salad. How can m'mother do this to me, is there anything I can do to resolve this quarrel to continue m'main quest in the fall. I guess m'mother couldn't cope with the fact that in university this fall I would meet a beautiful blonde with luscious DD cup breasts who would love me for the nice guy I am on the inside, and marry me for m'above average brain and m'degree in Animation with a minor in Japanese Culture.

The treadmill broke when I started to hang m'sweat drenched T-shirts on it after intense matches of CS:GO in 4K so I don't know how I will lose enough weight to even leave m'bedroom now. Guess I will have to find a good online university to study for m'degree and guess I should upload a picture of one of those ugly guys all the hawt ladies seem to go crazy over to m'Tinder profile so I can acheive the life I was planning on while trapped here in m'parents' basement. Any advice for what else I should do? Maybe I should photoshop [this hat](http://i.imgur.com/xQ8fnW1.jpg) with m'LEET hacker skillz on top of the ugly guy's head so even more ladies will swipe right.

Sorry this was long, but thanks for hearing me out in m'moment of anger and fine ladies that I have seen in the selfie threads, feel free to hit me up in m'DMs.


Source: https://www.reddit.com//r/teenagers/comments/4mpm87/social_rant_mom_wont_let_me_go_out_in_public_for </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Logic: Another Form of Female Opression </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-05 01:41:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> ELI5: The FinFET process within GDDR5X memory modules. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-21 04:01:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> People are unwatching my videos. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-19 03:15:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Pancake Warfare </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-19 01:15:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> feelsgoodman.jpg </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-11 15:01:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> ELI5: AMD Mesa? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-10 20:36:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Polaris will do 4k60 recording with h.265 </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-10 05:42:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Are you for real? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-10 01:44:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Vram usage at 1080p Ultra textures? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-06 15:34:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> ELI5: Quantum Breaks Volumetric Lighting System? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-05 16:45:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Rattling noise from Hyper 212 Evo when gaming </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-04 22:04:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> http://i.imgur.com/BgwxpyK.jpg

That's a pic the cooler

https://youtu.be/6YpYEUOgftU

That's the rattling it makes. 


I'm confused, this started the other day while I was playing GTA V and it wasnt very noticeable. Putting my fan speed at 100% with speed fan and running a CPU stress test won't make this noise, but when gaming it's unbearable, and has also hurt my temperatures. I got my cooler a month ago, and has been working flawlessly since. I haven't opened my PC in Atleast a week before it started happening, and I'm too scared to turn my PC on right now cuz I'd rather not have a roasted CPU. 

My mobo is a GA78LMT-USB3 and my CPU is a FX 8320 4.2Ghz

Help of any kind would be great

Edit: one of the fans clips went connected to the heatsink. I'm testing it right now, I'll update

Edit2: NOPE NOT FIXED HELP </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> How do I fix this? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-02 01:27:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> This Rom is great! Extremely stable! </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-29 20:44:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Only crashes like twice an hour! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> ELI5: Why can't binaural audio engines be created </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-29 19:31:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I don't understand how this isn't possible. It clearly works on different binaural audio plays on YouTube, you can simply have an engine that interprets the audio as a human ear would, and have a left cup for your left ear and a right cup for your right ear. This would make games like CSGO so much more enjoyable, and for single player experiences it can make for an amazing experience! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Those with 144Hz monitors... </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-28 18:03:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Does is feel strange and slow to use your phone? That's one of my biggest worries, that my second monitor and my phone will feel slow. Thanks!

Edit: thanks </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Should've got a 390 </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-24 01:13:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Help! I signed up for opinions two years ago, and I still haven't even gotten a verification survey! </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-22 18:17:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> I just got an 825MB update </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-21 23:07:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> This Time it's Different - Evans Blue (Rock) </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-21 05:15:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> ---- number of explosions caused by the GTX 480 </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-17 05:32:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Any LAN parties? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-15 04:44:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> As a teenager who's indulged a lot of time into CSGO, I always wanted to try playing at LAN. Anything going on? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Siri is veryinsecure </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-13 20:39:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> This Seed to Leech Ratio </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-11 20:19:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> when youre in the zone </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-09 05:45:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> "Windows will hold PC gaming back until Xbox 2 comes out!11!111!!!!!1" </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-08 23:07:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Quick start to this sub. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-08 17:39:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hey guys. I just want to make this clear. This subreddit isn't just for the sleek looking black and white cable managed water cooled dual 980Tis. This is for everyday builds as well. Don't ever get scared to post your build. We'll appreciate it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> We are the 9th most toxic subreddit... </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-08 05:46:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> I have pre-order bonuses - I didn't pre-order the game. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-03 17:30:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I've had these for a while, but I never researched how I got them. I checked it out, and the Digital Customization Pack - which I have, and is apparently a preorder bonus. As long with the Black Ops 3 camo in extras. Anyone else having this? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Go home Steam, you're drunk </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-03 05:31:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> fresh dr. pepper meme </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-28 18:32:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> For those with EXTREME stutters and crashing </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-26 08:49:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Find your proper audio drivers. I know, sounds useless, right? Worked for me. And worked for three friends I suggested the fix for. 

First off, if you have a sound card, you should get the cards drivers. Except Asus Xonar, avoid the stock drivers with a 10 foot pool and get the UNi Modded Drivers. 

If you do not, go to your motherboards page on the manufacturing website and download the audio driver, then restart your computer. 

I hope this helps! It fixed my crashing, but it supposedly fixed many friends extreme stuttering! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Did you guys actually get the nuketown came? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-23 05:49:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If you didn't already have nuketown before the update, do you get the camo? Just wondering. I got the camo, but I had nuketown before the update. Wondering if the camo is still considered rare or if literally everyone has it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Mouse sensitivity help </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-17 02:19:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> mouse-sensitivity seems to have a premium requirement for bo3   I really want the same sens cuz muscle memory, any help would be nice :-]
1200 dpi, .9 ingame on csgo, 96 fov on bo3. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Mouse Sensitivity help bo3 </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-17 02:08:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> mouse-sensitivity seems to have a premium requirement for bo3   I really want the same sens cuz muscle memory, any help would be nice :-]
1200 dpi, .9 ingame on csgo, 96 fov on bo3. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> can someone explain to me what the fuck happened here? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-14 04:15:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Up to date installation? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-09 23:34:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> police officer plays cs go </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-09 18:46:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> anime_irl </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-08 00:31:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> meirl </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-08 00:10:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Random jumps scrolling only in browser </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-05 02:44:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> LG G3 with Fulmics 4.2 @ Stock kernel running latest Reddit is fun version available through the play store. Extremely annoying. Only started happening recently. The jumps are consistent and there is no way for me to look through an imgur gallery or read an article without opening via Chrome </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Fulmics 4.0 D852 Constant Signal Loss </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-29 15:39:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> How would I go about fixing this? Data works fine when the signal is there, and WiFi is fine. Do I just need to wait for an OTA by xpirt or can I fix it myself? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> This price tag </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-20 19:52:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> When using multiwindow mode, can I remove the border? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-19 17:42:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The annoying blue border around the window selected, can I get rid of it? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> When should we be expecting a Marshmallow CloudyG3? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-18 21:45:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Source? More like this? (1920x2880) </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-08 05:51:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [Serious] Managers of Reddit, have you ever had to fire someone because of Internet activity? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-03 05:22:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> meirl </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-29 00:58:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Pickup line </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-24 22:22:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> "I'm cold, will you be my GTX 480?" </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Moron on YouTube thinks that the use of an intro makes his argument invalid. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-24 02:08:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Comment section on a "What Mac Should I Buy?" Article </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-23 17:12:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> ELI5: Why has the audio department not grown nearly as much as the graphical department in the past 10 years? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-16 22:17:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Inferno T spawn Bomb unretrievable in fountain </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-07 05:48:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I dont have any pictures (mobile)

Just thought i should report it </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Screen suddenly using up 10x more battery than usual. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-05 03:46:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Title says all. I didn't change anything to my phone, but it suddenly just started draining 10x faster. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Windows loads fast? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-04 06:28:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Which OST is this from? (7:33) </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-01 19:19:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Cloudy G3 lack of data? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-31 18:05:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> D852 here! I dont have any data using cloudy g3. I turn it on but it never connects.

Edit: i also have an issue where to turn on the phone i have to put out and back in the battery? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Looking to get BF4... </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-23 09:43:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> (CAD) [W] Battlefield 4 [H] Any steam game 9$ or below </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-23 09:30:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Glorious Christmas Gift </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-23 04:52:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Whats up with Steam's built-in FPS counter? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-21 21:19:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The built-in steam FPS counter shows generally more than 500fps. Yet net_graph never shows over 200 unless private servers.

My specs is an r9 380 and an fx 8320. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> A professional comedians job is to be unprofessional. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-14 04:16:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Am I the only one who just got a 900mb update? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-12 02:10:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> i just got a 900mb update... no one is posting about it. I had it almost 20 mins ago? is it just me or something? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> My palms have ascended </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-09 23:27:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Battery required to be taken out and back in to be restarted. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-08 17:12:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I have a g852, with root and twrp. This has been happening for a while and I have been looking for a fix </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The first thing I learnt on Reddit a few years back was that my opinion is wrong. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-05 06:02:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> I have no idea what all this Richard Lewis drama is right now. Can someone explain? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-01 21:13:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> admin hes doing it sideways </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-11-29 22:26:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> My Math Teacher is Bullshit, how do I Deal With it? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-11-25 17:31:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So my math teacher isn't very good. I could explain how she doesn't explain well and everything but everyone knows what that's like. The real problem is the grades. The class average is 62% so that proves that. My first report card I got a 74%. Now I wasn't very happy with that (obviously) so I tried my hardest to improve. Since then we have done 2 tests and a quiz. The tests I have achieved 93% and 81% respectively. The quiz was about 70%. One kid asked for her to show us her updated marks after the stated assessments, and my mark has dropped down to 71%?? This confuses me and is hurting my head. How could this be possible. I finish all my homework and quite frankly should not have had my mark drop. This is grade 9 math if it matters and yes I understand grade 9 grades don't really matter but they do to me. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> People are just normal type Pokemon. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-11-22 08:00:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> FNATIC.com: "It's Our Time" - Announcing Fnatic Gear </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-11-19 01:46:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Best Pro Games This Month? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-10-19 03:01:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What are the best pro games and most interesting/fun to watch games played in leagues this month? looking to kick back relax and watch some games but I don't feel like pickin' choosin' and getting a boring game where they wreck 16-2 or something. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Any e-Shop's Selling Black NiP Jersey's for Cheap in Canada/America? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-10-09 03:24:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> ie: http://www.esportstore.com/t-shirts/ninjas-in-pyjamas-2/player-jersey-2015-black-edition-nip

By cheap I would prefer to be 20-30 CAD without extra payment or shipping. 

Would love to wear this around but can't find anything online </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Looking through games my games back in silver I found this. Not bad compared to new silver. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-10-01 04:55:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [H] Gut Ultraviolet MW + Adds [W] Bayonet Ultraviolet FT </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-09-23 23:27:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Microsoft David as Voice Chat? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-09-18 15:49:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I was playing a game of MM and one guy on our team didn't have a mic, but he was using voice chat with Microsoft David, now if I wanted to do the same thing for many reasons how would I go about doing so, every time he spoke he stopped as if to write something first. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> (GAME ISSUES) Low fps on high end computer w/ details </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-09-10 02:13:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Im getting about 40-55fps in a valve deathmatch. I have an r9 270x and an FX 8320 Game is unplayable for me and I would love to see if any of you could help me. Afterburner after 6 minutes of Valve Deathmatch: http://imgur.com/LK6G8H4 CPU-Z on CPU tab (without cs go running): http://imgur.com/SzVCtU3 If you need any more info I will give, but I want my framerate back! I used to get a good 300-400fps. Now it just feels slow ;-; </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What does C9 say to the clutcher? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-08-18 06:48:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> n0thing, he's clutching </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Struggling to get the game running. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-04 19:12:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I launch the game and it starts normally, but in 4:3 aspect ratio and a really low square resolution taking up about 1/4th of my screen, when I go to the settings and change it, the game freezes. I can choose it. But as I click apply it freezes. I have deleted the file in my documents and tried. I may have reinstalled it im not sure though. Any fix? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Don't downvote "stupid" or naive posts and comments: You're basically telling kids and other people trying to learn something about CS to Shut Up and Go Away. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-03 17:38:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> All left mouse commands unbinded on accident? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-17 20:08:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I accidentally unbinded my left mouse key. Can I have a command that binds all needed things back? Also Ive noticed when im holding the bomb and i get onto site it automatically plants without me doing anything. Fix?
EDIT: Right clicking with knife doesnt do anything either
EDIT#2: tried going into game settings and its fixed. But I cant shoot for some fucking reason </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> (HELP) Trying to make a clutch config with voice_enable </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-15 22:56:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> bind "o" voice_enable 0, "say_team Clutch Mode Enabled! I can't hear what your saying. Go ahead and spam voice chat!"

bind "p" voice_enable 1, "say_team Clutch Mode Disabled! I can hear you loud and clear!"

This doesnt seem to work. Pressing O says the thing in team chat but does not disable voice chat. Whats the issue? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Help creating an autoexec? Would it even be legal? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-11 18:53:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I have trouble switching to my pistol when im out of ammo. I think t switch but I never do and end up just reloading and dying.

Could there be a script that allows you to automatically switch to a pistol when you run out of ammo, and would that be legal in normal Valve matchmaking? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Unplayable lag ever since update? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-02 01:15:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I updated. And now my game has lag spikes every 1 or so second it feels like 15 fps. I am getting 60 but spikes make it 15. I just attached a new monitor so that may also be an issue, but my card is an r9 270x and that shouldnt be a huge issue. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> (Question) Is there a way to purchase a canadian Steam card for a friend when I live in the UK? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-24 23:18:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Text says all. I want to gift my friend a 20 canadian steam card but im in uk and i cant find anywhere to buy it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Satan had a Change of Heart </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-07 03:42:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Lets play a game. Things you say during BoI that can get you arrested IRL </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-02 16:03:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> "Stupid headless baby creep not working right." </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> (DISCUSSION) To Opening or Not to Opening, that is the Question. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-30 21:54:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Do you watch openings on all your anime shows? Do you skip them after watching it once? I personally try to watch all of them. Sometimes I skip it if I just can't watch it cuz it sucks or something but personally I see Openings as a work of art. (Unless they suck) But most are great. So what do you do? Discuss. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> DLC Idea? Mom Transformation. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-18 22:34:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Obviously it will be very overpowered. But to transform into her you are going to need 6 Mom items </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Uhm... Definitely not a won run. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-18 21:33:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> 71% Acheivements in 171 hours... Am I bad? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-17 00:36:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Title says it all 
Update: 90% now </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> So... What exactly is the Gurdy family? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-15 03:43:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Not to mention the Mega Maw, the Adversary/Dark One, The cage, and obviously Mr. Fred. What are these bosses? I have no idea of what they are supposed to represent/be.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Acheivement flair not updating? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-10 21:06:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Original BoI Mods? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-10 17:43:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So I sent my GPU off for repairs and my integrated card doesnt support OpenGL. So I cant play Rebirth. But I dont want to play the original normally. I would love to play it but I'd like mods to make it more interesting. Anyone wanna link me to the must-get mods for the original BoI? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> How to tell what items you need to PICKUP for RPlat. God? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-08 04:05:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> How can we tell what items we need to pick up, not unlock, pick up, for platinum god? Is the items tab in game show whats unlocked, or whats been picked up? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> (Request) mixed soundtrack mod? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-06 05:12:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I was thinking as a person who couldn't get into vanilla very much I do like the soundtrack. But I don't want to replace the soundtrack. Why not make a mod that randomly alternates between vanilla and rebirth's music. Any thoughts? If you know how, I'm begging you to make it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Has the dead cat been improved? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-12-31 18:26:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> From pictures on this subreddit I can tell that the dead cat item no longer puts your heart containers as 1. But the wiki still says it puts it at one. Can I have some confirmation about this topic? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Question about library   TF2 </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-12-30 20:23:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If you download a game such as L4D2 from someones elses library via family sharing, will you get the frying pan in tf2?
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [CAD] [H] Tropico 4 Collectors bundle [W] Paypal </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-11-28 04:48:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> (REVIEW) Cortex:Deals! Save money on all the games you buy! </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-11-16 02:02:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The Binding of Isaac: Rebirth STEAM CD-KEY GLOBAL 14 dollars </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-11-06 00:21:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [CAN] [H] Tropico 4 Collector's Bundle [STEAM] [W] $ </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-10-27 00:53:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [CAN] [H] Tropico 4 Collector's Bundle [STEAM] [W] 33.99$ (Canadian) in  (Preferably) Amazon, or PayPal
For proof I own the bundle PM me
If you have any other offers just comment. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Earhoox Free refferal Jogging Earbuds </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-10-20 00:21:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
