<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject2044</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-13 10:54:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Firstly, why not do what everyone else in Hollywood does and watch the original Twilight Zone episodes. There are episodes like your idea, but many of them, and all only 22 minutes long (enough to get the idea rather than drag a one-note idea into a feature length like all these other shitty twist-driven films seem to do).   

Secondly, how can you keep your integrity as a writer by asking people for ideas? If you're not inspired, what's the point?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-13 10:48:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Exactly. OP has distorted the obvious into something obtusely generalized.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-12 13:10:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I really enjoyed watching Sucker Punch at the cinema. It was just the right balance of visual and intellectual for me, and by intellectual I mean I appreciated the various symbols, metaphors and layered analogies that were going on. I saw it as essentially Sweet Pea's story.   

Anyhow, because I gave it an 8 on IMDB, whenever I get into situations of criticizing a fan-boy magnet film, morons tend to trawl my IMDB review history, going back however many years it takes for Sucker Punch, then write the obligatory "well you liked Sucker Punch, so goodbye to your credibility!" etc.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-11 17:23:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> When it started, I thought "oh gawd, is this going to be ok", as nice and cheery as that opening number was I thought it might be Moulin Rouge all over again. So happy to be so wrong.  

The story was perfectly balanced, feeling like a bigger film but afraid to be small and quirky either. I really wasn't prepared for the ending, it lodged a haunting thought so deep in my mind I can't shake it. Few films have that power.  

I think it will win best picture, but its a shame that the hype will then likely smother it and ruin its low-key feel. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-09 02:18:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Sing Street </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-09 02:18:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Great film, love the panning shots that link the different time periods.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-09 02:15:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Olympus Has Fallen is fucking shit compared to 80s action films, it doesnt have much rewatch value at all.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-06 15:47:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The was the first 18 (UK) film I saw as a kid, aged about 12, and this scene had me absolutely petrified. It was like it was happening to me. When he's being rushed to hospital having those flashbacks, I could barely breathe. 

Modern films will never be able to create that insane impressionability and automatic empathy of those pre-teen years. I think it's why I'm so fond of Terminator, Aliens, Die Hard and Predator too, I felt like I was IN those films.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-05 14:17:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yes, that bit was cringey as hell. The whole Valek thing felt so much cheesier at home. Also, at the cinema the bit where the girl levitates and has the exorcist face thing going on somehow worked, but at home I felt a bit embarrassed like someone was about to laugh. 

It does go to show though how much more engaging the cinema experience can be. It's hard to trust amateur reviews these days too, because people watching on laptops etc have a wildly divergent sense of engagement.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-05 14:12:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The space ones are always nice, like Hubble and Space Station. My favourite though is Deep Sea smething or other, the feature length James Cameron one with his deep sea submersibles. The 3D is excellent, as it's super interesting too. Warner Herzog's caving documentary is pretty good too.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-04 12:57:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I agree completely. It was also too dark, poorly edited in places, and suffered that endless death/get-up-again videogame mentality. Im confused by the praise it gets, even Green Room last year was a much better film, and I wasnt its biggest fan.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-04 12:53:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I watched Mockingjay 1 2 with a friend the other day and we found them absolutely dire. Then, because she hadnt seen Raiders ever, we watched that and loved it. Its so infused with a great balance of action, humor, mystery and little offbeat moments. Also, the music is so emotionally stirring, especially that spooky track when they're looking at the illustration in the bible.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-03 13:40:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I saw The conjuring 2 again and it was nowhere near the experience of seeing it the first time at the cinema. The scares lose obviously impact, and without them there isn't really much else to get into. But I did love it at the cinema. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-03 12:25:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's great fun to watch, very rewatchable. Feels like Twilight Zone and Quantum Leap rolled into one. On that note, Scott Backups plays his dad, and says "oh boy" when he hears from his son.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-29 18:25:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I saw Citizen X last night on Prime US, and thought then how great D Sutherland is. I hope he stays alive a little longer and knocks out more great performances. He was terrific in Eye of The Needle too. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-29 18:23:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I absolutely hated Good Kill, and found EITS much more interesting. GK was such a dull film, and so massively clichd. Smoking, punching mirrors, acting distant and frustrated at bbqs, it was almost satirical. I actually wish EITS had been more satirical, it would have been great as a Dr strangelove/in the loop style film.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-28 14:10:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Another scene I love in this movie is where he goes to dinner with the in-laws, but gets hopelessly distracted by his deadlines. His finger twitching, eyes darting around, losing concetration to listen, then just announces that hes leaving, knowing full well he's truly in the shit with his wife.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-28 14:07:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Pain and Gain is one of my favourite films, Ive seen it maybe six times so far which is unusual for me for a modern film. I love the soundtrack, satire, editing, acting, color saturated shots, and energy.  

Also, The Living Daylights is my favourite Bond film by far, and in my top ten of all time (Im talking personal favourites here, not saying its one of the ten best films ever made, although I do think its hugely underrated as a Bond script).  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-28 14:02:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I saw that again recently and it felt just as terrifying as when I first saw it at the cinema. That sense of inevitable death, like "ok, this is where I die" and the quiet, panicked nature of it, so chilling.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-28 14:00:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This is why random opinions have no real value if someone is about to watch a film anyway. They influence the perception rigjt off the bat because the viewer is more likely (even if unconsciously) to see through a negative lens. Eye In The Sky was one of my favourite cinema experiences of last year, when seeing a preview before knowing anything about it. Reading your line beforehand though, I can see how someone would look at it negatively instead.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-23 15:32:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Listen to the soundtrack for the game Hotline Miami (which is VERY Drive-ish, down to masks, hammers, cars and whatnot). Also stuff by Cliff Martinez, Clint Mansell, John Carpenter.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-23 15:30:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I hate seeing fake CGI blood in action movies when someone gets shot. Something about those bright red pixels that fly out of their neck or whatever that removes me from the moment and makes me feel like Im watching a cartoon. I dont see whats so expensive about good ol' fashioned squibs  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-22 14:22:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You went into the movie blind... yet you wanted it to be a particular way?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-22 13:38:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I think you were too bound by your expectations to see the film for what it actually was. There is far more than what you noticed, especially around the ambiguity of the word "drive" and how characters are motivated. Maybe in a few years when you've flushed your expectations and resistances, you'll appreciate it in a different way.  

Drive can seem a little pretentious though, especially if you notice the repetitive teal/orange color pallette. The soundtrack and retro vibes redeems it a little.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-20 01:11:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thats awesome. Its so great when you sync with something obsessively. Did you see The Newsroom? Its not quite there in terms of Steve Jobs quality, but has its moments. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What good Cardboard games have you gotten into lately? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-19 16:52:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> After playing a bunch throughout the year (mostly shit that gets boring after a minute or so), my favourites by far have been Gravity Pull (would love more levels/gimmicks on this one), Hardcode (would love more levels, and much prefer the collect levels to the shoot endless baddies ones), Retro Wrong demo and Wrong Level (both incredibly atmospheric and immersive, and decent lengths too). I would love to see more like the latter two, I love the sense of space and huge abstract structures.  Retro Wrong demo is actually my favourite game so far in terms of variety, gameplay, atmosphere. The darker levels are also pretty frightening in places like where the skeletons come rushing out at you, and I like that the levels have their own unique feels and ideas.  

Mostly I've found the gamepad controlled shooters (zombies etc) to be pretty lame, its quite hard to aim with your head and they just get repetitive after a while.  

Mostly though, games seem to just be incredibly short or show some promise without being properly developed. I'm not sure why there arent more developed/complete games for Cardboard, I would happily pay for a decent, bigger version of Wrong Level for example and I'm sure others would too.  

I find the space shooters mostly repetitive and not interesting enough to want to return to. I love the immersive feel of good space apps but most of them are pretty lame. Returning Home is amazingly good in terms of relaxing atmosphere and epic James Cameron feel, I wish they would build a great game around it. E.g. being sent to various space stations to collect/fix/eliminate things would be awesome.  

What are your favourite games? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Superman II gave me a false memory for 30 years - what false memories did you get from childhood movies? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-05 10:57:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> *** Superman II spoilers follow ***

Superman crushing Zods hand In Superman II was one of the most cinematic, exciting moments of my childhood. I was so gutted that Luthor ratted out his plan, and that he'd lost his powers *again*. I could have cried. So the surprise and awesome turnaround in that moment was mind-blowing.   

But - for 30 years, even with all the TV repeats, I distinctly remember seeing Superman CRUSH Zods hand. I always saw it as a prosthetic hand, that Superman actually does crush, before cutting to Terence Stamp's actual, non-crushed hand as he flings it away (which even as a kid I saw as a continuity niggle).   

So watching on Bluray over the weekend I was amazed to see that he doesn't crush his hand at all - it just seems that way from the bone-crunching sound effects and Zod's "aarrggghhh". If you watch it on mute, it just looks like a tight grip. I couldn't believe it.  I still think its the best superhero film of all time. 

Also, I remembered his trek back to his ice-home to get his powers back taking *days*, like it was a real endeavor that takes up a lot of screentime. But in reality it takes about 10 seconds. The time from his losing his powers to getting them back again is about 5 minutes, basically the scene in the diner.   

**TL,DR: Superman doesn't actually crush Zod's hand, just grips it tightly.** 

What films tricked you into remembering something that didn't actually happen? Another example is the ear-cutting scene in Reservoir Dogs - always surprises me when the camera pans as if its a censored version, I imagined it so strongly on first watch that I remember my imagination more than the film.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> David Cronenberg films are the "Black Mirror" of their day </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-12 11:03:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Gus Gorman in Superman III was an incredible genius </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-31 16:03:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> He designed a computer on the back of *sweet wrappers and receipts*, which has some ridiculously good hardware and functionality. It can suck power from electricity lines, through miles of ground, eventually knocking out whole states on the national grid. It can create bubbles which completely encapsulate people. 

Most impressive though, it can turn a woman into a robot within seconds, affecting her personality and corneas, as well as providing her with the ability to stick people to walls. 

Also of course he hacked the payment system for those lost decimal pennies (which they tried to do again in Office Space). 

Was there ever a cleverer character in a film?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Post Offices asking whats inside your parcel... then discussing it </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-11 10:51:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I find it infuriating in Post Offices when they ask whats inside whatever you're sending. As if trying to catch out customers who are sending batteries, or flammables, or bombs or whatever.  

I can half understand the safety angle, although it would be easier to just ask "does it contain any of these items? No? Good", because you could just answer anything. These days I just say "socks, biscuits, no batteries" whatever it is.  

My main frustration is where the ill-trained, nosy tosspots in Post Offices (particularly the smaller town/village ones) then use it as a point of discussion. I want to say "actually its none of your business" but that would risk "suspicion".  

The other day I was posting a small quadcopter sold on ebay, the guy then asked "how many of those do you sell then? Do you make a profit do you? Where did you get that then, from China?" On another item when saying it had no batteries, an old lady serving another customer with food next to the post office bit who was listening in (as they all seem to do) screws her face up and says "how does it work then?" to which I said "the person uses their own batteries". She looked at me like I was trying to send anthrax or something. Then I've had staff stalling what they're supposed to be doing whilst they ask me more about what I was sending as if they're interested in buying whatever it is, with the building queue behind listening to every word. I just find it embarrassing, and it goes well beyond the point of why they're asking.  

Don't even get me started on how they mix up 1st/2nd class about 30% of the time because they aren't listening.  

Although I like the connection/face-to-face of places like banks, shops and supermarkets, the Post Office is one place where I can't wait for automation to take over, the sooner I can just scan, pay and send stuff with a machine, the better.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Primer (2004) - Did you know the weebles were a hoax? That Abe has already time-travelled at the start of the film? This website explains everything, and will stretch your brain. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-10 13:49:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Films that are disproportionately remembered for smaller segments </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-14 11:27:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I was watching **Westworld** again recently and realised that the Yul Brynner's robot doesn't kill anyone until after an hour into the movie. The first signs of things going wrong don't even happen until about 55 minutes in. That's almost an hour of set-up, for a less than twenty minute climactic chase scene, for which the film is mostly remembered.  

I remember **Home Alone** as Kevin setting traps for the burglars, but weirdly the traps scene only happens within the last ten minutes of the film.   

**No Way Out** - I remember the film being about the feds closing in on Kevin Costner's framed character, with the polaroid gradually scanning. I thought that all started after perhaps 15 minutes, but it actually starts half-way through the film. The first half is all used to set up the second half, for which the film is mostly remembered.  

Are there any other examples like this?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> How do you define hypnosis? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-02 15:21:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I've read so many definitions, and its so difficult to find one that can't be pulled apart. If you Google "what is hypnosis" the definition that pops up talks about hypnosis as state, narrowing of consciousness and suchlike.   

Whats your definition?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What did you think of Tony Scott's last film "Stop That Train!" (2010) </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-02 14:01:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> How much does your videostore charge for late fees? Do they check if you rewound the cassette? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-09 19:19:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I recently returned Robocop 2 and Dead Calm a day late, and was charged 2. They noticed I hadn't wound back Dead Calm and made a thing of it. I don't really care, the tapes stunk of cigarettes anyway. What's your local store like?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Name the films of the paraphrased quotes, then add your own </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-04 14:10:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> 1. They have taken it upon themselves to prevent the flow of free electrons into the cabling surrounding our vicinity. Its a mystery to me as to how they would have the capacity to carry out such a measure, being that they are sub-human creatures. 

2. You have a desire for a description of events that is entirely free of deception, yet you lack the sufficient capacity to be able to adequately process the information. 

3. It is a requisite that I ensure the whereabouts of a collection of magnetic media is restored to its former location.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Why I love Pain and Gain (2013) </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-02 12:42:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What do you think of Pain and Gain? 

I think it suffers from a massive case of negative bias, because its rare that a typically trashy director could pull off something brilliant. I'm pretty sure if it was a subtitled Spanish movie by the director of Timecrimes or something that it would be heralded as a cult classic. I love Hitchcock, Kubrick, Coens, Billy Wilder, Tarkovsky, Kieslowski, Lynch, even Wild Strawberries - but Pain and Gain somehow became my favorite movie. 

Here's why I love it:

**Its brilliantly satirical.** The writers took a fascinating true-story and recognised its potential for a piss-take of the American dream. How greed, selfishness, stupidity, pride and excessive indulgence all became entwined. In classical style, the script structure mirrors a lifetime - the young, early days of yearning/scheming, the flabby indulgent middle age where emptiness and desperation kick in, the inevitable fall where it all gets taken away. The references to pop-culture ("the greatest men were self-made; Rocky, Scarface, The Godfather", the stripper basing her plan on Julia Roberts in Pretty Woman), the toxic values of the self-help industry (Johnny Wu standing in for Tony Robbins), the liberties taken with the story - it all adds to the fun of the satire. After all their incarcerations and the final edits of what happened, the voiceover of "that's the American dream baby" before the credits hit seals the deal. 

The **color saturation, photography, editing** perfectly match the story, tone, energy and satire. Its why I think Michael Bay was the perfect choice to direct. It never gets boring on re-watches. Its shot and edited so tightly, with a ferocious energy that really makes the most of the medium. The use of different cameras and styles with kinetic editing reminds me of what Oliver Stone was going for with U-Turn, but Pain and Gain works so much better. 

**The soundtrack is brilliant.** I've listened to it a lot as standalone music whilst swimming in Portugal, and hearing it in the film anchors me right back to those awesome summer vibes. The use of non-score songs like Gangsta's Paradise also fit the film perfectly. It needs to be seen/heard on a good system for sure, to do justice to the film.  

There are so many other great touches throughout - Ed Harris's reflective narration about life to anchor the overblown satire to some grounding (with an excellent bit of score - [Du Bois](https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=WFs4MJWLfeM)), the toe-shooting sequence, the Rock's acting of being high, the scenes shot in Bay's own house, Tony Shalhoub's performance.  

**TL:DR; Pain and Gain is better than you think, and you should re-watch it on a good system.** 
  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Implausibility I noticed in Bill and Ted's Bogus Journey (1991) </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-01 10:13:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> When Rufus throws his electric guitar at the phone box to follow the evil robot Bill and Ted's back in time, it sticks in the top as though it were a pointed blade. I'm just not sure about the physics of that, it would surely just bounce off?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What movie am I thinking of? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-28 13:00:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It has Harvey Keitel and Michael Madsen, a retro soundtrack, a cult film director, a cop gets locked in the trunk of a car, two main stars in the final shot supposedly die out of frame. 

Oh yeah, and its not Reservoir Dogs.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Replayed for the first time in two years, found it underwhelming </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-11 12:01:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I've quite enjoyed replaying games in the past (e.g Max Payne, Portal, Limbo, I'm not much of a gamer). The first play through of TLOU two years ago was a great and novel experience.   

Recently I played through again on PS4, but found it underwhelming, to the extent that it tarnished my memory of the first playthrough. Yes, the graphics are gorgeous, but once you adapt the playability then becomes the important factor, and this is where I felt it lacking. 

The only bits I really enjoyed are the action bits that involve choices, strategising a route through a room to get the bad guys with stealth kills. The rest of it was just linear - ladders, pallets, generators, doors, walking, more walking, cut-scenes, exploring everywhere for annoying extras/ammo. Even the story this time felt cliched - there are a few interesting moments (e.g. the end) but mostly its "oh here's a character - get used to them - now they're changing in some way! Surprise!"   

So yeah, I would be interested to hear if others have replayed it a lot and what your experiences are?    </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Charley Varrick (1973) is well worth seeking out </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-11 11:11:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I saw this awesome Don Siegel (Dirty Harry, Invasion of Body Snatchers) movie over the weekend, and couldn't believe I hadn't heard of it before.   

Walter Mattau playing the Tommy-Lee Jones of his day is a bank robber, helped by Andy Robinson (the bad guy from Dirty Harry, also in Hellraiser). I won't ruin anything, but it was clearly obvious that Tarantino loves this film, and you even get to hear the original delivery of "get to work on you with some pliers and a blowtorch". Its an intelligent film with great characters (Joe Don Baker is awesome) and a fun, fast-moving story. Bits of it also reminded me of Fargo Season 2. The picture quality on bluray is amazing, the cinematography is interesting too.   

I enjoyed it far, far more than most modern films I've seen recently.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Wrong Level VR - excellent atmospheric VR game </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-27 10:49:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Did you miss Green Room? If you're near a Picture House you can see it for free this Sunday </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-26 10:17:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> ShowFilmFirst website, code is 757053.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> BoboVR Z4 - Headphone jack issue for bottom-jack phones (e.g. LG G3, G4) </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-26 10:04:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This has been briefly touched on in [other](https://www.reddit.com/r/GoogleCardboard/comments/4g9lam/bobovr_z4_and_lg_g3_rotate_screen/) threads but I thought it would be useful to draw more attention to it. 

If you've ordered/thinking of buying a BoboVR Z4, and your headphone jack is on the bottom (e.g. LG G3, LG G4, I'm sure a few others), then the headphone jack won't extend to the other side.  

Some say "doesn't matter, most apps rotate the screen anyway" but its too annoying, e.g:  
Cmoar cinema: (and I'm sure most other cinema apps) doesn't preserve the correct 3D once its flipped, also the tracking is completely affected, often horizontal motion completely freezes.  
Hardcode: controls are reversed  
QVR: doesn't flip at all  
Zombies and Aliens: you're now on the underside of your gun, like a badass mini-me   

There is about 2 inches of cable inside the headset, so frustrating that they didn't think to make this longer.  
 
I bought an [extender](http://www.ebay.co.uk/itm/2x-3-5mm-Male-to-Female-Stereo-Audio-Extension-Extender-Cable-Cord-for-Headphone-/381492695551), but whilst waiting for it to arrive I've realised that the volume control and mic functionality will be lost, and Amazon reviews of these short extenders are dreadful in terms of crackly sound.   

I don't fancy re-soldering to the mic board as its tiny, but something I might try is cutting the cable near the mic board, soldering/twisting/wrapping as many leads as I need to extend the cable as much as I need to, then carefully fixing the dodgier section of cable along the underside of the front panel so that the decent end is free to be connected to the right side.  

If any one else with this problem tackles it effectively, would be keen to hear! 


 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Z4 finally arrived, can compare to Fiit/LeNest (also, thoughts) </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-25 12:12:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> **First impressions of Z4** - really impressive. Comfortable, nice big bright and clear image quality. I used Ceder Falls Coaster as a tester, and it looked great. The adjustment dials (moving the phone forward and backwards and lens width for IPD) are GREAT for quickly getting that nice sharp image. The image is almost *too* sharp - watching a high bitrate rip of Bladerunner in Cmoar, I could notice the artifacts/colour palette reduction of the app's image processing.  

**Sound** - I wasn't as disappointed by the sound as I was prepared to be. I think its fine - but there is a caveat. The headphones sound A LOT better if you push them onto your ears more. On the Cedar Falls Coaster, you could then hear the bassy thunder of the coaster. In Cmoar cinema, it made the sound "truer", the bass notes filling the screen more. Without pushing the phones in to your ears, it sounds tinnier and the bass notes are lost. This difference will probably create a hugely varied difference of opinion in people based on whether they push them in more or not. I really think the headstrap should have been on the *other side* (i.e. outer side) of the headphone arms - so that they naturally push them into your ears. I'm going to have to take it apart to switch them around. Other than that, I love the convenience of the headphones, and the weight/balancing on the head is great.  **Edit: fixed them**. Using assistance from /u/VRKommando's [mod tutorial](https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=1EeqAWxX1nI), [I fixed the straps to the other side](http://imgur.com/a/YfFeq). Sound quality is loads better.   

**Compared to Fiit**   

Comfort wise, Z4 wins so much. The face surround (for me) lets in no light, whereas it does a bit with Fiit. The convenience of the adjustments on Z4 is great. With Fiit, I *hate* the individually adjustable lenses, they're a pain in the ass. You have to remove the thing to get at them. If you wipe mist in that first 10 mins of settling into a movie, you inadvertently twist them round until they're imbalanced, and I've had them fall out a few times as well. The comfort of the lenses themselves is also much better on the Z4 - they don't touch my face at all. With Fiit, the big ridges around the lenses (where you adjust them) dig into the underside of my brow and it bugs the hell out of me. Z4 is really nice and comfortable.   

**FOV/image.** I set up Perfect Beach to compare image size, area etc. The overall image size of Z4 seems about 20-30% bigger than Fiit, its definitely an improvement. BUT - the actual area of 3D is about the same, and this has consequences. The image in the Z4 is like a Venn diagram (two circles overlapping), so a chunk of the image on each side is only seen by one eye. I would say its about 60% in the middle is 3D, with 20% on each side 2D (maybe even 50/25/25). When you're looking dead center, its not a problem, everything on your fovea looks fine and your peripheral vision doesn't pick up the 2D on the sides. But if you look around a bit, its noticeable. With the Fiit, the image is smaller, but more wholly 3D (better overlap). So I'm not sure what to make of that. If you were watching a film where the image was fixed (e.g. to prevent drift, lying in bed or whatever) then the outer sections of the frame would only be visible to one eye. If it was a 3D film, then it could ruin the immersion. In Cmoar cinema, I loaded a 3D film and found it felt better with 120 set in the FOV settings, to make the screen smaller. But, it was still loads better in the Z4 having a bigger overall image for the sense of immersion. The Fiit in comparison felt like looking down a looroll. NB: I set QR codes/adjustments right for the comparisons. 

**Headphone jack issue on Z4** - the headphone jack can't stretch to the other side of the phone. Most apps flip the screen accordingly so its all good, but I know a few are fixed, so on an LG G4 or any phone where the jack is at the bottom of your phone, there could be a problem there and you might need to get an extender at some point. Cmoar cinema for example, if watching a 3D film and you flip your phone so the top of the phone is on the right hand side, then the 3D of the film gets inverted. So yeah, its an issue. **Fix**: [This](http://www.ebay.co.uk/itm/2x-3-5mm-Male-to-Female-Stereo-Audio-Extension-Extender-Cable-Cord-for-Headphone-/381492695551) should hopefully do the trick (when they finally arrive). 

**TL:DR;** Z4 way more comfortable, excellent adjustments. Sound is fine *if* you push the phones in more, you should purchase a headphone extender if your headphone jack is on the bottom of your phone. Nice FOV, but compromised 3D area, hopefully not too much of an issue.    </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Frustration importing a Z4 from China, ugh </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-18 16:04:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So I ordered a Z4 from Netswin on aliexpress on 30th March, received an email to say it was shipped 31st March. I was quite surprised about this, because I thought they were only available from one company before April 10th.   

Was given a tracking number, it just showed "no information available".  

Yesterday I emailed the company to ask why its late - I paid an extra $10 for 5-10 shipping. They said to wait, be patient etc. Then, miraculously a few hours later, the shipping is updated to say its left the sorting office... *but hasn't left China yet.* Really fucking frustrating!  

How are you guys getting on with your orders?   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Odeon ruin the surprise for a third time </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-10 20:21:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So first they revealed The Big Short with an explanation of the first clue in its email.  

Then they email out Midnight Special in the title of their reminder email. They say its a "glitch with the email" and that it won't happen again.   

So the very next time - they do the exact same thing, putting the film in the title of their reminder email.  

Seriously, how fucking stupid are they. Its one thing to make a mistake, its another to specifically say you won't make the mistake again, then do that same thing at the next opportunity.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> WEARVR - an awesome collection of VR apps. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-08 10:25:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I got kinda bored trawling Play for VR apps, the same stuff kept showing up over and over (fibrum etc) and the longer you scroll the more irrelevant (and lower rated) it quickly seems to get. Also, there are loads of VR apps without VR or 3D in the title, so they're hard to find.  

Then I downloaded WEARVR app. Its a collection of VR apps which you can order by newest etc, and I found loads more stuff on there which seems buried on Play store.  

Check it out, I'm sure you'll discover some cool new experiences.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What are some good VR games? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-05 16:14:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I've noticed the Google Play store games tend to be pretty shoddy - single levels, unfinished, full of ads etc. E.g Go4d has great potential, but is just a single short level. Hardcode is pretty good. Some of the zombie shooters are ok.  

I only discovered DVR and QVR (the Doom and Quake ports by DrBeef) via an old thread - they don't tend to show up in searches for VR, Cardboard or 3D. Are there any other good games that are hard to find? Or maybe available elsewhere from the Play store?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Odeon really frustrate me </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-31 15:49:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Here's the thing - ScreenUnseen is a brilliant idea. Its fun, the films are (mostly) great, and I LOVE that bit of excitement just before the cert screen where you're thinking "whatsitgonnabe?" I also like the shared experience of other people showing up for it, its like you're all in this experience together. Its nice when people chat about it afterwards, you don't normally get that after seeing a film. Basically, its like a big film club for film fans, and kudos to Odeon for having the balls to do something different. 

YET...

They completely screw it up by having the most incompetent schmucks in their marketing department, spoiling the last one and the next one. 

This contradiction is perfectly encapsulated by their in-screen branding. When you get into the theatre, you see this huge O on the screen, blue swirling background, it looks cool and exciting. Then you get the clip where some juvenile, self-conscious idiotic ass-hat says "now its time for the trailers - ah - the trailers - my favourite bit!" and then the clip about switching off phones and not talking "yeah, that includes you two in the middle!" His voice is so pathetic it carries all the persuasive power of a perturbed ant. 

  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> First VR experience - using LeNest (Fiit)   LG G4 </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-31 10:06:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I researched for days, eventually settling on the LeNest (aka Fiit) based on u/MariaKorolov's review [here](http://www.hypergridbusiness.com/2016/03/review-lenest-viewer-is-close-to-perfect/). I've ordered a Z4 too from alibaba.  

I'm using an LG G4, and it fits in perfectly in the holder bit. I have a QuickCircle case on my phone, and it works fine to bend the case around to the back - it still cushions in perfectly. I used the QR code for Freefly as per MK's recommendation. 

Thoughts - the FOV isn't quite the immersion I was hoping for, so I hope the 120 promised by Z4 is better. I can see the square shape of the screen in front of me, some of the surrounding internals of the device, and even light between the cushioning pads between my face and device. I have quite a deep brow, and something that doesn't get mentioned much in reviews is how individual face shape effects the experience. The face comfort for LeNest isn't great - its thin foam, and the material between the strip of foam and the plastic device is translucent. This means I have to hold my hands around the gaps to get darkness (until I mod it at least). Also, the plastic upper ridge really digs into my forehead as I try to push it on tight enough to close out the side light.  

I've unscrewed the eye lenses as far as they'll go before falling out, to ensure they're as close to my eyes as possible. The image is really clear - I was really impressed and expected it to be far more pixelated.  

The IPD adjustment is essential to get a comfortable view - I know the Freefly lacks this, so I'm glad I didn't go for that. 
 
Also - I found it essential to get easy access to my phone (again the Freefly is apparently a nightmare for this). Most apps are pretty short, and even gimmicky videos (e.g. on VRSE) lose their novelty after a while. I was constantly taking the phone out to try new things.    

From the things I've tried so far, I loved the Cedar Point and Blockbuster rollercoasters, Titans of Space was pretty cool too. I'm waiting on a controller so I can get stuck into games. 

**EDIT - since using more, I've discovered a fatal flaw of this device for me.** I have a brow which is just above my eyes (I'm not being funny, but it really is *just* above my eyes). When pushing my face into this thing, it really hurts on my brow. I thought it was the plastic ridge on the top of the device, which I could perhaps mod in some way. But its actually the 5mm or so ridge around the lenses. Because they're adjustable, the adjustable bit sits around the lens - but means the overall diameter is much bigger than the actual lens itself. This is really annoying. I've looked at pics of the Z4 and see there isn't much beyond the width of the lens. So I'm hoping the Z4 will be much more comfortable. To fit under my brow, I was moving the lenses too low on the LeNest which was making the vision blurry (you have to look dead center through the lenses for a clear image).    </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Surround sound for cinema vr apps </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-28 16:49:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hi, I'm fairly new to VR (heck, waiting on my first headset). I'm mostly excited for the VR cinema experience - I can't wait.   

One thing that I'm unsure of is the sound. I'm using a LG G4 - I'm not too experienced or knowledgeable about sound quality on these things. Should I re-acquire my film files in stereo sound because 5.1 is a waste of space? Or is there a way to make the best use of surround sound?  

Thanks </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> A couple of issues I have with Short Circuit 2 (1988) </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-18 10:25:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> #1: Johnny 5, with Michael McKeen on his back, somehow descends down a sewer manhole. There is no explanation of this, how his big tank style feet are able to use a ladder or even slowly descend into a hole. He then ascends repeatedly at various other manhole covers to keep tabs on the car he is chasing. The implication is that he is quickly rolling down sewers to get around NYC, but there is no shit anywhere on his wheel things, not a single fleck on either of them. The real thing about this whole sewer business that confuses me is that he's able to lift an *entire car, with three men inside,* from a manhole. I have no idea what he's standing on, or how he's able to do that, or how he's able to spin the car around like he does.   

#2: At the end, Johnny 5 swings across a river, to grab a fat man on a moving speedboat. The combined weight of a very heavy robot, and a fat man, are held by a *rubber sucker stuck to a rusty crane hook*, that Johnny 5 shot out from about 50m away.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> ELI5: Why haven't spider's webs evolved to smell like dog shit, to attract more flies? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-14 19:03:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> ELI5: Why isn't the supermassive blackhole at the center of the milky way gradually sucking everything up and becoming bigger? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-18 18:43:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm not sure why the orbits of the closest stars aren't being sucked in, making the mass bigger, then sucking in the next nearest stars, and so on. Is it because time slows right down for those stars? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Bizarrely, The Revenant reminded me of Gravity </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-07 12:50:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> SPOILERS FOLLOW 
SO IF YOU HAVEN'T SEEN THE REVENANT 
THEN STOP READING. 
======================================================


Even though their contexts couldn't be further apart. Here's what the films share in common (mainly structural):  

An initial scene to introduce the characters and establish the context.  

We'll be shown lots of long takes throughout with impressive choreography/design/VFX to orient us to the context. 

A pivot point (impressive VFX, talking point) which leads the protagonist to be cut off, and to all intents and purposes "left for dead".

Person they were with dies soon after.  

Protagonist then overcomes a number of obstacles to survive. Each one slightly different, taking them closer to the hope of their goal.  

Protagonist faces death but chooses to fight in, because of thoughts of their child.  

Protagonist sees a vision of the person who died earlier, which inspires more drive. 

Protagonist ends up in water, eventually reaches their goal, survives. 

Ends with a kind of "what now" moment, leaving the audience to contemplate their own journey in life.  
 

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Movie references </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-04 11:43:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Three I noticed -   

The obvious Fight Club reference relating to the imaged figure, and destruction of banking infrastructure with a piano version of Where Is My Mind (ep9).   

Some very Mica-Levi sounding music (Under The Skin) on ep10, also with the close up of the camera lens like Under The Skin. Camera lens also shot like HAL from 2001.   

More Kubrick influences - the classical pieces from Barry Lyndon, Eyes Wide Shut, and symmetrical compositions </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Review of a stage hypnosis show, wasn't great </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-11-30 13:57:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I went to stage hypnosis show this weekend. The hypnotist is very renowned, but his performance was pretty bad. I thought I'd write about it so others could learn from it. Here are the main things:  

- He didn't project belief that he could/would hypnotise anyone. The audience was fairly small, and it seemed to really knock his confidence (despite being one of the most authored/reputable hypnotists). This negative suggestion of the evening probably not going to go well really didn't help.   

- Very negative rapport. Most of the bad jokes were aimed at audience members. It didn't help with trust, rapport or prestige.   

- The suggestibility tests were delivered poorly - no persuasive, commanding voice or expectancy, just complacency.  

- Despite not responding great to the tests, I volunteered to go on stage. Surprisingly, we were given a progressive relaxation induction, which bugged me because there was too much time/opportunity for my own thoughts/awareness to counteract the response.  

- Went straight from "assumed" hypnosis into giving post-hypnotic commands to sleep, and trying to elicit phenomena (laughing at a funny film). I found it hugely awkward and uncomfortable.   

- When he said sleep, I closed my eyes and bowed my head, but only to save him from being embarrassed/being awkward/evoking some kind of mocking response from him (I didn't particularly trust him). I still lifted the "heavy" object though and didn't laugh at the imagined comedy film, because I really didn't want to play along to that extent.   

- The only person on stage (out of three) who responded was a previous trainee of the hypnotist, who was also a friend. Her reaction was very overblown and sycophantic, didn't have any of the naturalism/genuineness that I have seen in real hypnotic subjects before.  

- Because I wasn't responding well, I was told I wasn't very good at imagining, which really bugged me and dissuaded me from playing along from that point on. I'm very good at imagining, I was just too aware of all the negative suggestions and implications this guy was offering.   

- Before the hypnosis bit, he did some really lame mentalism tricks to "prove" various psychological things (lie detection, by pretending to read body language in guessing a card he'd forced to someone, so lame, and ideo-motor movements with another forced choice trick, again very lame). I was on stage at this bit too and had to pretend to be impressed by his supposed lie-detection/body reading/ideo-motor sensitivity when it was clearly all bullshit. This bugged me because actual hypnosis is fascinating enough with its implications that you shouldn't need to resort to lame nonsense to trick the audience.  

- Afterwards he tried to console the audience by framing the evening as "just entertainment" and that if we had a few laughs that was good enough. I found that pretty lame, and I expected far more from it.  

- I came away from the evening believing that the hypnotist (who again, is very renowned/published/known) didn't really understand about hypnosis or feel particularly confident about using it, didn't know how to relate to an audience, and didn't know enough about psychology to deliver something genuinely interesting rather than pseudo-tripe.  

- I kept quiet about my (extensive) knowledge/experience of hypnosis. In the bar afterwards, I listened to a fair few excruciatingly dull/egotistic anecdotes/claims of some hypnotherapists/hypnotists in the audience. I came to think that despite it being a fascinating subject, most self-proclaimed hypnotists are in desperate need of approval and prone to massive egos. It was oddly disturbing, and made me feel awkward/embarrassed about how the hypnosis industry must look to outsiders (tacky, egotistical, self-obsessed). 

Am open to questions if you have any.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> My girlfriend made this for me, its burned. Isn't it awesome? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-10-16 12:53:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Regression (2015) with Ethan Hawke   Emma Watson is shockingly bad </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-10-10 13:51:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I saw **Regression** last night which for some reason isn't released in the US until next February. 

Its one of those films that ends with a complete anti-climax, where the whole story and point of the film cancels itself out in a moment of complete stupidity. I want to explain the basic story structure, because its *so* shockingly bad and stupid, so mild spoilers follow. 

Ethan Hawke (playing his usual character) is a cop investigating a girl (Watson, pretty good performance) who claims to have been abused by her dad as part of some weird ritual, who accepts it but can't remember doing it. He's balding, so you know, he must be a bad guy. 

Hawke gets a lame, generic psychologist (a complete waste of David Thewlis) to do a regression on the dad, with the worse example of hypnosis/regression you'll ever see in a film. The dad then "remembers" a bunch of other stuff including a cop. Watson has seen the cop before too, so points him out among some photos. So Hawke promptly arrests the cop because he has no actual understanding of what police-work involves or what evidence is. 

They then do a regression on the dad's other son, and he comes up with a bunch of other stuff. Hawke talks to a few other people, and gets nowhere fast. 

The bulk of the film is then Hawke getting paranoid, and having bad dreams, which are just an excuse to have the films ONLY scare scenes. Literally all just dreams, how lame is that? They're cheap and unscary too. He dreams about some scary lady who he later learns he saw on an advertising billboard. 

Which leads to the climax of the film, because only then does he realise that suggestion is a thing, that people can be influenced by what they see, and that memory is subjective. FUCK KNOWS why it took him this long to realise. He goes back to Emma Watson, and tells her a bunch of stuff that someone else said happened to her. She agrees with it all, and cries. He's been reading from his notepad - which he throws down and * gasp * its blank! He was just making it up! Which means *she* was just making it up! He then suggests that yes, evil *does* exist, implying that its her. Because you know, telling lies is evil. 

**So the basic story is *a girl makes up a rape tale, then milks it for a while, until a cop calls her out on it*.** In the meantime, because he's such a shitty, shitty cop who can't tell the difference between rumor and actual fact, he gets all paranoid and has bad dreams about 80's special-effects.

The film then has a horrible title-card saying how no satanic ritual cases were ever proved, and how regression was discredited. 

*What?* 

Its like saying "body language was never used to prove someone is guilty, so it was discredited". Its the most obvious, pointless conclusion! You've literally just shown me a film about how rumor, hearsay and biased memory aren't FACTS, and made out like its some big revelation. 

But there are three things which are worse than that. 

Firstly, it doesn't define regression. Its essentially just "remembering" something that was previously difficult to remember (e.g. because of an emotional barrier of some kind). So making a film to attack the idea of regression per se, is just flimsy and stupid. 

Second is that regression can be useful, in some contexts, e.g. unlocking repressed memories etc. Of course it shouldn't be used in court, or as evidence, but that doesn't mean it can't still be useful. In the same way Cal Lightman uses body language in Lie To Me for example, it can point to other things that *may* have more evidence. People *have* for example uncovered repressed memories that had details later corroborated by evidence. 

Thirdly, because something like regression doesn't necessarily prove something happened, it doesn't prove it didn't happen either. The film completely ignores this idea, suggesting that because none of the reports of ritualistic abuse were ever proved, they therefore didn't happen - they must have been the product of rumor and suggestibility. *What the fuck?* 

**TL,DR: Its misjudged, imbalanced, stupid and not scary.** 

 
   



 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> My hamster is over 3 and a half years old - is this normal? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-09-28 17:39:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> My hamster was a rescue hamster (found in a derelict flat), which my mom acquired and I volunteered to look after. I had no idea how old he was when I got him, but I expected him to last a few months perhaps. This was over three and a half years ago. Whenever I kept hamsters as a kid, they seemed to average about two years.   

Is this normal? He's a white hamster, black eyes, used to have light brown bits but they faded away and now he's pretty much white.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What are some good non-Bond spy movies? (With some good sneaking around / spycraft) </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-29 13:52:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It seems like an under-utilized genre, particularly the more action based spy film, which Bond is probably partly to blame for (because it would suffer from obvious comparisons). 

I'm looking for some good sneaking around style genuine spy movies. 

Some favourites are:
**Spy Game** (some good sneaking around / action)
**Breach** (some good sneaking around)

Tinker Tailor is great, but there's not much sneaking around or spying. 

What else is there? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What are some good films where a man slowly gets drawn into a dark mystery? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-12 10:15:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Films like Ex Machina, Cold in July, Eyes Wide Shut. 

The structure is basically where things start out as normal, then a man gets drawn into some kind of intriguing mystery. It could be through invitation, noticing something and acting on it, some pivotal event. 

I just enjoy watching these kinds of films where its like you go on an adventure with the protagonist. 

Films like Blue Ruin or cop films wouldn't count for example, because the film already takes place in the context of the story that unfolds. I want examples where the beginning is largely unrelated to what follows.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Kinked exhaust - could this have have harmed the engine? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-08 12:08:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Ford Fiesta 2014

I recently bought this car, one year old. There was a rattle on the bottom. I discovered a loose heat-shield. 

This led to a further discovery that the exhaust was dented. 

Pics - http://imgur.com/a/wR7Uk

My question is - could the inability for emissions to fully escape cause harm to the engine? Its done 9000 miles, and its possible that the dent has been there from the beginning (if a transporter for eg). 

Thank you!

PS the garage is aware of it and will rectify, my question is more about any other long term consequences to the engine.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> TIL Interstella was shot at 60 Zimmerframes per second because everyone aged so much </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-01 19:01:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Friend left some science humour on my fridge </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-19 20:02:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Name some good movies about a central non-romantic relationship? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-08 13:57:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I realised that I always find these films compelling to watch, splendid metaphors as they are for relationships in general with all their complex dynamics, transferences and projections. 

Examples of good ones: Whiplash, Roger Dodger, Frost/Nixon, Silence of the Lambs, Three Colours: Red, Good Will Hunting. 

Edit: (added) Fight Club, Shawshank, Rush, The Prestige, Sleuth, Moon, Two Faces of January, In Bruges

I wouldnt really include films like Lethal Weapon, Kiss Kiss Bang Bang, Crimson Tide, Usual Suspects (for the Chazz/Spacey dynamic) as the relationships in those movies arguably don't really form the focus of the films compellingness.

Can you think of any more?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> I think "It Follows" will become a cult horror film </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-17 13:34:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I saw this intriguing little horror movie last night. Its the latest in the wave of 80s inspired movies (Drive, Cold In July, The Guest, The Way Way Back) complete with a John Carpenter style synth soundtrack.  

The story is about a curse whereby a person is followed continuously by a murderous walking ghost (which can look like anyone) until they're dead - *unless* the person sleeps with someone else, in which case they pass the curse on.  If that person gets killed though, the follower goes back to the previous person. It basically channels that relentless menace of the Terminator, mixed with that creepy old man in the black hat from that Poltergeist sequel. 

Some of the scenes genuinely scared the hell out of me, perfectly capturing that eerie what-the-fuckness that you crave from a decent horror (even more so than The Babadook managed last year).   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> How could a major film like Taken 3 have such poor editing? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-28 12:13:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Anyone who has seen Taken 3 will surely notice how awful the editing is. Shots sometimes last only a few frames, and a simple shot of Neeson jumping over a fence has about 30 shaky cuts from all angles. Every single action scene is shot and edited so poorly that you have absolutely no idea of space or motion. 

Then there are strange moments like when twice, a car explodes with Neeson in it, then moments later he is somewhere else. 

My perception is that the film industry is highly competitive, with technical roles hugely sought after by highly talented and dedicated people. Taken 3 is honestly worse than The Room in the editing stakes - its worse than a student project. Its *terrible*. I just don't understand how something like that could happen? How could its rough cuts make it through production screenings?   

I've honestly never been so confused by the poor quality of a major release (I'm not even talking about the writing, cinematography or directing here).  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Old school John Carpenter fans - this new album of his synth work is excellent. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-23 11:28:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Edge of Tomorrow surely deserved a Film Editing nom, especially over American Sniper </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-15 18:16:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah its science fiction which the snobby voters hate, but come on, the editing in Edge of Tomorrow was outstanding. The time jumping, action scenes, pacing, it was terrific. Not a single dull moment. What the hell was so remarkable about American Sniper's editing? It was pedestrian as it gets.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [TOMT][FILM] Old suspense movie that starts with someone hanging from a tree </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-06 10:43:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> About 25 years ago I sat with my parents to watch a film on tv, that film was cancelled and in its place was some other film. We sat and watched it anyway, and it turned out to be really suspenseful and memorable. I just can't remember what it was called, and trying to track it down is proving really difficult. 

Here's what I can remember: the opening scenes show someone's feet hanging from a tree. Its eerie and mysterious. A story develops that I think takes place in an empty school over summer. I think there are only a fee people involved, but it ends with some threatening character chasing another through the school - the chasee hiding in various places. I found it pretty scary. Somehow it ends with the surviving character (I think) hanging himself or herself from a tree near the building, and we return again to the opening scene. 

I would love it if someone could recognise this movie! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> I had a thought about the nature of time and would like some feedback </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-11-19 13:44:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Motif of Hands used in TITANIC (1997) </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-11-13 15:37:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What are your thoughts on cinema audiences? Better quiet, busy or not at all? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-11-08 21:01:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Almost every film recently has had noisy idiots who either underestimate how far their voices/whispers travel (quieter screenings), don't even notice they're vocally responding to things on screen (any kind of screening), or are just flat out rude. I hate it when someone assumes everyone wants to hear their wisecrack, as if the film experience will be better with their commentary.  

Then there are the people who laugh at anything they perceive as comedy, even if contextually its only supposed to convey a character's nervousness or something. Something is meant as dark sarcasm, and an idiot guffaws to let everyone else around know they got the joke. 

Then there are idiots who go on their phones, and you can see the bright screens popping up a few rows in front whilst they update FB about whats happening in the movie. 

I fucking *hate* the risk of morons being at the cinema. They distract and fuck up my first time viewing of what could be an lifetime favourite or important movie.

What's your experience like, do you ever have to tell people to shut up?    </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Ripley was the original Bad Luck Brian </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-11-02 12:20:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> How does the xenomorph in Alien (1979) grow so big in an hour? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-11-02 11:48:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> After the chestburster runs off, its not long until the crew reconvene to go looking for it. I'm guessing its about 45 minutes, maybe less, that Brett goes looking for the cat. By then, the chestburster is bigger than a man, fully developed, fully coordinated. There's no inbetween. How is this possible? Further, how the hell did he make enough alien-resin stuff to paste a whole couple of walls in the directors cut, in such a short space of time? As far as I can tell, there's only an hour or so between the chestburster scene and Ripley discovering it. Its not like they ever say "ok, enough hunting, I'm going to take a bath and read a book, let's carry on tomorrow".  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> British retail </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-10-31 11:59:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Something missing a bit from the game (spoilers) </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-10-27 10:15:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> When Ricado(?) had the facehugger on his face, I was fully expecting him to show up later in the game, coughing etc, so we could see a chestburster. Then it dawned on me that whilst they've crammed in a lot of the alien lore, we don't actually get to see the full life-cycle. A really fun thing would have been if it all began with an egg in the part of the ship that Amanda arrives at, then a facehugger on a crewmember, then seeing the alien tiny - then as the game progresses, it gets bigger and bigger until the full size monster that takes up the rest of the game. Maybe it would have been a little too close to Alien that way, but that wouldn't have necessarily been a bad thing taking into account all the other similarities? The alien as it was felt a bit like a secondary thing in the game, after the relentless and plentiful androids (also that it didn't have a satisfying death).  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> I find the loading screen tips really annoying </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-10-14 10:55:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I wish they hadn't followed this trend - I feel that they remove you from the atmosphere by reminding you "hey, its a game that people have made who have built all these little mechanics in, and now they're trying to teach you about them".  

Sometimes the tips refer to androids, other times synthetics, they give many tips about the alien before you even see it which ruins the suspense and surprise, they often contradict ("running is a last resort / run whenever you can"), and they ruin the sense of discovery of things (why tell you that people might be hostile or friendly? surely its more fun to discover that yourself).  

I'd have personally preferred just seeing the ominous fuzzy vhs shots of the ship with the wind sounds, it works perfectly as a primer for the atmosphere that follows.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> A:I reminds me a little of D/Generation, anyone remember this awesome old game? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-10-13 12:22:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> I want to enjoy the scares of Alien Isolation </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-10-11 17:07:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Roger Dodger (2002) is like a prequel to The Social Network </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-09-27 14:33:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [Roger Dodger (2002)](http://www.imdb.com/title/tt0299117/) is about a washed-up player (Campbell Scott on top form) showing his younger 16 yr old nephew how to flirt and score with women. Its witty, subtle, understated and great fun to watch.  

Jesse Eisenberg plays the nephew - who looks and sounds exactly like his performance of Zuckerberg a few years later in The Social Network. He even wears a blue hoodie over a grey t-shirt. 

[Jesse Eisenberg in Roger Dodger](http://i1.cdnds.net/14/05/618x430/movies-roger-dodger-jesse-eisenberg.jpg)  

[Jesse Eisenberg in Social Network](http://images4.fanpop.com/image/photos/20500000/Jesse-Eisenberg-The-Social-Network-jesse-eisenberg-20554687-1238-800.jpg)

In Roger Dodger, his character wants to go into computer programming, is a virgin, and is very socially awkward with girls.  

It leads perfectly to his performance in Social Network. 

...all this obviously ignores Social Network being based on a true story.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [TOMT][WEBPAGE] Trying to find the page of Arnie going "gawaahahahahaa" </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-05-30 10:07:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Its a full frame webpage showing a short loop of the bit in Last Action Hero where Arnie is doing that "gahahahaha" weird shouty/peril shriek thing he does. It was hilarious but I can't find it. Can you help?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> I'm having trouble understanding the logic of Moonraker (1979) </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-04-06 20:52:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Mainly, the assassination attempts on Bond's life are ridiculously elaborate, and ALL FAIL:

Jaws pushes Bond out of a plane. 

Centrifuge - Bond is sped up to 12G until he miraculously fires a wrist-dart into the right control panel to disable it. 

Man up tree clumsily aiming at Bond. Could have just walked nearby then shot him?

"Corpse" in a funeral boat in Venice opens the coffin and throws knives - gets stabbed by Bond. Ridiculously elaborate, could have just stabbed him off the boat. 

Crappy Korean martial arts guy follows Bond to Venice and tries to bust him up in a museum, fails miserably. 

Jaws follows Bond to Rio, and plots with a bald man to tamper with his cable car. He then jumps onto his cable car to "do him in". Pretty damn risky if you ask me. Fails.

Jaws et al chase Bond in boats down an Amazonian river. Fails, falls down huge waterfall (but manages to get to the base in a few minutes intact whilst Bond has to glide for a while). 

Drax has Bond wrestle with some beastly Amazonian water snake under water (Bond happened to be standing on the wrong rock, which was designed to tip into the water, clumsy Bond. Bond stabs snake with poison pen he stole from CIA girl, that didn't fall out of his loose shirt pocket whilst gliding or struggling underwater). 

Drax puts Bond and girl into a meeting room which also doubles up as a fire chamber for a rocket launch. Pretty dangerous meeting room, but at least it has a large escapable air vent. 

Drax later attempts to put Bond and girl into airlock on the space-station, but a fight happens instead. 

When a gun is *finally put to Bond's head*, he manages to switch off the gravity inside the station and gets away. 



I'm also slightly confused by how Drax managed to build a huge multiple spaceshuttle launching space-facility inside a rock in the Amazon jungle, as well as a huge centrifugal space-station above the earth. WITHOUT ANYONE KNOWING.  








 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Why didn't Predator kill the cabinet minister's crew? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-03-16 16:45:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So Predator killed Jim Hopper, the first guy that went in to do the mission. Then it skinned the first rescue team. So it was pretty active in that area, for a decent while. So why did it not touch the little bad-guy village, despite them executing people and sitting around with weapons? It would have been more appropriate if by the time Dutch and co reached them, they were all already slaughtered and/or missing (but then the film would be one nice action scene less). 
 
Edit: I just gotta say thanks for the awesome replies, I genuinely laughed wholeheartedly and even spat tea out reading some of these comments. It made my day.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> 15 years ago today, Stanley Kubrick was having the last full day of his life. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-03-06 14:02:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Was Upstream Color too intelligent for the Oscars? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-03-04 16:53:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I thought Upstream Color was an incredible achievement - in writing, direction, cinematography, editing, acting and even the soundtrack is amazing (much better than Gravity's imo).

The story itself was fascinating - exploring themes such as slavery, control, life-cycles, connection, love, loss, meaning, voyeurism, memory and sensory perception.   

Really, its an incredible movie, and an outstanding cinematic achievement. 

I have no idea why it wasn't nominated for anything. People like Shane Carruth should surely be commended for their originality and daring, not snubbed. 

I just have a feeling that it went way over the academy's heads. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> How many hours have you been playing GTA:O? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-02-18 17:51:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I checked out my stats and I'm up to 90 hours, I only got the game and a PS3 mid December. As a newbie gamer this is pretty shocking to me, its the equivalent of watching 50 movies. How many hours have you been playing? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Online - am I missing something? Can't seem to cross the tipping point </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-12-17 13:13:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Been playing for only a few days, and saved up $10k, but have no real idea what to do. I do missions, try to sell cars to Simeon, rob stores to make money. But there are always lots of other players with huge guns, firing rockets from their cars and blowing me up all the time. Sometimes I seem to get chased and bullied because its obvious I'm a newbie. I accidentally found a players apartment who let me in, who had a garage filled with chrome supercars. How on earth do people get to this level? Do you just have to play for thousands of hours, saving up cash gradually, or are there quicker ways to do it? Sorry for the stupid newbie question.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Where you sit in the cinema, and when, are big variables on the experience of a film - do you factor this in? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-11-27 14:29:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Two variables I've noticed that make a massive difference on the experience of a film (found through watching some films 2 or 3 times at the cinema):  

- **How far you sit from the screen** - the screen can be HUGE sat close, or tiny from the back. Huge difference in how engaged and immersed you'll be in the film! With something like **Gravity** its best to sit close (where 3D is also enhanced due to wider parallax), whilst something like **Captain Phillips** (or shaky-cam movies) is best to sit further back to absorb the image easier. I honestly think that people who watched Gravity from the back of the theater would have had a completely different experience to those sat closer to the front. But, if the screen doesn't have tiered seating, then sitting too close can also distort the image (keystone effect, which also happens if you sit on the very edge) which harms the ability to engage with the film.  

- **Packed screening or just a few people**: makes a huge difference on atmosphere and distraction levels. Strangely, I've found noise levels to be much worse in a fewer-populated screening than when its packed. I think people underestimate how far their voices/whispers travel when there are few people, so they're more likely to talk. Whilst in a packed screen, there is more a group pressure to be quiet, and also more people around to tell people to shut up. I've found packed (e.g. opening weekends) to be quieter than smaller screenings a few weeks later. I also found that bigger audiences gives a much better atmosphere, like its more of a shared experience. All the people I know who loved **The Worlds End** (myself included) watched it in busy screens, the people I know who didn't think much of it watched it in quiet screens. 

I know this probably seems obvious, but maybe not for all. I do think these variables can affect the experience of a film so much, I'm surprised they're not taken into account more when people are discussing differences in perception of recent movies.   

**Are you fussy where you sit in the cinema or when you go?** </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Something strange about the Indiana Jones films </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-11-26 10:56:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Frequently, when Indy is in some secret place, the way out is far, far simpler than the way in.  

- Raiders: After all the effort it takes to get into the chamber of the idol, the way out is a big corridor with a large exit next to some trees where Belloq and the natives are waiting. If the exit was so obvious, why hadn't anyone *ever* gone in there, and already tripped the big ball?  

- Raiders: Who knew, that next to a small airfield, if a large block was pulled out from a wall, behind it would be the Ark of the Covenant? Again, great pains to find the secret chamber, has to prize open a "lid" to the place, but then is able to push a brick out to easily get out.   

- Last Crusade: Secret tomb is hidden under a converted church/library. Right next to the tomb, with barely any exploration at all, Indy says "I've found a way" then they pop up out of an easily removable *manhole cover* in the middle of a outdoor square. So no one has been down that easily removable manhole cover, where they would have quickly discovered the not-very-well-hidden tomb.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Just did a sketching, can you recognize the actor? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-11-18 11:29:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The Hunt [2012] a compelling emotional drama with Mads Mikkelsen </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-11-05 12:26:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> An incredibly moving and powerful film. A simple little moment of dishonesty unravels and amplifies into something life-destroying with layers upon layers of human irrationality, fear and cognitive bias. Really psychological and compelling, very subtle and excellent acting from everyone.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The Harrison Treadmill scene with a laughter track (LOLZ) </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-09-13 12:38:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Just saw an incredibly tense, exciting   thrilling film that only got 9% on RT. WTF? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-09-08 20:55:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Cute spider I just found in my bath </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-09-05 00:29:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Just finished Ender's Game: is it about capitalism? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-08-30 11:23:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Is there a better movie than 12 Angry Men about human nature? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-08-21 11:01:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I saw 12 Angry Men again last night and really enjoyed it, each time I notice more nuances and observations about human nature. It seems to effortlessly portray many modes of influence, conformity, prejudice, socialisation, anxiety, aging, various biases, hypocrisy, influence of upbringing, ignorance, emotional repression, leadership, the class system. Its like a masterclass in the human condition. I can't think of another film that achieves this as well as 12 Angry Men, but would love to hear any recommendations.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What film am I thinking of? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-08-18 13:11:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Some frames you may have missed from Event Horizon </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-08-12 11:05:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Very recent Corgi pups (album) </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-08-11 20:36:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> A few frames you may have missed from Event Horizon </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-08-11 13:04:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Who's going to the London Scala show? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-08-09 16:40:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The conditions for the [tickets](http://tour.nin.com/ticket-info-london) seems pretty strict - I daren't buy tickets for friends in case they can't make it (they can't be sold on).  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> A few questions about Season 8 </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-08-06 10:08:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Where is Harry? As a visual metophor of Dexter's conscience it was a really effective way of allowing his reflective thoughts and themes to layer out the episodes. I'm not sure why they got rid of that. He'd have surely talked Dexter out of his ludicrous, out of character decision to not kill Zack - which I can't accept no matter how hard I try. Based on all that has happened to him (his various doomed liaisons with *anyone*, especially after letting Hannah go) it seems like a huge insult to the audience, as well as all his past kills, to not have him follow through. All because Vogel suggested it? Again, after all he's been through, this makes his character dorkier than ever and I'm sure most of the audience facepalmed at that moment.     

The role of Vogel - what is this all about? First she's helping Miami Met catch a killer. This is then dropped and she becomes a target instead. Then she turns out to be Dex's kind-of surrogate mother. Then she blackmails Dex into finding her killer, which he does. Then Zack's dad *randomly calls her up to talk to his son because he thinks his son might be a psychopath?* I honestly can't think of a more forced plot contrivance ever in Dexter! Even Dex doesn't seem phased by the sheer coincidence of it.  

I feel like this season has already almost "reset" after six pointless episodes - there's no accumulative build up of tension at all. I feel pretty angry at the writers - fans deserve better.  
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> William   Kate's son - pretty successful I'd say </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-07-22 22:31:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Something I'm confused about with Superman IV </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-07-22 12:06:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> In Superman IV, Nuclear Man and Superman are fighting in outer space. Nuclear Man blows onto Superman, and suddenly Superman is encapsulated in a huge ice cube. Where would the water come from to create such a huge ice cube around Superman?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Do you think modern movies are making less use of our imaginations? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-07-18 22:30:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Some of my favourite moments from films are where my own imagination becomes the stimuli for the incredible excitement and suspense that the unconscious mind can generate. Examples (for me):

- the vibrations of the T-Rex in Jurassic Park, the water in the cup
- The AT-ATs in Empire Strikes Back, creeping over the horizon through binoculars
- Newt and Ripley in Aliens waking in a locked room with overturned Facehugger canisters
- Finding the first shed skin of the xenomorph in Alien
- Pans Labyrinth where the girl sees the horrific drawings of kids being slaughtered by the monster, then it suddenly wakes at the table 

Recently having seen Star Trek Into Darkness, Man of Steel, World War Z and Pacific Rim at cinemas, it dawned on me that I can't think of a single memorable moment in any of them like these where my imagination was stimulated in interesting ways. I don't think I got any of that mind-magic because everything was up there on the screen. 

Its like all the effects and CGI are replacing the need for an imagination. I'm not saying I'm right, its just a subjective observation, so wondered what you guys thought (and whether I missed something).  

Also - feel free to add your own favourite imagination-moments in movies! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> I took this image of the moon with a handheld camera </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-07-18 18:12:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Dad found this weird slug at the bottom of his tea </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-05-22 13:36:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
