<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject6842</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Beer makes humans more attractive to malarial mosquitoes </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2010-03-04 17:33:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2010-03-02 13:18:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The thing is, there are *in vitro* studies that only work as proof-of-concept showing that there are positive as well as negative effects of THC (which is almost always the only substance studied) on neurons. 
In a petri dish, THC can (in pretty high concentrations) kill hippocampal neurons or in another study alleviate effects of excitotoxicity on the same neurons.

Anyway, as far as I know, especially heavy smokers of cannabis are in danger of negative effects to the nervous system. [example](http://archpsyc.ama-assn.org/cgi/content/abstract/65/6/694)

BUT: There have only been very small (and again more or less *proof-of-concept*) studies. Therefore I wouldn' say there is a high degree of certainty in this matter, but there is just as little certainty in the notion that there are *no* effects. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Biggest Marathon, Half-Marathon Training Mistakes </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2010-03-01 14:53:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2010-02-26 16:25:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The consensus right now is that coffee in moderation does not act as a diuretic and dehydrate you. The water from coffee hydrates as much as liquids from other sources. [study](http://www.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/pubmed/16131696), [NYT article](http://www.nytimes.com/2008/03/04/health/nutrition/04real.html?_r=2) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2010-02-26 16:05:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's right that ARD/ZDF and the others produce mostly crap, but the BBC does the same. The thing in Germany is that the "good" (which, you know, is subjective) programs are mostly shown on those so called "third" channels like 3Sat, arte, Phoenix where people don't bother to look. So they are there, just not in a prominent position. 

Another thing: A lot of the money goes into sports events, Olympics, World Cups, Bundesliga... you name it, ARD/ZDF show it. That is expensive. And the reason for them to pay for these licenses is that the officials (including politicians who sometimes occupy seats in the supervisory boards) only have ratings in mind and therefore nowadays show sports events and make soap operas/game shows like everyone else.

Besides: We pay for 2 independent stations with many affiliates each. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2010-02-21 14:26:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The Federal Reserve doing something like [this.](http://articles.sfgate.com/2009-03-22/business/17214641_1_funds-rate-short-term-interest-rates-treasury)
But as I said I am not very familiar with the exact situation in the US. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2010-02-21 14:15:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> A very big chunk of the debt of most countries actually stays within its border. Investment firms such as mutual funds buy a lot. [Example: (PDF in German!)](http://www.bundesbank.de/download/volkswirtschaft/monatsberichte/2006/200604mb_bbk.pdf) About 60% of Germany's debt is owed to domestic creditors, and of those 2/3 are banks/investment firms and 1/3 non-banks like insurances, other companies or private individuals.) 

The situation is slightly different in the US where intra-/intergovernmental agencies like the Fed buy a pretty big chunk of government-issued bonds. [See here](http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/File:Holders_of_the_National_Debt_of_the_United_States.gif) for instance. I am not too familiar with that situation though. Overall about 25% of US governmental debt is in the hands of foreign creditors. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2010-02-16 18:58:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm not sure this is the reason but up until 1981 playing cards were subject to (relatively high) taxation in Germany. 

Also: Who would buy individual cards anyway? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2010-02-13 14:20:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> And [here](http://www.liveleak.com/view?i=a37_1265758326) is the video that .gif is from. Action starts at about 30 seconds. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2010-02-06 20:01:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Nelson Mandela's "Long Walk to Freedom" </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2010-02-06 02:04:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> As far as I know he dictated at least some of it to Rudolf He. However, relatively new research suggests that several drafts for 'Mein Kampf' have been written by Hitler himself. (I can only provide a [German source](http://www.augsburger-allgemeine.de/Home/Nachrichten/Bayern/Artikel,-Mein_Kampf_Hitler_Landsberg-_arid,1685379_regid,2_puid,2_pageid,4289.html) right now, though. It says that they tested the paper of some newly found drafts physically and compared handwritten corrections to other manuscripts - among other things) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2010-02-05 13:11:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Some info on that can be found [in this interview](http://stefanmey.wordpress.com/2010/01/04/leak-o-nomy-the-economy-of-wikileaks/).

*In mainstream media as well as in non-commercial media there are two important questions. What does it cost? And how is it financed? Would you please first describe the cost side *

By far the biggest cost is people. Thats also a cost that scales with operations. The more material we go through, the more the management and labour costs are. People need to write summaries of the material and see whether its true or not. In the moment everyone is paying himself, but that cant last forever.
[...]

*So at the moment the labour costs are still hypothetical, but the big costs that you really have to pay bills for are servers, office, etc.?*

On the bandwidth side, the backing is costly as well when we get big spikes. Then there are registrations, bureaucracy, dealing with bank accounts and this sort of stuff. Because we are not in one location, it doesnt make sense for us to have headquarters. People have their own offices across the world.

*What about cost for lawsuits?*

We dont have to pay for our lawyers time. Hundred of thousands or millions dollars  worth of lawyer time are being donated. But we still have to pay things like photocopying and court filing. And so far we have never lost a case, there were no penalties or compensations to pay. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> MPEG LA: H.264 for Internet video to be royalty free till 2016 </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2010-02-04 13:42:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2010-02-01 20:10:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm pretty sure "Discokugel" (or sometimes "Diskokugel") is a lot more common.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2010-01-24 00:20:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Actually, there is (or was) [cell coverage even at the summit](http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Mount_Everest#2008:_Summer_Olympic_torch_summit). The Chinese put it there for the Olympic Relay in 2008. I'm not sure if the cellular tower is still there, though. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Google patents MapReduce </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2010-01-20 14:46:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2009-12-31 15:59:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  The New Year's Eve blue moon will be visible in the **United States**, Canada, Europe, South America and Africa.

This may be the sentence he had in mind.
To sum up: *The blue moon will be visible in the USA, the eclipse won't.* </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2009-11-10 00:45:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Try the sugar-free Red Bull. That seems to work better for me, though still not as good as coffee. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Balance organs affect brain blood flow </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2009-09-23 13:56:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> E.U. Nations Fail to Agree on Bluefin Tuna Ban </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2009-09-22 18:44:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> EU frdert Projekte zur Totalberwachung der realen und virtuellen Rume </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2009-09-22 12:04:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2009-09-21 21:08:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> FC Hansa Rostock </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Black holes invading stars may provide an alternative explanation for gamma ray bursts </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2009-09-18 17:58:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Goalline referees to make debut in Europa League matches today </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2009-09-17 17:14:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2009-09-17 13:45:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Here in Germany UHT milk with a shelf life of several months has a market share of about 70%. [the best source I could find (German)](http://www.milchwirtschaft.de/aktuelles-und-termine/aktuelles/2009/01/05_stellenwert_milch.php) 

I don't think a lot of people drink this kind of milk directly, though, as it tastes horrible compared to the normal stuff. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2009-09-17 13:29:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Well, depends.. Pasteurizing milk at normal temperatures (below 90C) allows a refrigerated shelf life of some weeks at best. 
You'll need higher temperatures (above 140C for some seconds IIRC) to extend the shelf life to months. The milk is then called UHT-Milk ("*H-Milch* in Germany") and packaged in something similar to Tetra Paks.
Granted, this is some *kind* of pasteurization but the point stands: You'll need specific pasteurizing techniques to months of shelf life possible. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2009-09-14 23:17:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yes, that sucks. Anyway, [here](http://arxiv.org/abs/0808.2277) is the source. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2009-09-13 13:16:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Non-traditional preparation of kava products (pills, usage in alcoholic beverages etc.) is also associated with severe [liver damage](http://www.cdc.gov/mmwr/preview/mmwrhtml/mm5147a1.htm). </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2009-09-13 13:02:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Haber_process

The Haber process is important because ammonia is difficult to produce on an industrial scale, and the fertilizer generated from the ammonia is **responsible for sustaining one-third of the Earth's population**.

Alright, [Fritz Haber](http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Fritz_Haber) is also known as *father of chemical warfare* but still, without the Haber(-Bosch) process the green revolution wouldn't have been possible. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2009-09-11 13:47:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [This one](http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Dinosaur#Modern_definition "second paragraph") </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2009-09-01 13:28:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm no pilot but there are some points I'd like to mention:

The German press reports the same story, as far as I can see. Even the local public news station [MDR (German.)](http://www.mdr.de/thueringen/ost-thueringen/6649553.html)
The airfield is positioned between to major cities (Jena, Gera) and many small towns. I guess there would have been the danger of confusing the already confused pilot even more?

The next major airport is 55km (30 nm) away. I don't know if that would have been a good option, especially since we have no information on the fuel situation and such. Using a stand-by rescue helicopter as guidance doesn't look like that bad of an idea to me, though.

The absence of radio conversations isn't *that* suspicious, actually. Perhaps the police uses the recordings as evidence and won't release them to protect the person. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2009-09-01 12:51:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [Damn Interesting](http://www.damninteresting.com/the-unfortunate-sex-life-of-the-banana) had a, well, interesting article on that topic lately.

By the way: the navel orange is another example. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2009-08-31 18:02:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  He's simply misrepresenting the main arguments for organic and the position of the Soil Association which he attempts to smear with the label a "2bn industry".

He's simply pointing to a possible conflict of interest here. A significant part of the [Soil Association's funding](http://www.soilassociation.org/Aboutus/Funding/tabid/299/Default.aspx) comes from the industry producing organic food. He is *not* attacking all organic food but merely pointing out weaknesses in these particular arguments. It's Goldacres 'Bad Science' column after all.

 If he's lying, I'm sure it will only take a few days for someone with access to the preliminary reports to expose him. You should be aware that the production of peer-reviewed papers takes a long time - hence the need to wait until April for publishing.

I am aware of that process, but it's still a pretty irrelevant point in an argument. You'll need tangible evidence to prove any claim. Saying there's something on the way, doesn't prove anything. And seeing that you are eager to criticise certain assumptions in the FSA study, how can you be sure similar 'mistakes' have not been made in the upcoming one?

So, all pesticides (and antibiotics) are just fine for long-term human consumption? There's no chance of anything ever going wrong? Mmmkay.

That's the FSA's stance on pesticides (I did not read the word 'antibiotics there, did you?), not mine, so I'm not going to defend it. Anyway, *not an unacceptable risk to human health* and *no chance of anything ever going wrong* are pretty different. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2009-08-31 15:39:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yes. Read it. Ben Goldacre does not develop a case against organic food, he develops a case against the arguments of one big lobby organisation regarding a study about nutrional benefits of organic food.

Also, I do like organic food but this:
 There really are nutritional benefits, as research to be published next year will show

is not really convincing, is it? Let me read it, then I might actually believe it.

The FSA study referenced explicitly [excluded](http://www.food.gov.uk/news/newsarchive/2009/aug/letter) pesticides and looked only at nutritional value in comparison to non-organic food, by the way. 
Of course, you don't have to agree with the sentiment, that *"[...] the use of pesticides in either organic or conventional food production does not pose an unacceptable risk to human health [...]."* (source from above) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2009-08-26 16:36:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [RealClimate](http://www.realclimate.org/index.php/archives/2009/08/plimers-homework-assignment/) offers a bit of debunkery debunking.

fyi: The link above is not about the book per se but about questions Pilmer [asked](http://www.guardian.co.uk/environment/georgemonbiot/2009/aug/12/climate-change-climate-change-scepticism)
George Monbiot of the Guardian in response to criticisms of the climate change denial. It does say something about Pilmer's credibility, though. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2009-08-08 02:07:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Well, it's not an insecticide, it's an insect repellent and therefore mostly used directly on the human. This justifies further research, I think.

Additionally, even though some degree of "toxicity" (1 case of epilepsy in a 100 million persons using DEET; at least that's the kind I know of) may have been known for some time, why should that stop anyone from looking into the matter? Isn't it useful to know the *why* and *how* in order to prevent damage or make future insect repellents less toxic? In fact, that's what science is for. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2009-07-22 02:03:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Damn. That first pic is scary. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2009-07-21 13:44:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Mixing Red Bull and Wodka has been a trend here (in Germany) for some years, and I've done it on two or three occasions. Being drunk, hyperactive/hypertonic and sleepless is not the best combination and will bring you one of the worst hangovers ever. Also, it tastes awful.

On the health effects: Combining caffeine, taurine and a great deal of sugar can't be good for you and I think everyone knows that by now. It's almost inevitable that people who consume these drinks constantly will get problems sooner or later, but these are the same problems people who overconsume soda may get. Maybe the additional compounds will worsen that, maybe not. We'll have to wait for (long-term) studies to judge that. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2009-07-20 20:03:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You can often hear *'n* and *'ne*, though. Maybe that e is simply due to their way of speaking in general? Many people here (ok, I'm in Dresden right now, where some may take it to the extreme; I didn't notice that farther north, though) can't or won't end a word on "n" without appending a slight *e*-sound to it.

Also, "Mdchen" is a bad example, I think, as the word is simply a diminutive of "Magd" (old German for "maid") with words ending on *-chen* or *-lein* being grammatically neuter? There are no equivalents for boys in use, though (or are there? I can only think of "Brschchen".) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2009-07-19 21:57:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [Solyanka!](http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Soljanka) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2009-07-19 12:49:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You are right. In German it would be "geschrieben *von* author". </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2009-07-14 21:37:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You should look at [Ficly](http://ficly.com/), too. The stories are *very* short (1024 characters) and everyone is encouraged to write sequels or prequels for existing ones. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2009-07-13 20:46:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Are you suggesting there are Native Extradimensionans to be found? I like that. 

But why not discovery? It seems to me, that the word *discovery* is sufficient in the framework of the knowledge available to you/your peers. In this respect, Columbus "discovered" the New World, because he was the one who found it *for* the Europeans. They didn't know before, y'know? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2009-07-09 17:48:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Ah, now that I think about it, I believe it's the same here. When I got glasses I didn't have to pay.. but that was 10 years ago. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2009-07-09 17:42:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> We have both more or less. There are private insurers for those who have the money and there are compulsary health insurances with the latter being a lot more common. And they don't cover optical care fully either. (Examinations are mostly free, except for these 10 'Praxisgebhr' (practice charge)) E.g. if you need glasses you only have to pay for the frames.

It did get worse in the past years, though. You have to pay more for some things and won't get coverage for others, but I think it's still a lot better than what you hear about the US for example. I've not heard of people going bancrupt because of medical bills, anyway. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2009-07-09 16:12:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I've lost a lens once - because I opened one eye while diving..

Those lenses are mostly water and they sit on your eyes tightly enough not to be noticed. If they fit, you really don't have to worry about losing one (except maybe by scratching your eye very intensely). 

As for the price: I use lenses you can use for a month at a time (provided you take them out at (most) nights, of course) and pay about 50 (~70$, but I'm pretty sure the prices in the US are better) for 6 months. For me that's clearly worth it. The only problem one might have is putting them in and taking them out in the beginning, as your eyes are very sensible. You should really try it, most opticians let you have a test pair for free (at least here in Germany)

edit: I forgot to mention infection.. Well, normally you would take them out in the evening and put them in a solution that should keep this from happening. If you do that and keep them clean, you won't have problems. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2009-07-09 15:58:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Have you ever considered contact lenses? It's really great to be able to see clear without something sitting on your nose. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2009-07-07 12:12:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> \[NSFW\] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2009-07-06 02:17:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> They are *theoretical* insofar as their existence has been predicted theoretically/mathematically by Lagrange, at a time when there was no way of testing this in practice.

This mission does not have to test this, as there have been [spacecraft](http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Lagrange_point#Lagrangian_point_missions) put into orbit around Lagrange points already. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2009-07-06 02:11:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's in orbit around the Lagrange point (L2), though. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2009-07-05 21:51:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I think the problem with factory farming is that the animals don't get to eat what they are supposed to (cattle normally wouldn't eat corn) and may get sick, therefore needing antibiotics. These will be in the meat you eat.
They are farmed/selected to grow as fast as possible, making their meat less tasty (seriousy. try a *real* steak..) and so on..

Anyway, meat is awesome. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> US-Konsulat warnt vor Reisen nach Garmisch-Partenkirchen - wegen Kneipenschlgerei </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2009-07-05 16:15:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2009-07-02 02:37:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Be careful, July 4th isn't far away :) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2009-07-01 23:28:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Well, see for yourself:

"\[...\] She \[Jane Austen\] makes me detest all her people, without reserve. Is that her intention? It is not believable. Then is it her purpose to make the reader detest her people up to the middle of the book and like them in the rest of the chapters? That could be. That would be high art. It would be worth while, too. Some day I will examine the other end of her books and see." - [source](http://www.twainquotes.com/Austen_Jane.html)

(the third quote on that page is especially....interesting.) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2009-07-01 12:18:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> There probably is one, though. In mice and in rhesus monkeys, at least. There will not be clinical tests of this in humans, of course.
Additionally, the estimated LD50 (dose at which ~50% of patients die) for humans would be too much to be consumed realistically and at some point even absorption in the lung would not go further. You'd have to take THC intravenously to get that amount into your blood. Therefore there are no known cases of death from THC overdose. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2009-06-30 18:00:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If you aren't afraid to register, you can download it from NASA [here.](https://wist.echo.nasa.gov/~wist/api/imswelcome/) (click that **Enter WIST** link)

*edit*: You can get it [here](http://www.gdem.aster.ersdac.or.jp/index.jsp), too. Registration required + overloaded servers as well. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2009-06-30 00:47:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Air flow will only happen when there's a difference in air pressure between two places in or around the container. I don't think you'd have that in a fridge. 
There may be *some* flow, due to temperature discrepancies but these would happen regardless of the packaging.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2009-06-30 00:35:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yay for the sun's input. Justifying nonsensical emotion for over 15 minutes. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2009-06-29 19:41:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  Air Force tests Minuteman missile, fired from California coast to Pacific target

I don't think he'd be able to see that from San Antonio. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Site For Alcohol's Action In The Brain Discoverd </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2009-06-29 15:38:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2009-06-29 13:24:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I don't think that tactic will work, actually. Caffeine has to be metabolized and will only get flushed out when converted to some form of uric acid. By drinking a lot you will not accelerate that process substantially.
Maybe you've just developed some kind of habituation to caffeine limiting its impact on your body? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2009-06-29 02:50:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> My point is that everthing a human brain conceives of is in a sense conceived of by nature (thus the word 'subset') because the brain is nature's achievement.

What I mean is that nature not only had a head start but it started the head thing as well ;) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2009-06-28 22:44:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Our imagination is just a subset of nature's. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2009-06-26 03:00:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Well, so does Megan Fox.. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2009-06-26 02:53:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Nein.

edit: That's because the word seems to be pretty new and slang-y. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2009-06-24 13:40:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [This site](http://www.exrx.net/Beginning.html) should help you get started.

Please don't forget to exercise your legs. Doing squats, deadlifts (you should have someone with experience with you at first, getting the technique right is hugely important here) and similar stuff. Those are essential exercises for general body strength.

 I guess I'm afraid that I won't be able to jog long without huffing and puffing, or that if I go the gym

Simply start with intervals of running and walking and you'll see pretty rapid improvement of your endurance until you can leave out the walking-part altogether. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Tauss erklrt das Verhalten der SPD zur Internetsperre </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2009-06-24 02:56:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2009-06-16 03:03:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Also, Handy is not a brand/product name like Cola/Fn/Tempo/Tesa etc., but an entirely artificial construct.

I think the jury is still out on that one. No one really knows why the  word "Handy" prevailed. Still, there have been products called 'Handy' or 'Handie' in the past.

 Regardless of that, it's an adjective, not a verb.

I'm with you on that one. Let's just say I could use some sleep. 
Though it's never been a German verb either.. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2009-06-16 01:58:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Of course they don't know it *anymore*. It has never been a German verb.

There are many cases were brand or product names became synonymous with the general thing. Look at Coca-Cola or the Fn.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2009-06-13 20:06:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Like dsfox pointed out, this *ban* only concerns the states directly. The federal government is allowed to take on debt up to 0.35 % of the GDP. 
Granted, that might not be much, but there are loopholes: There is an explicit allowance for debt as part of counter-cyclic fiscal policy and natural desasters. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2009-06-11 15:11:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The term 'Republican' shall not include brains. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2009-06-01 02:20:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [Wikipedia](http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Miranda_rights) should help </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2009-05-20 14:21:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Rather about people who have dreams and like being irrational at times. That does not make them dumb and/or bad in maths. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2009-05-10 19:28:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That may have been the case from 1990 to 2008, but it's not anymore. Right now unemployment (in part due to government policies like "reduced working hours"(Kurzarbeit)).

Figures from January show a different picture:

The figures for January 2009 that are already available for the two countries show that, following equal unemployment rates in December 2008, Germany had a lower unemployment rate (7.3%) than the USA for the first time in 16 years. The US rate in January was 7.6%. ([source](http://www.destatis.de/jetspeed/portal/cms/Sites/destatis/Internet/EN/Content/Publikationen/STATmagazin/LabourMarket/2009__03/2009__03Unemployment,templateId=renderPrint.psml)) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2009-05-02 22:33:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I don't think "solving problems" is the point. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2009-02-17 05:08:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Except they [don't](http://www.faculty.ucr.edu/~eschwitz/SchwitzPapers/DreamChina051031.htm) say that.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2009-02-15 02:46:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> (Open) Transport Tycoon Deluxe.

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2009-02-01 01:36:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This "alternative course selected by the manufacturer" meant letting a bunch of journalists drive the car through the US. 
I've seen A3s with equivalent engines drive at 55mpg or more - on the Autobahn. Now try that with a Prius. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2009-01-26 16:47:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It is blocked because every video from BBC iPlayer is available only to people in the UK. The headline seems to imply that all this happened due to the content of said documentary.. which is wrong. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
