<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject3045</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-17 16:19:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Happy Feet is a great movie to watch when you're stoned. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-17 16:04:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Rush Hour is pretty fucking bad. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-14 18:44:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I don't like Star Wars fans. They're coarse, rough, irritating, and they get everywhere. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-14 06:05:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'll probably get downvoted into oblivion, but did anyone else think Shyamalan could have handled the childhood flashbacks scenes better? I understand Casey being molested is a part of her character and it's what saved her from the Beast, but that one flashback in particular was just too much for me. I didn't need to see a grown man strip naked in the woods and get on all fours like some greasy pedobear. That was just fucked up. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-27 06:28:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  He has no reason to leave. When I drop passengers off anywhere commercial I tend to stay.

It wasn't that the driver didn't leave, as much as it my suspicions that he was waiting outside because he was getting ready to call the police. I definitely think he would've had I stayed at the store any longer. He wasn't playing around, and was also on the phone with someone when my new driver came to pick me up. 

 Now approaching the other driver too is legitimate if a driver had concerns over a scam.

Of course it's legitimate, but outright telling the other driver that I plan to cancel and scam them, on the other hand, is not.
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> As a passenger, have you ever accidentally cancelled a ride during your trip? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-26 18:55:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It happened to me the other night. When I was on the way home after seeing the new Power Rangers, I was messing with the Lyft app and I accidentally cancelled. The driver thought I was trying to scam him. I tried explaining to him, but he didnt believe me at all. He dropped me off at a nearby store, and told me to get out. I thought he would leave afterwards, but he didnt. Now, this is when things started to get intense.

I requested another ride, and when a new driver showed up at the store, I noticed the other driver was still waiting outside. He ran up to the car window, and started trying to convince the new driver that I was scamming and planning to cancel. Ok, I don't mind the driver getting mad and dropping me off after I cancelled (even if I cancelled by accident), but he really should have left after dropping me off. At the very least, don't try convincing other drivers that I'm planning to scam. It seemed like he was one step away from calling the police. Oh well, at least I contacted Lyft and they said they'd pay the driver back. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
