<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject4342</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-12 01:21:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Like with any skin, you're only looking at basic scratch protection. Something like this won't do much with regards to protecting from drops. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-12 01:18:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I had a rhinoshield on both the Nexus 5X and 6P. Quickly got rid of it though. They do have a loyal fanbase, but I just couldn't get used to the bumper. It made the phones awkward to hold and taking it off requires a lot of force.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-11 22:18:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> All Verizon phones, with the exception of prepaid ones, ship carrier unlocked.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-11 21:27:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Just tested it out and it works fine with the Note 5. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-11 04:54:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Not sure. I usually prefer matte back skins since they do a better job of preventing fingerprint build-up. I had a glossy clear skin from a different company on my Note 7 and it showed fingerprints way too easily. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-11 04:46:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It means you have to spray a liquid solution onto the adhesive side of the skin to apply it. Once on, the excess water is squeegeed out. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-11 04:08:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I had the Naked Wrap on my 6P. Album link below. It's a good product. It is a wet application skin so keep that in mind. I had no issues applying it since I've used those types of skins fairly often, especially from other brands like Skinomi and IQ Shield.

[SW Naked Wrap Nexus 6P](http://imgur.com/a/Yuu69) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-11 04:02:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> They did the same thing for the first Note 7 recall, but that never got any coverage. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-11 01:19:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> None gained and none lost. Just pop in the Verizon sim and you'll be set  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-10 22:33:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Why have you ruled out selling it via eBay, Craigslist, or Swappa? You're going to get more money selling it to an individual than some online business like Gazelle. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-10 22:28:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> They aren't limiting it. The person somehow doesn't have it activated on their account. With Verizon, the option has to be added manually through their My Verizon page. It's kinda dumb though since it's a free feature that should automatically be added, but Verizon must have their reasons for not doing it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-10 21:01:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If an unlockable bootloader matters to you, then you should probably stay away from the Verizon version. Other than that, people saying that updates will be slower are just speculating right now. The "bloatware" is just three uninstallable apps. Security updates will still be through Google, with OS-level updates handled by Verizon. Tough to say if there will be much of a delay since the Verizon Nexus 6 has gotten OS updates as quickly as the unlocked model. That said, unless you can get a discount by ordering through Verizon, then go that route, but the Google Store model is probably the safest route for the moment. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-10 20:38:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It appears to only be common among readers of The Verge. Jokes aside, it isn't a common thing, but every defective Note that goes up in smoke gets blown up by the media coverage and it makes it seem like it's happening more often. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-10 16:38:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The update situation is still sketchy. Whereas the carrier versions have been good with the monthly security updates, the unlocked U.S. model has only gotten one OTA (August security patch) since it released. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-10 15:16:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Verizon phones ship sim unlocked. I've seen some people confusing the locked bootloader with a locked sim. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-10 15:15:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> With the exception of prepaid phones, all Verizon phones ship sim unlocked. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-10 15:10:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Better title:

*Comment: Samsungs literal meltdown will mostly benefit Apple, but should help Google   LG too*

Apple is in the best position. The V20 has yet to launch and the Pixel phones are only available through one carrier and online it's backordered. People that will be swapping out their Note 7 will want a new device right away. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-10 04:02:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The Pixel phones won't be able to charge fast by any QC adapter. They don't support it since proprietary fast charging tech over USB-C is against the spec. Both the cables and wall adapter matter. A bad cable that is out of spec can potentially damage a Type-C device. Same goes for an adapter since only spec compliant chargers will be able to properly charge Pixel phones quickly. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-10 02:00:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> They certainly are in a better position due to Samsung's mess. However, given the lack of carrier availability, I think the impact will be rather small. The people that are going to be returning their Note devices to carriers other than Verizon are going to be opting for whatever device is in stock. My money is on the iPhone being the next obvious pick since LG still hasn't launched the V20. As good as the Pixels may seem, most people aren't likely going to be waiting around for stock to replenish in order to get their order in. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-09 21:05:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> ()

   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-09 18:27:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Most people just like them for the leaks. I hate reading AP for reviews, no matter the device. David is mainly the one doing reviews and he always finds something to complain about. Discussing cons is one thing, but he really likes to dwell on the negative aspects. Even the guy who created AP and APKMirror (Artem R.) is the same way. [Here he is](https://plus.google.com/+ArtemRussakovskii/posts/dFuE11p5Uaw) singling out Backdrops because he didn't like how they did version numbers. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-09 05:57:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Sounds like a fake one to me

 Klering says Samsung also wanted possession of his device but he refused to give it up. 

Also, the hole in the case is rather suspicious. Those Pelican cases are pretty thick and a Note 7 bursting still probably couldn't cause that damage. A puncture through the case, whether on accident or purposefully, would cause the phone to burst. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-09 04:17:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It doesn't. Same goes for other phones. With phones that have OIS, both it and EIS are used together when shooting in certain resolutions. When shooting in an unsupported resolution, such as UHD, only OIS is used. The person who shot this video could be using a gimbal, but no one knows. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-08 21:48:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It is not one man's opinion. From the beginning, it is made clear that it's the stance Android Police has taken:

 Android Police rarely issues any kind of directive not to purchase a particular product


I enjoy reading the site, but this is a bit much. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-08 19:28:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'd probably go with the matte black skin. However, I currently have the [bamboo dbrand](http://iimgur.com/a/jOkOP) on my coral blue Note since I ordered it back when I had my recalled black Note 7. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-08 19:24:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Your snide remark aside, I'll be getting the Google Store version for better resale value. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-08 17:38:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> There are reasons to buy from Verizon, if you're a Verizon customer. Yes, Verizon sucks, but it's still going to be interesting to see how much slower the updates will be, if at all. The Nexus 6 on Verizon has been getting updates as quickly as the unlocked model and I'm sure Verizon also has to approve those. The main thing that will probably matter to some is the bootloader, but in that case, you already likely decided against the Verizon model. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-08 14:32:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I have it, but did not apply it yet since I went with a bamboo skin first. I did put it on my Moto Z Force, but did not look as good as I expected. Then again, the phone itself isn't really all that good looking.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-08 06:05:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The internet is obsessed with him. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-08 06:04:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> They're two different things. Also, Verizon phones ship sim unlocked out of the box.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-08 02:00:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Honestly, I'm surprised they didn't go this route. This is how I pictured the skins looking, but was let down when they revealed the actual design they went with. Great job with the concept because there's no way I could've done it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-08 00:49:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If you're referring to my old Note 7, I cut out a sticker to place over the camera for protection against scratches. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-07 21:36:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> No problem on my current one, but I did have a noticeable gap on the left side of my recalled Note 7 and the S7 Edge I had before. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-07 21:32:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It would make no financial sense for the phone manufacturers. There isn't a large enough consumer base for it to work out in the long run. Even with the previous GPE devices, manufacturers still had to add in extra stuff to get certain parts of their hardware working correctly (e.g. HTC's sound mods and other software that is licensed). So now instead of supporting just their line of devices, they need to allocate developers to support a separate model. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-07 21:01:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Just wait it out. Besides, it'll suck later down the road if you fill up the storage and regret not having waited a bit longer for stock to replenish. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-07 20:47:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I can't help you with your question, but I have also been considering getting the UAG case. I've had it for previous devices and it was always one of my favorites. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-07 20:14:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Nice. I've never even heard of upsie, but I did a quick search and it looks pretty good.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-07 19:40:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I sold them since they weren't compatible with the edge-to-edge screen protector. For the few times I do use a case, I don't want it to cause the screen protector to lift along the edges. Case friendly screen protectors exist, but I always like more coverage if the option exists. I had the SW Naked Wrap on my Nexus 6P and really liked it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> How are you protecting your Note 7? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-07 19:16:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Decided to post this to see how others are protecting their phone. I've opted for just a back skin and screen protector.

Album links below to what I'm currently using:

* [Skinomi TechSkin Full Coverage](http://imgur.com/a/2aI5o)
* [dbrand bamboo](http://imgur.com/a/jOkOP)

I also have a [Spigen Thin Fit case](http://imgur.com/a/oHqSJ), but haven't used it with my new Note 7. The Thin Fit is the only case I've owned that is compatible with the full coverage screen protector. If anyone out there is using a full coverage screen protector with a different case, please let me know since it's always good to have some options.

For my old Note 7, I used the [IQ Shield Full Body skin](http://imgur.com/a/MG30u). If anyone is curious in how some cases look on the Note 7, I had the following ones for my previous Note 7, but ended up getting rid of them.

* [Caseology Parallax](http://imgur.com/a/MOJvD)
* [Spigen Rugged Armor](http://imgur.com/a/vr5FU)
* [Spigen Neo Hybrid](http://imgur.com/a/Efc26)
* [Spigen Neo Hybrid Crystal](http://imgur.com/a/Q9dTb) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-07 05:13:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Must be that Kodak phone that was recently teased </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-07 01:53:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Nothing annoys me more than seeing a dbrand or SW sponsored video. They're everywhere these days. lol </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-07 01:52:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> For phones with 2.5D edges, I usually opt for wet-application screen protectors from companies like Skinomi and IQ Shield. They tend to offer the best edge-to-edge coverage. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-07 01:48:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> One less bill to manage. Also, a credit inquiry needs to be done to get approved for Google's financing and some people prefer to limit those as much as possible since a hard inquiry can hurt your credit score. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-06 23:09:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> True. I haven't gone to Yahoo's homepage in a while, but back when I did, I would regularly come across BGR articles they promoted through their feed. The sites that don't deserve the clicks are usually the ones that are easiest to come across. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-06 20:30:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Most Android enthusiasts know they put out crap. I can't remember the last time (if ever) they were worth reading.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-06 03:13:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> They are uninstallable. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-06 00:40:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You could apply a skin to the back to give it a new look. I tend to go with dbrand, but slickwraps is another option as well. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-05 23:14:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Google really messed this up and they need to fix it with their marketing. If the enthusiasts are questioning the Verizon exclusivity, I can only imagine it'll turn away a large amount of normal consumers since Verizon is pushing the "only on Verizon" angle. People aren't going to be interested if they think it's only available through Verizon. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-05 21:45:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> At this point, not even Google could get VZW to offer unlimited data. However, it would be interesting to see if Google is able to convince them to be a part of Fi. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-05 02:57:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Verizon has two types of stores. The corporate owned ones and the authorized retailers, which can also look like Verizon stores. The non-corporate ones usually have "Authorized Retailer" or "Premium Retailer" in the front of the building. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-05 01:00:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If you get it through Fi, it will work on VZW. The sim is the same size as the one in the 6s so you're good. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-05 00:55:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If you go to a corporate store, the sim is free. Authorized retailers will likely try to charge you something like $15 for the sim. All your account info remains the same. It's just a new sim and your phone number gets transferred to it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-05 00:51:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> As a regular seller, I've learned that bundling accessories with your devices doesn't necessarily lead to more value when it goes to sell. There are exceptions for some accessories, but most of the time, you'll only get back a small fraction of what you paid for it. Just look at other listings and compare what they're offering for the price they have. If someone is just selling the phone with the original accessories, you can obviously price yours higher, but you also need to take into account the condition of the phone. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-04 19:14:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Verizon was not an exclusive carrier retailer for the Nexus 6. They didn't even carry the phone at launch. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-04 14:40:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Verizon phones ship sim unlocked. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-04 05:29:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Wouldn't be surprised if this is why HTC is currently offering a $150 discount on the 10. Take advantage of some people getting turned away from the Pixel pricing in hopes those same people jump onto the HTC 10.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-04 04:03:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The Nexus 6 on Verizon came without the usual Verizon bloat. I believe the My Verizon app would install itself, but it could be uninstalled. People bashing the Nexus experience on Verizon are still upset over the mess that was the Galaxy Nexus. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-03 17:47:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That's my 6P and it has no case on it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-03 16:05:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What case are you referring to? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-03 04:01:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I've had both. I can't really say much about battery life on the S7 Edge (VZW model) since I had wifi problems with it which led to average battery life based on other phones I've owned. Also, I couldn't stand accidentally touching the edges, especially while in the camera app. I sold it after a month or ownership. I got an unlocked S7 (U.S. model) recently. Battery life was great. I would easily get 4-5hrs of SOT. The size was great for one-hand use, but dang did I miss having the larger display.

If your main concern is battery life and don't care about a larger screen, then I'd go with the regular S7 and decide at a later point if you need the battery pack. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-03 03:00:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This is one of the main reasons I didn't last long with my 5X. I thought I could get by with a 32GB model. Nope. I need at least 64GB of built-in storage. If you plan on sticking with the 5X, you could look into expanding your storage via USB-C. It's not an ideal solution, but for playing/storing music, it could alleviate some storage issues. I used the [Nonda adapter](http://imgur.com/a/tnkKb) on my 6P.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-02 05:39:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Nope. My experience with the 5X has been positive. I sold my first one after I got the gold 6P. I started to miss the 5X and jumped on the Fi deal when they discounted it. I sold it afterwards since I ended up getting an S7 Edge to use alongside the 6P. My last 5X was an impulse buy and just sold it off right after buying it. I think I have issues. LOL.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-02 01:36:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Back around the time when the Note 7 was first announced, someone from The Verge stated on one of their podcasts that Samsung did have plans on releasing an unlocked unit later down the road. However, with the recall, I wouldn't be surprised if plans changed. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-01 22:30:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Honestly, I think LG just manufactured a lot of them in the beginning and stopped after December. I've had three different 5X devices since release. The first one I got in November from B H. That was manufactured the same month. I got another one from Fi in April and had a manufacturing date in October. The last one I got from an eBay seller (new) and was made in September. These were all 32GB U.S. models.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-01 06:59:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That is the international model (G935F). International devices sold in the US tend to not come with a manufacturer's warranty. Also, it will not work with CDMA carriers like VZW and Sprint. The US unlocked model is G935U. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-30 23:21:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This has been option for years. Since Swappa uses PayPal to complete transactions, during checkout, buyers can change their funding source to PayPal Credit. Nothing new, but this email probably serves to educate those that didn't know it has been an option. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-30 22:57:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm just not going to take a chance with damaging my current phone, or any future one I own, by doing quick charging over Type-C. [Check out this video](https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=ujaapnnNzsQ) if you want to learn more about it and also checkout the video description. 

As a real world example, [here's a write-up](https://plus.google.com/102612254593917101378/posts/Vp5pDHvd84j) about the HTC 10 getting damaged while quick charging. Tronsmart charger and iOrange cable. He updated his original post and will be studying what happened to see if the charger, cable, or phone was to blame. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-30 20:43:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This hit Slickdeals yesterday. I'm surprised the code is still working. There's usually a limit to how many codes can be redeemed, but be aware that it can stop working at any time. 

I was going to purchase it yesterday, but I decided against it since it's doing quick charging over USB-C. Anyone who follows Benson Leung or Nathan K will likely know that proprietary fast charging techniques go against the Type C spec. If you see [this Tronsmart listing](https://www.amazon.com/gp/aw/d/B01L6BONYK/ref=mp_s_a_1_sc_5?ie=UTF8 qid=1475260737 sr=8-5-spell pi=AC_SX236_SY340_FMwebp_QL65 keywords=teonsmart+usb+c+car+charger), they removed the quick charging feature from the USB-C plug and only did it for the Type A port. The USB-C port for that one is now described as meeting the USB-C standard. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-30 15:33:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Keep in mind that people are more likely to post about their negative experience than a positive one. This then makes it seem like there's some big issue with the phone. However, for every person posting here about some of their problems, there are many more owners out there that have been having a solid experience with the phone. I've had mine since the beginning of February and sold it a little over a week ago since I got a couple of new devices. I never had any issues with it.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-29 03:37:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Simultaneous voice and data should work fine, but likely a no go for HD Voice. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-29 00:55:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I've had both. I first owned an S7 Edge. I'm currently on the S7 after returning the Note 7 for the recall situation. Both of them are great. No battery issues with either one. I'm currently getting over 4hrs SOT with the S7. Out of the two, I prefer the S7E for the looks, larger display, and bigger battery. The S7 is still a great choice if you dont want the Edge. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-28 23:25:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yep they do treat iPhones differently. I've used at least 6 different unlocked Android devices on Verizon and notice the difference as soon as I switch to a Verizon-branded one in regards to HD Voice. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-28 22:17:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I did a crappy job of explaining it up top. Back when Verizon first rolled out Advanced Calling 1.0, users had to go online and enable the option to get features like HD Voice and simultaneous voice   data. Verizon later changed the branding from "Advanced Calling" to just "HD Voice." With HD Voice enabled, people with unlocked phones on Verizon will only get access to simultaneous voice and data. Below is how VZW explains it:

 With HD Voice, when you're connected to the Verizon 4G LTE network, you can surf the web, continue a download, use an application, or use a feature like Mobile Hotspot while talking on a call, regardless of whether the person you're calling has HD Voice or not.

They bundle HD Voice, Wifi Calling and simultaneous voice   data all into one option. However, enabling that feature on your Verizon account  doesn't give you access to all those things with unlocked phones. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-28 20:54:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> VoLTE worked fine for me while I had my 5X activated on Verizon. I'm not sure if it's different for prepaid customers, but HD Voice can be enabled by yourself on Verizon's account page. 

My Plan   ServicesManage Product   AppsGet ProductsFree Products </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-28 20:00:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> With unlocked phones on Verizon, VoLTE works fine. However, other things like Wifi calling and HD Voice won't since those require Verizon specific software. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-28 16:21:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I usually wait at least a month after release to see if any hardware problems are brought up. I recently broke that rule with the Note 7. Never again. It's nice having a new device as soon as possible, but sometimes patience is better, especially if there are any deals for the holiday season later in the year. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-28 16:18:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> 2 to 3 months after release tend to get replaced with new units since there's little to no stock of refurbs. Once refurb stock builds up, you won't be getting new replacements. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-27 22:23:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The unlocked European models have the September patch, but the unlocked U.S. models are still stuck on August. Keep in mind that the August security patch is the first and only OTA they have received. The carrier variants, on the other hand, have been getting the monthly updates. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-27 21:57:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Even then, I'd stay away from the unlocked variant if the S7 and S7 Edge are anything to go by. Updates for those unlocked models are not as timely as their carrier counterparts. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-27 21:52:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Haven't you heard about the bird?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-27 20:03:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That is incorrect. Samsung did recall a small amount of Chinese units. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-27 20:01:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Cringe-gate </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-27 03:53:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Since HTC is the one making it, for the front design, I'd go for [these M9 renders](http://cdn02.androidauthority.net/wp-content/uploads/2015/02/HTC-One-M9-render-9.jpg) some dude came up with. So much hope, but we were let down once it actually launched. [Here's another angle](http://cdn02.androidauthority.net/wp-content/uploads/2015/02/HTC-One-M9-render-8.jpg). </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-27 02:55:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Unlike the mess that was the Galaxy Nexus on Verizon, Verizon's Nexus 6 has none of their bloat and gets updated at the same speed as the unlocked one. The only real con some will mention is that Verizon put their logo on the back of it, but it's just a logo. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-27 02:51:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Verizon's Nexus 6 ships without their bloat. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-26 20:36:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yep. There was a big push from enthusiasts back in the day saying "I'd totally buy [insert manufacturer here] flagship if it came with stock Android." Well, they got their wish and it flopped. There's not a big enough market for it to make sense as an investment for companies. They're better off focusing on what they originally developed than drop it all and do stock Android. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-26 15:30:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I know, but in his post Nathan also mentioned that "there is another report on Amazon of this iOrange cable damaging a Nexus 6P" and which is why I posted it here. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-26 15:08:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> There was another leak as well he brought up earlier in the year, but I forgot which one it was. It too ended up being true. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-26 14:10:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [Based on the info](https://plus.google.com/102612254593917101378/posts/Vp5pDHvd84j) Nathan K brought up, I'd stay away from that cable for now. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-26 02:27:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I easily switch between both platforms, but I tend to prefer Android because the software experience suits my needs better. The one positive thing about the lack of homescreen customization on the iPhone is that it sure helps me stay more productive. I'm also addicted to getting new devices and waiting an year to hop onto the next iPhone is too long of a wait for me.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-26 02:24:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Stock, but I don't mind some manufacturer skins. Out of the phones I've owned, LG's skin is probably my least favorite. However, Artem from Android Police did have some [very positive things](https://plus.google.com/+ArtemRussakovskii/posts/MzD4mPp89mJ) to say about the software experience on the V20. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-25 22:14:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yep. Been stuck on 6.0 and is still on the May security patch.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-25 19:36:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The 10% figure mentioned is pretty much correct for the U.S. When Samsung officially announced the recall with the CPSC, they confirmed 92 cases occurred in the U.S. As seen [in this article](http://www.gsmarena.com/hoaxers_took_advantage_of_the_note7_recall_at_least_26_false_fire_reports-blog-20658.php), nine of those 26 false reports originated in the U.S. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-25 05:48:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yep. Can confirm the experience is much better with the Note 7. I sold my S7 Edge after a month back when it first came out since I couldn't stand the accidental presses. Never had this issue with my Note 7. I'm currently on an S7 since I ended up returning the Note. Depending on how the Pixel phones turn out, I may go back to the Note 7 since I only had it for a week before the recall was announced. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-25 01:27:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> No one knows. However, if the Pixel devices are as expensive as they're rumored to be, don't expect much of a price drop. Honestly, I wouldn't be surprised if Google kept the 6P around as their cheaper model with maybe a modest price cut. Apple does the same thing. Not sure how much it'll clash with their Pixel push, but it'll probably please some that are turned off from the Pixel line.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-24 15:47:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Moto is rather poor when it comes to updates. Yes, the Style/Pure Edition got marshmallow quick, but that's about it. Users complained about bugs and Moto didn't push out updates. They then got the February patch and the May one. It has pretty much been forgotten since then. It's also still stuck on 6.0. 6.0.1 never rolled out to it.  

Here's the report card for Moto: 
https://www.google.com/amp/www.computerworld.com/article/3052937/android/android-upgrade-report-card-marshmallow.amp.html

Edit: guess I annoyed the Moto fanboys. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-24 04:11:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The Moto X/X Force launched with the May patch and then got the July patch (in late August). They got the September patch a few days back. Honestly, I'm a bit surprised they've been doing somewhat good with these devices so far. On the other hand, the Moto X Pure is still on 6.0 with the May patch. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-22 19:15:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This is the same guy that said last year Verizon would never offer rollover data.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-22 16:03:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's really tough to fully lay the blame on Verizon. Samsung has been able to quickly push out their security updates with the recent Galaxy flagships on Verizon. Meanwhile, other devices like the HTC 10 are stuck on old patches. Even the Verizon Nexus 6 has been getting updates at the same speed as the unlocked models. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-22 04:53:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I hate using a case, but I do use a back skin to protect from scratches. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-22 04:44:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Judging by the case the phone is using, it's not the Priv. Here, the volume buttons are separate from the power button. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-21 23:03:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Correct </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-21 22:38:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I regularly buy and sell devices and this one seems legit. High rated seller and S7 prices have been falling. The other day Best Buy was selling the unlocked U.S. Galaxy S7 (refurb) for $369.99. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-21 20:07:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I had these connection issues with wifi back on my S7 Edge. No matter what fix I tried, nothing would solve the issue. Wifi would regularly disconnect when the screen would be off. With my Note 7, I never encountered this. If the issue still remains for you, then I'd go back and ask for a replacement. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-21 00:34:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm torn between two.

Old Samsung feature: swiping left and right on the status bar to control brightness.

Double tap to wake and double tap the status bar to shut the phone off. Off the top of my head, I know LG uses this. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-20 21:53:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> No one knows, but the consensus seems to be that the price will remain the same, but they'll likely continue with new promotion deals. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-20 19:43:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Verizon's Nexus 6 ships without any bloatware and gets updates at the same speed as the unlocked ones. Anyone still complaining about the Nexus experience on Verizon is referring to the Galaxy Nexus. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-19 22:13:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I had a Moto Z for a week as I used it alongside my Note 7. Performance on the Z was phenomenal, but that's really all that stood out to me. The phone was alright, but nothing that got me too excited about it. I know Moto doesn't have the best track record when it comes to camera quality, but the Z's camera wasn't as good as I expected. I looked up data about the rear sensor and saw that it's the same one that shipped in the Nexus 6. I ended up selling it before I returned the Note 7. I'm tempted to hop onto the Z Force for the extra battery and better camera. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-19 00:27:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This is why I have cut back on some of my YouTube channel subscriptions. Some people are just too obsessed worrying more about "crisp" footage than actual worthwhile content. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-18 02:15:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> For the V20? It's not a lie. See [here](http://gsmarena.com/lg_v20-8238.php) under the camera specs. Also, it has been mentioned by some YouTubers. The first one that comes to mind is Tim Schofield in his first impressions video. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-18 01:13:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I've been subscribed to his channel for a while and he is far from an Apple fanboy. He's pretty unbiased when it comes to these comparisons. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-17 21:58:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> For as much as they push the iPhone's camera, Apple still opts for subpar mono audio recording. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-17 21:54:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It'd be nice to see how the V20's 2x optical zoom stacks up against the 7 Plus. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-17 18:39:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> After all this time, the iPhone is still stuck recording in mono audio. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-17 16:00:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's just a mixture of water and soap. I'd say use about a cup of water and a drop of dish soap. Mix the two slowly to avoid forming soapsuds. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-15 19:42:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Phones still have sim card slots and a lot of manufacturers are pairing those slots with microSD. Water resistance is not a valid reason to keep the slot away.  Same goes for anyone saying the headphone jack should be removed due to water resistance. 

Edit: misspelling  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-15 02:33:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This thing hit Slickdeals first and they pretty much jumped on it and cleared out all the stock Amazon had at $277. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-14 22:30:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Others haven't had much luck. From the reports I've seen, Samsung reps are also turning away people that purchased them second-hand. They only deal with buyers that got a Note straight from them and referring others to contact their carrier or store they got it from. I ended up returning mine to my ebay seller since I was within the return period.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-14 16:33:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> LG and Sony phones will still be around for a while. Their mobile divisions only make up a small part of their overall company. On the other hand, HTC pretty much has to rely on phone sales to remain in existence. They have VR, but their main focus is still mobile and it is not bueno. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-14 15:25:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Here are the skins I've used on my gold 6P. I feel like I'm missing one, but these are the ones I took pictures of while I used them. I think a matte black with the gold 6P would probably look the best, but I didn't go with it since the black/gold combo is pretty common.

[White carbon fiber](http://imgur.com/a/O3KeX)

[Purple](http://imgur.com/a/eSV6I)

[Red](http://imgur.com/a/P8zqn)

Bonus clear skin:
[Slickwraps Naked Wrap](http://imgur.com/a/Yuu69) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-14 14:43:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I like to live dangerously. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-14 03:18:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Not everyone is like you. Accidents happen. It's much better to have water resistance than run into an unexpected situation where the phone gets wet and your expensive devices dies in you.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-14 01:17:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Nope. I'm usually a tech junkie and tend not to stick with a phone for more than a few months. It has now been over six and I'm still happy with it. I thought the S7 Edge would sway me away, but I sold it after a month. I tried with the Note 7, but we all know how that went. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-14 01:15:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [AC breaks down](http://m.androidcentral.com/googles-september-security-update-has-three-patch-levels) the three September builds based on patch level. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-13 22:47:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [Here's a quick explanation](http://m.androidcentral.com/googles-september-security-update-has-three-patch-levels) of the three patch levels for September. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-13 04:41:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If you're worried about resale value, stay away from Android devices. iPhones hold their value much better. As for the recall, it'll likely affect second-hand prices in the short term, but probably won't do much to affect depreciation two years down the line compared to previous Notes. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-13 04:38:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's a vape battery. Nothing to do with the Note 7. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-13 04:37:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> At this point, it's easier to blame Samsung. People hate reading. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-13 03:42:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I was slightly interested back when they first released it, but I'm just not a fan of the way it looks. The alcantara series probably has some good grip though, but since I may sell my 6P in the near future, there's no point in spending money on another wrap. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-12 22:59:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I bought my Verizon Note 7 relatively cheap and new on ebay about a week before the recall was announced. I tried going the Verizon and Samsung route, but also had no luck. I ended up returning it to the seller since I was within their 14 day return window. They received it today and already issued me the refund. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-12 20:55:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> As stated already, that's for accessories you got from them or your carrier. I'm sure most carriers will accept accessory returns even if you don't plan on switching to an S7 or S7 Edge. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-12 20:23:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Honestly, I have used all types of skins available and have yet to come across a skin that adds noticeable grip. Yet I still come across people saying how much more grip a certain skin, such as a carbon fiber one, adds. Sorry for the short rant. LOL. 

It's certainly an improvement over a naked 6P, but "grippy" is far from what I would use to describe it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-12 20:15:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This is something all manufacturers should be aiming to do. Partnering with celebrities for subpar commercials or launch events is useless, in my opinion. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-12 20:14:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Samsung is not responsible for accessories you purchased.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-12 16:33:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I don't drop my phone so I'm not sure. It works fine with cases if you don't apply the side skins. Skins along the sides tend to peel off if a case rubs it enough while it's being put on or taken off.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-12 14:54:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I posted about it here a few months back. [Here are some pictures](http://imgur.com/a/Yuu69) of it. It does cover all parts of the phone. If you do get it, take it slow when applying the sides because they can move around a bit during installation since it's wet-application. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-12 14:11:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I was correcting the pricing. As you can see, the person responded to me and edited his/her comment. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-12 01:55:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> iPhone 7 starts at $649. $769 is for the 7 Plus. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-11 20:42:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> None, but I wouldn't be surprised if that changes soon now that I posted this. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-11 07:12:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I saw that video earlier, but I must have not been paying attention during that part. I looked into it more and noticed [gsmarena](http://www.gsmarena.com/lg_v20-8238.php) does list "2x optical zoom" under the specs section. The same thing is noted in the LG G5 specs page. None of the mainstream sites have reported on it. I don't even think LG made an effort to point it out.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-11 06:38:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It does not.

Edit: see below </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-11 05:25:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Apple, LG, and Huawei all use their dual camera setups differently. From what I understand, Apple mainly uses it for the 2x optical zoom and the bokeh effect. With LG, you can take a normal style shot or opt for a wide-angle one. So pretty much here both are acting separately. Like Apple, Huawei uses both sensors simultaneously. However, one is RGB and the other is monochrome. Huawei uses both sensors to supposedly create the best shot. They also have their own bokeh mode. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-11 01:43:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Oh yeah the 6P is a bit larger. The benefit is having dual front facing speakers, but Samsung sure did a great job packing in the same display size in a smaller form factor. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-11 01:06:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's a great phone. The camera is solid and overall performance has been great. I'm a tech addict and usually get a new phone and sell my previous one multiple times a year. However, the 6P has been the first device I've kept for longer than four months. I've had it for a little over six months and it has never let me down. 

That said, it was really nice when I finally got my hands on the Note 7. I instantly got hooked. I previously had the S7 Edge, but got rid of it since I would accidentally touch the curved panels way too often. Though the camera on the 6P is no slouch, the Note 7 is on another level. I saw people complaining about lag on the Note 7, but I never noticed any slowdowns. I also don't have any problems with OEM skins. Stock Android is great, but it's also nice to move away from the plain experience to a more robust set of features like Samsung provides. If this battery recall never came up, I likely would have sold my 6P.

Forgot to mention that battery life is much better with the Note 7. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-10 23:56:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Make sure it's a U.S. model and not the international one. The model number for the U.S. one is LG-H790 and the international 5X is LG-H791. 

To check for the Google account thing, just verify you can go through the setup process without needing to use a previous Google account. It's a security feature they put in place a while back. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-10 23:53:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I went back to my 6P. I almost sold it right after I got the Note 7, but thankfully I decided to hold onto it for comparisons. I also had a Moto Z in hand, but ended up selling it since the camera was subpar.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-10 20:30:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If you do switch and don't like the iPhone 7, you'd at least be able to sell it for good money and return to Android. The iPhone holds its value better than any phone. If you do jump back, the Pixel phones will likely already be out and the Nexus 6P will probably be discounted even more. I'd say give it a shot. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-10 17:06:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I've had my gold one for over 6 months and no bending. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-10 14:25:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> No U.S. CDMA carrier support with the international one and LG won't provide any warranty support for it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-10 05:57:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If you order from ebay, make sure it's the U.S. model. I've come across a lot of people here on Reddit thinking they got the U.S. one, but in reality they purchased the international variant because it was on sale. If you're not aware, the model number for the U.S. is LG-H790 and the Intl one is LG-H791. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-09 19:34:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It won't affect carrier branding. Besides, the recall only affected the batteries. The other aspects of the manufacturing process hasn't changed. That means those colorful backs with AT T and VZW logos are well in stock. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-09 03:33:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yes. Verizon and AT T love putting their branding everywhere. It sucks, but it's just how it is. Until Samsung releases an unlocked U.S. model compatible with all the carriers, you're stuck getting carrier branded ones. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-08 19:26:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This certainly smells like fraud to me. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-07 15:06:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It has held up great. I usually buy these type of screen protectors for my devices with curved edges so I'm not new to them. As for the thing you're referring to, it's called the orange peel effect and is common among wet application films. It's only noticeable with the screen off. With the screen on, it doesn't affect the display quality and pretty much doesn't look like a screen protector is on. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-07 05:01:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That is not the first U.S. case. The guy (Ariel Gonzalez) that uploaded [this video](https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=HQQOiilJwJ0) to YouTube lives in the U.S. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-06 06:09:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Manufacturers tend to not offer warranty support for international models in the U.S.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-06 04:29:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The international version is not compatible with the U.S. CDMA carriers. In addition, LG won't provide warranty support for the international model if you're in the U.S. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-05 20:21:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Since Verizon occasionally does open enrollment for phone insurance, that'll probably be your only way of hopefully getting onto a newer revision. However, then you're at the mercy of Asurion's stock quality. The few times I've used them, I haven't had any major issues, but there's usually someone out there with a bad Asurion experience. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> PSA: Do not buy any Anker PowerLine 3.1Gen2 Type-C cables </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-24 00:06:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Verizon Moto Z and Z Force arrive on july 28 </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-14 17:23:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> 32GB Nexus 5X (US Model) New for $229.99 via eBay </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-12 06:44:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Best Buy Ebay Store $80 off Nexus 6P </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-29 23:12:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Slickwraps Naked Wrap on Gold Nexus 6P </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-26 22:04:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [Slickwraps Naked Wrap](http://imgur.com/a/Yuu69)

Other skins I've used on my gold Nexus 6P

* [Purple dbrand](http://imgur.com/a/eSV6I)

* [White Carbon Fiber dbrand](http://imgur.com/a/O3KeX)

I installed the clear skin a few days back. Overall, it's a great alternative to those who want to protect their device with a skin, but still want to keep the original look. For those who have used a liquid installation skin before from a brand like Skinomi or IQ Shield, the process is the same. Installation instructions are included with the skin.

Even though Slickwraps customer service stated it adds grip, it doesn't really add any grip. It does have a matte finish and does a great job from preventing fingerprint buildup. The only really place the skin is easy to spot is over the black bar. Other than that, it blends in with the phone nicely.

Comparing Slickwraps to dbrand shipping: 

* SW: I got this skin during the recent sale they had. I ordered it late in the morning and it surprisingly shipped out the same day and arrived quickly via the standard shipping method. I say "surprisingly" since my previous shipping experiences with them in 2015 were less than stellar. It arrived in a padded envelope and the packaging shown in the imgur album. The skin arrived undamaged.

* dbrand: Shipping with them can be a hit or miss. Sometimes they've shipped out a skin within a couple of days and other times it has taken up to a week or slightly more. However, they recently switched their standard shipping to DHL with tracking so that's a nice change compared to the previous (slow) one with USPS and no tracking. The one negative is their envelope. It's basically a standard envelope and isn't padded. I've had a couple of skins arrive creased, likely from damage during shipping.
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Nexus 5X from $199 through Project Fi </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-07 19:48:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Black RhinoShield pics + comparison to Nexus 5X and microfiber case </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-08 01:26:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Google Store Gold Nexus 6P $50 off </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-26 20:28:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> In addition to Amazon and Best Buy, it looks like Google has decided to join the discount for the gold variant. Probably a better choice for those who want to sign up for Nexus Protect and better support from Google CS.

https://store.google.com/product/nexus_6p

[The Verge](http://www.theverge.com/2016/1/26/10836414/google-nexus-5x-6p-price-cuts-valentines-day) states the sale is good through February 14 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Skinomi MatteSkin Fully Body </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-27 23:28:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Slickwraps 30% off sale plus $5 off any Slickwraps purchase [AMERICA] </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-06-27 00:46:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> $5 off your Slickwraps purchase - ends 6/29/14 at 2pm </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-06-26 23:40:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Question about studying for the FE Exam </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-05-28 21:36:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So I recently graduated and never took the exam while in school even though the professors kept telling us we should. For those who past the new computer based exam, did you use any of the review manuals provided by Kaplan or Lindeburg? I have to take the Civil version of the exam and I already know I should familiarize myself with the reference handbook. If I do buy a review manual I think I might go for the Kaplan version since it's a lot cheaper than Lindeburg's $160 book. Just hoping it's not a you get what you pay for situation since Kaplan's only costs $68. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
