<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject278</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-01 22:00:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It sucks that Google Maps doesn't have a 'common sense' feature... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-28 23:26:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I agree. China doing a formal execution seems much better than being beheaded inside a stinky shack. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-28 19:53:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I agree, although the central focus of this story is the fact the policewoman was munching the carpet of a rape victim. At McDonalds. That's easily the most morose bathroom in the galaxy. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-28 19:46:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's some fuckered up shit for sure. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-28 16:46:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I think an old German Panzer would do the trick. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-28 16:26:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> $60 a barrel sucks donkey balls. Think we just need to buy Saudi Arabia... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-28 15:36:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I feel badly for those caught in the web of things like this. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-28 13:02:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I have *no* idea what country would employ a leader who just brought on oil tycoons and multibillion dollar businesspeople... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-28 13:00:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> A sick reality, but true to form. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-28 01:50:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Twerked AND vibrated. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-28 01:50:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Safety first!  :) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-27 21:45:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> ...now can you understand the stink in America with all this undocumented immigration crap? If you're here 19 years but haven't applied for American citizenship, ya kinda goofed. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-27 21:34:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That's all we can ask of those who enter our country - go through a process like anyone else.

Think of it this way: if an American illegally entered Mexico (or any other country, for that matter), we'd be shot on site or immediately arrested. Border Patrol escorts most back to the other side without incident. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-27 21:06:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Still, after 27 years? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-27 19:28:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Exactly.

I suspect this uptick in 'closet religiousness' will continue with every word spoken by Trump. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-27 19:16:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'd be happy with an endless supply of coffee and ESPN. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-27 18:03:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I believe this entire Trump presidency has a trickle down effect that will have more the 3/4 of humanity eating shit (or at least holding a bag of shit). </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-27 18:01:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Religion - the breakfast of champions. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-27 18:00:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Correct. However, if we're logically deducing here, the afterlife is supposedly endless... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-27 17:55:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Virgins are only worth what someone is willing to pay. In this case, I believe the price for 72 virgins is allegiance. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-27 17:41:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> There is nothing in it. I assume virgins in heaven are surprisingly subservient, however. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-27 17:02:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I think the IS is everywhere. It's a 'thing'. He assimilated.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-27 16:49:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Probably be some sort of rotation setup where year 1-1M will be one, then 1M-2M will be another...you know, build up suspense... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-27 16:46:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It would be peaceful, less stressful, much less scamming. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-27 16:42:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Well put.

I agree - being rewarded with 72 porn stars who know how to handle the mangoods sounds much better than having to pop 72 cherries en route to an outright miserable coitus session. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-27 16:36:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> And Mikey really liked Life...and still does. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-27 16:35:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Well, I think (opinions will vary) that heaven is a human's 'reset button'. If they took 50 dicks in 30 years on earth, those notches get erased in heaven. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-27 16:33:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Not sure his level of sanity has a mathematical value... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-27 16:33:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Ah, now there's a new one - the media inspired political bullshit.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-27 16:32:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What if the 72 virgins in heaven he refers to are really 36 two-headed hydras? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-27 16:30:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I condemn any religious activity, present-day eschatological psychobabble or bullshit speech that takes away from what religion is designed for.

World news and astrological viewpoints seem to fall parallel on many news outlets (if you read them). So fucking what. 

Religion and recruiting forces have been bedfellows since Napoleon fucking Bonaparte. And they'll be buttfucking each other long after our existences. 

It's fucking news. It's entertainment. Call it what you want, or don't call it anything. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-27 16:24:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So this boy's religious 'epiphany' or whatever you wanna call it is nothing more than a Ponzi? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-27 16:23:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yes, I agree. Anyone who would thirst so heavily over 'a few pumps and a smash down' needs psychiatric evaluating. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-27 16:21:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What if those 72 virgins have already committed themselves to Prince? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-27 16:20:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> A </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-27 16:09:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I don't think there is sex in the afterlife. A human's desire for feeling whole, gratified, etc. encompasses the very selfish nature the afterlife was designed to avoid. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-27 15:50:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I certainly agree. How or why someone chooses a life/sexual partner should be none of society's concern.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-27 13:11:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I agree, especially given the fact Scotland seems to be a nation rarely heard about in terms of having widespread hysteria. They seem to be operating just fine without EU's dogmatic political viewpoints or actions. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-24 22:59:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> She's pictured wearing a whorish white. Double attention whore. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-24 22:58:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's going to be fun to see how much Tillerson and the rest of Trump's entourage profit off this presidency. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-24 19:48:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Not as much a getaway vehicle as someone trying to grease someone's palms. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-24 18:08:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Political corruption is much more entertaining than today's eschatological nonsense. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-24 17:26:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> As technology increases, the level of sophistication will increase as well.. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-24 17:26:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Well, then there's Wembley Stadium, the Royal Guard, and lots and lots of tea. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-24 17:20:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Notice how when the right candidate comes along in any political race, the presence of 'fake scandals' and hacking jobs increases? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-24 16:56:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The long arm of the law apparently doesn't extend far enough in the UK.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-24 13:22:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah, I agree. Not exactly a fashion forward statement given her legal issues... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-24 12:48:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Noticed that, too. Almost like she's a broom stick away from Salem... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-24 12:47:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Diplomatic immunity - the breakfast of champions. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-24 12:33:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Note they didn't mention anything about "bartering" for sex... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-24 11:54:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> ...now take me to your leader. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-24 01:44:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm feasting as we speak. Brown-chicken-brown-cow! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-24 01:43:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's sports. Everything you read is an inside account of 'something'. Get over it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-24 00:20:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The reality they see is actually more religious than anything. I mean, shit, if my God was a pedophile, I'd be pretty shitty about life, too. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-23 23:11:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> ...I don't get their angst. We give them a free place to hang out, tax-free business funding for convenience stores and hotels, education, whatever they want. Now let an American setup a convenience store in an Arab country, see what happens. Let an American bitch about loud cricket matches.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-23 23:00:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Please, do tell us more... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-23 20:02:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Uneasy rests the head that wears the crown, huh? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-23 20:01:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Remember, it's the media's job to instill whatever emotion garners the best ratings. So if an American magazine conflates an Asian problem that may soon require Trump to make tough decisions, expect 10% to be true (usually within the first two paragraphs) and the 90% that remains to be conjecture. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-23 19:52:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> ...then wonder why they're the butt of so many bipartisan jokes. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-23 19:50:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Everything. Even the Arab world strikes a nerve with the Arab world. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-23 19:27:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Wonder if we should just create an Arabian Swimsuit issue... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-23 19:23:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The commercially commercialization of commercials. Pfft. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-23 17:56:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You taking a hijab at me? ;) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-23 17:01:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Lol...and I'm not sari I did it... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-23 16:22:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Commercially speaking, yes. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-23 16:13:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Just wonder what Gomer Pyle would have felt if those repeated blows were real... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-23 15:58:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Ah, I am rereading it Quimosabi. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-23 15:44:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> One day, they'll be sari for being prudish.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-23 14:31:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So basically Morris Day is responsible for this unfunny joke we call life? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-23 14:27:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I completely get the Christian way of thinking, but I believe we as humans are more than capable of debunking what many believe to be an illogical, narrow scope of thinking that somehow a mythical deity capable of speaking everything into existence out of nothingness has no prior history. We're trained to believe that an essence of faith and intentional ignorance of happenstance will land us into an already created realm where all plagues (induced by man) no longer exist. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-23 14:10:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Wasn't really shooting for the etymology of translation. Was more or less trying to figure out what came before 'The Word' or 'God', you pick which (as they are the same). </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-23 14:07:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Exactly. Perhaps someone else fucked our prior universe up, then a period of intergallactic unrest took place followed by the appearance of 'The Word'. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-23 14:06:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I concur. The word of opportunity (hence the reason for my inquiry) is 'possible'. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-23 13:53:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> We as humans believe (in a narrow minded fashion) that a beginning has no prior ending. We thing when you begin anything, it's fresh and new. We are taught to believe this. Stepping outside the status quo, I believe something predates the beginning. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-23 13:51:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You can. Every new beginning comes from some other beginning's end. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-23 13:49:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That's what I am trying to get to the bottom of...what came before 'existence'? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-23 13:48:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Agreed. I'm assuming that there's no scientific means for there to be 'nothingness' then, one day, a still figure appears with Words to construct humanity. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-23 13:46:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's almost like The Buggles predicted internet video domination. Then, as you said, the internet predicted digitality. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-23 13:39:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Uncontrolled? Plenty of law enforcement and fire people nearby. Besides, the burning is some type of sacred ritual. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-23 13:16:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> According to CBS news last night, county deputies were arresting holdouts who stayed past 4pm deadline. Sucks that freedom of peaceful assembly rights no longer exist... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-22 22:45:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Wonder if the Juice is 'loose'? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-22 22:14:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'd assume that CIA involvement is imminent. North Korean defectors? Surprised to hear natives can fly out of Pyongyang in one piece these days, let alone to defect. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-22 22:10:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> ...and a fuckboy in a pear tree...lol </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-22 21:40:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Piss the boss off? Sticky situation... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-22 21:32:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I was imagining something more 'missionary'. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-21 21:33:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Either them, or Kim Jong himself. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-21 19:33:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Right? Guess that somehow slipped by Stephen Colbert, huh? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-16 12:58:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Your talking about Zuckerberg. His thinking is as unconventional as an unlicensed hotdog stand in front of Yankee Stadium. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-16 12:45:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> With so many new click bait sites popping up daily, human eyes are definitely needed. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-16 12:44:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Americans need Warren Buffet to step it up... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-27 16:48:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Most of them were fighting for this fate. They think a dishonorable death is the ultimate prize on their path towards Allahdom. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-25 21:06:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> They spoke about this (about nuclear facilities being cased out) last night on the CBS Evening News with Scott Pelley. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-25 21:04:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Let's put this in different terms.

Two men blew up a high traffic area in Brussels.
Suspect list up to 6.
Suspicious man has a suitcase.
Police shoot to avert another tragedy.
In mathematical terms (and all human rights aside), shooting one to save dozens (or hundreds) makes sense. If no explosives were found, at least that's one person to cross off a suspect list (and one less **possible** threat) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-25 20:39:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Due to our heightened state of panic, I guess people are 'shooting first, asking questions later'. Especially now knowing terrorists are shooting for our infrastructure and nuclear facilities. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-25 19:40:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Disgusting and inhumane, but most definitely true.  

I wonder if they use the garrote... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-25 12:37:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Umm...apart from maybe Kim Jong Un's hidden sex tapes, probably nothing. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-25 12:27:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Somehow I think a murdering pink leprechaun stands a much greater chance of survival than, say, a four-eyed pedophile corporate spokesman. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-25 12:08:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Some reports say they make prisoners fight over small rations of food. Wait. Maybe that's Mexico. Anyway, you're right - I'm sure the commissioner of prisons makes sure NK detainees (especially of American descent, or those who defected) are treated with the utmost uncouth methods. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-22 21:17:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> My biblical side votes pro-life for the sole purpose of repopulating the world.

My more sensible side tells me that if two people feel inclined to terminate the life of an unborn fetus (rendering you a piece of shit in my eyes), so be it. I mean, at the end of the day, they're the ones who felt inclined to not use protection - they're the ones who have to choke on their own vomit. Who are we to tell them what they can or can't do?

My even more sensible side says if Jared Fogle and Timothy McVeigh got to live, why not let anyone? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-22 14:05:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm thinking we start euthanizing those engaging in gross stupidity. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-21 20:00:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I would assume that they're enacting these rules to avoid that, yes. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-21 13:00:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> They're the 'hidden power of the world' in my view. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-19 20:38:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Lol.

I first read it as "Nerdanderthals" </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-19 19:20:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> How are the waffles? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-19 19:03:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The commercial says to seek immediate medical attention for an erection lasting longer than 4 hours. 

If I get an erection lasting that long, fuck the doctor...I'm calling Ripley's. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-19 19:02:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> "El Chapped Culo" </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-19 13:08:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's about as large as my pool, but a great nation nonetheless! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-18 19:57:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Fuck an orc, I'm all about the dryads and magical shit. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-18 19:43:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'd pay two goats to see someone beat his ass. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-18 15:44:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Me too. It's like wishing in one hand and shitting in another with these fucks. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-18 14:31:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I think the general consensus is to send in Dennis Rodman (with considerable Un experience) with a condom laced with dysentery and anthrax. If he'll fuck a kid, he'll take some of that Alabama black snake right up his brown eye. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-18 14:07:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I cannot think of anything we'd want to offer NK. I mean, they're already breaking sanctions by firing missiles like wild men. Do they want Pyongyang to be seen as a visitor's hub? Want our blessing or to dispel their stupidity? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-18 13:45:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Well, true, considering he WAS up inside Matuna (I mean Madonna). However, just to make sure, let's see to it Mr. Rodman's mini warhead is well stocked with anally discomforting diseases. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-18 13:42:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The Swedes? I mean, the ladies ski team is pretty fucking hot, but since when did they pick up collective bargaining skills? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-18 13:41:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm thinking a condom dipped in a mixture of dysentery and anthrax should do it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-18 13:22:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Exactly. I bet if he goes in and offers Kim Jong Un some unprotected sex, he'd get that boy freed in a hurry. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-18 13:01:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This had absolutely NOTHING to do with his crime, and EVERYTHING to do with sending a message to the American government: stay out of our business. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-18 11:46:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I think the whole "prank" was just to do it... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-18 11:45:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Ah, yes - the power of absinthe reveals itself again... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-17 22:35:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm wanting to know the 2016 version of "hard labor" - is it, like, pots and pans duty in a 120 degree kitchen? Hod carrying bricks? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-17 22:09:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Kim Jong Un: "Eat a Snickers, Otto:
Otto: "Why?"
Kim Jong Un: "Because you try and steal political propaganda when you're hungry" </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-16 21:34:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Apparently the Frenchmen aren't good gatekeepers. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-09 22:50:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Well, and that's the problem. These idiots are bringing a 'Hatfield/McCoy' situation to landmarks/fields abandoned by our government. **Occupiers** should go squat in Detroit or something... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-09 14:18:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> A nice nuke center mass in Somalia should cover that. I mean, since people are senselessly dying anyway, may as well take out Somali forces while you're at it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-09 14:04:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Correct you are, although this whole 'Holy War' thing is getting too far out of control. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-09 13:09:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Amen brother. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-08 22:20:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Dead or alive, he's still a child of God. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-08 22:19:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It appears so... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-08 21:58:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Nietzsche. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-08 21:58:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Smoking, although I'm about to round the corner... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-08 21:48:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Well, you know *some* Yahu is going to talk foreign policy before he exits, even though it may not be Netan. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-08 17:28:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Correct you are.

Seems as if though we'll need to pound that ideology into North Koreans sooner than later. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-08 17:05:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Exactly my point. *Nobody* </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-08 16:31:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> To my knowledge, surface to air missiles and ballistic missiles were totally the reason the deal was enacted in the first place, especially from a bipolar ally like Iran. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-08 15:01:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Have to understand how these journalists think.

The comma acts as an 'and'. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-08 12:47:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Demolition man </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-08 11:38:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It appears likely given our society is a shifting paradigm wrapped inside an evil conundrum. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-07 19:16:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Sanity </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-07 19:13:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> ...soon enough, El Chapo will get broke out... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-07 13:01:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> They're moving alot of people around to other prisons, but not officially hearing if Gitmo is done. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-07 12:55:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Our school mascot was a reaper (the old school crop harvester). Need I say more? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-07 02:58:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Rad!

The only noticeable damage I did to my sister's upbringing was total destruction of her NKOTB posters, tapes, bedding. And shirt, of course.
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-07 01:12:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I had several. In fact, I tried redoing my sister's beautiful little girl into one. Did NOT go over well with the parents given the fact they stood in line 5 hours in the 80's (just like you've probably seen in pictures) to get one. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-07 01:00:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The mechanical version of Garbage Pail Kids? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-07 00:48:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Sounds delectable - what is that? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-07 00:07:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> And we wonder why everyone thinks of America as the 'mecca of opportunity'. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-06 20:29:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Makes me wonder why we're a NATO country anymore since we seem to go rogue quite a bit where humanitarian missions are concerned. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-06 19:40:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Eating lunch with Trump I presume... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-06 19:30:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> "Heavy Metal (Takin' a Ride)" by Don Felder </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-06 19:08:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> GoBots.

Transformers seemed to have survived the 80s, GoBots really never took off. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-06 18:34:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Racial bigotry, IMHO, has less to do with color or creed and more to do with lack of formal knowledge of that which we choose to hate. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-06 18:31:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If there is a subreddit specifically set aside for those who'd wank on Kardashian dolls or Clooney pics, please keep me far, far away. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-06 18:29:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Ummm. Good question.

I'd say during The Prohibition Era. I mean, speakeasies would probably be raided daily if some moron posted pics on Facebook. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-06 18:27:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> /r/tifu </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-06 17:53:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Nancy was truly a decent First Lady, and will be missed. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-06 15:57:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> A well-funded Taliban, no less... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-06 13:40:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That's about as accurate of an account as I've seen!  :)

Your third sentence is exactly why every gas station, hotel and Oracle job is going to foreigners. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-06 13:33:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Maybe these immigrants view death as a worthy penance for a shot at freedom. You are correct in deeming Turkish officials 'incompetent', but some weigh the rewards of their effort against staying, and choose to accept death. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-06 13:26:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> 31 individuals won't get to enjoy life because some de facto holy bomber decided to shred himself in the name of Allah. The verbosity of these attacks is off the charts. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-06 13:01:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> No, it just means we'll all get shittier cocaine. Unmoderated. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-06 12:55:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Which sucks for humanity - but is just another day for the cartels... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-05 18:44:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> He'll also need to build one around the entire Gulf. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-05 17:09:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It would be easier if other countries would be more open to accepting people fearing for their lives. I'm sure plenty could fit in Lichtenstein or Luxembourg  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-05 14:31:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> His outlandish campaign tactics are paying dividends, indeed. Not that he can't self fund this whole escapade himself... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-05 13:04:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> With razor wire... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-05 12:41:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Absolutely. It's called 'take a boat to New Orleans'. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-05 12:40:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Somehow the movie Machete (the scene when they're showing the design plans for an electric fence) comes into play here. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-05 04:25:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> ...you can add the fact we're losing jobs, losing sleep, wasting money and (in egregious cases) losing pussy over some border jumper hungry for a taste of American pie. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-05 04:18:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Anthrax is cheaper than landmines. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-04 22:25:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What about the Canadians? I mean, if we're building walls and all... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-04 22:12:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Problem is, another report by CNN just stated he's scared and living in horrific conditions. Wants immediate extradition. Now, if I was Joaquin's son, I'd be gathering up some plans... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-04 22:09:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> "Hot" as in...wanted by Los Zetas? Or "hot" in terms of being the most sought after human being in existence? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-04 21:55:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> LMFAO...right?

Don't forget the thousands of 8 year old drug mules. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-04 21:48:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That is true. Tired of hearing him defend his 'endowment'. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-04 20:50:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> ..which surprises me that nobody is accepting the bribes he's offering. Maybe the Federales are sick of him. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-04 20:41:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> All the more reason to make sure Trump has a successful run. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-04 20:34:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> 40' high and painted with the same poison on those Amazonian frogs. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-04 20:22:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Wonder if Carlos Slim isn't helping him out... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-04 19:38:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> His son has vowed either revenge, a breakout, or both. Joaquin loves his drug money too much to take his own life, unless someone from Los Zetas makes him... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-04 19:37:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Almost sounds like something out of a Griselda Blanco movie... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-04 18:56:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It would be shocking if El Chapo doesn't bribe his way out before any potential extradition. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-04 14:56:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Not sure if it's new, maybe rehashed.

Nonetheless, I'll make sure to addendum this to my growing list of overseas duplicity. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-04 14:22:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The Civil War. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-04 11:44:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Well explained. Thank you.

I couldn't figure out if this was an attempt to siphon money from a major hotel chain, or a presumptive loss. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-04 00:58:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Well, some say it's doomsday because it will likely clear the path for Hillary to become president, which we apparently don't want. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-04 00:56:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Motorhead - Sympathy for the Devil </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-03 20:34:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Ummm...they get scammed by Trump University? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-03 20:32:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Probably have a masturbate-athon. While flying in a gulf stream jet with endless fuel. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-03 20:28:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The usage of "tragic" should be called to question.

Tragic in terms of an expected fate that was rather emotional? 'Armageddon'.

Tragic in terms of an unexpected scenario that turned south really quick? 'Devils Rejects'.
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-03 20:22:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Well, I'm OCD about cleaning house. Thanks to mom.

I'm content being alone. I have months of grounding to thank for that.

I have been completely self-sufficient for 27 years. I have many, many motherless nights to thank for that... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-03 20:19:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Not really, IMHO.

Acceptance is more of a widespread necessity in our younger years. As we age (present company included), the more 'set on our ways' people become. With that comes the attitude, "Don't like me, kick rocks." </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-03 20:16:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Bwahaha! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-03 20:02:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Van Halen's "Ain't Talkin' 'Bout Love".

How the first line goes: "I heard the news baby, all about your disease."

How I presumed it went: "All you loose ladies, and all about your disease"

(Listen to it. It's a plausible scenario) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-03 19:59:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Wearing your man's clothing is a symbol of comfort. By enshrouding herself in her man's garb, the woman is exuding her trust in you. Besides, some men's clothing just looks and feels better than women's. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-03 18:10:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Porn </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-29 20:15:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> ...and if you act now, we'll even *double your order* **free**! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-29 20:05:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Damn. Here I thought we could all learn to be anti-social and get an SSD check to boot... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-29 19:47:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I think if personal finance was a high school class, fewer Ponzi schemes and poor investment choices would be made. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-29 19:45:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Right? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-29 19:44:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Interesting. I may tend to agree since I learned most of what I know in terms of rules of the road by watching my parents. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
