<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject8120</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-05-21 04:05:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This draft was invalidated to me IMO after aj green went 2nd off the board... If it was Calvin maybe... But not with megaton still on the board.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-05-18 15:01:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I see what you did there.... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-05-17 22:30:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Gronk definitely will not keep his current ADP with all this news however. The risk is too great for a 2-3 round pick. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-05-17 18:02:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I use default yahoo waivers.

When the league starts the person with the 12th pick has #1 waiver and so on..

When they use the waiver they go back to last..
I've never had an issue with it.. It benefits people that don't make all kinds of waiver moves and managers benefit from just picking up on FA. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-05-17 17:58:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I also think if Geno wins out the QB battle that Ivory should be in for a good year as well. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Mike Goodson Arrested (NYJ) Christopher Ivory's stock to go up (more) b/c of this? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-05-17 17:49:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-05-17 06:07:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Pete rose that shit </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-05-14 04:58:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's too early to rate.. I think that's why every post of this kind I see is getting down voted...  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-05-11 01:30:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Any advise this early will just change when the season gets closer.. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-05-11 01:12:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I agree with this.. not because of Reggie... but in comparison Aaron Rodgers was still on the board.. I'd rather have AROD than Bush on my team in the 3rd round there. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-04-30 18:30:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thanks everyone for the advice </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-04-30 14:01:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thanks for giving me an answer and not just down voting my post. You are most likely correct. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-04-30 05:34:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's a fantasy football site.. Recommendations for draft and weekly advise.. It looks tempting... I just want to see if anyone here has used them before, </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Anyone use draft sharks? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-04-30 02:33:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm thinking about using it this year but wanted to see if anyone has had any good experiences.. Is it worth the 45 dollars?


Edit... Www.draftsharks.com </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-04-24 03:14:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Not sure how you survived sugar rush..... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-04-15 02:52:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Box fan </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-04-12 21:40:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I actually have a miniature pot belly pig.. I can literally hear that pig in the picture... However these little guys make awesome pets. (mine is only 50 lbs fully grown now compared to this one in the picture.)

EDIT.. forgot to mention this pig has probably shat itself from being picked up like this too... not joking. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-04-12 20:32:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Our league plays in yahoo as well.. It's just really user friendly to the non-technical people in our league. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-04-01 19:11:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> **Well be seeing a lot less of the dragons and direwovlves due to the new budgeting that will have to be done to compensate. But in the end its a small price to pay for this kind of acting gravitas....... **

This is when I stopped believing this story and looked at the date lol. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-03-27 03:07:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This is great to check out too.. I forgot about this. My mother had this and for the longest time the Dr's just kept on telling her it was anxiety.. Turned out it was actually her thyroid.. a good thing to get checked out just in case. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-03-26 19:35:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Got through it.. Took a .5mg of lorezapam before leaving to go there... Got numb and dizzy for a min like i was going to have an attack and then just went into my breathing exercises and didnt have anymore issues.

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-03-26 17:00:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Also, When you have a panic attack, your body sends all of your blood away from your extremities and into your core. My therapist told me it's because of the fight of flight symptom and when it does that it's bracing for an injury and most of your major organs are in your core area and your body wants to protect these at all costs thus the feeling of cold extremities and sometimes numbness while this is happening. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-03-26 16:51:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I had the same symptoms...

Make sure you cut out caffeine and limit your sugar intake... especially before bed.

When you wake up like that.. don't just lay there. Get up and do something for a few minutes... I know from experience that if you just lay there it will get worse. 

Try some breathing exercises next time you feel your heart pounding like that.... Breathe from your stomach and take deep breaths.. also through in one or two breaths where you hold your breath for a couple of seconds and slowly exhale.. It has a really great calming effect. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-03-26 16:47:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> yes.. I have the same urges... but therapy has taught me not to care as much about what people think about me so i've gotten better lately but I still find myself doing this from time to time. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Going to Dentist </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-03-26 16:32:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Haven't had to take an Ativan in almost 2 months, but im feeling really anxious today about getting a filling.. Should I take one just to make sure I don't have a panic attack and get calmed down before I go in? I just don't want to have a full blown attack while they have a needle in my mouth. But I also don't want to be dependent on this medication... What would one of you do in this situation? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-03-21 03:02:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Tineye had no hits as well </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [Request] Macho man merged with the dragon from the hobbit </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-03-21 02:36:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Not a big deal if it can't be done.... I've been searching on the inter webs... But am only finding skyrim dragons....with macho man.... I know it's silly but this would be awesome to see </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Optimistic Post (from r/fantasyfootball) </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-03-12 19:57:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-03-11 21:33:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Infiltrator all the way! When it gets real.... Cloak and gtfo... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-03-01 01:33:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Mass effect 1 and 2 should be 20 or under.... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-02-28 04:39:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's got to be the meth </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-02-16 03:09:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It amazes me how many times I play this game and still find something that I didn't see/hear before. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Breeding Requests </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-02-16 03:08:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-02-04 06:27:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Ravens win the Super Bowl ...and he's just sitting there masterbating... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-01-26 08:21:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Do mundane tasks... Like washing dishes... Yes get up and wash dishes or something.. If you are having an attack.. Let it happen.. Don't fight it..it gets worse if you are afraid of it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-01-24 07:20:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I've lived in tn my whole life and now had the epiphany that east tn is rednecks,middle tn is suburban, and west tn is gangster </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-01-15 06:18:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I don't have an answer to your particular question... But I think a better setup if you have 50 dollars or so is to buy a wireless range extender that has extra Ethernet ports to direct connect the Xbox. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-01-15 05:59:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Looking at your previous posts it looks like you just want things from people with giving nothing in return.. Maybe if this post gets 1400 down votes. I'd consider  giving you 1400 points.. Maybe </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-01-11 14:14:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Oh ok.. Says casual up there in your question. She made me want to cry when I played it on hardcore/insanity. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-01-11 02:46:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm going to sound like a db. But you are having issues on casual? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-01-09 03:38:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That's fine... we will take him. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-01-08 20:54:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I thought all "Men in Black" were humans? When did they start letting aliens into the rankings? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-01-08 18:24:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Also Amazon has this cheaper for preorder. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-01-08 06:22:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If you can tell it not to update you should clear the cache from the hard drive.. This fixes many issues and is worth a try. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-01-08 06:20:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This happened to my brother in law... They should really stop advertising about being able to do online gaming... Non tech people sign up for the service and then find out the hard way that it won't work.. We tried everything. Called support and they said it was a known problem that their engineers were working on..  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-01-08 06:15:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You will know when you can't get on live. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-01-08 05:28:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Faunts "M4 (Part II)"
http://www.youtube.com/watch?v=gISlB1IdUjI

When I finished ME1 and this came on during the credits I about died with excitement... I knew then that this series was destined for greatness.

also

ME2 Afterlife club music (I use this to work out to alot, it pumps me up)
http://www.youtube.com/watch?v=POHscfRZty8
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-01-07 23:08:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hey i just got those too. A fine selection. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-01-07 06:32:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I just ordered all the graphic novels (4)  for around 12 bucks a piece on amazon </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-01-07 06:21:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I just finished it as we'll.  I'll agree with everyone else... It's just the story of Vega's character. I'll be sure to listen to him on my next play-through now. Very happy with this though, I hope they make more. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-01-03 19:05:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> A long shot here.. But have you tried clearing the system cache on the hard drive and deleting the update from the hd? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-12-31 18:11:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Ask and you shall receive... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> You drink on New Year's eve do you? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-12-31 17:55:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-12-26 22:31:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Assassins creed </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-12-24 07:17:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yes you can.. But you have to do it from the Xbox in account settings. And you will have to know the old username and password combo.

http://support.xbox.com/en-US/billing-and-subscriptions/account-management/manage-microsoft-account 

Scroll to the last option. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-12-24 06:15:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> No. No. Execution all wrong.. Here let me help.
* I used to be Gandalf the white, but then I took an arrow to the knee.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-12-22 22:55:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Delete skyrim title update from your hd. Then clear cache of hard drive.  Hopefully that works </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-12-19 05:11:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That's it.... Someone make a Santa Claus Mod... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-12-19 05:09:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You and I.... we think alike. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-12-18 23:26:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> May be the settings within the xbox.. I'm not sure but i think you have to make sure it's set to the right resolution in the video set up </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Regret </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-12-17 04:22:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-12-16 18:19:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Not a player but defense... I've finally come to terms with TN playing monday night.. Hopefully i'll be ahead before then though. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-12-16 18:16:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I would like to know what ffsteroids think about TN defense as well
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Wdis pick 2 wide reciever woes </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-12-15 23:19:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Shorts vs miami
Britt vs nyj
Nicks vs atl
Garcon vs cle
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-12-15 21:46:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Doesn't powell have a broken toe? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-12-15 19:38:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I have yet to play one of these maps on another gametype... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-12-14 23:00:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I just picked up TEN as well... Hopefully.. "butt fumble" for TD. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> I feel I need to share this </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-12-14 20:30:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I feel i need to share this...

I found the panic away pdf from here http://www.reddit.com/r/Anxiety/comments/10y4nt/panic_away_program/ that was posted awhiile ago...

I'm not sure what happened but as soon as I read this and followed what it said (Basically letting the panic attack happen and not fighting it, observe and tell it you want more)

I was having attacks almost everyday.. Now with not being afraid.. (and I've started exercising..) I haven't had one in almost a month now...

I highly recommend everyone read that or buy the actual program.. Just by reading this for 10 min it has saved me from what was becoming a debilitating ordeal.

Thanks for everyone that supports people on this subbreddit as well it really is a great therapy. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-12-14 15:19:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> However they have been playing well over the last 5 weeks.. (exception to the Houston game) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-12-13 19:20:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Big thing with Cecil though is this http://i.imgur.com/kaZTA.png 

He may not play or be limited. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-12-13 18:58:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> on the left.. sorry </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-12-13 18:58:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> F... sorry on the left </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Week 2 of playoffs.. Any changes i should make? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-12-13 18:48:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-12-13 04:23:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The reason he did horribly week 8 is because the coaches were retarded.. They have been using Charles as they should now.. I'm not sure how many touches he got that game but I'm sure it was not enough. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-12-11 20:05:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> We have it locked when teams are eliminated.. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Should I drop Lloyd for Jennings? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-12-05 03:41:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> other WR are Nicks, Shorts, Garcon, Britt

Standard Scoring </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Who do i drop?  </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-11-28 15:32:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I need to pick up a defense.. Do i drop b.lloyd, antonio brown, kenny britt </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> I've been sending this quote to the people eliminated from playoff contention </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-11-26 21:05:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> "Winning is not a sometime thing; it's an all time thing. You don't win once in a while, you don't do things right once in a while, you do them right all the time. Winning is habit. Unfortunately, so is losing."-Vince Lombardi 


Sorry losers </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Anyone else starting to notice this about Brad Evans? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-11-23 22:32:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That he is looking more and more like "Andre" from The League everyday? His fantasy football logic seems to be on par with that as well. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> I just picked Garcon back up.. I recommend you do the same </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-11-22 23:52:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Fix this now 343 (CTF) </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-11-22 16:06:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> When I pick up the flag in CTF I am not supposed to be on enemy HUD's if I drop the flag you can show where the flag is... If it is in my hand.. Do not show it in HUD for the other team...It's simple, why would you mess with this from previous games? It's already hard enough to make it across the maps to even pick up the flag, now it's almost impossible to capture once taken b/c of this BS

/rant </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Matt Ryan Rant (To make him play better) </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-11-18 19:42:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Ok, that's enough... Let us downvote now... </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-11-13 23:06:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Please? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Yahoo issues causing dispute </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-11-12 17:37:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Ok so I need some input here a commish... Because of Yahoo issues yesterday one player did not swap out hernandez for Rudolf.. Rudolf was on his bench..however he does not tell me until this morning that he couldn't do out.. (says he just got my text then) by changing this i effect the outcome of the game.. What to do? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Yahoo... Why is this a tough matchup? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-11-11 17:23:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [Trade] My Josh Freeman for Hakeem Nicks? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-11-06 04:19:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I have Matt Ryan... and have no legit WR1... Antonio Brown... Kenny Britt...Brandon Lloyd... Santana Moss... Thoughts? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Request: Can someone make an avatar for fantasy football for Doug Martin? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-11-05 01:47:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Maybe a beefed up hamster with his face? I'd love to use this now. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Sneaky TE play this weekend... Dwayne Allen </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-11-01 23:06:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Ben Tate... Still worthy of handcuff? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-11-01 16:43:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Title says it all.. Is it even worth holding on to him at this point? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Jared Cook asking for trade from Titans </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-10-29 19:53:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Romeo Crennel </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-10-28 22:19:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Pretty sure this guy doesn't know how to coach a team.. Swapping out RB's every play is just stupid... (Jamaal Charles owner /end rant) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Need help with starting lineup (pick 2 of 4) </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-10-28 17:13:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> * Brandon Lloyd vs STL
* Kenny Britt vs. IND
* Brandon Stokely vs NO
* Vick Ballard vs TEN

Need help with my WR2 spot and Flex play </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> To every one that recommended Freeman over Cutler </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-10-21 22:12:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thank you very much sir! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Anyone else pick up vincent brown? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-10-17 19:44:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Just picked him up and stashed him for the future. I'm hoping he is the vjax of 2010.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> (WDIS) Jay Cutler @ DET or Josh Freeman Vs NO </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-10-17 17:44:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Cutler has been more consistant.. but Freeman is playing NO.. who to start for my bye week fill in? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Let's go Arian!! </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-10-15 04:20:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Chest tightness near shoulder and back? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-10-14 05:49:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So doctors tell me that I have general anxiety... But mainly its hypochondria I have started having tightness in my left side of my chest up near my collar bone and shoulder plus in my back I have popping with pain whenever I move in certain positions. Would anxiety cause this by tensing of muscles in these areas? Basically my worst fear is I have some sort of tumor etc.. But I've had multiple X-rays and nothing shows up... So now I've been having panic attacks more frequently bc I cannot stop thinking about my issues... Can anyone relate to this? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> WDIS Linup this week? Any changes you would make? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-10-11 19:39:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Trade review </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-10-10 05:05:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> 2 teams doing this trade.. one is a very savvy player the other is a newbie.. Is one taking advantage of the other? As commish does this meet acceptable criteria for a "fair" trade.. Both of these teams are 0-5.

Team1 trades
* Dez Bryant
* Mikel Leshoure
* Fred Jackson
* Garrett Hartley

Team2 trades
* Ryan Matthews
* Randall Cobb
* Kevin Smith
* Matt Prater </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> League champion of last year reduced to this. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-10-10 04:08:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Just when I thought I was a genius for drafting Doug Martin  </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-09-29 02:54:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [WDIS] PIT or DET defense this week? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-09-22 17:16:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> PIT @ OAK
DET @ TEN </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Ryan Matthews or Jamaal Charles </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-09-19 03:41:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Who would be the better option for the rest of the season?
Charles is hurt?
Mathews is coming back from injury..

I have Charles now.... should I look to trade for Matthews? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Down by 6.. Do I stand a chance.? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-09-17 16:25:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Score is 75 to 69...
My opponent has Peyton left
I have Matt Ryan and Jacob tamme..

What are my odds of pulling this off? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Foster leaves practice.... please tell me this isn't going to be a weekly thing... </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-09-13 14:32:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What stupid draft choices have you seen people make? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-09-03 02:00:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I just had my draft last night.. Everything was going predictably until the second round when guy drafts Darius Reynaud (TEN).... wut? Then goes ahead to draft the rest of the Titans..

What stupid things have you seen someone do in your draft? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Trade- Rashad Jennings for Tony Gonzalez </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-09-03 00:31:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I have Rashad Jennings and the MJD owner has Gonzalez as their backup tight end...

Should I attempt to make this trade? And will they take it?

My only TE is Jacob tamme at this point... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Internet Trolls Vote To Send Taylor Swift To Deaf School </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-08-31 23:42:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> I have first pick in a 12 man draft... I'm torn between Rodgers/Foster </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-08-31 20:11:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Would like some opinions on this

My league is a 12 team standard scoring
RB gets 1pt per 10yds/ 6pts per TD
QB gets 1pt per 25yds/ 4pts per TD -2 int

My main concern about getting rodgers is that there will be no stud RB left when my next pick comes around. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> WTF? Beverly Hills Chihuahua is number 1 in the box office?  </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2008-10-06 15:55:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
