<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject2991</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-30 17:48:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's weird seeing it cost so much! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-27 01:53:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Harrison ford couldn't look more like Han solo there. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-24 22:01:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Trauma and phobias are two different things, but both are debilitating in that they can result in severe avoidance of instances. Simply put:

Phobia is an irrational fear of something, usually developed over time by avoiding the feared thing. Avoidance makes the fear stronger, and treats it like it is as irrationally dangerous as you think. Doing so means it will usually seep in to other avenues of your life due to stimulus similarity - e.g. arachnophobia can lead over time to a fear of spindly legs etc.


Trauma is different, its a normal human response to an abnormal situation. It can result in flashbacks and severe avoidance of anything that evokes emotion similar to the traumatic incident. Over time the avoidance can again result in leaking effects on to other things - e.g. not going out at night after being mugged, becomes not going out during day either over time. 

Source: CBT therapist. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-24 21:51:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That first dog never stops tumbling. That's my kinda dog! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-24 21:49:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Pineapples </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-22 21:50:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Those darned illuminati. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-22 21:45:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> A simple explanation would be that normal sugar increasing in intake would result in an increase of insulin - leading to no longer feeling hungry.

Fructose doesn't cause the same reaction in insulin in the body, and is converted more readily in to fat (triglycerides). So not only do you not get the reduced hunger as you consume more, it is more easily store as fat in the body.

Bad times.

Edit: spelling </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-18 11:27:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Play PlayStation whilst holding a sandwich and a drink. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-17 22:16:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Avengers, ASSEMBLE! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-09 21:24:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Level 1: Destruction magic seems cool!

Level 30: Why do I keep dying!? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-26 11:55:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Omelettes. 

Even when you ruin its shape, still tastes pretty great. Can be done 100 ways! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-14 12:25:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Disneyland. Or any theme park.

Except I don't really hide my childish glee. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-14 12:15:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Actually knuckled down at school from the start, not half way through. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-11-17 20:42:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm fine, thank you. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-11-15 17:23:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> As soon as I start feeling guilty for my own laziness, that happened. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
