<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject6750</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-20 08:36:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Also.  Put flower or baby powder around the window and doors you'll be able to tell if someone's walked in or near. I'm going back to my oriental idea get a paintball gun and get your home alone game face on.  "THIS IS MY HOME AND I'M GOING TO PROTECT IT" stay up and aim at him his car whatever.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-20 08:28:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Shiiiiiit. Buy a stun gun online. Also turn off the WiFi at home, maybe this guy is cyber stalking you and your family.  Next time he's around try to do something to his car to make it more recognizable. Paint? Break a window from a far.  Make sure you're safe tho. Get all locks changed. Don't talk to anyone anywhere. I just want you to go back to college lol. I'm so annoyed for you.  Get the locks with the old school chains. Alarms on the windows. Um yea. I don't know. Try to get a paint ball gun those things hurt too. A bow and arrow a dog idk . Oo set up a spare Webcam at the entrance of your home and watch from your phone maybe you'll be able to recognize him.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-19 21:04:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Was the station equipped with security cameras?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-15 00:19:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This guy's kurdish, look at the flag.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-14 06:48:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Be ourrrrr guest! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-14 06:47:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Very very unlikely that she would be pregnant from that incident.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-13 10:23:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Disaster.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-11 05:37:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Neither is jebus, the tooth fairy or Santi clause. :/  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-10 06:14:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I work with a company that places bank levys. It will take a week or 2 to have the issue resolved dispite what the bank/collector tells you.  Cash your checks by a Third party. Anything that goes into your bank account will not be taken back out until the issue is resolved. Also might want to call your payees so they aren't charging your card and getting more fees once this is over. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
