<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject6922</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-26 23:51:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> We have this record - I love it and it creeps everyone out! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-26 23:49:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I don't think they'll leave you without any food, hopefully...  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-26 23:47:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I saw Paul Simon play Graceland 30 years after it came out in Hyde park. He had ladysmith, Hugh masekele, Jimmy cliff... It was amazing.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-26 23:43:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Power ballads </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-26 23:42:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Going to hell. I was terrified of it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-26 23:41:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Eurovision Song Contest. Every damn year. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-26 23:40:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> And then (insert person) died. At the end of the story. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-26 22:05:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Ah sorry, these were the ones I watched and didn't like </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-26 21:35:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> the good the bad and the ugly, blazing saddles, fistful of dollars, el dorado... 

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-26 20:02:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Cats </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-26 20:00:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Definitely - autocorrect just fixed it for me.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-26 19:55:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I think a lot of it is just jumping in. You'd be surprised at how little money you actually have to spend. Creative thinking, organic growth and hard, hard work were crucial. If you're flexible and find opportunities and say yes to everything you can start making money pretty quickly. I used savings for rent/food and invested time in the business. We have 2 incomes as my other half works which is obviously very helpful. We may not have gone out for dinner but I love what I do and with minimum spending the business became cash positive pretty soon! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-26 17:15:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Use charity apps like charity miles or ecosia search engine so you do something good by doing something you would have done anyway.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-26 17:13:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> In my pants after every sentence is good. Also gecko - someone yells gecko and the last person to have 3 limbs touching the floor or the wall has to drink </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-26 17:11:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I set up my own business after quitting and its been tough but I've learned far more from people and actually doing business than textbooks. I'm pretty positive about the future and I'm proud of my business. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-26 17:08:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> When they stormed out in a restaurant yelling at me for being selfish. For once I actually was selfish and didn't follow her. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-26 17:01:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm a vegetarian and my husband is too - he just kind of stopped eating meat when we moved in together. Now he's a total veggie but he said if he could have a lab grown steak he'd definitely eat it but wouldn't eat a normal steak. Which I thought was really interesting? Is it vegetarian meat?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-26 16:56:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm the same... I got to the beginning of season 3 and gave up. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-26 16:53:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The IT crowd countdown episode </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-26 16:46:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Our local pub is showing it on a big screen. Nothing more British has ever occurred.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-26 16:44:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> We live in a block of flats so never get any trick or treaters - I miss it! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-26 16:42:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Antwacky which is an old scouse word for old fashioned/out of style.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-26 16:40:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm kind of shocked still.. America has so many incredible people who have done incredible things and have awesome ideas - why are trump and Clinton the candidates??  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-26 16:37:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> We've had some real tragedies and hard times since our wedding and sometimes it seems like the only thing we've had is each other. But I think that the fact we have that and we are so together means that being married is AWESOME and has made unbearable times bearable.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-26 16:33:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Death in paradise </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-26 16:25:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Getting stuck in things... Lifts, water slides, in a garage, under a desk. It's like ridiculous claustrophobia.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-26 16:18:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thanks guys! I shall definitely watch a few  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-26 15:43:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> My father in law told his kids there were ice cream vans and pie vans and they both played music. So when they heard an ice cream van he's listen and be like "nope, definitely the pie van, it's got different music".  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-26 15:40:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I always thought San Francisco looked like a good place to live. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-26 15:38:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Make jewellery </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-26 15:36:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I watched the lady in the van recently and thought it beautifully suggested the stories and reasons why people end up on the streets. I've smiled and chatted to homeless people more. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-26 15:24:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The guilt trip  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-26 15:14:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Every breath you take by the police is terrifying

Every breath you take
Every move you make
Every bond you break
Every step you take
I'll be watching you
Every single day
Every word you say
Every game you play
Every night you stay
I'll be watching you </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-26 15:12:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Prime ministers questions  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-26 14:56:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> My hubby had an application form where he had to 'draw a picture that represents yourself and explain why'

He drew a batman symbol and got the job.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-26 14:55:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Inappropriate </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-26 14:54:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The godfather.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> I hate westerns: convert me? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-26 14:54:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I love films, but I just can't stand westerns. I've tried a few of the classics but they're just boring. Any brilliant western suggestions that will change my mind? Thanks!!  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-26 14:48:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Now it'd be far too expensive... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-26 14:30:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> And when they start drawing on a napkin or acting it out to make the point better. Yes for brains. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-26 14:27:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Noticing things about you and then mentioning them. Like ordering a drink with no ice because you don't like ice - makes you feel like a damn queen. Very attractive. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-26 14:24:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The fact that it may look like you're just staring a wall but actually you're reliving every painful moment in your life, you're hating everything about yourself, you're feeling every hurt in the world and you're going through hell in your mind. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-18 11:37:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> My mother in law is the best for this - buggering fuckbags is my favourite.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-18 11:13:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> My grandad used to always bring my grandma flowers after a walk to the shop. I went with him once and by the graveyard there was a big pile of fake flowers that had been thrown away like yours and he went and found the nicest bunch. My grandma always had lovely flowers and she never knew.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-18 10:48:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> We did the same! Me and My dad got all sorts of wood and wires and metal people were throwing away and we'd make furniture and toys with it. I thought it was totally normal to just take things out of skips and bins until I moved away to a red brick uni (like Ivy League) and my housemates were genuinely appalled. I had way cooler stuff though. Like a bar fridge.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-16 23:16:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Haha, it's okay until he tries to take the duvet off me in the middle of the night! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Our chihuahua made himself a blanket fort </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-16 21:35:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-16 18:34:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thai green curry. Winner. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Liverpool 1963 - my grandparents wedding </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-16 11:35:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-16 11:17:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Love a good jigsaw - also whenever there's one on the coffee table everyone has to put a piece in. You can't help it! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-16 11:06:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Putting on new clothes as soon as you buy/find them. In the middle of the road. Off a corpse you just robbed.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-16 10:55:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Painting apron with colouring in book. I was 16. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-20 04:24:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Definitely water street/ James street/ exchange flags </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
