<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject9619</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Lumia Camera on a 1520, never noticed the video record button makes a sound. I turned off shutter but its still on. Anyway to turn it off? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-13 02:26:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> My friend Allyse is trying to raise money to pay for housing while at school. I donated what I could for now, any help for her would be awesome! </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-12 16:28:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> My friend Allyse is trying to raise money to help pay for her housing while at college </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-12 16:16:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I dontated a few bucks, I don't have much to spare at the moment with trying to fix my car.  Here is a link to the page: http://www.gofundme.com/wr7uuk </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [Serious] What's the best way to help a friend that started a gofundme besides having her correct spelling mistakes and giving a few bucks? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-11 21:38:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> You will be missed Sir Christopher Lee </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-11 15:51:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> According to my roommate, our local weatherman looks like Tim Allen </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-11 00:20:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Mass snooping fake mobile towers 'uncovered in UK' </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-10 16:47:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Why do U.S. republicans have so many slurs for liberals? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-10 13:58:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I hear the slurs against liberals/democrats all the time on the radio, TV, and in comment sections of websites.  But there seems to be a lack of conservative/republican slurs. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> With facebook connect dropping from the people app and outlook, is there anyway to store the data and calendar events that are already there? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-09 22:42:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Autopsy - Lessons from Failed Startups (This website has short answers on why startups failed and links to more in depth articles) </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-09 16:50:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> So I guess this may be a dumb question: The Xbox One controllers can be updated?? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-09 16:14:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So I was reading about the new 1TB One and it mentioned wireless controller updates.  Have their been controller updates so far?  Does the Xbox prompt you to update them, because I've never seen it.  
  
Thanks for any info on this. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> U.S. tech companies expected to lose more than $35 billion due to NSA spying </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-09 15:15:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> South Korea tracks mobile phones in MERS battle </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-08 20:07:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Citizen gives shit to a sheriff/deputy (I think) about trampling the constitution, LEO was a former marine and in my opinion not an asshole. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-06 13:51:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Bell Media president says using VPNs to skirt copyright rules is stealing </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-05 16:46:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> A Bay Area Startup Spins Lab-Grown Silk </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-05 16:42:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Hunting for Hackers, N.S.A. Secretly Expands Internet Spying at U.S. Border </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-05 16:32:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> NSA said to increase monitoring of US 'Net traffic to catch ha </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-05 16:23:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Graphic Body Cam Footage Shows Killer Cop as He Murders an Innocent Unarmed Man [Since No Youtube direct posts] </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-04 22:57:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Measles Explained  Vaccinate or Not? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-04 22:52:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Pink Slips at Disney. But First, Training Foreign Replacements. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-04 17:39:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The characters http://: in a chat message can trash a Skype installation beyond repair [Says Metro style is immune] </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-03 22:15:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Six-year-old diagnosed with first case of diphtheria in Spain since 1986 </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-03 22:10:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Denny Hastert is Contemptible, But His Indictment Exemplifies America's Over-Criminalization Pathology </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-03 21:28:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Denny Hastert is Contemptible, But His Indictment Exemplifies America's Over-Criminalization Pathology </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-03 21:17:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [Serious] Why/When/How did the US Marshals get their power curbed? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-02 21:53:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The US Marshals were the sheriffs of the US, they could go into any territory, any state, any town and execute local and federal laws (no other federal agency can do this) so why are the relegated to mundane tasks of prisoner movement and catching escaped convicts (yes that is cool) but there is so much more they can do.  
  
Wouldn't the FBI/NSA/CIA/Homeland Security/Border Patrol all be way more effective if they were under the US Marshals purview? I've always wondered about the need for all of these other agencies when the initial declaration of the US Marshals makes them more than capable of doing all the tasks those agencies do.  
  
Thanks in advance for any history lesson provided. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Corruption is Legal in America </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-02 21:21:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [TOMT] Music video (late 90s early 2000s) with a man and woman sitting on a couch, there's a riot in the living room </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-02 20:29:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Ok, so the only lyric I remember is something along the lines of "You are the left eye, I am the right." and in the video there's rioters and at one point cops on horses ride through the rioters and for no reason there's a part where an ambulance makes a sharp turn and rolls onto it's side.  All of this in the living room area. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> So what's going on? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-29 04:12:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Any update after the memorial day test didn't precede? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Cortana only picks up what I say after trying again 3 times from the lock screen. Anyone else seeing similar performance problems? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-29 00:11:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Is there any way to get more than today's heart rate and more than a week of steps? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-28 13:33:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What an embarrassing American headline to see about FIFA </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-27 23:55:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Volvo says horrible self-parking car accident happened because driver didnt have pedestrian detection </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-27 22:57:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Does anyone else have an issue with the Band just sitting on connecting when trying to reply to a text? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-27 19:25:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It isn't all of the time, but frequent enough that it's annoying.  Should I restart my Band more often, as of now I hardly ever reboot it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Amazon prime promotional $1 credits, should I just buy everything individually? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-26 21:31:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So I've seen for a while you can get $1 towards rentals, mp3s, and game/movie/kindle book downloads, so is it worth buying everything one item at a time for the credit?  I noticed that it offers it to me only once on a bunch of items or if I buy only one thing. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Pimp my band, it says it saves the theme for future use but I can't locate this save to reload it. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-24 07:31:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Does it seem like you get a lot of Cortana (for those of you with it) weather updates? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-22 16:31:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I feel like everytime I check my band there are several Cortana alerts and it's mostly weather and it doesn't vibrate me whenever it's updated. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Teen pleads guilty to 23 charges of swatting, harassing online game rivals </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-22 15:29:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What was the effect of Rand Pauls 10-hour filibuster? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-22 15:02:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Hackers build a new Tor client designed to beat the NSA </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-22 14:58:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> PEMEX Refinery Explosion 19/9/2012 - alternative angle </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-22 11:22:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Are there any Bing bots for Windows Phone? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-21 19:52:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Hopefully a quick question, any "cheap" Windows Tablets/Laptops that take a sim card that you would recommend [X-post from /r/windows] </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-21 18:36:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm not looking for anything flashy, and by cheap I mean reasonable, not $1000 or I know what I'd buy.  Used is also an option, so if you're like, "oh this tablet from 2 years ago is beast, find it on Swappa or Ebay or something" that would be helpful.  
  
Thanks </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Hopefully a quick question, any "cheap" Windows Tablets/Laptops that take a sim card that you would recommend </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-21 18:07:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm not looking for anything flashy, and by cheap I mean reasonable, not $1000 or I know what I'd buy.  Used is also an option, so if you're like, "oh this tablet from 2 years ago is beast, find it on Swappa or Ebay or something" that would be helpful.  
  
Thanks </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Since Android and iPhone have them I'll ask here, any bing rewards bots for the WP? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-21 17:39:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Watch mode wrecks your battery </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-21 05:00:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So I tried watch mode for a week and it wrecks the battery life hard. Basically more than halved it. I am able to get 3-5 days without a charge, but with the watch mode on with auto dimming it barely lasts two days. That is all. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Texting while walking ends badly </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-21 04:28:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> How much do you think a used Lumia 2520 should be? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-21 03:52:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Fair to good condition.  I check eBay every once in a while and I'm just wondering what the people of this sub think knowing its only going to get windows 10 lite.  
  
Edit: I am looking to buy one, not sell. Sorry for the confusion. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Idiot father holding a baby gets hit by train </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-20 00:18:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Texas stops cities and towns from banning fracking - BBC News </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-19 23:02:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Battle to Regulate Uber, Lyft Moves From City Halls to State Capitols </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-19 17:24:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Trojanized, info-stealing PuTTY version lurking online </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-19 16:46:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Where it's heart rate data kept? I don't see it in Microsoft health or in the WP health app. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-19 13:29:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Just noticed they dropped Xbox Music pass and you get a $60 gift card instead. That's $40 less value than before. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-18 21:14:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> North Carolina sues FCC for right to block municipal broadband </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-18 20:16:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Obama Gives Shell Green Light for Arctic Oil Drilling </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-18 18:28:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Has the 1520 ATT gotten update 2 yet through the insider program? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-18 04:29:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> US Passport Agency contractor stole applicants data to steal their identities </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-14 18:17:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> How (and why) to write good documentation - RTFM </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-14 17:07:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> When adding or deleting a tile through the health app is there a way to avoid it clearing out my pimp my band scheme or the band flash light app? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-13 21:59:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Wearing my band while typing at work is carpotunneling me :( Does the band work in a pocket though? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-13 21:46:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I've been really enjoying the functionality of the band.  Unfortunately if I wear it while typing a lot at work it sometimes will rest on my wrist pad and cause me thumb cramps or outer hand/arm muscle irritation. Will the band still measure steps and such if it's in my pocket instead of on my wrist? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> I thought I read something about this but can't locate it, OneDrive app is at 2gb, WTF? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-13 18:27:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> My OneDrive app shows 1.98gb on my storage sense app.  I thought I read a post discussing this issue but I can't locate it.  Any help would be apprectiated since my 1520 is the 16gb version and between maps and the OS I only have like 5-6gb to spare.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Verizon and Sprint to pay $158 million for cramming charges on customers' bills </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-13 18:09:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Americas Changing Religious Landscape </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-13 17:33:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The Pledge of Allegiance </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-11 04:11:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Iranian Kurd father kills 3 daughters </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-10 22:49:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> So, second call? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-10 19:34:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Any news about Xbox 360 playability coming to the One through the preview system? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-09 19:35:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Man brings his 7 month pregnant wife along for an open carry demonstration - large police response </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-08 21:41:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> He intentionally looks for a cop to harass </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-08 19:47:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Pointless, so pointless: [Open Carry AR-15 Into Police Station PT.1] </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-08 19:34:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> This guy wants to run for "Federal Congress in Washington" </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-08 19:11:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The man who wants to outlaw encryption </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-08 18:41:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Main screen used to show steps but now shows miles </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-08 18:34:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Is it random which it shows or does it change? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> I wish it came in extra large... </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-08 17:15:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I've got some wrist fatigue/numbness on my left wrist from wearing the band the last two days.  Similar to when I ride my motorcycle on the highway for a week straight to and from work (so an hour each way) and I get numbness/muscle weakness from holding the throttle down.  
  
But I wish I could make it a little loser sometimes and still wear it, the hard sides press a little tight even on the loosest setting. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> PSA - So having some solo joystick time counts as a heck of a lot of steps. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-07 22:59:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> POLICE SHOOTOUTS [BODY-CAM] WARNING GRAPHIC FOOTAGE - Not all are deaths but many are </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-07 21:58:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Is there a way to move a file like a video from the SD card to OneDrive without a computer? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-07 03:48:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hoping it's something simple or an app.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What are the vertical cylinders next to the doors/hood on Peterbilt trucks? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-06 15:20:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I've tried googling, binging and diagrams online but I just can't find out what they are. And no, not the gas tanks under the door. Also I'm sure other semi trucks have them, but I mostly see them on Peterbilts. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Man jumps out of window of burning building [NSFW] </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-05 02:20:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Who Pays When The DEA Destroys Your Vehicle And Kills Your Employee During A Botched Sting? Hint: Not The DEA | Techdirt </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-01 21:27:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> So my doctor told me to get a fitbit, but I'd rather have a band, and I have some ?s for users. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-01 18:08:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I know the Band does basically the same stuff, heart rate, pedometer, etc, I also have a couple Windows Phones so the band integrates with Cortana and such.  
  
Since the cost difference isn't very high I think the band would be a good way to go, does the Band do sleep monitoring too?  
  
Do any of you regret buying the band over a fitbit?  
  
Is there a new version on the horizon that should make me want to wait?  
  
Has anyone bought a used one before, any issues?  
  
Thanks in advance to any responses. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Second ever super-rare pocket shark discovered </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-01 16:42:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Screen sharing has come to the Xbox One as an app - couldn't connect my 1520, but the 635 worked straight away </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-01 16:27:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Preview for Developers is on the Xbone now, and even though it's in beta it worked really well with one of my phones. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Court Orders UK ISPs to Block Popcorn Time Sites </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-01 16:18:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Music Streaming Website Grooveshark Shuts Down </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-01 16:12:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> New screen sharing app on one only works with one of my phones, same OS </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-01 12:40:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So I have windows phone 8.1 specifically a 1520 and a 635, for whatever reason the more powerful phone keeps failing to connect, the $30 toss away phone connects fine. Lol </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> WW2 Japanese sub's long-lost airplane hangar </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-30 18:45:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Submersible photographs WW2 Japanese sub's long-lost airplane hangar </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-30 18:42:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> I never realized how slow Map apps load without downloadable maps </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-30 14:55:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> My buddies Android phones and iPhones take forever to get directions, my only wait is basically for traffic to load or for Cortana to open the app.  
  
Also, when I pull up my commute through Cortana she routed around traffic to a road I never take to work. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> We have to cover these new Win 10 annoucements with the phone integration. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-29 21:46:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [X-Post from r/XboxOne] New Xbox One Miracast Preview in Action: Android and Surface test : xboxone [might be able to push games to WP 10] </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-29 18:49:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Is Windows Phone's real problem that it's Microsoft? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-27 22:13:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I think the question explains itself.  I see constant posts and comments from people saying they need a new flagship (even though their oldest ones are still competetive (I think people just want newer things and I don't blame them)) or that their aren't enough apps.  
  
In my years with iPhones and short stint with Android the volume of apps are worthless. What really seems to be the issue is the few apps people want.  Snapchat, whatever other 3rd party supportless apps their are, and google apps, but most of these companies are waging a war from the 90s and early 2000s to hate M$.  If snapchat either allowed 3rd party apps or built one then half of the complaint posts would disappear and a lot of people on here would have convinced their friends to buy WPs.  
  
What I'm getting at is that most of the articles posted on here show that these companies or CEOs ust have something against MS the company.  It's really an image thing, and MS needs to correct that to correct it's other issues. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> One minute review or discussion </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-26 18:48:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Maybe it would be fun to have a super fast review or discussion over small things or apps. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> WhatsApp notifications, nonexistent? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-24 21:12:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So I'm trying to use What'sApp to talk to a friend in another country and I'm not recieving notifications.  In the settings of the app they are on with tone 5 or something and it is set to run in the background.  Any info would be appreciated. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> How scared do you think car companies and cities are of millennials not driving and requiring good public transit? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-23 21:55:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Watch an angry Robert Downey Jr. walk out of the worst Avengers interview ever </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-23 20:39:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Why one-way streets are bad for everyone but speeding cars </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-22 21:36:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Some tech firms being 'friendly to terrorists' says UK police chief </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-22 20:40:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Some people seemed concerned over Enterprise use on the WP. Device Guard seems to cover it. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-22 20:34:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Apps that don't work from the SD card...(add to the list) </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-22 18:29:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Realarm doesn't seem to work form my SD card.  I moved every app I could to the SD card yesterday (this was an accident, but I decided to see what would happen) and I added an evening alarm to Realarm which worked fine but this morning it didn't go off, I had two set.  
  
Also, On This Day's app and the built in News app live tile doesn't seem to update.
  
Some apps like the Universal Windows BBC app still seem to work from the SD card. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Does unbiased journalism really have the power to sway votes or do people simply seek out articles that support what they already believe? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-21 20:04:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Any sources to back up assertions would be great but not needed.  
  
Thanks. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Is the option to store map data on the SD card gone? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-21 18:16:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> After my reset a few quirks I noticed on my phone, I have maps on both my SD card (don't know how though) and my phone, deleted the phone one, but offline doesn't work with maps so I deleted the maps data on my SD card too (lost my commutes for some reason).  I'm just really confused about how the maps were still on my SD card after my hard reset like 2 weeks back yet don't work.  Now I'm gonna have to check my 635 too.  Do the map updates save to the SD card? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Questions about hard resets and the SD card </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-21 17:47:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Has anyone been able to do a hard reset yet not reinstall all the apps that were on the SD card?  Everytime I do it tells me the SD card is from a different phone and formats it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> "People" will be confused - the Lumia low end story </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-15 16:42:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Everytime a new phone gets release I read the comments here and on the websites they link to, even MS's own.  There are a lot of positive comments, but you'll always see folks complaining that "people will be confused."  
  
Who are these confused people?  I don't know, I don't think they exist outside of the folks that are actually confused and use "people" to describe themselves.  It's the "hey doc, my buddy says it pees when he burns" style of lying.  
  
Most people will look at the phones and see the different price points and base their decision on that.  When I worked retail that was my most common expierence.  If the prices were close and the packaging didn't really tell a difference in specs they would ask questions.  Usually it boiled down to quality differences like a plastic pop off back versus a nice removable back for instance.  
  
It just seems ridiculous that a lot of comments I see reflect this when overall the system makes sense.  I think the last few itteration of phones muddied the waters, but the XL thing and the X40 line of models will be more cohesive to be able to quickly look at the model numbers and get an idea of the quality and specs.  
  
I mention this mostly because of the 540 dual sim - the phone looks great in the pics, but that's my opinion.  I went to the MS store link from this sub, and even there most of the comments were positive, with a few complaining the specs looked like the 640 and now they don't understand.  Those people are clearly the one like on this sub that look more into the specs and try to find a value in a second, third, etc. phone.  Sure, some consumers do that, but from my years working selling phones and helping friends buy phones they either want the "best" phone regardless of price, the one they can afford, or the cheapest cause they just need a phone that works.  
  
Summary:  
I just feel like most of the commentors about the "it's so confusing" either haven't taken the time to look at current models and include too many past releases etc and get rightfully confised, or they themselves are just confused and want to see if others are too.  And sure lots of people get confused over this, but looking at recent phone releases and trends it looks like MS is making the numbering system make sense.  But we'll have to wait and see if I'm right. ;)  So chill out people, enjoy the ride. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Why oh why does Windows Phone backup and restore toy with me so? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-14 04:10:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So my phone said last backed up 9 hours ago while I was at work. Cool. Got home and forced a backup. Hard reset my phone, selected the backup with today's date, and it's like a restore from several months ago. The fuck? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Quick question on hard reset after trying to get update 2 </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-13 22:36:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So I tried the method of enrolling in preview, fast, uninstalling app, searching for updates, and the only one there is 10 TP, not the 8.1 update 2.  So now my phone prompts me there is an update and I turned off automatically install.  But my question is when doing a hard reset can I restore from backup?  I have a backup before I tried so that'll work fine for me, but if I do another backup when I get home, and use that one, will that mess it up? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Which time periods won't they do? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-11 21:56:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Sorry I'm on my phone and couldn't find it in the search or online, but didn't the developers say there were some time periods they wouldn't do? I'm talking to my buddy about the series while we drive. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Who else goes caseless? Why or why not? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-07 20:20:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I had a pretty nice case for my Lumia 1520.  I bought it and got it before I had my phone knowing about the screen bending in the pocket and popping out and I didn't like the camera resting on the table.  
  
(Funny that Apple didn't even look to the competition for issues with large phones)  
  
The case was nice, but I really like the phone without it and whenever I pulled it out of the case to show off people were impressed by the feel, the lightness, everything.  So now I just roll with my screen facing away from my body so it bends the other way and stays working.  
  
So do you go caseless or not?  And why?  
  
PS my 635 is caseless too ;) ooolala </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> 'Brontosaurus' name resurrected by new dino family tree </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-07 18:17:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Hawaii 5-O, which voice recording app did they use? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-04 22:28:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> As many people know Hawaii 5-O is heavily funded by microsoft, the cast even uses a microsoft surface table. Anyone watch last weeks episode and see the app? I'll post a picture/video link in a bit if anyone doesn't know off hand. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> 1520 and lock screen passwords </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-02 23:56:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's almost like why the fuck? Anyone standing within 50 feet can clearly see which numbers you hit. There either needs to be a smaller pad or a pattern or something that's more hideable. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Which reddit app sucks your battery away faster? Vote in my poll </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-02 18:08:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> http://vote.pollcode.com/93341657 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Trying to read through older posts to figure it out, Youtube App (3rd Party) question </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-31 18:12:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Ok, so I was trying to search through but it seems like the issues come and go. Which YouTube apps are working right now? (Not the one that links to the website, and why does the website look so shitty on our phones?)  
  
Also, do any of the YouTube Apps support pushing?  I use TubeCast right now. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> SIM cloning question </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-31 06:14:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So I have a few questions, this all stems from AT T not being able to register a phone as a data only device from my tablets SIM card.  
  
I want to copy my SIM, not to try to use at the same time, but for convience. I'd like to use my smaller phone either as a GPS/Internet device in my car or at work and my other tablet at home or if I go somewhere that I need it. For whatever reason AT T is unable to let me use the SIM from the Tablet in my secondary phone. They said I'd have to terminate the tablet contract (it was $0.99 plus 2 years at $10 for connection), pay the termination fee, then start a new connection plan or $15 a month plan for the secondary phone. Normally I've been able to and can switch my SIM card from phone to phone sometimes using a sim adapter because of SIM size issues and the phone works fine regardless of contract or not.  
  
So what I now want to do is create a copy of my phones sim to use in my secondary device. I know that only one can work at a time, etc. so that won't be a problem (the secondary phone is better to have while riding my motorcycle) it's just about not having to take the SIM out, risk breaking the SIM card tray or the card itself.  
  
If you stuck by this long we're at the questions:  
  
Are there any all in one cloning tools/kits that are less than $50 out there that will work with newer SIM cards? Mine has NFC ability so I know it's more encrypted.  
  
If not, is there any software compatible with MAC OSX that can handle the more heavily encrypted SIM? I haven't upgraded to Yosemite yet (I actually haven't used my computer in two years, between two tablets, a phablet, a phone and my work computers I don't really like using a computer at home).  
  
Since I'm not trying to just copy contacts and need a working SIM what SIM do you recommend?  
  
Should I get another AT T NFC enabled SIM to write over or is there a 3rd party I can get it from?  
  
Yes I know that AT T could detect the 2nd SIM, but if they cut my service I don't care, just means I won't pay any termination fees. Like I said, I'm just trying to avoid having to dismantle cases and covers everytime I want to switch devices.
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> SIM cloning questions </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-30 22:14:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So I have a few questions, this all stems from AT T not being able to register a phone as a data only device from my tablets SIM card.  
  
I want to copy my SIM, not to try to use at the same time, but for convience.  I'd like to use my smaller phone either as a GPS/Internet device in my car or at work and my other tablet at home or if I go somewhere that I need it.  For whatever reason AT T is unable to let me use the SIM from the Tablet in my secondary phone.  They said I'd have to terminate the tablet contract (it was $0.99 plus 2 years at $10 for connection), pay the termination fee, then start a new connection plan or $15 a month plan for the secondary phone.  Normally I've been able to and can switch my SIM card from phone to phone sometimes using a sim adapter because of SIM size issues and the phone works fine regardless of contract or not.  
  
So what I now want to do is create a copy of my phones sim to use in my secondary device.  I know that only one can work at a time, etc. so that won't be a problem (the secondary phone is better to have while riding my motrocycle) it's just about not having to take the SIM out, risk breaking the SIM card tray or the card itself.  
  
If you stuck by this long we're at the questions:  
Are there any all in one cloning tools/kits that are less than $50 out there that will work with newer SIM cards?  Mine has NFC ability so I know it's more encrypted.  
  
If not, is there any software compatible with MAC OSX that can handle the more heavily encypted SIM?  I haven't upgraded to Yosemite yet (I actually haven't used my computer in two years, between two tablets, a phablet, a phone and my work computers I don't really like using a computer at home).  
  
Since I'm not trying to just copy contacts and need a working SIM what SIM do you recommend?  
  
Should I get another AT T NFC enabled SIM to write over or is there a 3rd party I can get it from?  
  
Yes I know that AT T could detect the 2nd SIM, but if they cut my service I don't care, just means I won't pay any termination fees.  Like I said, I'm just trying to avoid having to dismantle cases and covers everytime I want to switch devices. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Found this Nachos Bell Grande in my driveway Sunday morning. No one from the night before will own up to leaving it there... </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-30 17:38:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Weird color distortion with Lumia refocus </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-30 04:43:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Here's the regular picture:  
http://1drv.ms/1NsFldZ  
Here's the refocus picture:  
http://1drv.ms/1xNGTO1 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> I upgraded from a Lumia 1520 to a Lumia 635 for only $30! - Boy what an upgrade!! </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-27 20:28:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Going through by hand overwriting my comments, yaaa! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> I was hoping for a weather answer, but Cortana is too literal </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-22 23:40:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> If everyone voted democrats would win </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-19 18:44:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Has anyone looked at all the MS apps in the SysAppPusher app? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-18 15:39:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> There are a lot of apps like messanger+ and nokia chat that do what imessages does, but apparently weren't released or limited or something.  I find it neat to look at the apps not available for my phone but were created that do the things people in this sub wish they had an app for. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Thought this sub might enjoy this - One time use monocles </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-16 19:00:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> So my alarm just vibrated this morning, no sound. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-16 10:11:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Usually I have one of those sleep sounds app running during the night. I've never had any problems until like two or three days ago and then this morning. My alarm just vibrated and didn't sound like it usually does. Any ideas? I don't have quiet hours enabled. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> With Cortana coming to IOS [x/post microsoftband] </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-14 20:27:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Anyone else worried that iOS and Android will get a better version of Cortana? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-13 18:31:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> People on here are always complaining that their version of the windows apps are better.  They have here maps, soon Cortana, WP is losing a lot of the things that make it unique and nice. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Cortana coming to iOS and Android - will it still be MS Band exculsive to get band sales? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-13 17:59:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Your thoughts?  Are you excited for those without WP? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> So the 635 is $30 and I ordered one, but does anyone have a waterproof case they'd recommend? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-13 16:15:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I ordered a 635 since they're so cheap (guessing to clear stock for the 640). I'm going to use it while riding my motorcycle, but I'd like a water proof case for it, does anyone have any recommendations with some real world use?  If there are handlebar mounts for the case like Lifeproof has that would be a huge bonus. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Possibly the most helpful webpage for windowsphone I have ever found, scroll to top, translate a page, etc. All through IE using the favorites function. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-12 17:37:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The resuming screen - a solution </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-12 17:08:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> iPhones and Androids both hang up when launching apps or going back into something, especially a larger app.  The only difference is that the phone doesn't let you know it's working, it just hangs up then loads.  Yet the same thing happens on WP and their courteous enough to let you know the phone hasn't froze.  People who complain about resuming screens are pathetic.  But here's the solution, just let the phone "hang up" for a moment and then it's solved. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> L1520 Hey Cortana with glance screen always on </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-12 03:05:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The title fills in a lot, I'm trying to see if Hey Cortana will work without the phone plugged in or on the lock screen or in the phone. I thought I had done it with peek, just wave my hand and say hey Cortana. But I couldn't get it to work today so I set glance to always on. And it worked a few times but stopped. Has anyone else noticed weirdness with Hey Cortana? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Huetro for Hue app, geofencing </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-10 19:38:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I have remote access turned on and geofencing on, but it doesn't seem to work.  Has anyone else had success? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Live tile update frequency </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-09 23:39:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Does anyone else wish their live tiles updated more frequently? The MSN news app feels ultra slow now, but I wish it would change more frequently with other news stories. Readit gives me post updates but they're hours old. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Vote this up please - A TileArt or Tile Layout shareable app/feature in Windows User Voice </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-09 21:23:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Closing the gaming gap, but only sort of mentions mobile (Surface Pro) :( </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-06 19:26:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Star gazing apps </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-03 19:38:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hi, anyone kow of any stargazing apps that are easy to use, I don't need to set up a telescope with it.  If anything I'd like it to link or have built in stories of the constellations (the more versions the better).  Thanks to anyone that helps. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Seems that gestures broke on Denim </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-03 04:01:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Went to complain through the app and there seem to be hundreds all ready there.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Xbox One Smartglass </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-02 01:55:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Anyone else use this app? I have both the beta and regular app, but on both the remote for the cable box isn't working. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> 6tin, anyone not getting notifications? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-26 21:46:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> New matches, messages, etc and I'm usually logged out when I open the app.  Anyway to keep it logged in? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Hoping this thread gets popular - Your Favorite Games (more obscure the better) </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-26 17:08:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So I took a look with a quick search and it's been 6 months since a proper game thread.  What are your favorites, any gems that might be hard to find?  Use the "wpapp[name app]" to help us find these games.  I'm always willing to give a game a try. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> SquadWatch - got it working </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-25 22:30:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> But I only know one other person with a windows phone... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> AC Liberation for Xbox 360 - Uplay link </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-25 21:52:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I couldn't find info while searching so hopefully someone here knows the answer real quick.  I have AC Liberation for 360, is Uplay linking not a thing for this version, can you play the Connor mission still?
Thanks in advance. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> LG g pad 7.0 AT T mirror to LG TV </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-19 22:05:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hi all, so I got a free LG g pag 7.0 when I purchased a smartphone from AT T.  For a low pudget tablet it's pretty good, just expanded it with an SD card.  So here's my question, is there a way to easily mirror or send what is on my g pad (like a movie or better a game) to an LG TV?  I have the LG smart app or whatever but it doesn't seem to have any real functionality besides crappy apps/games or something. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Didn't see it in the search so - the Lumia 636 and 638 phones, do they work in the US? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-18 21:07:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Cortana and traffic </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-16 23:47:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Weird question/discussion - Best WPs not sold in the US that would work here </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-12 22:03:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So I'm on AT T, but I like the idea of a back up phone or one for the preview build, I've looked at a lot of Windows Phones and in the states on either amazon or ebay I've found a few decent ones that are $100 or less new/used (doesn't matter if the screen isn't cracked). But it got me thinking, what WPs are outside of the US that I could be missing out on? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Cortana - Facebook and Twitter </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-10 23:51:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm pretty sure I had Cortana post a tweet before, but now I can't get her to do that or anything facebook related. I tried searching Bing with Cortana, but that didn't give me any results I wanted. Any ideas fellow WP users? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Account was banned - any advice? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-09 21:42:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hey all, hoping for some advice.  My bing account was banned, but I don't do any of that botting or mulitple IP thing.  Except my work's IP says I'm located in San Fran where our headquartes is, not here on the East Coast.  I have a windows phone and an Xbox One (and a hardly used 360) that my accounts are linked up to.  I sent an email to their customer service, but I was looking for any advice if they respond with a blanket statement and no real reason. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Dead Kings DLC - multiplayer not going online </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-08 23:22:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So for some reason when I'm playing the dead kings dlc the two multiplayer missions only allow me to do a local play. Is anyone else having this issue? I tried a search from my phone but couldn't find anything if this is a known issue.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> App search help - Tile Header App </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-08 20:52:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I remember someone saying they created an app that let you make headers or something like it to help sort out your start screen. I'm trying to get my sister to use windows phone and and I think this will help.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Lumia classic camera app - video not recording </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-08 02:37:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> 1520, the built in camera app will record videos but for some reason the Lumia classic camera app won't record. I click out, the button is red as long as I hold it but doesn't record. The cemera works fine though.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Hawaii 5-O was windows phoned out this week. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-07 17:21:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I wish I had taken some shots of it and knew the phone model. Windows products are heavily advertised in that show from the interactive table that actually exists for thousands of dollars, lol, to the phone car syncing.But I've always laughed about how obvious the in show ads are. "Don't worry guys, my windows phone will sync to my new Chevy Cobalt in Bow Tie Blue an exclusive new color for the 75th anniversary of Chevrolets' OnStar system and I can track the car with this awesome windows phone OnStar app, and then we can turn the engine off with the help of the friendly and courtious OnStar reps." "Great Kono, lets go." </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Any other Philips Hue apps? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-07 13:52:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I currently use wpapp[Huetro] but it constantly forgets my lights recently. Are there any other hue apps that you can recommend? I have apps loaded on my old iPhone, iPad and LG tablet, but I like being able to turn the lights off as I'm leaving our on as I get home. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Does this annoy anyone else? - Cortana related </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-05 22:59:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> When I click my glowing flipping Cortana tile of course Cortana pops up and gets things ready.  The reason I clicked on the tile was from a news alert that alert is in the top area with a news icon in your scheme color. What gets me is that when I click that icon I'm not taken to that news story, but to the news app or some other page that it's from and then I have to sometimes hunt for that article. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Taking photos with a Lumia - at night </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-03 21:38:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Ok, so weird question (maybe there's another sub for it); but with your Lumia phones (I have a 1520) what settings have you found the best for trying to capture the night sky?  Or an photo apps that do it well? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Can you project your phone to Xbox one? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-30 03:11:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I think the title sums up my question :) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> If enough of you contact Chase or BoA they might keep the app. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-29 20:28:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Calling and letter writing to the office of the president can have results you'd never think of with banking.  I work for another large bank, and if we recieved a letter to the office of the president there was a special team assigned to look into it.  If several of you (10s of you) took the time to post an actual letter they might continue support for the app. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Snapchat - is it a big deal? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-29 18:43:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Personally, I know only one person that uses snapchat and I don't talk to her anymore.  Is snapchat really that important to so many people or just folks on reddit? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Still looking for My Commute help </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-28 02:17:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I've uninstalled and reinstalled Here Drive+ deleted all commutes and set up my commute to work with a return time. If I'm lucky my commute updates for the return journey. Cortana has only mentioned my commute once. I've turned her options for reminding me to go to work etc from my calendar and she doesn't do that either. I have the address in the appointment daily for work. Any help would be much appreciated.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> HELP! - My battery life is too awesome. Plus a shameless app plug through pictures </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-26 18:54:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> http://imgur.com/TCiRjTu
http://imgur.com/GIMltuv
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Sister needs a new phone, introductory windows phone search </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-25 18:44:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So I'm going to give my sister an introductory windows phone, I figure a used one in good condition would be best. Then if she likes it I can help her get a nicer one. So far I've been looking at the 920s trying to stay below $100, closer to $50 would best. Thanks in advance for any advice.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> 1520 and gloves - What they heck? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-23 16:02:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So whenever I wear some thin gloves (I have them for driving and walking short distances in the cold) and I try to use my phone it recognizes the taps or scrolls, then when I stop it goes crazy selecting or tapping or swiping words.  This only happens outside or in my car while it's cold.  The second I take my thumb out of the glove and use it it's fine.

 nbsp;

I figure it has something to do with the cold, I just tested it at my desk and it seems fine.  But it doesn't make any sense because once I use a non-covered finger the weird clicks and scrolls stop. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> X-Post for help, anyone know of a fix? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-21 20:16:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Help - Location based Cortana Reminders </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-20 17:11:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hi all, so I ask Cortana to remind me of things when I get home, but I live about 1/2 mile or so away from the main road where Cortana figures my address to be (it's also a little off).  I can't find a way to set my homes address/location based off chosing on a map or by "find location."  Am I missing something or is the only thing you can do is manually enter an address?

 nbsp;

Side note - I do not get a signal near my house, or up to a few miles away, so I have a microcell at my home.  This is really why I need to change the location reminder because Cortana (WP) doesn't seem to be able to associate my closeness and activate reminders. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Pop and circumstance over Google Translate, but WP Translator by MS already does it </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-15 22:59:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So I've read a few articles about how google translate now does voice translation and pictures can be translated, but the Windows Translator already does this stuff, yet no one seems to care :(

http://www.theverge.com/2015/1/15/7551061/google-translate-app-ios-android-hands-on </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Gestures Beta - Hey new people! </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-15 19:08:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So I'm sure that this has been posted about before, but if you're new to Windows Phones try the app wpapp[Gestures Beta] (I don't know if the bot will pick this up so I put a link at the end).  It's super sweet, it picks up calls when you hold it to your ear, lay it down face up while on a call and it puts it on speaker, flip it over to it's face and it mutes the call but leaves it on speaker mode so you can listen. 


http://www.windowsphone.com/en-us/store/app/gestures-beta/38384829-0b39-4f21-a954-d2d4f8a4ac96 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> My Commute App - only working sometimes </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-15 18:56:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Does anyone else's My Commute app not actually work?  Mine will update around the time I said I return from work (I did the trip style commute with when I leave and when I return).  But it won't update in the morning for my drive to work and Cortana never alerts me that traffic is bad and I should leave early. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Skype as video calling app for 1520 help... </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-14 23:16:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So I was looking through my settingsapplicationsphone and saw that I did not have an app set for video calls, I clicked the get app button and Skype came up, already installed too.  I checked skype, it's all set up and I've been logged in.  But I can't set it to be the video call app from my phone's settings.  Any ideas? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Hubble's High-Definition Panoramic View of the Andromeda Galaxy - Zoomable [69,536 px by 22,230 px] </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-06 20:52:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Hubble's New High-Definition Panoramic View of the Andromeda Galaxy </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-06 18:37:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Tim Hortons: an American in Canada Story </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-12-29 20:58:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> I know the truth about a Canadian apology </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-12-19 18:22:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> 3 of my coworkers with all of the clothes collected from our employees for a clothes drive </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-12-19 18:06:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Even in the retirement home my grandpa has still go it. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-12-16 22:50:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> My new team at work sets this up every year </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-12-12 15:36:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> My work does a Santa program for disadvantaged kids - there are like 10 more bikes I've seen roll past my desk and there are tons of presents in bags all over the place. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-12-12 15:32:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> A man with a beard never sleeps alone </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-12-11 20:44:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> MRW trying to act cool looking at r/gonewild at work </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-12-11 18:56:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> MRW the cop try to leave Nakatomi Plaza after it was taken over by terrorists who convinced him it was all ok and I throw a body out of a window </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-12-06 02:26:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> My friend gets voicemails from a teacher about her student Marcel - it's a wrong number </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-12-02 20:28:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> My sister's friend went for a walk today in Buffalo. Thats the sidewalk. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-11-21 02:56:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Anyone with a mom that constantly calls or texts in a panic about every little thing on their phone or computer knows how big of a victory this is. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-11-19 20:49:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> My friend spotted this while driving around today </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-11-18 02:16:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Vladimir Putin cuddling with a Koala. Just prior to this the Koala attacked a journalist, biting his leg and drawing blood. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-11-16 00:08:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> I'm a big guy and this is too accurate for being in a row boat </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-11-15 19:20:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Not much has changed since the '90s </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-11-14 00:06:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> College advice from Candorville </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-11-03 21:17:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Megan Mahoney, Gym Teacher, Charged With 30 Counts Of Statutory Rape </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-10-24 12:00:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Taco Bells new TV ad disclaimer </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-03-28 19:20:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> You know nothing (about driving) </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-03-25 11:46:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> My mom and I texting about the walking dead </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-02-20 23:37:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> From BBC - First Porsche revealed to be an electric car from 1898 </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-01-29 14:49:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Interesting questions came up on slashdot about this article. Why is it legal for a company to just include you in their facial recognition software? Why isn't it opt-in rather than opt-out? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-12-24 13:32:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Lego Car That Runs On Air </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-12-20 13:28:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> McLaren To Do Away With Windshield Wipers? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-12-16 19:32:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Megatons To Megawatts: Russian Warheads Fuel U.S. Power Plants : NPR </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-12-11 19:59:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> FCC chair: ISPs should be able to charge Netflix for Internet fast lane </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-12-05 20:52:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Gov't Puts Witness On No Fly List, Then Denies Having Done So To Prevent Her From Appearing In Court </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-12-05 17:35:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> World's largest ship floated for the first time </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-12-05 17:28:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
