<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject1841</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Opinions on The Undateables?? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-10 13:27:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Its a UK based show revolving around people with various learning difficulties attempting dates/blind dates and such, as far as I'm aware. 

I haven't watched it personally, but I hear about it all the time at work (everyone there is NT as far as I know and they're unaware i have AS) and the way they talk about it I get major vibes of condescension and pity for the people, which really doesn't sit right with me. Is this really the sort of impression the show gives off? Or do I just work with shitheads (very likely, most of them are anyway).

I might pick it up and see for myself, but I'd like to know some fellow aspies opinions on the show. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-09 13:28:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Afterwards. Seems a little harsh to rule them out entirely, decent pokemon in all of them. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-07 21:40:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> INFP-T apparently. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-07 13:54:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Out of the three, I'd definitely confirm I'm in your boat; I've lived my life up to this point worrying about my weaknesses and losing sight of the strengths in between.

I do have to rule out your third point though, because history has disproven it. There have been many, many people in our world who have made great successes despite this condition, It's even been thought to have been a contributing factor in a lot of cases. Of course I don't know how Aspergers affects you personally, and it's easy for me to say "other people have done it, you can too!". It would sound cheap if I was the one reading it.

I think it's a matter of conditioning. One of my oldest friends has more severe Aspergers than I do, he can't look at anyone, stims a lot, all kinds of stuff. Spent nearly 6 years on his own after dropping out of school. This weekend I went to his first book launch in London; about 300 miles from where he's from. And he handled it like a fucking pro.

I think my point is you have to start believing what YOU think you can do. Those people who told you to focus on your weaknesses, you can only focus so much.

I hope this helped in any way, I wrote this very quickly :) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-05 20:20:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thank you so much! I'm really glad you like the idea :D Sadly I haven't got a precise log from the start of my run, but I remember most of it pretty well so I shall post whats happened so far and whats to come! 

I've been considering a similar rule to yours for a couple of days, that if a comrade dies, then the Emperor must automatically step in straight after for his fallen comrade. I like the idea of him coming in to finish the battle in particular though :) seems fitting. 

My team is:

Auroru the Togekiss
Frazzle the Umbreon
Salvadore the Poliwhirl
Hugsy the Dratini
Vindaloo the Typhlosion
Geodank the Golem

All of them are in their late 30's/early 40's except Frazzle and Hugsy, who I'm trying to bump up for the E4 :) I've been trying to fit grinding at Victory Road in over the weekend! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-04 11:09:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah! :D I'd been wanting to do this for so long, waiting for S/M bank to come out was painful...but hey ho its doable now :)

What do you mean when you say "the current team captain or the champion team"? Do you mean for who you'd be picking to carry over to the next game? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> My nuzlocke idea! The EmperorLocke </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-04 10:25:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This is my take on a nuzlocke that spans over multiple games, as I've really wanted to do something like this since Sun and Moons release. I'm going to outline all of the rules that I'm currently using for this Locke, so any rule variations or feedback would be great, I'm really looking to flesh these rules out :D Okay on to the good stuff...

The core rules still apply of course:

 Permadeath clause

 One catch per route clause

 Dupes clause (resets after every game)

 Shiny clause

 Nickname clause

The first game would essentially be a standard nuzlocke challenge, right until the very end of the game you start in. Once you've defeated the champion, you choose a surviving member of your winning party to be the first Emperor. Renickname him this and then breed him once to come along into the next game. Nickname the child "Emperor" also. 

Now the Emperor Pokmon has his own special rules to follow; until you complete the entirety of the challenge, the Emperors bloodline must maintain intact. He must survive to the end of each game to breed again for the next one, and so on until you reach the end.

Emperors Rules

 The Emperor must survive at all costs to your other Pokmon

 The Emperor cannot be boxed, he must stay in your party

 The Emperor cannot use exp share while it is an individually held item (but is allowed the later gen partywide benefit)

 If the Emperor is not the same level as the final battles highest level Pokmon by the time that battle comes around, the challenge is forfeit (this rule does not apply until your first full game with a chosen Emperor).

The last two rules are to encourage active use of the Emperor, and not to just leave him in the back of the party with the share on.

I've been playing with these additional rules:

 In the event that the Emperor dies, you may select a new member of your party at the time to take his lead, however this comes with a big penalty; renickname this Pokmon "Brutus". The Emperors old rules now apply to him with these additional caveats:

 No healing/status items can be used on Brutus in battle.

 Once switched in, Brutus is not permitted to switch out for the remainder of the battle. If Brutus dies, the challenge is forfeit once and for all.

 You may not catch any legendary Pokemon, but successfully killing the mascot of your game lets you revive a fallen comrade (ONCE per game). This revive CANNOT be carried over to later games.

 Tracking and killing a roaming legendary lets you roll a dice: 1-4 is no revive, 5-6 is an extra revive. The Pokemon must actually roam i.e, Mesprit and Cresselia, but not Azelf or Uxie; Raikou and Entei but not Suicune.

 You are not allowed to revive your deceased Emperor if you are awarded a revive.

 In game gift pokemon are permitted.

The only Pokmon you are allowed to carry over are your baby Emperor and your Ditto; all others must stay behind (unless you want to keep them boxed for nostalgia in later games etc.).

 You cannot rebreed the Emperor/Brutus for more ideal natures and such. What you get is what you're given.

 Due to the nature of the Locke, you are permitted to catch a Ditto at any time, but only the first Ditto you come across.

Those are all the rules that I'm currently using, and my starting game is Soulsilver, so I'm considering Red as the "final end" where my Emperor first gets chosen. I'm currently grinding my team for the HGSS Elite four. But once i defeat Red,my new Emperor bloodline must survive Platinum, possibly Black, X, AS, and Sun. :D As they say a lot on here, its really up to you to decide your nuzlocke, feel free to make/break some rules to fit your experiences! Also let me know what you think of the idea, I'd really like to know :) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> "6IV 20th Anniversary Event" Pokemon question </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-17 11:48:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
