<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject155</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-18 04:20:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Surgery wouldn't be necessary. All you need to do to change your gender is make a statement to that effect, and no one would be able to challenge it because of political correctness. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-18 04:12:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The only people bringing up racism during the campaign were leftists. Trump and his supporters were focused on the issues. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-17 20:53:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Why? Holding the corrupt accountable is important in a country which prides itself on enlightenment and wants to serve as an example to the rest of the world. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-17 08:50:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> No, people like that live in bubbles in Manhattan, completely uninterested and unaware of what real America looks like. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-17 04:05:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Not for the price she's asking. It's like $100 for each viewer CNN has. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-16 23:54:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> People have been using Staples and Best Buy to price match. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-16 20:45:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That nation state is called the United States </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-16 20:19:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> How many Trump supporters, or accused Trump supporters, have to die before we say enough? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-16 08:42:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If he can accomplish even half of his agenda, which is possible given his incredible people skills, he will certainly go down in history as one of the greats. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-16 05:33:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Bernie doesn't collapse a lot </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-16 04:43:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I hope every day of the next four years will be just like this for CNN. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-15 23:20:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The 1980s called. They want their foreign policy back. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-15 23:13:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It basically is the second coming of slavery. Illegals aren't owed minimum wage or any wage. They have no protections of labor laws or safety rules. They can be exploited as tools rather than human beings. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-15 23:01:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Call them what they are. Anti-democracy riots. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-15 10:16:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Art is about creativity and the piece is very creative. I would fight it until the teacher was reprimanded and a new grade assigned. If the teacher can't separate their personal life from work they should be asked to voluntarily resign. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-14 15:51:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> She would have to run as a Democrat. I don't see a Republican winning in 2024 regardless of Trump's popularity. It will be the same situation as this year. The goal will be to select the best Democrat candidate. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-14 15:37:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Trump supporters aren't the ones harassing people. They are the victims. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-13 03:10:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> http://www.telegraph.co.uk/news/newstopics/howaboutthat/8003542/British-teenager-banned-from-US-over-drunken-email-to-Barack-Obama.html </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-12 23:02:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> There was a revolt inside the FBI. At least one hundred agents revolted over the recommendation not to indict. They've seen the evidence and that's how strongly they felt about it. Clearly there's more involved than poor judgment. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-12 22:59:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If absentee ballots were counted in states that have been declared, Trump would probably have the most votes. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-12 21:12:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I liked hearing Wolf announce states for Trump.

"*sigh* we have another projection to make" </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-12 20:26:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> There are probably a billion people who would give serious thought to moving to the United States, and perhaps another billion who live in poverty and would be eager to come here if they knew what life was like here. It's a challenge. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-12 11:46:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> And their trees are the right height. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-12 09:23:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I agree with her. We do have a kick ass president! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-12 05:42:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Unfortunately I see Soros paying for it, framed as some concerned rights organization stepping in to protect "free speech" </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-12 01:05:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> He didn't. He's been asked many times over the past 30 years whether he wants to be president and he always said he's not really inclined to do that because he enjoys running his business. He said the only way he would jump in is if the situation in the country got so bad and no one was attempting to fix it. So yes, he's a reluctant president. It's a sacrifice for the country. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-11 23:53:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> He wasn't wrong in 2011

http://townhall.com/columnists/benshapiro/2011/04/13/the_magic_of_donald_trump </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-11 07:19:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Obviously it's theoretically possible but I've only heard three electors this year claim that they will vote independently. Two of them, from Washington state, say they will refuse to vote for Clinton, and one, from Texas, isn't completely sure he will vote for Trump. In reality they will probably all conform to expectations. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-11 06:50:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If he's involved with the same criminal activity the pardon will be invalid </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-11 04:56:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The left are absolute animals. Primates. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> These people had no idea </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-11 02:12:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-10 23:16:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Unless he seriously screws up it will be 8 years. It's very hard to unseat a president. The country likes to give each one two terms and then elect the other party, regardless of who the candidates are. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-10 21:21:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Who was dyzo-blue anyway? Maybe someone influential at CTR? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-10 20:55:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> All 250,000 copies are being destroyed. Only a handful were sold. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Hillary Clinton signing Newsweek cover on November 8 </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-10 20:18:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-10 09:41:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Like I kept saying, it's a Republican year.

He'll win in 2020 too, and then in 2024 we'll get a Democrat, maybe Elizabeth Warren beating John Kasich. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-10 09:30:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> They're thinking of the Supreme Court. It's settled law though. The issue was covered and argued extensively by the court last year and all the counter arguments were meticulously nullified. It's the law now and not going back to the states. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-10 07:02:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Why not [this](http://media.gettyimages.com/photos/democratic-presidential-nominee-former-secretary-of-state-hillary-picture-id621965298)? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> National recall after Newsweek misfires with Clinton cover </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-10 06:55:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-10 04:13:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That policy was refined a few months back to be a halt on immigration from areas associated with terrorism. It's still on the website.

  Suspend the issuance of visas to any place where adequate screening cannot occur, until proven and effective vetting mechanisms can be put into place. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Kasich BTFO </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-10 01:55:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-10 00:09:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Did you see the Arizona poll which sampled almost double the number of Democrats vs Republicans? Some of the polls were completely removed from reality. Last night was reality. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-09 23:07:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Rosie is no angel. When Tara Conner was found to be abusing drugs, Trump gave her a second chance after she agreed to go into rehab. He lost his brother to substance abuse and it's a big personal issue for him and he wanted to help Tara and not punish her for making a mistake. Rosie O'Donnell called him an idiot and said he should have stripped Tara of her title, and then made further insults against Trump's family. That's what this long feud is about. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-09 20:56:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I hope he didn't do it in secret and that's what led to the FBI statement. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-09 20:33:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Huh I thought it was spelled Berenstein. Did Trump just change reality? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Stock Traders Chant Lock Her Up On NYSE Floor </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-09 20:05:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-09 19:31:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That depends on the media for one thing. If they're not willing to treat President Trump fairly, it will just feed division and intolerance. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> FLASHBACK: Two simple reasons a Republican will likely win in 2016 </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-09 11:30:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-09 10:30:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The postmortem they're airing right now </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-09 10:28:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> CNN is starting to talk down Hillary now, calling her a very flawed candidate </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-09 10:26:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> No brakes! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-09 08:07:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I have my doubts. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-09 08:02:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> And it looks like they may have instructed the networks not to declare the winner too. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-09 07:47:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> There's no way Hillary is still awake at this hour. Will we get a concession speech? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Belichick, Brady back Donald Trump, the candidate says </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-08 03:53:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Clinton donor allegedly killed National Enquirer stories </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-07 05:17:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Simpsons did it </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-25 22:19:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Hillary Clintons security detail laughed when she broke her elbow </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-24 19:39:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What kind of feminist seeks out funding from regimes which force women to be accompanied by a male relative under penalty of lashing and prison, stone women to death for adultery, forbid women from driving, exposing their body, using swimming pools, playing sports, or reading fashion magazines? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-06 20:21:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> MFW Assange delivers the deathblow </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-04 02:53:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Wasp nest advice </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-28 02:08:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> In the spring I noticed wasps building a nest by the door of my house. It has happened in previous years and I leave them alone because they never bother me and seem to recognize that I'm not a threat to them. This year the nest is growing larger than normal with about 200 cells and a third of those are white. There are 10 wasps sitting on it and there are now several smaller nests close to it. I'm not sure if it's appropriate to let it continue to grow.

Will they eventually abandon it? If not, is there something humane I can do to encourage them to leave while allowing the remaining cells to hatch?

The location is Texas and they look like paper wasps. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Falguni Pathak - Meri Chunar Udd Udd Jaye [Indi-pop] </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-15 21:37:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> A-Mei -  [T-Pop] </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-12 10:16:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Mike Pence Shows Greater Gains in Favorability Than Tim Kaine </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-11 00:20:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> A.R. Rahman - Kay Sera Sera [Filmi] (a lesson in choreography) </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-08 12:51:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Bran Van 3000 - Drinking in L.A. [Alt Rock] </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-07 22:08:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Bobby Pulido - Se Muri De Amor [Tejano] (Llvame Contigo) </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-18 22:57:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Kelis - Jerk Ribs [R B] </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-16 21:57:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The Beach Boys - Good Vibrations [Psychedelic rock] (Stereo remaster) </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-04 11:27:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> How a Camera Adds 10 Pounds </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-31 03:20:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Falwell on Trump's embrace of gay community: 'I support him 100 percent' </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-25 03:57:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Reminder: When a second term president's approval rating is 50%, the chance of his party winning another term is only 28% </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-19 21:44:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Antiques Roadshow - Chekhov's Gun </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-16 19:47:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Amazon Yesterday Shipping </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-11 19:44:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [WP] The president's aides have a meltdown after he insists on following a local custom during his visit to a foreign nation. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-20 19:33:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> U.S. Visa Interview Gone Wrong </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-16 22:07:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Bingo Chips Mad Angles </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-16 21:48:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Bjrk - I Love to Love [Pop] (early recording) </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-02 20:07:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The Carter Family - Wildwood Flower [Folk] </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-26 19:39:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> MADtv Mo Collins' Life Story </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-22 20:48:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> That's My White Mama </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-15 20:06:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [WP] Having suffered a humiliating defeat in the Republican primary battle, Ted Cruz and Carly Fiorina head off in their rickety Volkswagen Type 2 in search of new adventures. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-06 18:32:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Ted Cruzs Support Softens Among the Delegates He Courted </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-01 18:34:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [WP] A bride arrives at the church to find that the bridegroom has married the wrong woman </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-23 19:58:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Rudy Giuliani (sort of) endorses Donald Trump </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-19 17:20:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Video Emerges to Suggest WaPo Reporter Ben Terris Misidentifies Lewandowski in Fields Incident </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-11 16:47:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Trump campaign volunteer says he was attacked </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-11 00:03:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Donald Trump presser tops cable news on primary night </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-09 23:02:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Murdoch: GOP 'would be mad' not to unify around Trump if he's nominee </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-02 23:39:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Donald Trump on VP pick: We need a political insider </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-24 21:11:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [WP] In a surprising and constitutionally questionable move, Bernie Sanders and Donald Trump agree to forgo the election and preside over the country together, Bernie handling domestic issues and Donald handling international issues. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-11 17:48:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> TIL that in 1991 Donald Trump told his limo driver to pull over so he could stop a brutal mugging attack </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-11 16:52:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> PredictWise - 2016 Republican Nomination </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-11 00:00:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [WP] To improve her public image, Amy Schumer decides to write a children's book </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-28 18:14:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [WP] It's one week before the election. On the same night, one of the candidates has a fatal heart attack and the other is shot by a protester at a rally. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-26 19:32:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Hillary Clinton: A Career Criminal (2015) </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-16 20:30:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [WP] Your boss asks you to take a language class to help you schmooze the new foreign partners, so you sign up for Conversational German 101. What you fail to notice is that the class is actually called Controversial German 101. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-29 19:21:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Claude Dubois - Le Blues du Businessman [Chanson] </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-11-24 18:55:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Philosophical question. In your opinion did Bill Clinton rape Monica Lewinsky? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-10-04 23:02:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This question was recently raised in the media and I thought it would be insightful to hear a range of opinions. Monica Lewinsky has of course stated many times that the relationship she had with then-president Bill Clinton was consensual on her part, however we know that even if a victim consents it is not necessarily legal. Children and the mentally disadvantaged are not able to reliably consent, for example.

Relationships between employers and employees are controversial because it is unclear exactly how much power the employee has to consent. The employer holds a degree of power over them and the employee is risking their job and reputation if they say no, which can be seen as coercion whether on a conscious or subconscious level. Even if they approve of the relationship it could be argued that they did not have the ability to fairly consent, and it turns out there is a scholarly debate over whether Monica Lewinsky was the victim of rape.

Bill Clinton was her superior in several ways. He was more than twice her age, her boss, and the president of her country. Those three things gave him enormous power over her.

What is your opinion, and would you feel the same way in that scenario? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> TIL that, hours before his death, Einstein was still alive </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-10-02 06:02:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Judge: Clock kid family could be charged with fraud if incident is proved purposeful hoax </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-09-23 14:41:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Hey, It's Ovens For Kids </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-09-22 19:00:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> TIL Britain uses a political selection system known as first-pass-the-parcel where a bundle of newspaper is passed around and each politician unwraps a layer when the national anthem stops playing. The politician who unwraps the final layer becomes prime minister and finds fish and chips inside. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-09-12 07:48:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> TIL the first #1 charting song to contain a rap section was performed by a white woman </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-08-27 01:13:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [RF] During a Republican debate, one of the candidates unexpectedly announces his intention to overturn gay marriage. Taken by surprise and thinking on their feet, the other candidates announce their own increasingly bold ideas in the hopes of stealing the spotlight. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-08-24 20:44:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Do frogs help tadpoles to leave the water? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-08-13 07:12:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> A few weeks ago I acquired some grey tree frog tadpoles and have been raising them to keep in a terrarium. A couple of them have already turned to frogs and are doing well, looking and behaving very differently from their tadpole life.

Today I had a couple of tadpoles which are close to leaving the water. They have four strong legs and have turned green in color, so I moved them to the large water dish in the terrarium so they can climb out when they're ready.

One of the frogs saw this and hopped all the way across the terrarium and started looking down into the water. It then crawled down to the dish and lowered itself into the water, holding on to the edge and facing up, and stayed like this for ten minutes. A few hours later the other frog noticed the tadpoles and did exactly the same thing, first observing and then climbing into the water. Other than this they haven't shown any interest in the water before.

Are the frogs trying to guide the tadpoles out of the water? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> ELI5: Can't modern DNA testing identify who the unknown solider is? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-16 18:52:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This guy has tombs literally all over the place. He must be the most famous solider in modern history yet no one knows his real name. Are they just reluctant to run the tests because it would mean having to print a bunch of new plaques? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> ELI5: Why are there no countries which recognize the existence of both Chinas? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-13 20:56:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I learned a while back that there are two countries called China. There's the People's Republic of China, which is larger, and the Republic of China. A lot of the products we buy are labeled 'made in PRC' or 'made in ROC', identifying that they are two separate countries and they both export products to the rest of the world.

It seems that every country diplomatically recognizes only one China and refuses to recognize the other. Why are there no countries which recognize them both? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [WP] An immigrant has worked hard his entire life to come to the USA. On the eve of his citizenship oath he finds an agent from his birth country in his house, who informs him that he has been conscripted to commit an act of sabotage against the United States. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-11 18:26:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> TIL The reason LSD (acid) makes you experience weird things is because it gets absorbed and replaces some of your DNA (acid), causing you to experience a bit of life which is different from your real one </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-11 00:37:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [WP] Write an excerpt from a cookbook whose author seems to have a deep, seething contempt for the cuisine (s)he writes about </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-22 00:42:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [WP] The nation is on high alert after a string of acid attacks on celebrities leaves some of Hollywood's most famous faces disfigured. What happens next, however, is as fantastic as any Hollywood movie. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-15 00:12:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [WP] The presidential debate has been given a revamp. Each candidate now has a score on the front of their podium, and the person with the highest score at the end wins the debate and a new car. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-07 22:06:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> I'm sick of people saying that oil is cheap </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-24 21:09:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I keep reading it, even hearing people here in Houston complain about it. No it isn't. Oil is not cheap. I was alive 15 years ago. I remember the way things are supposed to be. I remember how much things are supposed to cost.

15 years ago oil was $30 a barrel, the same relative price it had been for decades. $30 a barrel is the price that oil settles at, the price that works. Then in 2003 the US invaded Iraq and it caused a massive spike in oil prices. Oil jumped from $30 a barrel to $140. It was chaos. It affected every area of the economy and prices doubled almost overnight. Travel costs doubled as airlines tacked hundreds of dollars onto the price of tickets, calling it a "fuel surcharge". The cost of food doubled because of the increased cost of transportation. It caused misery for everyone. Millions of people were pushed out of the middle class and into poverty because they now had to pay double what they were paying before. The only hope we had to cling to was the knowledge that eventually things would settle down and oil would return to a normal price, and the other prices would eventually follow.

Finally it's happening. Oil is falling, but it's still high. It's still over $40 a barrel. This is still an inflated price and it's still too much. It's moving in the right direction, but it most certainly is not cheap. Until it hits $30 we are still paying too much. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Is America ready for its first child president? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-18 01:53:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Plumber wants to replace my water heater with a Rheem </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-12 06:58:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I have an A O Smith water heater which was most likely installed when my house was built in 2001. I've been very happy with it for the two years I've lived here - the water is always hot and it costs less than $10 a month in gas to run it. Unfortunately it's leaking and needs to be replaced. The plumber wants to put in a Rheem, and insists it's the most reliable brand they see. It's the only brand they install.

Is Rheem a good and reliable brand?

He also said the life expectancy would be 6 - 8 years. That seems quite short. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [WP] A 10 year old child places an item in the school time capsule, confident that it will make him incredibly wealthy when it's opened in 50 years </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-06 22:38:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Cheap eye test? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-28 03:51:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I moved to the US almost two years ago and my contact lens prescription is now out of date. I thought Walmart's vision center would be a cheap place to get a prescription, but they told me it would cost $125! That seems outrageously expensive for a simple eye test. Are there cheaper options I should be aware of? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Budget steadicam/stabilizer? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-09 09:56:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I recently purchased a Canon t3i to replace an older DSLR and would like to get more familiar with using it for video. It seems that handheld video is not very graceful and stabilization would help a lot. I'm a college student so finding a good price is important, and I'm only shooting video casually and experimenting so there's no need for professional equipment.

I found a few budget options and was wondering if anyone is familiar with them.

First is the [Sutefoto S40 Pro 40cm](http://www.amazon.com/SUTEFOTO-Portable-Handheld-Stabilizer-Panasonic/dp/B00P92DLQO/) **($72)** This seems to be identical to the unbranded S40 items on ebay so I'm assuming they are the same product. Amazon's price is lowest.

Next is the [Neewer Carbon Fiber 69cm](http://www.amazon.com/Neewer-Handheld-Stabilizer-Release-Weights/dp/B00P760R32/) **($80)** A familiar name in budget photography equipment.

I also found the [Flycam Junior](http://www.amazon.com/FLYCAM-Junior-Camera-Stabilizer-FLCM-JR/dp/B00IVJAE4O/) **($100)** This is available on ebay for $70 + $30 shipping, so $100 total. A little more expensive but I think it is a more familiar name in stabilization.

These are all a little more money than I'd envisioned. I know that professional equipment can be a lot more expensive still though. How well do these consumer level products perform? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Refilling ink cartridges </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-08 09:52:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I moved to the US last year for college and needed a cheap printer for homework. I normally do a lot of research before I buy things but in this case that wasn't too important. I picked up an HP 3511 at Walmart for about $30, very affordable and it's also a scanner and copier, wireless (which is a big plus). It's been just fine for the past year, churning out tons of pages.

After about a year it was time to replace the black ink and there were a few options. I decided to get a generic cartridge on ebay for $10 and that worked fine. Although there are chips on the cartridges the printer doesn't seem to care about using old cartridges. It just asks if you bought an authentic cartridge and you say no. When the color levels started to get low I looked into ink refilling. I bought a 'starter' kit on ebay for $7.50, which contained 30ml of each color ink and four syringes. I was very surprised to read that the ink cartridges only contain a few ml of ink, so this refill kit will actually refill the color cartridge about six times. Refilling was very quick and easy, just locate the filling hole and gently syringe the ink into the cartridge.

Until recently I've considered laser printers to be the best value for money, but now I think refilled inkjet cartridges are probably even better value. I've seen entire liters of ink available for $10 on ebay, enough to refill a black cartridge 125 times. Who knew. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> TIL by 1983 Coca-Cola had lost significant ground to Pepsi and only commanded 24% market share </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-05 19:22:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [WP] The president slips out of the White House late at night to visit the capital's homeless </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-12-07 22:26:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> A plane crashes on the border of North Korea and Russia. Where do they bury the survivors? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-11-18 10:29:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> ELI5: Why don't planes incorporate noise cancellation into the cabin? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-10-26 18:24:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Excluding the Airbus A380, which I've heard is already quieter. I've traveled on a lot of planes, and every time the experience has been insanely loud. Having a conversation with the person in the next seat is difficult, and communicating with someone in the aisle involves shouting or gesturing. It's like trying to communicate underwater. In recent years a lot of people have started to wear noise cancelling headphones on flights, but it seems like this problem could have be solved by placing microphones in the cabin and cancelling out the noise through the speaker system. Why isn't this done? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What electronic devices and gadgets do you own, and how long do you expect each to last? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-10-08 00:19:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What types of gadgets (example tv, ipod) do you own? What do you expect the lifespan of each device to be, and would you keep it until it reaches the end of its life? If you plan to replace a device before then, how long do you expect to own it? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> I have Amazon Prime. Ask me (almost) anything! </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-09-18 04:23:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I will be here for the next couple of hours to answer your questions about streaming media service Amazon Prime and its related features.

**Edit:** Thanks for all the great questions! Time for me to go and find some awesome new things to buy. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> TIL if you're a European citizen you have the right to live and work in French Guiana in South America </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-09-14 20:52:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> These images of America's beauty always take my breath away </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-08-30 21:02:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Fast food workers of Reddit... why don't you mark the packaging? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-08-08 03:42:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Which Walmart mountain bike would be best for me? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-07-20 06:33:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> **UPDATE: I ended up buying a used bike from Craigslist as suggested and will be taking it to a shop shortly to see what tune ups are needed. I've left the original post below for the benefit of others who might have a similar query.**


*I've barely ridden a bike since I was a kid, but now I'd like to ride for exercise and to explore the area. I would mostly ride around the streets, parks, and woodland paths, nothing challenging. I live in Houston where it's very flat.*

*I'm 6' tall and probably weigh around 240lb, leg length 34".*

*I can't afford to spend too much, preferably under $150. There are a couple of bikes I've seen on the Walmart website which interested me.*

*The 26" Roadmaster Granite Peak is $80 and has many positive remarks around the internet.
http://www.walmart.com/ip/Roadmaster-Granite-Peak-26-Men-s-Mountain-Bike-Black/34931885*

*The 29" Genesis GS29 is $150 and has fewer reviews
http://www.walmart.com/ip/29-Genesis-Men-s-GS29-Bike/34116311*

*I had an opportunity to briefly see these bikes in Walmart, and to me the Roadmaster looks very small but sturdy, while the Genesis looks somewhat cheaply constructed but a more suitable size.*

*Can anyone offer some advice on what might be best for me, or have a better suggestion considering my limited budget?* </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Non-smoker considering nicotine patches to aid with ADD, anxiety and depression </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-07-19 15:01:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I recently read that nicotine may help to improve mood in those suffering with depression, and may help to overcome some of the debilitating effects of anxiety and ADD.

As a non-smoker, I am curious about trying it for myself, a controversial decision, but the negative effects of those conditions affect the quality of life and may justify unusual steps. What risks are associated with nicotine patches? Can they be detrimental to health over a period of time?

About me, I'm 30, overweight and have high blood pressure. I am not on any medications. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> It offends people too... </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-05-03 21:09:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
