<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject7451</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> In 1897 the New York Sun responded to 8 year old Virginia O'Hanlon's question about whether there was a Santa Claus. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-12-05 17:10:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Giants' Terrell Thomas guarantees the Giants will win </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-11-24 15:11:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Jimmy Johnson, Charles Haley among NFL Hall of Fame finalists </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-11-22 12:10:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Garrett still best option for Cowboys </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-11-22 12:06:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Article 2 of 2: Tim MacMahon says it's about time the Cowboys hold players accountable (and praises Garrett for changing the culture) </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-11-20 20:56:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Article 1 of 2 (read them both for a balanced perspective): Will Allen says micromanagement hinders the Cowboys </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-11-20 20:55:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Plex installation problem: can't access PMS </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-11-19 01:40:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hopefully someone can help!  I installed Plex, no problem.  And after some finagling I was able to access PMS.  I even got 3 shows installed in the library!  But then for no apparent reason I couldn't access PMS anymore.  Which is to say: when I right-click on the tray icon and select media manager, it takes me to the Plex logo and stalls.

I tried uninstalling/reinstalling and doing a few other things, including accessing PMS through Chrome, Firefox, and Opera, with the same result.

THEN I tried accessing PMS via IE.  I received a message saying I needed to enable intranet, and when I did, suddenly I could get in!  Using IE is problematic, though, as I frankly don't use it at all.

I tried googling how to enable intranet in Firefox and tried a couple of things, but clearly I wasn't doing the right thing, as I still can't access PMS via Firefox.

What setting would be identical in Chrome, Firefox, and Opera that would prevent me from accessing PMS but would be fixed when I enabled intranets in IE?  This is a mystery!

Oh, ALSO!  I am able to access the server on my machine from a second machine!  That's obviously fubar; I'm blocking myself somehow but I don't know how. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Dez Bryant buys PS4s for shoppers </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-11-15 16:14:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Is there a way to configure Plex so that it opens in a browser that *isn't* the default browser? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-11-15 03:43:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Generally, Plex seems to be a lot more stable in Chrome, but for reasons I won't get into here I need to use a different browser as my default.  So I was wondering if there might be a way to configure Plex so it runs in a different browser than the default.  It must just be a setting somewhere in a file, right?

**Edit**: thank you to everyone who responded! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> DeMarcus Ware: best fix for D is health </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-11-13 19:39:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Cowboys' problems start with Jones's personnel decisions </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-11-12 13:48:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Please help: installation/setup problem </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-11-11 17:44:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I installed Plex on a 64-bit Win 7 system.  Installation seemed to be fine.  However, when I right-click on the tray icon and select Media Manager, it opens a browser and displays the Plex icon (an arrow), but won't do anything else.  It won't let me specify a server or anything else; I click on the screen and nothing happens.

This occurs whether I use IE, Chrome, Firefox, and even Opera.  

Things I've tried:  
1) uninstalling/reinstalling the program;  
2) turning off my firewall;  
3) turning the program off and back on;  
4) starting Firefox in safe mode to see if an add-on was causing the problem;  
5) based on a suggestion at the Plex site, I also tried resetting the system bundle;
6) tried opening the port on the router.    

All had the same result.

When I directly enter the address http://127.0.0.1:32400/web/index.html, it takes me to the same screen.

I would appreciate any suggestions on how to fix this.  I've posted on the Plex site but haven't received a useful response.

Thank you for any info/suggestions you can provide.

**Edit:** As posted [here](http://www.reddit.com/r/PleX/comments/1qdv6f/please_help_installationsetup_problem/cdc79cf), this problem somehow solved itself after I opened a log and pasted it on the Plex site.  No idea why this might have correlated to the solution, but it did.

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Dorsett, other ex-NFL players told they have CTE (generally caused by head trauma) </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-11-07 04:47:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Why Marinelli may be the Cowboys' best hope to return to Super Bowl contention </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-11-05 05:44:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Skip Bayless: Why Jones's Cowboys won't win </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-11-03 00:08:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Lions 31 Cowboys 30: a few observations </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-10-29 11:46:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> As usual, feel free to agree/disagree.  Please just dont downvote anyones responses simply because you disagree.

**1)** This was a team loss, but not for the reason one might think.  This loss was all about depth, or lack thereof.  

In the fourth quarter, with the game on the line, at times the defensive backfield consisted of B.W. Webb, Jakar Hamilton, Jeff Heath, Scandrick, and Carr.  Theres a reason I mention the first names of those first three guys: you might not recognize them otherwise, as none of them were on the active roster even a week earlier.

But that was the group expected to cover possibly the best WR combo in the NFL.

Surprised that the Cowboys lost?  More surprising that they kept it close.

**2)** Depth is something I harp on repeatedly because the Cowboys dont have it.  No matter how good a teams stars, if it doesnt have adequate replacementsi.e., players who can come in and get the job done when starters are outthat team is going to struggle.

As discussed repeatedly in this sub, years of bad drafts had led to the decimation of the Cowboys depth.  Only *8 players* from the 6 drafts (dating back to 2005) prior to the Garrett era still are on the team: [Ware, Spears, Hatcher, Spencer, Free, Scandrick, Bryant, Lee](http://www.pro-football-reference.com/teams/dal/draft.htm).  (I didnt go further back because given the brevity of the average NFL career it didnt seem fair.)  But 8 players out of a possible 48 is just abysmal.

Garrett has been trying to correct that, but a team which had been as weakened as the Cowboys doesnt rebuild overnight.  And hes been trying to do that on both sides of the ball.  In the 3 drafts during the Garrett era, the Cowboys drafts have been about as evenly-split as a draft could be: theyve drafted [12 offensive players and 10 defensive players](http://www.pro-football-reference.com/teams/dal/draft.htm).  As its too early to judge the quality of those drafts, Ill avoid the temptation for now.

Point is: it takes time to replenish a teams depth.  And the Cowboys are trying.

But games like this demonstrate just how important depth is.  And how far the Cowboys still have to go.

**3)** Before I conclude my rant about depth, consider that the Cowboys had at least 6 defensive players late in the game on the field who hadnt even been on the roster at the start of the season: the 3 new guys in the backfield and the 3 guys from Walgreens in the defensive line.  Thats 6 out of 11.  This is turning into a repeat of 2012.

It would be idiotic to blame Kiffin for this debacle.  Just like it wasnt the most accurate to blame Ryan.  

Though I like the Kiffin/Marinelli combo better.  Among other things, theyve shown that they can be flexibleshifting away from the Cover 2 when it became clear it wasnt working.

Speaking of which (this is only a question, not an expression of opinion), is it too early to start describing Claiborne as a bust?

**4)** Hard to say whether the Cowboys got too conservative too early or whether they simply failed to perform.  But in the final 3 series before that last abysmal play they seemed to try too hard to run the clock down, resulting in repeated losses of yards, 2 punts, and a field goal.  However, if the offensive line simply had done its job (block), this strategy would have worked.  

It wasnt as though the Lions defense was so great.  In fact it was [28th against the pass and 23rd against the run](http://www.prideofdetroit.com/2013/10/25/5028102/detroit-lions-dallas-cowboys-on-paper-preview).  But once again the Cowboys inability to execute on offense let their opponents weak defenses off the hook.

On the one hand, a coach should know the limitations of his players.  But on the other, he should be able to expect his players to perform.  It didnt seem to be asking too much for his offensive line simply to do some run blocking.  Against the 23rd-ranked team in the NFL in run defense.

The offensive line may be better.  (Admittedly weak praise.)  But it still isnt fixed.

**5)** Once again Tanner was involved in a pivotal play in the game.  But it's hard to believe that, while explaining why [Smith's holding penalty didn't have to happen](http://espn.go.com/blog/dallas/cowboys/post/_/id/4718220/why-tyron-smiths-penalty-didnt-have-to-happen), Garrett meant to suggest that Tanner shouldn't have tried to gain a first down.  Can't blame a runner for running to daylight; and it's not Tanner's fault that Smith exercised bad technique.  Unless that play has a notation next to it in the playbook that says something like *simply run into the backs of the offensive linemen and fall down*.

Otherwise, it sounds as though Garrett's signaling that Tanner isn't long for the team.  If they had any depth at RB that is.

**6)** If you havent seen it already, you should watch [this video of Dez](http://www.nfl.com/videos/nfl-videos/0ap2000000271580/Dez-sideline-sound) during his supposed rant.  Not only was he not a distraction, but he was focused, analytical, and professional.  Hint: thats how you describe a leader.

**7)** Sean Lee may be the best Cowboys linebacker since [Lee Roy Jordan](http://www.pro-football-reference.com/players/J/JordLe00.htm).  I still say its a travesty that hes not in the Hall of Fame.  But thats how good Lee is.

**8)** Bottom line is that we should continue to expect under/inconsistent performance on both sides of the ball until:  
**(a)** Kiffin/Marinelli can work their magic on a bunch of rejects;  
**(b)** the defensive guys on whom the Cowboys expected to rely can regain their health (i.e., next year);  
**(c)** the Cowboys find a good RB who can stay on the field (see comment about next year); and  
**(d)** they can build a decent offensive line.  

In the meantime, theyll be playing on heart and the occasional flashes of brilliance between Romo, Bryant, Williams, and Witten on offense, and Lee, Carr, and Hatcher on defense.  

This is a team in development, and it still doesn't have the players yet to be a legitimate contender.  But it's gotten a lot closer.  Now it just needs to develop its depth.  Then it can learn how to win games like this one.

Which is to say its going to be an interesting and aggravating second half of the season.

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> How TX lost the world's largest supercollider </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-10-29 03:21:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Time to look for Ware's replacement </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-10-25 19:49:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Cowboys' young receivers make Austin an afterthought (some amazing numbers in here) </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-10-21 15:40:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Tanner acknowledges: intercepted pass was meant for Beasley </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-10-21 13:10:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Kiffin gets the last laugh </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-10-21 13:09:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Cowboys go to head of NFC East with defensive feast </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-10-21 11:53:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> PFO's analysis of the Cowboys' OL vs. the Redskins </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-10-18 16:59:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Jay Ratliff contract may have been Cowboys' worst </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-10-17 12:01:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Scouting the Eagles </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-10-16 17:06:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> With injuries mounting, Cowboys must rely on Jerry's drafts </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-10-15 14:44:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Cowboys 31 Redskins 16: a few observations </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-10-15 12:38:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> A few observations.  This is the harsh realities, or stop me if youve heard this before edition.

As always, feel free to agree/disagree.

**1)** Once again, the Cowboys may be hurt by a lack of depth.  Murray and three of the four starting defensive linemen (Spencer, Ratliff, Ware) are out for unspecified periods.  

Injuries hurt all teams, but the best teams manage to perform despite injuries.  The lesser teams are the ones which let injuries finish their seasons.  Well see which kind of team the Cowboys are.

**2)** With respect to Murray--sure, I know everybody loves him.  But, again, he is not going to be the answer.  He  performs when hes on the field, no question.  But he has missed significant playing time every year hes been in the NFL.  The best runnersSmith, Dorsett, Sanders, Paytonfound ways to stay on the field.  

Murrays style of running, in which he refuses to shy from contact, is the very thing thats hurting him.  At this point in his career, he wont change his style.  Unfortunately, that means hes going to keep getting hurt.

So far it still doesnt look like the Cowboys have a replacement for him.  Randle hasnt shown any indication he can be a go-to guy.  Though he may yet be, the game looks like its still moving too fast for him; hes not sure what hes seeing, so hes struggling to find holes.  This may change; the more snaps he gets, the more he'll see.  As always with this team, though, time will tell.

**3)** Regarding the defense, weve already seen complaints about Kiffin.  The problem is, the complaints about his schemes are as ill-informed as were the complaints about Ryan.  A coach only is as good as his players.  Ryans defense was decimated by injuries; the Cowboys are beginning to struggle with the same thing.  

By now were all becoming aware of the [no-names along the defensive line](http://www.star-telegram.com/2013/10/14/5246573/injuries-force-cowboys-to-use.html).  Can the Cowboys pressure Qbs using Drake Nevis, Caesar Rayford, David Carter, and Edgar Jones?  Again, well see.

But it would be ridiculous to blame Kiffin if they dont.

**4)** The Cowboys shifted to a man-coverage scheme against the Redskins.  Some say this was a marked improvement.  But as  I mention below, it's hard for me to agree, because the Redskins still gained a lot of yards, and they would have gained more if Griffin's passes had looked more professional.  Clearly, though, Claiborne is better at man coverage than zone.  He couldn't be much worse, though, right?

**5)** Speaking of the defense, is it too early to say that [Drake Nevis](http://www.pro-football-reference.com/players/N/NeviDr00.htm) is becoming one of my favorites, along with George Selvie?  Or should I wait until hes at least played a quarter of a season with the team?  But in the Redskins game that big squat body was getting some nice penetration along the line.  He looked like a massive fireplug in there.

**6)** In the absence of an effective running game, we should expect the Cowboys to become even more one-dimensional than they were in the first quarter of the season.  This wont be the fault of Callahan or Garrett.  Itll be the fault of whoever has been responsible for building depth on this team.  To keep Stauby from fussing at me again I wont say his name *coughJonescough*.

**7)** Which reminds me.  While the Cowboys drafts seem to be getting better (cant get worse than that infamous [2009 draft](http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/2009_NFL_Draft)), the teams lack of depth was why so many people were howling that *coughJonescough* blew it by trading down.  Think the Cowboys couldnt use [Shariff Floyd](http://www.pro-football-reference.com/players/F/FloySh00/gamelog\//) now?  More than Gavin Escobar?

**8)** I had a weird sensation watching the Redskins game.  Again, the defense didnt play well (giving up 400+ yards for the fourth time this year).  And it could have been a lot worse: a number of Griffins passes to wide-open guys just looked *terrible*.  And the offense, of course, went dead in the second half after Murray left.

Like all of us, I was ecstatic at Harriss returns.  And his tackling!  Dont get me started.  And thank goodness for Nevis and Wilbur.  And I expected an offensive drop-off after that Broncos game.

But somewhere around 24-16, I found myself thinking that no matter how they looked against the Redskins, it wouldnt affect how they might look against the Eagles, the Lions, the Vikings, or any game after that.  Sure, every games a new game.  But we kid ourselves when teams are doing well that they have personalities, that we know what to expect.  

This team, though, is as inconsistent as it gets.  Lets face it, even if they win the next three, so they bring a four-game winning streak and a 6-3 record into that November 10 game against the Saints, they *still* might wind up 8-8.  

This team *almost* reminds me of the 1975 Cowboys, when [12 rookies made the team](http://www.knowyourdallascowboys.com/2009/05/30/the-greatest-draft-dirty-dozen-in-1975\/). That team went on through the Hail Mary to the great hearbreak of Super Bowl 10.  But the '75 Cowboys were *good*.  They certainly wasn't as inconsistent as this one.  It's maddening.  Interesting, but maddening.

**9)** With all of that said, two of the Cowboys' three losses have been to the only undefeated teams left in the league--by a total of four points.  So this team may be better than its record suggests.

As always, we'll see.
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Cowboys release Will Allen </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-10-09 17:11:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> "[T]here is ample reason to fear that the game has passed the 73-year-old Kiffin by" </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-10-08 14:44:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Deciphering the decision: Romo's interception </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-10-07 15:18:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> A few observations. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-10-07 14:42:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> A few observations.  As usual, feel free to agree/disagree.
	
**1)** This was one of the most entertaining NFL games Ive ever seen.  Someone had to lose.  It happened to be the team that made the most mistakes.  Which was fitting.

**2)** To say the Cowboys lost the game because of Romo ignores the obvious and numerous other reasons the Cowboys lost, including, but not limited to:  
**a)** the defense gave up 51 points.  51!  I dont care who youre playing, if you give up 51 points youre awful;  
**b)** even after the interception, the defense failed to stop the Broncos after the Cowboys used up their timeouts; preventing the Broncos from making a first down would have given the Cowboys one more chance with about a minute left;  
**c)** Romos the only reason the Cowboys even were in the game.  Against one of the best defenses in the league, he had the best game ever by a Cowboys QB, and his 506 yards was the 12th best performance *in NFL history* by a QB;  
**d)** the OL allowed the Broncos to control the line of scrimmage on that last Cowboys sequence; the result was a sack and pressure that led to the INT.  This kind of thing happens to *any* team that loses control of the line of scrimmage;
 
**3)** If Romo had thrown that INT in the first quarter, no one even would remember it.  The timing of the INT, though, will add fuel to the perception that Romo chokes in the clutch.

The problem with this concept is that the clutch doesnt exist.  Which is to say, its a misperception arising from our own emotional involvement in a game, based on what weve seen so far.

Said another way, every other play matters just as much as the purportedly clutch play, as every other play has led to the moment of the clutch.  

In baseball, SABR has proven that there is [no such thing as a clutch hitter](http://research.sabr.org/journals/do-clutch-hitters-exist).  Instead, it famously has concluded that *most . . . of the differences among player's PWA's (i.e., player win average, or clutch hitting) are really attributable to differences in the quantity of their hits, not to differences in the timeliness of their hits.*  This means that a players performance the rest of the time matters every bit as much as his purportedly clutch performance, *because his team wouldn't have gotten to that point otherwise*.

Sound familiar?  

That INT hurt us because we imagined the Cowboys marching down the field and winning, given what wed seen already (and what Romo already had done).  But what hed done was play incrediblyso incredibly, in fact, that they still were in the game at that point, notwithstanding the atrocious performance by the Cowboys defense.  Said another way: every sensational play Romo made (and there were many) were clutch perfomances.

If Romo can be accused fairly of anything, its that hes unable to carry a team on his back to the point where it can overcome his occasional mistake.  But no player in any team sport ever has been able to do that, based on the very definition of team sport.  The outcome of a game in a team sport is based on the performances of every member of the two teams involved.  As mentioned in (1), a lot of other players let the Cowboys down a lot more than did Romo.

The media focuses on Romo the same reason it focuses on celebrity: its easy to write about one guy, particularly under deadline pressure, and doesnt require significant analysis.  Its easier to focus on his fumbled snap of a PAT than on all the other mistakes in that playoff game; its easier to blame him for that choke in the Lions game than on all the bad routes receivers ran/truly excellent plays made by the Lions; etc.

Just as easy (and accurate) to blame the OL for that INT as Romo; it didnt give him time to do what hed amply demonstrated he could do.  And Escobar wasnt in the proper position for the pass.  Which isnt to displace blame; obviously Romos the one who threw it.  But he wasnt the *sole* reason the INT happened or that the Cowboys lost.

**Edit**: in fact, check [this link](http://www.bloggingtheboys.com/2013/10/7/4811472/cowboys-broncos-deciphering-the-decision-tony-romo-interception), showing exactly why the INT happened.  And it was not because of Romo.  Ach!  I'm so brilliant.

**4)** I continue to appreciate the extent to which Bryant has changed his life; his performance on the field is simply a demonstration of his commitment to seizing the opportunity before him.  Many people never reach the point in life where all they ever wanted was right in front of them, and all they had to do was work to take it.  Hes come from a terrible background and hes reached that point.  Looks to me like hes made the right decision.  

He's becoming a man right before our eyes.  Not because he can catch a ball.  But because he's learned to maximize his abilities and his opportunity.  That makes it easy to cheer for him now.

**5)** FYI the Cowboys could have run at the end; in retrospect, it would have been preferable to what happened.  But coaches cant coach in retrospect.  Romo was lights-out; no coach in his right mind would have gone away from what was working so tremendously.

**6)** I love the sudden revelation of the long game.  Id like to see a lot more of that.

**7)** Terrance Williams is starting to look like the real deal, huh?  Anyone who watched him at Baylor could have told us that.

**8)** All day, the Broncos looked like the better teamin fact, they looked like the best team in the NFL.  Amazing that the Cowboys almost won that game.  The difficulty lies in drawing conclusions from the loss.  I remember reading a few years back that most NFL games are decided by less than a TD.  Point is that teams are roughly equivalent; this is why we say things like any given Sunday.  Almost always in the NFL teams beat themselves.  Its what happened in this game.  But the Broncos still looked terrific.  Big fast guys everywhere.

Every game is its own universe.  I would have been euphoric if the Cowboys had won.  But my attitude about the team actually wouldnt have been that different.

The effort the Cowboys demonstrated was night and day better than in that [Packers debacle](http://www.pro-football-reference.com/boxscores/201011070gnb.htm).  And this Broncos team is better than that Packers team.

Notwithstanding whatever mistakes he still may make (and believe me, Landry made *many* (or at least he was accused of it)), this is what Garrett has brought to the Cowboys: a change in attitude.  It is being demonstrated on the field; its just not showing up in the W/L columns yet.  Remember, though: teams *always* are works in progress, either up or down.  Teams do not turn around overnight.  This team is not going sideways at all.

Sure, the Cowboys have been a [sub-.500 team since 1997](http://espn.go.com/dallas/nfl/story/_/id/9784140/dallas-cowboys-continue-find-creative-ways-lose?ex_cid=espnapi_public).  But to say that nothing has changed is just idiotic.  This group of Cowboys isnt responsible for Campos ineptitude, the personality disputes between Jones and every head coach hed ever hired until Garrett, Jones inability to evaluate talent.

This is a new group that has changed dramatically since Garrett became head coach.  It is trending up.  But as anyone familiar with trends understands, trends represent measurement of general direction, not specific performance.  There will be a lot of games like that Chargers' bomb and a lot of heartwrenching losses before they figure it out.

Question we'll have to wait to see answered is if they'll ever figure it out.

It will take patience and time for it to succeed.  But Garrett is building something.  All the best coachesLandry, Lombardi, Gibbs, [Noll](http://www.pro-football-reference.com/coaches/NollCh0.htm)understood that success is built primarily on a change in attitude.  This team has a different attitude than any Ive seen on the Cowboys since the early 90s.

I wouldnt be surprised at all if this game changed their season.  Time will tell, of course.  It always does.  While the team is improving, it's not at a championship level yet (or even genuine contender yet).  Right now it's 2-3, inconsistent in many respects, beating itself as often as being outplayed.  But it's not quitting.  And if it can show the hunger it demonstrated in this game, it could be on the verge of breaking out.

**9)** Let me repeat it: more long passes please!


  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The Year of Selvie </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-10-04 02:45:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Peyton Manning's kryptonite </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-10-03 18:17:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Thunderbird problem (help?) </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-10-03 02:19:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm using Thunderbird 17.0.8.  For about a year (i.e., stretching back through previous versions), Thunderbird has been having problems with emails either past a certain size or which contain HTML (or both--I'm not really sure which).  When it tries to download one of these emails, I get different error messages, along the lines of:

*The RETR command did not succeed.  Error retrieving a message.  Mail server localhost responded:*

(and then it provides a variety of messages which themselves seem garbled, such as (this is not the only one) "etica, sans-serif; color: #ffffffff, font-size: 13px; border-bottom: 1=").

Another sample error message: "The DELE command did not succeed. Error marking a message as deleted. Mail server localhost responded:"

Ultimately, if I keep pressing ctrl+F5, the message downloads, but it's garbled or truncated.  I think it has something to do with a chunk size maybe?  Maybe something to do with a fetch by chunk option?  I'd read that by increasing that option in the config file this problem would resolve.  So I tried it, but couldn't find that option in the config file.  I wound up adding it manually, but it had no effect.  

So that made me think the chunk issue only was relevant to an older version.  Even so, it does seem that something about the way Thunderbird is configured to download emails is interfering with their delivery.  I'm just not sure what.

I've also tried compressing the file folders; no effect.

I realize we're in a small sub, and I'm not being very clear.  But as you can see I'm not sure even how to describe the problem.

If I have to uninstall/reinstall Thunderbird, I'd want to save my email files, as they go back years.

I appreciate any help anyone might provide. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Chargers game: pass v run (warning: long) </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-10-02 15:46:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> After seeing all the squawks about the Cowboys' purported failure to run the ball enough in the Chargers game, I decided to examine the play by play to see if there were any merit to that idea.  I'm always on the lookout for biases that might skew my opinion of the state of the Cowboys, so I figured this was worth doing, as I might learn something.

[My source](http://www.pro-football-reference.com/boxscores/201309290sdg.htm#pbp_data::none).

**First possession, 1st Q, 0-0**

On 1st down Murray gained 10 yards, earning another 1st down.  

Romo then was sacked for -4, setting up a 2nd and 14.  With regard to that play, while the Cowboys could have run again, there's nothing inherently wrong in occasionally passing on first down.  So that early in the game, it's not a bad call.  

The result was bad, because running on 2nd and 14 probably isn't the smartest.  2nd down was an incompletion.  Not many people credibly will suggest running on 3rd and 14.  So that series was a bust because of the sack, which, sure, wouldn't have happened if the Cowboys had tried to run, but as already discussed, running then passing is called mixing it up.

**Second possession, 1st Q, 0-0**

Two runs gave the Cowboys 3rd and 2.  On 3rd down, they could have run, sure.  They also could have passed.  This one I'll call a wash, leaning toward the idea that they should have run, but recognizing that the call could have gone either way.

**Third possession, 1st Q, 0-7**

On 1st, pass incomplete.  On 2nd, pass for 7.  3rd and 3.  Result's okay as of this point.  Sure, they could have run.  But 3rd and short isn't bad.  Then a sack.  Okay, there could have been some runs, but this isn't terrible playcalling.  It's just starting to shift toward an imbalance.

**Fourth possession, 1st/2nd Q, 0-7**

9 plays, 3 runs, 6 passes.  The runs averaged 4.67; the passes averaged 7.167.  The Cowboys ran for 6, then passed for 5, passed for 10, passed for 10, passed for 13.  Then they ran for 2 on 1st as a penalty gave them another 1st.  Pass for 13, run for 6, then the pass to Bryant for the TD.

They averaged 2nd and short after each 1st down pass.  They averaged 2nd and middle to long after each 1st down run.  To me, the results shift the balance back to neutral. 

6 runs, 13 passes as of this point.  32 yards on 6 runs (5.33),  51 yards on 13 passes (3.92).  On sheer numbers, run seems more effective; however, discounting Romo's early 0-4, pass plays were averaging 5.67.  The sacks hurt more than the playcalling.  But the Cowboys could have run the ball a bit more, arguably with roughly equivalent results.

**Fifth possession, 2nd Q, 7-7**

1st down, a run for no gain.  2nd and 10.  They're supposed to run on 2nd and 10?  Sure they could have.  It may have gained about what their pass did (4 yards).  On 3rd and 6 there aren't many teams that will run.  The Cowboys passed incomplete.  This is when Bailey tried the long field goal.

With respect to that call, the Cowboys were on the Chargers 38.  They could have punted, but something I havent seen discussed here is that Jones isnt so great at pinning guys inside the 10.  This is anecdotal until I can find hard evidence, but I read somewhere that hes middle of the pack when it comes to that.  

So the choice was between letting the Chargers start at their 20 or letting them start at their 46.  So far, the defense had looked pretty goodthe Chargers had gained a total of 108 yards through a quarter and a half.  That projects to under 300 for the game.

Conservative call would have been to punt.  But pretty much all of us think Baileys a terrific kicker.  This is the kind of call you criticize or praise in retrospect, depending on results.  Unfortunately coaches cant coach in retrospect.

**Fifth possession, 2nd Q, 7-10**

1st down pass to Bryant for 14.  Sure they could've run, but subbies seem to love whenever the ball is thrown to Bryant.  And the Cowboys didn't have a 14 yard run all day.  Three runs gained 24 yards.  Then the 34 yard pass to Bryant for the TD at 2:44 mark.

**Sixth possession, 3rd Q 9:32, 21-20**

A lot happened here between possessions.  Sean Lees interception and Rivers switch to short drops were the most important.

As an aside, I would argue that Rivers switch just before halftime affected this game far more than the Cowboys playcalling, as it ended any inability by the Cowboys to pressure him.  It seemed like pass after pass was just a little loop or flare out of the backfield.  It should be noted that the Chargers ran 14 passes to 3 runs on two drives while scoring 10 points.  

In any event, on 1st Murray ran for 3.  A penalty gave them 2nd and 12.  Im sorry, but almost no team runs on 2nd and 12.  A pass gave them 3rd and 3.  A pass gave them 5 and a 1st down.

As this point, as others have mentioned, the Cowboys tendency to pass on 3rd and short seems a lot more obvious than that a run/pass imbalance overall is hurting them.  Said another way, if an imbalance is hurting them, its on 3rd and short. 

On 1st, Murray ran for 4 and a penalty gave them 15.  On 1st Murray lost 1.  Again the Cowboys faced 2nd and long (10+).  This was the 4th time in the game the Cowboys faced 2nd and long.  2 of those happened after runs on first down.  1 happened after a penalty, and 1 after a pass.  

Observation: the Cowboys passing on 1st down was not forcing them into 2nd and long as much as the Cowboys running on first down.  

Teams rarely run on 2nd and 11.  This doesnt suggest that they should; it suggests that they dont because *it rarely helps*.  If theyd tried to run on that play, they would have been criticized for it.

Anyway, two incompletions, including Bryants inability to hold the ball on the sideline, ended the possession at 6:18.

Note: if Bryant had caught that pass, theyd have had a 1st down.

**Seventh possession, 4th Q, 14:41, 21-23**

By now its become obvious that the Cowboys didnt adjust on defense to those short passes.  They also had numerous blown coverages (though the killer of course came after this).  In short, the Chargers were beating the defense by offsetting the Cowboys rush with short drops and utilizing short routes to find holes in the zones.  Heres a [search](https://www.google.com/search?q=how+to+beat+the+cover+2) where you can see for yourself that finding holes in zones is how you beat the Cover 2.  Didn't help that Claiborne seemed to forget how to cover people.

I'm beginning to wonder if maybe he's not an ideal CB for a Cover-2.  Supposedly he's got all the skills, but his technique looks bad to me.  His footwork seems to get his body out of position on a lot of plays.  Also, I remember at least 2 penalties (not just in this game) on him that didn't seem justified.  So he needs to control his body more to stop the completions and to stop making refs think he's fouling players.

In any event, on 1st they ran for 9, then passed for 6.  On 1st, they ran for 6.  Then they passed for 10, 6, and 6.  On that 3rd pass, a penalty on Leary, not the pass, hurt them.  The penalty pushed them into their 5th 2nd and long (here 2nd and 14).  

They passed for 6.  Arguably if theyre going to pass for 6 they might as well try to run for 6.  But trying to use this one call to argue that the Cowboys didnt run enough seems weak.  

On 3rd down they passed.  It was expected but it also was rational, as the Cowboys werent averaging 6 per carry, and they *were* averaging 6+ per pass.  

Anyway, this was the play where Witten dropped the ball; it looked to me like it hit his shoulder pads.  He almost always makes this catch; heck, hes built his career on this catch.  If hed caught it, theyd have had a huge first down.  He was in perfect position and the ball was on target.  But he dropped it.

**Eighth possession, 4th Q, 6:69, 21-30**

Sorry to anyone who says they didnt have to pass by now, but down by 2 scores, in light of their defenses vulnerability, it was time to pass.  2 passes gained a first down.  A 3rd pass to Murray gained 1.  But the killer here was the penalty on Parnell, which forced them into 1st and 20.  

No one sensible is going to suggest they should have run on this play.  

Sure, maybe they should have run on that 1 yard pass to Murray, but it wouldnt have mattered what they called there, due to Parnells penalty.  Sure, it was holding, which almost never gets called on running plays.  But come on: someones going to argue that the Cowboys should have run because an OL was called for holding?  Thats Monday-morning quarterbacking at its *worst*.

Anyway, they passed the rest of the way, leading up to Williamss fumble.

People will say they shouldnt have gone to Williams, the *rookie*, when they had Bryant.  But Williams was having a decent day (his best so far).  And if Bryant was such a go-to, why the heck didnt he get open more often?  After all (supposedly), the Cowboys passed way too much today.  Bryants a 4th year man, who supposedly is a beast.  So why hasnt he learned to break double coverages yet?

I don't want to diss Bryant, who's shown marked growth and maturity.

My point: Williams made a mistake, but the pass to him was not a mistake.  He should have tucked that ball in and relied on the next play.  But he was trying to make a play.  In 40+ years of watching the Cowboys, Ive seen that good players learn from that kind of mistake.  Bad players repeat it.  Well see which kind Williams is.

**Ninth possession, 4th Q, 1:02, 21-30**

Short passes to the left and middle, ending in a fumble.

If someone wants to complain about the Cowboys passing game, heres where Id raise a point: Romo never, *ever*, has been good in 2-minute mode.  He always takes too long to make reads/call plays, and far too often the passes are short and/or to the middle of the field.  This goes back his entire career.  Could be because the Cowboys have lacked the receivers to get open on long sideline routes.  I realize this is sacrilege, as seemingly everyone except me thinks they have such great star power at receiver.

But this doesnt have anything to do with the run v. pass argument.

**Conclusions (a kind of TLDR)**

The Cowboys didnt lose this game because they failed to run enough or because of playcalling.  They lost because:

1) they faced too many 2nd and longs, almost always because of mistakes by the OL (sacks, penalties);

2) they werent able to adjust to Rivers short drops, which eliminated any pressure and allowed the Chargers to take advantage of an inherent weakness in the Cover 2;

3) at key moments, drops by Bryant and Witten, and Williams fumble.

In short, this was a team loss.  It wasnt because they didnt run enough.


 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> BTB: is offense the Cowboys' weak link? (Should be titled: why are they passing so often on third and short?) </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-10-01 12:08:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Jones: Give Garrett credit </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-09-28 02:02:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Since when is this a thing? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-09-25 13:07:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Vendors offering to give refunds for positive reviews?  Of items in a quantity we didn't actually order?

Note: I had ordered one item from this vendor.  The redacted links pointed to multiple sets of the item.  (Redactions are intended to avoid giving the vendor publicity.)  

Received this email:

Dear Customer,  

Thank you for shopping at [REDACTED [an Amazon storefront)] some days ago.  
We are writing to inform you that you are one of the chosen buyers who have the opportunity to receive 15% of this order refund.  

To receive 15% of this order refund, all you have to do is to write a customer review on BOTH of product pages below.  

Steps:  
1. Click the links below:   
[REDACTED (points to item I never ordered)]  
[REDACTED (points to item I never ordered)]  
2. Scrolling down the page until you see 'Customer Reviews'  
3. Click the 'Write a customer review' button  
4. Sign into your Amazon account and write a customer review about our product. A five-star review will be highly appreciated!  
5. Send us an e-mail AFTER your customer reviews are POSTED on the product page.   
6. We will issue 15% of this order refund to you after we confirm your review.  
7. Deadline:2013/10/25.  
We hope the customer review can contribute to improving our products and services.  

Your participation will be highly appreciated.  

Best Regards,  
[REDACTED] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Cowboys 31 Rams 7: a few observations </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-09-23 12:40:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> As always, feel free to agree/disagree.  Please just be polite.  And explain your reasoning!

**1)** A good day to be a Cowboys fan!  They played well and actually looked good.  It's been a while.  Plus all the other NFC East teams lost!  Let's savor this feeling.

**2)**   The Cowboys found a running game two ways: (a) by running Murray through/off the tackles, and (b) by blocking.  However, it probably would be a mistake to expect him to play like this every week.  

Coming into the game, the Rams had [one of the worst-ranked defenses in the NFL](http://www.stltoday.com/sports/football/professional/rams-pass-defense-gets-another-big-test/article_8e2090cd-a86c-582d-938d-5df3a3b27028.html) and they clearly expected the Cowboys to pass.  When they changed their scheme late in the game (long after it was too late), they stopped the run.  And now that the Cowboys showed how they could run, defenses will know how to plan.  Then it will become a question of which team executes.

At the very least, that the Cowboys demonstrated that they can run will give defenses something else to think about.  Which is a good thing.

In any event, by running Murray outside, the Cowboys freed him from having to rely on his vision and having to make the directional decisions that had caused him so much trouble the first two weeks.  Freed from having to cut significantly, he was able simply to enter the holes and run.  This plan worked because of (b).  The holes the OL gave him often were *big*. 

Quite a few times he tried to juke, doing little wiggles, and the defenders absolutely did not fall for it.  He also started trying to change direction by spinning.  

I also noticed that guys had a lot of trouble trying to tackle him high, whereas the low tackles brought him down somewhat easily.

Still, he played well, taking what the OL gave him.  

Interesting that his two biggest rushing days have been against the Rams.

**3)** Speaking of the OL, it might be time to stop thinking of it as a weakness.  I'm not ready to call it a strength yet, but even against the Chiefs it pass-protected well.  In that regard, we've seen all season that Romo has had time to throw.  It's possible, if the Cowboys continue trying to run Murray outside, that they may be able to run-block, too.

Looks like Callahan's efforts--and the rotating door on the line--finally may have resolved the biggest problem on the team.  Consider: when was the last time we heard Doug Free's name called?

**4)** Is it too early to start considering George Selvie as defensive rookie of the year?  Yeah, yeah, I jest (maybe).  It's not like defensive linemen [never win](http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/National_Football_League_Rookie_of_the_Year_Award).  Unlike their counterparts on the OL (poor overlooked fellers).

Edit: as Greg604246 points out below, Selvie's a 4-year vet.  So it's not too early at all.  It's too late!

**5)** As a digression, check out how many of the great Cowboys' defensive players have won ROTY!  That's right: *none*.  Not even Thomas "Hollywood" Henderson, who had an excellent rookie year.  So he lost out to Robert Brazile, who became a [7-time Pro Bowler and 5-time All Pro](http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Robert_Brazile), while Henderson was out of the NFL by 1981, due chiefly to [problems with cocaine](http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Thomas_Henderson_(American_football\)).  He also won the Lotto Texas in 2000, so maybe at last he's found peace.  

**6)** I like Ware *much better* as a lineman.  His speed, moves, and strength let him do what he does best.

**7)** As much as I hate to say it, I have to say it: Austin's hamstring.  I actually thought of it shortly before he left the game.  On one of his two catches, he was tackled by a guy who was riding his back.  I thought, "Geez, that can't be good for his hamstrings".  Sure enough.

Listen, he was a bright spot for us for a couple of years when we didn't have many bright spots.  But once a guy's hamstrings start to go, they go.  I'm hoping he's not hurt too badly, but I fear that the rest of his career will be like this.

**8)** I cannot be the only one who, near the end of the game, actually wanted the team to pass.

**9)** Maybe it was obvious to everyone else, but for the first time yesterday I actually considered that maybe the Cowboys drafted Escobar as an eventual replacement for Witten.  Hey, I don't remember Bennett ever looking that smooth on any TD reception.

Given that Bennett only ever scored [4 TDs](http://www.pro-football-reference.com/players/B/BennMa00.htm) for the Cowboys, and none in his last 3 years with the team, maybe that's why.

**10)** Funny to see Witten in the backfield; he's always blocked better than any FB anyway.

**11)** Dez Bryant has 17 catches for 201 yards.  He won't hit 2,000.  But he's on pace to gain 1,000 yards, and with a big game here or there he may blow through that.  As long as he keeps working hard on every play, that'll be good enough for me.

**12)** I know, I know--every time Jones speaks he weakens the nation.  But he may have been somewhat accurate when he said that he didn't remember the Cowboys ever playing better defense.  Maybe he only meant since Johnson left.  (Those 90s defenses were *fast*.)

But since Johnson left, I might agree.  And that includes the 2 shut-outs at the end of [2009](http://www.pro-football-reference.com/teams/dal/2009.htm).  

Maybe it's been so long since I saw a good defensive game that I've simply forgotten what one looked like.  

I like the swarming tackles though.  Makes me wonder why every coordinator doesn't emphasize that.  

But let's not get ahead of ourselves.  Play with some of the categories at [NFL.com](http://www.nfl.com/stats/categorystats?tabSeq=2 defensiveStatisticCategory=GAME_STATS conference=ALL role=OPP season=2013 seasonType=REG d-447263-s=TOTAL_YARDS_GAME_AVG d-447263-o=1 d-447263-n=1) and you'll see they're still middle of the pack in almost every category.  11th in total points, 14th in Yds/G, 19th in Yds/P (yike!), 5th in 3rd-down percentage (oh-ho!  maybe that's why they're looking so good).  

They are definitely headed in the right direction, though.

Still, a real test for that defense comes in two weeks.

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> DeMarcus Ware set to pass Harvey Martin as Cowboys' (unofficial) all-time sack leader </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-09-21 02:55:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> For Dez to be considered great, he has to make the big catch </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-09-20 14:06:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Chiefs 17 Cowboys 16: a few observations </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-09-16 12:25:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> As usual, a few observations after the latest ~~debacle~~ game.  Feel free to agree/disagree; please just explain your reasoning.  

And try to be respectful.  As though you're talking to friends.  Because, hey!  Guess what!  Maybe you are.

1) The Cowboys beat themselves.  And they did it long before the two turnovers; they did it when they settled for a field goal when they were up 10-7.  Maybe when they settled for 7-3.  

2) On a related note, the Cowboys still haven't figured out how to reach the end zone.  So far they've scored 3 TDs and 5 field goals (not including the 2 TDs by the defense).  As Brad Schamm used to say, a field goal is a waste of 4 points.  So they've left at least 20 points on the field.  Good teams score TDs.

And no, I'm not suggesting that the offense is bad (though it still seems to be a work in progress).  It's just not *efficient*.

When the defense scores almost as many TDs as the offense, there's an issue.

And don't look now, but the Cowboys have been outscored in the second half in both games.

3) I'm surprised/impressed by the OL.  Though Frederick at times looked like a rookie against the Chiefs.  And it seems to be wearing down at the end, suggesting that there's an issue with conditioning.  Which isn't surprising, given the new faces.

4) This week, the defense played better than the offense.  Which should make up for last week, in which the reverse was true.  But it wasn't able to make the big stop when the game was on the line--instead drawing a pass interference penalty on the play that would've stopped the Chiefs' drive at the end.  And as [Apefist said](http://www.reddit.com/r/cowboys/comments/1m9kdr/the_turnovers_were_nice_and_all_but_the_cowboys/cc8d31g) right here, just last week: *live by the turnover, die by them*.  -2 turnover ratio = (far too often) a loss.

5) I am heartened by Dez Bryant.  Not because he's living up to his talent, but because *he's living up to himself*.  At my age, after what I was lucky enough to overcome in my own life, I have come to appreciate when others can overcome incredible adversity.  Bryant's play on the field is a direct result of his effort and focus in practice, and *that* is a result of his maturity and recognition that he's reached the point toward which he's fought his entire life.

Bryant's chance to pull himself out of the hole in which his background dropped him at birth is now.  And he's doing what he must to climb out.  Bravo for him!

Makes it easy to root for him.  And not because he wears a star.

6)  Re Bryant: I loved that diving catch.  And obviously he didn't commit pass interference.  And sure the game would've been entirely different but for that blown call.  But Bryant still has to learn how to fight off double coverage.  The Chiefs shut him down in the second half.  And the great receivers don't let that happen.

7) I'm going to keep saying it.  Over and over.  Because I was derided when I kept denying that Garrett's playcalling was the problem.  But it should be clear now to everyone that execution, not the playcalling, was and is the problem.

But for people who still insist it was the OC, sure, I'll instigate. Callahan's playcalling so far doesn't seem to be an improvement.  A sequence which didn't look like check-downs near the end, when Romo kept throwing to Witten in the flat, was downright awful.

And what was with that last play?

Good teams actually try to throw the ball down the field with 16 seconds left.  Could you imagine the Broncos, Packers, or Patriots calling that little dump to Murray?  

8) Witten has been so used to being ignored; in the past, he just could turn around and catch the ball.  But on one of those plays near the end, I remember thinking that he should've moved toward the ball.  I guess even a future Hall of Famer can have a bad play occasionally.  

That Austin failed to do it too didn't surprise me so much.

9) George Selvie reminds me of Harvey Martin.  What made Martin so excellent was that he never quit.  Selvie's like that.  I admire those who refuse to let anyone else outwork them.  It's one reason why Witten's been my favorite Cowboy for a long time.  But if Selvie continues what he's doing, he'll move right up that list.

His story of course is outstanding: unemployed, hoping for work.  He sounds like a vast number of Americans today.  What's not to root for?

10) Fans who've been waiting for Murray to give the Cowboys a running game (which includes, I guess, basically everyone) should skip this paragraph, because they're not going to like it.

But mark my words: Murray isn't the answer.  He runs like Herschel Walker, a tremendously gifted athlete who had, by all accounts, an astounding fitness routine (famously saying, at 50, that he still did [1,500 push-ups and 2,000 sit-ups each day](http://edition.cnn.com/2010/HEALTH/10/11/herschel.fitness.martial.arts/index.html)).  Heck, I'm in that age range, and if I can sit up out of bed it's a miracle.  

But Walker ran like a cannonball--that is, straight ahead.  If he'd cut it would have broken his ankles.  He lacked ferocity, though.  Unlike, say, Marion Barber III.  And he'd stop when people hit him.  

Yep, that was Walker: a Nerf cannonball.  However, he, too, was easy to tackle by the ankle, as is Murray.

Go back and look at the video (if you can stomach it) and compare Murray's running to Dunbar's (before the fumble).  Dunbar actually *cut*.  Murray, in contrast, tended to run right at the back of guys, even if gaping holes were on either side.  Last year he made some nice cuts, which was one of the reasons why I praised him over Jones.  But this year he hasn't.  Not sure why.

The greatest runners--Sanders, Dickerson, Dorsett, Payton--weren't just fast, but could use a defender's momentum against him.  Murray hasn't.

I realize I didn't include Smith in that list.  We can talk about why another time.  But probably we all know why.  Which isn't to question his toughness at all.  Smith had a tremendous hunger to succeed.

In any event, there's a reason why we've heard the phrase: *run to daylight*.

11) Jason Garrett in a [nutshell](http://espn.go.com/blog/dallas/cowboys/post/_/id/4714983/cowboys-looking-like-the-same-team-as-always): 

*"We just have to go back to work," Garrett said on being 1-1. "We don't really say anything to anyone who says anything about us. We'll evaluate what happened to us in all three phases of our football team and try to get better."*

12) As I've said before, the Cowboys are headed in the right direction.  But assuming Jones leaves Garrett alone, they're still at least a year away from being a genuinely good team.  Someone wrote last week: you can't question their top 10.  But it's everyone after that who's a question mark.

That said, it's not so hard now to get a sense of who they are.  At best they'll be 3-2 after the Broncos game, 5-3 at midseason.  *At best*.  

I'm afraid we're looking at another 8-8 year.  Anything better than that would demonstrate that they're growing ahead of schedule.  It would give us reasons for hope, like when they went 5-3 after Phillips was fired.

But teams can improve over the course of a season.  And they remain extremely competitive.  And they are, of course, ~~excrutiating~~ *interesting* to watch.

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The turnovers were nice and all, but the Cowboys rank 30th in total defense </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-09-12 21:21:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Cowboys 36 Giants 31: a few observations </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-09-09 12:22:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> As usual, a few observations about the latest game.  Feel free to agree/disagree.  Please just explain your reasoning.

(1) The Cowboys won.  Everything else is secondary to this.

(2) Six turnovers!  Six!  Nowhere close to the record for a single game, [which is 12](http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/List_of_National_Football_League_records_(team\)#Turnovers).  Still, in one game the Cowboys gained 37.5% of the total number of turnovers they recovered all last season.  It was the most turnovers recovered by the Cowboys since [December 14, 2003](http://www.pro-football-reference.com/boxscores/200312140was.htm).

(3) Despite the turnovers, not all of which were due to the defense, the Cowboys' defense looked *awful*.  In particular the corners were burned repeatedly and often.  Big play after big play kept the Giants in the game.  Doesn't bode well.

(4) I like George Selvie!  And that other guy--Hayden.  The defensive line played hard and seemed to pressure Manning a lot.

(5) Can I laugh now at all the fans who criticized Garrett the OC for passing too often?  By halftime--*halftime*--Romo had thrown 33 times.  He finished with 49 attempts.  How long before we start hearing that Callahan should be replaced as OC?

The simple reality is that the game has changed.  This now is a passing league.

And the Cowboys lack an explosive runner.  And with the OL still a work in progress, the Cowboys *have* to pass if they want to move the ball.  Last year's debacle had as much to do with Garrett's playcalling as last night's 49 pass attempts had to do with Garrett's playcalling.

Murray is not the answer, and if he keeps trying to run over guys, his career will be short.  Consider [Marion Barber, III](http://www.pro-football-reference.com/players/B/BarbMa01.htm).  More importantly, consider [Earl Campbell](http://www.pro-football-reference.com/players/C/CampEa00.htm), the most fearsome runner I ever saw, who only recently made news for [leaving a wheelchair for the first time in years](http://www.ktrh.com/articles/houston-news-121300/legendary-oiler-earl-campbell-is-out-11112906/).

(6) With respect to the OL, for the most part it seemed to play pretty well.  Romo had a ton of time on a number of plays.  I particularly liked, though, seeing Frederick help up the ball carriers over and over.  Then I started noticing other linemen doing it.  I'm guessing Waters will play well. Surprisingly, barring injury, the OL  may become a strength of the team.

(7) Guess we'll have to wait another week for Dez Bryant's assault on 2000 yards.  It shouldn't be news to anyone that Bryant will face double/triple teams all year.  He may be lucky to reach 1200 yards (which still would be an excellent season).

(8) Was anyone else surprised that Romo didn't go to Witten on that 2-point conversion?  Maybe simpler: was anyone not surprised when he didn't?

(9) Speaking of Bryant, I noticed that he was back to his old way of not making plays and then begging for penalties.  Listen: whether he actually was penalized isn't the point.  Jerry Rice, Lynn Swann, the true greats made plays despite the penalties.  Let's hope someone tells Bryant that.

(10) Dwayne Harris played great on special teams.  Second coming of Bill Bates!  Well, maybe it's a little early for that.  

(11) Everyone see that guy who was knocked on his butt by the Giants' defender?  It was late so I wasn't paying close attention to the players involved, but it was a heck of a hit.

(12) It was another entertaining game.  As long as Garrett keeps them interesting, I'll enjoy watching them play.

(13) FYI the Chiefs are not going to be an easy game.  Reid had them playing hard in the preseason, and they blew through a bad Jags team.  Alex Smith looks like the real deal, and the defense looks solid.
If the offense plays as inefficiently as it did against the Giants, the Cowboys may be looking at 1-1.

Edit: corrected numbering error Teves3D found.  Thanks T!


 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Could use info/help about NYC's Gifted   Talented program </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-08-31 05:44:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hopefully this won't get downvoted; we're really trying to figure out what to do for our son.

We found out today that our 7 year old got into the gifted and talented program for the second grade in Park Slope. We don't know anything about it other than its name (pretty much). He's currently in a Montessori program, where he's done well, but we're worried that the school's resources are somewhat limited and its class sizes are not big.

We could use any info we could get about the Gifted   Talented program's curriculum, how successful it is about preparing kids for middle school/high school, the responsiveness of teachers, class sizes, homework, etc.

Currently our plan is to try to get our son into the Mark Twain middle school, and from there one of the technical high schools.

Thank you for any info/help you can provide.
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Could use info/help about the Gifted   Talented program </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-08-31 01:14:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hopefully this won't get downvoted; we're really trying to figure out what to do for our son.

We found out today that our 7 year old got into the gifted and talented program for the second grade in Park Slope.  We don't know anything about it other than its name (pretty much).  He's currently in a Montessori program, where he's done well, but we're worried that the school's resources are somewhat limited and its class sizes are not big.

We could use any info we could get about the Gifted   Talented program's curriculum, how successful it is about preparing kids for middle school/high school, the responsiveness of teachers, class sizes, homework, etc.

Currently our plan is to try to get our son into the Mark Twain middle school, and from there one of the technical high schools.

Thank you for any info/help you can provide.
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> PA: our same sex licenses invalid </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-08-29 12:14:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> PA: our same sex licenses invalid </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-08-29 11:59:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> How a creepy stranger co-opted an Observer photo to infiltrate a small town </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-08-28 15:09:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Dollars and sense of releasing Ratliff </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-08-28 14:41:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> First 4 of 11 cuts include Stephens </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-08-27 22:58:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Sturminator says, among other things, that it's still all about the OL </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-08-26 19:25:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Murray benched in 1st quarter of Bengals game because of fumble </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-08-25 21:44:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> A few preseason observations </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-08-25 14:18:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> As we approach the last week before the start of the season, I thought I'd offer up a few observations.  If its too long, feel free to skip it.  Nothing you couldn't have seen for yourself.

Otherwise, though, definitely feel free to agree/disagree--but explain why!  Just don't downvote anyone's (relevant) comments, as all observations are equally valid until the season starts (yep I borrowed that from the [uncertainty principle](http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Uncertainty_principle)).

In no particular order:

**1)** The Tampa 2 notoriously is a bend/don't break defense.  This is because of its ability to create turnovers and the contraction of the defensive backfield as the other team approaches the end zone.

With respect to turnovers, I've always loved when the Cowboys have gotten them.  They really do stop the other team dead in its tracks, thus interfering with its process.  It's easily understandable why they correlate more than any other discovered factor to wins.

I'm not so sure, though, whether fumbles (as opposed to interceptions) should be attributed to the Tampa 2 as much as the coaching.  On the one hand, the Tampa 2's emphasis on gang tackling encourages them, as, while one guy holds the ball carrier up, other defenders work him over.  But based on what I've seen, the Cowboys this year are *tackling* differently.  Instead of going for head/shoulders (which guys never should do) or legs, they seem to be going for the *ball*.  This is leading to all those fumbles.

It makes sense, as if the defender hits the ball first instead of the body, that ball's going to come out more often than not.  Anyone remember the scene with Jeff Bridges and Rosie Perez in the excellent moive [Fearless](http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Fearless_%281993_film%29)?  I recommend the movie highly (though it's kind of a downer).  In it, Bridges' character, the survivor of a commercial airliner crash, demonstrates to Perez's character why there was no way she could have saved her baby, Bubbles, whom she was holding in her arms.  I won't say how he does this, so as not to spoil the moment, but the concept is the same.

It's possible this is a part of the defense, with its emphasis on gang tangling.  But I don't see why almost every defense couldn't teach this technique.  Still, whatever the reason, I've loved the defense's ability to create turnovers.  

Also, I'm not sure the Cowboys have gotten so many turnovers because the other teams haven't been very good.  The Bengals were a playoff team.  The Texans will be a real test.

**2)** In the past, I've been a very critical observer of Dez Bryant, saying that he hadn't demonstrated maturity on or off the field, that potential counts for nothing (remember that great line in the Pogues' song [Fairytale of New York](http://www.youtube.com/watch?v=HwHyuraau4Q) "I could have been someone/well so could anyone"?).  But the absence of news stories suggests that he really has figured out that this is his chance, his one opportunity to overcome his life--and if he's embraced that concept, I overwhelmingly cheer for and support him, as one person to another.

On the field, he has dominated every game when he's been in.  He appears to be uncoverable, and there's only been one other receiver I'd ever thought that about.  His name is Jerry Rice.  His on-field performance has demonstrated his emphasis on taking advantage of the chance he's got.  If he takes advantage of that, he'll be a Hall of Famer.

**3)** The OL still looks pretty bad.  Yeah, yeah, injuries.  But they had injuries last year too.  And the year before that.  Every team has injuries.  That's why the best teams build up quality depth.  Still doesn't look like the Cowboys have it.  Maybe it's an issue of first teamers v. everyone else.  But it's been hard to tell who the first-teamers are because of the injuries.  This will be an ongoing question as the season progresses.

**4)** Alex Tanney looks at least as good as Kyle Orton *right now*.  Almost every single pass has been dead on the money and delivered with touch.  I don't remember which play it was, but on one, he just floated it over a guy right to the receiver (Benford, I think).  His ability to adjust his passes puts him way ahead of Vinny Testaverde, another strong-armed gunner.  And Testaverde had a [20 year career](http://www.pro-football-reference.com/players/T/TestVi00.htm).  His biggest drawback was too stong a reliance on his arm, combined with an inability to adjust his passes, which caused him to force too many, which led to all those interceptions.

Tanney, in contrast, has demonstrated that touch.  I don't know what he's doing that's not making coaches see how special he may become.  Whatever it is seems to be stopping his career.  But he seems to me to be the real deal.

That doesn't mean he doesn't have things to learn.  He's not paying enough attention to the pocket, and that's leading to some ugly sacks.  Of course though to some extent that's on the OL.  See #3.

Everyone praises Orton as a backup QB.  But, as long as it doesn't cause dissention, I'd rather have 2 guys I'd want running my team as QBs, even if one is in development, instead of a "starter" and a "backup".

I like Tanney, and I think he could be not just a starter, but a quality starter, in the NFL.

**5)** Though I could make more, this will be my last observation, as the post is too long already.  

The defense is averaging 17.25 points a game so far.  Sure it's preseason, a lot of it's been against the Dolphins/Raiders, etc.  But even if the Bengals aren't on the level of the Pats/49ers, they're still a good team.  And they only scored 18.

But injuries are what decimated the Cowboys last year.  So we'll see what happens this year.

The offense may be better, due almost entirely to Bryant/Frederick.  But the Cowboys only will go as far as injuries/the OL lets them go.

I'm not sure any success will be sustainable yet.  This team still seems to be one good draft away. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Baby panda born 8/23 at the National Zoo </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-08-25 01:15:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Running game to blame for Romo's record? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-08-24 04:10:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [TOMT] [Editorial cartoon] demonstrating how much could be bought for $1 </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-08-23 17:28:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I realize this isn't a typical TOMT request, but the mods suggested I post it, so here goes.

Some years back, in a book of Americana, I saw an editorial cartoon, which even then must have been old, depicting a little boy in a shopkeeper's store, perhaps around the turn of the 20th century.  The little boy had $1, and he was listing all the items he was supposed to buy with the money.  I don't remember what all they were anymore, but they probably included household items like flour, eggs, sugar, cloth, seed, etc.

At the end of the list, the little boy said something like, "And mama says with the change left over I can buy some candy".

I'm trying to find that cartoon again, but the name of the book it was in would be even better.  I don't remember much about it.  It was hardback and had a lot of different articles, including (probably) stories about Custer, native Americans (called Indians back then), and, well, I just don't remember what all.

Anyhow, this is like an advanced TOMT challenge.  So thank you for any info you can provide!   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> There is no happiness like mine </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-08-23 16:20:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I received this message today. Words fail.

The only editing I did was to include the link (which he had included but couldn't be copy/pasted here) for context.

The message I received:

Hi, you might not remember me but my name is Scott. About a year ago I posted to /r/atheism about how I was considering committing suicide. [Link](http://www.reddit.com/r/atheism/comments/rr0bl/im_not_really_sure_if_i_should_ask_this_question) 

And in said thread that I made you wrote one of the most wonderful and amazing life stories that I've had the honor of reading. The situation at that time wasn't good, and it only got worse. For about 6-7 months I lived on the street. And it took me awhile to learn to ask people for things like spare change etc, as I didn't like asking people for handouts.

So anyway, I ended up living in the streets in the city when one day my older brother walks past. I was asleep at the time and he woke me up and broke down in tears. He said that he had been looking for me for quite some time but gave up. He had been kicked out of the Jehovah's Witnesses religion as well, thus ex-communicated from the family. So he was trying to find me to see how I was doing. He invited me to move in with him, so currently I am happily living under a roof, in a warm bed. 

Also I am now attending university, to become a primary school teacher. I only just recently started so it's still very new to me. Anyway, I just really wanted to thank you for your amazing story. I can honestly say that I don't think I would be typing this, if it wasn't for you. Your story gave me hope. Hope that despite things being shitty, that there was a better future. 

Thank You.


 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> BTB: Ranking the Cowboys' mid-preseason roster </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-08-21 19:59:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What does the notation in the sidebar "users here now" (or its various iterations) actually mean? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-08-21 15:25:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It can't mean the number of people browsing subs, as various tiny subs I moderate, which generate no traffic at all, (see r/waxahachie) show, for instance,  "~3 users", when the traffic is never higher than 1 (me).  I mean, sure, at some level one is approximately three, but that doesn't seem to be what's happening.

Thanks for any clarity you can provide. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [TOMT] European movie about a (possibly Roma) girl who loses her job on a food truck </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-08-20 16:14:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It came out since the 90s.  In it, a very poor girl, possibly a Roma, would keep things cold/secure in a bag she'd sink into a pond.  She'd put on big boots that she didn't keep at her house.  She'd trek a long way to her job on a food truck.  She suffered from some sort of cramps, possibly menstrual.  I don't remember exactly why she lost her job; maybe the cramps caused her to miss too much work.  Maybe a guy was stealing from it and she was blamed for it.

My impression was that the story was about this poor Roma girl simply trying to get by in the world.

I think its title started with a P and was reminscent of the Japanese animated film Ponyo. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> A reliable USB external 3.5" floppy drive? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-08-17 22:36:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Request: /r/40plus as it has no mod and its creator has not been active for 3 years </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-08-16 15:52:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> At 123+ years old, Carmelo Flores Laura is the oldest person ever documented. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-08-15 13:49:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> WISD earns top marks </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-08-12 18:59:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Garrett's opening day speech at training camp: a must-see for every Cowboys fan </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-08-08 19:41:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Cop arrests woman who lied during traffic stop </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-08-07 21:26:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Cop arrests woman who lied during traffic stop </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-08-07 19:57:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> PFF 32 teams in 32 days: Dallas Cowboys </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-08-07 14:12:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Does anyone know how to contact Tim Wisseman/recover VGA Planets registration info? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-08-06 04:39:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Alex Tanney trick-shot video </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-07-31 14:49:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The redemption of Doug Free? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-07-26 21:09:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> FYI for those who can't see their favorite team's preseason games: the NFL has an online preseason package for $19.99 </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-07-25 12:10:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Very basic starter question re touch sensors </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-07-24 17:56:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I am not robotically inclined at all, but I'm trying to help my son learn how to use the NXT 2.0.  Its manual says that ports 1 and 2 are for touch sensors; however, the NXT itself says that port 2 is for a sound sensor.  When we tried to plug in 2 touch sensors for a simple forward/back program, the touch sensor in port 2 did not seem to work.

I've seen programs on nxtprograms.com that use touch sensors in ports 1 and 2, so what are we doing wrong?

Thank you for your help--and sorry to ask what must be an obvious question. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Moby: The Day [3:22] </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-07-24 01:59:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Trailer: Spike Lee's remake of Oldboy </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-07-12 04:17:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Internet trolls: what to do about the scourge of the web? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-07-11 20:40:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> DNA may crack Boston Strangler case </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-07-11 20:39:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Jimmy's Cowboys: A Sports Illustrated short history lesson (written while it was happening) demonstrating who really was responsible for the Cowboys' 90s success </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-07-09 17:00:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> TIL every U.S. state has an Extension office, a (mostly) free governmental educational network staffed by experts who provide info to agricultural producers, small business owners, and others about a large variety of topics. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-06-27 03:01:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Our Darker Purpose: roguelike Kickstarter project with unique graphics style </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-06-11 17:53:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Ken Tarr's reality TV racket: he hoaxes an industry addicted to sleaze </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-06-11 14:29:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Three Days of the Condor (1975) </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-06-09 06:18:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Has anyone heard if there's going to be a sequel to Metro: Last Light? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-06-08 14:47:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm somewhat familiar with the development cycle, the bankruptcy, and so on.  But that had to do with THQ, not 4A Games.  

Anyone know of any news? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Josh Brent tests positive for marijuana </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-06-06 23:23:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Bank robber foiled by man wielding candy dish </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-06-06 12:03:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Judge sides with Murnaghans, orders Dept of Health/Human Services to consider 10 year old for lung transplant </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-06-06 12:00:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Slam Bang Theater opening theme song circa 1960 </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-05-12 18:05:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> BTB: notes from day 1 of the rookie minicamp </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-05-12 05:11:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Waxahachie on Good Morning Texas </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-05-11 04:44:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Northside students receive special glimpse of earth </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-05-11 04:43:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Two 7 year olds suspended from school for pointing pencils at each other and making gun noises while they played </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-05-08 21:10:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Interesting comment buried in an article about Frederick: the Cowboys drafted him in the 1st round because they wanted to sign him for 5 years (contract length: an issue experts don't seem to consider) </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-04-30 17:39:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> General musings after some 40 years as a fan </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-04-28 15:37:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> After many years I've finally realized this isn't the Cowboys team I grew up idolizing.  The first game I actually remember was [this one](http://www.pro-football-reference.com/boxscores/197212230sfo.htm).  Staubach came in at the end, after missing most of the season with a shoulder injury, and pulled out the first of his many legendary miracles.  The next week the Cowboys were blown out 26-3.  :p  

Anyhow, for years before that, and many after, the Cowboys symbolized, at the very least, professionalism and competence in their leadership.  They haven't symbolized that again, of course, since Johnson left.  Which isn't to say that Jones isn't a brilliant businessman, but no sports fans support teams because their owners are good at brand-building.

As I've mentioned before, Garrett really is my last hope for the Cowboys to be good again in my lifetime.  He's got what it takes intellectually, and I don't mind the mistakes as he learns.  I just want to see improvement.  So if Jones actually does stick by him and surrenders to his intelligence and football competence, they have a chance.

Most of the fans who complain about him, I think, maybe actually didn't play football past, say, junior high.  I played in college, and I can say that, based on my experience, how he handles team-building and the media is precisely how a good coach would behave.  *Praise publicly, critique privately.*  I'm not sure I first learned that on a football team, but it's certainly an approach to leadership I admire, practice, and support.

The problem is of course Jerry.  People talk about Stephen like he's going to be better--and he might.  But I haven't seen anything suggesting either way.

Anyhow, if Jones fires Garrett, I think I finally might be able to cut the cord.  I look around at the teams that do symbolize the values I admire in life--the Steelers, Giants, Ravens, Packers.  Some of those teams have ridden the cycle of success that the NFL generates--but at least they've been on it.  Other teams, like the Raiders, Cowboys of late, Chiefs, and so on, fell off and never got back on--because of the quality of their leadership (or lack thereof).

I wouldn't want to follow a team because of the personality of a coach or player--those things change.  But a system or approach I could appreciate.

Or maybe really at my age it just might be time to let the NFL go.  I can't say it's made my life any better being a fan.  It's been much more enjoyable and rewarding to be a fan of my wife, my children, my friends.  That it would take a lifetime to overcome the brainwashing of propaganda speaks to the strength of societal forces.

We really do only have a limited time in which to accomplish our lives.  I know, when we're young we think we have forever.  We think nothing of days spent like [this one](http://www.poetryfoundation.org/poem/177229).  But as the clock ticks, as we grow up, accomplish, and age, we realize inevitably the transience and brevity of existence.

As youths, we accrue things to care about.  Often because friends/society have told us that we should care.  But as we age, we begin to push those away which we find irrelevant or, often, which don't live up to our standards.

So we'll see what happens this year.  The Cowboys almost certainly won't be Super Bowl champs.  Honestly, if they even make the playoffs I'll be amazed, as the second half of their schedule looks hard.

But under Garrett they have grown from a lackadaisical team demonstrating the complete lack of effort they showed in that [Packers game](http://www.pro-football-reference.com/boxscores/201011070gnb.htm), which resulted in Phillips' firing, to, last year, a scrappy, *interesting* team, which, despite its mistakes, never once gave up trying or grew dull.  

As that pretty much describes every person of note, for now they seem to be a team worth following.  If Jones just can resist his mercurial impulses to interfere, they could be developing into something.

In life, character, will, effort all matter.  In a way, Garrett is conducting an experiment to see if the same things can change the course of an NFL team. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Garrett likes Frederick's makeup, football integrity, character, and intelligence </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-04-26 19:41:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Milwaukee Journal Sentinel: Frederick slowest center in 20 years, but possibly smartest player in draft </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-04-26 19:38:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Police looking for suspected road rage driver in incident captured by security camera in Beverly Hills </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-04-25 14:45:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Excellent program. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-04-24 03:44:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Fertilizer plant explodes in West, Texas (near Waco) </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-04-18 03:32:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Requesting r/services: creator deleted and no mod (would like to use it for non-commercially advertising purpose) </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-04-09 04:30:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Don't compare Romo to Super Bowl winning quarterbacks </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-04-01 21:01:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Woman fired for being homeless (or elderly) already has a new job </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-03-30 23:20:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> A short conversation with an atheist friend </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-03-30 19:29:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So I had a conversation recently with a friend who, it turned out, claimed to be atheist.  She's the only atheist I've encountered to whom I could say what I'm about to tell you without becoming offended, and even she bridled.

I told her that even the absence of belief was a belief system, though it was a system defined by her perspective of the value of logic and experience.  I also told her that in my experience when I encountered an atheist, s/he often thought I was religious, and when I encountered religious people they often thought I was atheist.  In any event, she said that she found the idea, that she might be defined by the fact that she didn't believe in an imaginary being, as mildly offensive.

However, I then asked her if she believed in the tooth fairy.  When she said she didn't, I said neither did I.  And I said that even though I don't believe in it, I recognized that not believing it was a choice I'd made, and that to whatever tiny extent my life was affected by that choice, it had defined me.  For instance, if I had a tooth capped, I didn't save the pieces/debris of the real tooth and put it under my pillow.  And I told her that by not believing in the tooth fairy, I wasn't being defined by what others didn't believe, but instead being defined (to a tiny extent, of course) by what I did believe: that a tooth fairy didn't exist.

She didn't really have a response to that.

It strikes me that we are so fearful of what we believe/don't believe that we often resist even considering that we might be wrong.  But we often define ourselves by who we're not.  And we become angry at others for reminding ourselves of it.  

That is not a righteous anger. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> TIL that in 1983 the US participated in 'Proud Prophet', a nuclear war game which resulted in 1 billion dead, major parts of the northern hemisphere uninhabitable for decades, and Reagan, that old hawk, saying, "A nuclear war can never be won and must never be fought" (links to Google books) </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-03-27 16:12:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> I've now lived longer on this earth than my dad. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-03-26 03:24:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> He died young.  A smoker.  When people just were beginning to realize how bad it was.

I've seen this day coming my entire life.  Now that it's here, I don't have any startling observation.  Except maybe that his life was far too short; the whole of it was encompassed in just a few years.  His dreams, aspirations, desires, accomplishments.

All of it gone now for almost as long as he was here.  Except me.  I remain.

His death when I was 6 (and then later my mom's) defined so much of [who I became](http://www.reddit.com/r/atheism/comments/rr0bl/im_not_really_sure_if_i_should_ask_this_question/c47zg09).  Who I am.  My relationship to my own children.  To my son, my eldest, now 6.  

To the world.  My profession.  My own dreams.  My understanding of mortality.  Everyone I've met.

There's just an absence, as there has been my entire life.  A sorrow that never went away.

I wonder what he would say.  I wonder that I've gone so long without feeling his touch.  Of course I don't remember his voice.

It's been decades and still I miss him. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [META] Thank you to everyone who offered to help moderate our sub! </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-03-18 00:38:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The mods would like to thank everyone who offered to help moderate our sub.  The applications generally all were excellent, and the applicants all impressed us with their interest, enthusiasm, experience, and ideas.  Thank you.

Our discussion about who to add was engaged and considered.  The decision was not easy, in light of the quality of persons who applied.

Ultimately we decided only to add three--chiefly in an attempt to balance our need for help with our disinterest in causing unnecessary disruption.  Each of the persons we finally chose has been engaged in the community and has demonstrated a lifelong interest in writing.  Which in no way should suggest that the persons we did not choose are not.

R/writing has grown a lot over the past year.  We look forward to continuing to try to provide what writers need, whether the approach is as a vocation or avocation.  We remain open to your ideas, suggestions, and criticisms.  We do genuinely appreciate every user and our obligation to provide as functional an online space as possible for you.

Thank you again for your help, and welcome to our new mods!

Regards,
MP  
on behalf of the old mods </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The Scar, by Sergey Dyachenko   Marina Dyachenko: one of the best fantasy novels I've ever read (and I've been reading fantasy a long time) </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-03-17 04:42:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> r/Waxahachie: a place for news about a thriving town in Texas </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-03-03 06:15:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> /r/Waxahachie is a place to post about the Gingerbread City.  If we ever can get enough traffic, that is. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> BTB statistical analysis: Did the Cowboys overachieve or underachieve in reaching 8-8? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-02-01 19:37:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> BTB: The Jerry Jones/Jason Garrett relationship </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-01-25 15:00:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Jay Ratliff arrested, charged with DWI </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-01-23 03:15:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> BTB: 2013 roster talk, free agent moves, draft wish list, etc. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-01-22 17:11:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Breaking down the Cowboys 2013 salary cap: where is the money best spent? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-01-15 20:14:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> 5 college football studs who can (help) turn the Cowboys around </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-01-15 20:13:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Wondering why the Cowboys wouldn't pursue Armond Armstead </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-01-13 16:24:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Larry Lacewell on Monte Kiffin: best hire Cowboys ever made </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-01-11 18:00:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What could Monte Kiffin mean for Dallas? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-01-11 14:20:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Garrett needs a commitment or should be fired now (excellent illustration of how Jones has interfered with the team over the years) </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-01-11 12:30:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> An alternative viewpoint on the firing: suggests Ryan wasn't Garrett's first choice and opens the door for them to return to the 4-3 </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-01-09 02:59:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Star Telegram: Grading the 2012 Cowboys </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-01-08 19:04:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> BTB: positional rankings of the NFC East </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-01-08 13:52:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> There'll be no change at Valley Ranch until Jones makes the one change everyone knows he should (and never will) make (not the headline of the story but the gist of it) </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-01-04 16:31:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Comment from a mod of /r/cowboys </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-01-04 15:02:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm a mod in r/cowboys.  It's late for me to be the first to say congratulations to you guys for the tremendous progress the Redskins showed this year.  But let me say it anyway: congratulations.  If Griffin can stay healthy, he and Morris may be excellent for years.  And Shanahan, of course, is a proven winner who seems to be following his formula for success.

That said, the mods weren't aware of [this post](http://www.reddit.com/r/Redskins/comments/15j4cm/cowboys_fan_here_any_bet_any_takers/) and wouldn't have supported it if we were.  He obviously is a kid or a blowhard, and this post is an embarrassment to sports fans and an affront to reality.

I won't apologize for his conduct, because of course I didn't have anything to do with it.  But this kind of post doesn't encourage the spirit of healthy competitiveness that lies at the heart of every sports rivalry.

The first Cowboys game I ever noticed was [this one](http://www.pro-football-reference.com/boxscores/197212310was.htm).  Over the years, I've seen a lot of excellent Cowboys/Redskins games and a lot of dogs.  I've seen each team rise and fall in precisely the manner the NFL seems to like its teams to develop.

I don't know how many years I have left (none of us do), but I anticipate a lot more entertainment from this rivalry and a lot of good-natured ribbing from fans of both sides.  If I never see or hear of another comment like this guy's, I won't mind a bit.

I wish you guys a lot of joy in the playoffs.  Best to you all. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Garrett is open to changes, including giving up playcalling </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-01-04 00:57:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> That Was the Worst Christmas Ever!  A holiday diorama set to the music of Sufjan Stevens </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-01-01 05:15:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Sunday's about more than Romo (excellent perspective on the current state of the team) </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-12-28 21:02:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Cowboys excited about playing the Redskins </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-12-25 05:00:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> NFC East race: the case for the Cowboys </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-12-21 22:05:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Cowboys suddenly look like legitimate playoff contenders </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-12-17 18:32:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> BTB: Cowboys played v. the Steelers with 5 of their opening day starters on defense </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-12-17 18:29:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Emotional Jason Garrett talks about tragedy </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-12-10 00:48:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Mom wants dead son's student loans forgiven; lender refuses </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-11-30 15:58:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> World's largest super collider: abandoned </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-11-29 00:15:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> NYC: gotta love it. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-11-23 14:18:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> I love Amazon, but... </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-11-23 03:38:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Sometimes shopping on it is so miserable.  I read a lot, and I don't want a kindle, but I haven't figured out yet how to shop for hardbacks *and* paperbacks within various genres without jumping through a bunch of hoops to filter out kindle.  

I also buy toys for my kids.  But even that sometimes is ridiculously difficult, as it seems that unless I find the perfect search term I miss out on lots of possibilities.  Not to mention that sometimes, oddly, Amazon prime items don't show up at all.

It would be nice to combine sort options, like *number* of customer reviews and "avg. customer review".  Or to have more sort options than the 5 provided.

Or to have the option of more than 24 showing in a list.

Amazon is just not an easy site to browse.

Hopefully this won't get down-voted too much, because I'd genuinely appreciate any suggestions people have on how to use the site more effectively. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> BTB: do the Cowboys have a problem with reality? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-11-21 17:22:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Aphex Twin - Windowlicker </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-11-18 02:39:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Bryant issued conditional dismissal--which requires him to attend anger management course and stay out of trouble for a year at risk of sentencing </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-11-15 15:51:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Morris Claiborne: the Cowboys in microcosm </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-11-13 04:28:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> FEMA closes disaster center, abandons Staten Island in anticipation of approaching nor'easter </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-11-07 18:04:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Units unlivable, renters review options </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-11-07 18:02:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Don't assume Jones wants to fire Garrett </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-11-05 18:57:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The Many Deaths of Lady Boyle </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-11-04 06:43:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Why you shouldn't buy Dishonored </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-11-04 06:33:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> BTB: Who to blame for the INTs </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-11-02 23:09:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The most preposterous team I've ever seen </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-10-29 01:08:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Surely in the history of the NFL there have been teams that have caused their fans more heartbreak.  Maybe I was spoiled by 35 years of mostly success, so I never noticed them.  But I do not remember ever seeing a team play like this one.

Bryant at one moment can look like an ungainly stork snagging a fish and the next he can do an idiotic thing like not make the proper adjustment or just forget not to sling his arm out when he falls--thereby costing them the game.  Best WR on the team is the TE.  2nd and 1, 3rd and 1, 4th and 1, game on the line, 3 passes in a row.  A starting RB who isn't quick and doesn't know how to make a cut.  One of the greatest QBs statistically in the history of the league constantly belittled because his WRs are imbeciles.

I've just never seen anything like this.

Obviously Garrett lost all confidence in Jones; that's why he ran the ball--what, only 2x in the second half?

Only recommendations I could make to Garrett: 1) don't start Jones again; 2) let someone other than Bryant catch punts.

Recommendations for Jones: 1) for God's sake, set aside your ego and hire a GM who knows how to evaluate players; 2) no  matter what, don't let Ryan go; 3) institute a ticket rebate for fans who can prove they screamed the whole game. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> PS3 hacked again: all future games decryptable, no solution possible </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-10-26 04:23:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Frank Luksa, 77, dies </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-10-24 12:49:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Study finds: relationship with dad affects teens' sexual behavior </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-10-19 12:34:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Westboro member stomps on flag at funeral of soldier killed by suicide bomber--attending soldiers re-enact Battle of Iwo Jima </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-10-19 12:32:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Garrett doesn't listen to Jones </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-10-18 02:19:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> In article titled "Jason Garrett admits to mistakes", pretty much everyone admits to mistakes (except Austin) </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-10-16 14:24:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Romney says: no American dies because he or she doesn't have health insurance </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-10-12 15:35:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Old School RPG: Kickstarter project by Tom Hall (Commander Keen, Doom, Anachronox, et al.)   Brenda Braithwaite (Wizardry, et al.) </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-10-08 18:52:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Morris Claiborne has been a pleasant surprise for the Cowboys </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-10-07 08:43:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> How to replace/reprogram your keyfob </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-10-06 18:19:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Waxahachie celebrates National Night Out </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-10-04 23:55:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Car dealership has buyer arrested after it sold car for wrong price </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-10-03 12:35:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Family which falls sick days after moving into new home discovers it previously was a meth lab </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-10-02 16:02:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Followup: Stuyvesant students describe how and why of cheating </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-09-27 12:17:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Sources: ref lockout to end soon </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-09-26 22:50:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> After Packers/Seahawks debacle, Aikman tweets: "these games are a joke" </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-09-25 14:54:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Man mauled after leaping into tiger area at Bronx Zoo </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-09-22 13:19:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Man mauled after leaping into tiger area at Bronx Zoo </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-09-22 13:18:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Is Russia's Lake Labynkyr really home to a monster? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-09-20 12:24:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> BTB: Projecting the 2012 Cowboys </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-09-19 04:08:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Cowboys expect Tate to be fined for hit to Lee </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-09-17 04:48:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> After 4 decades of planning, Roosevelt Island's Four Freedoms Park set to open in October </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-09-14 12:29:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> WHO: ebola outbreak out of control in Congo, risks spreading to major towns </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-09-13 16:54:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> WHO: ebola outbreak out of control in Congo, risks spreading to major towns </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-09-13 16:53:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> WHO: ebola outbreak out of control in Congo, risks spreading to major towns </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-09-13 16:52:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Man who claimed he was too racist and homophobic to serve on jury now faces prosecution </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-09-12 15:58:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Man who claimed he was too racist and homophobic to serve on jury now faces prosecution </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-09-12 15:58:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> 66 students face suspension at Stuyvesant over cheating scandal </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-09-10 12:29:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Lovers - Barnacle </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-09-09 19:58:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Jason Garrett's postgame speech </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-09-07 17:08:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> AZ woman receives $83,046 bill for 2 doses of medicine to treat scorpion sting--which would have cost $200 in Mexico </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-09-05 13:06:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> AZ woman receives $83,046 bill for 2 doses of medicine to treat scorpion sting--which would have cost $200 in Mexico </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-09-05 12:49:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> British family finds medieval well under living room floor </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-09-05 12:27:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Moments after tweeting "YOLO", driver crashes, kills self, 4 others </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-09-04 14:49:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Friendly warning: account was hacked. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-09-03 20:44:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I've been playing onliners for *many* years.  For the first time ever, yesterday my account was hacked.  When I tried to log in, I was told that my email address couldn't be found.  I also received an email from Arena Net saying that my email address had been changed.

I put in a ticket but apparently there's a big backlog on hacked accounts.

Also apparently there's a method in place for making email addresses difficult to change, which is based on the email authentication system.

I had tried to authenticate my email address many times (every time I logged on) without success.  Apparently Arena Net knows about this problem too.  I kept getting a message (if I remember correctly) that the URL wasn't valid.

No idea why Arena Net didn't require email confirmation of email address changes.

Anyway, further, apparently Arena Net disabled changing passwords to try to prevent hacking.  Obviously didn't do much good, since all the hacker had to do was change my email address instead.

And no I didn't share my password or account info with anyone.

Hoping that eventually I get my account back, that it hasn't been raided and everything cleaned out.  Not like I had a lot in there anyway.  But, still, what I had, I'd earned.  I wasn't involved in the karma hack.  Not even sure what a karma weapon is.

Just wanted to submit this as a caution to everybody.  Make your password *complicated*.  I thought mine was, but it wasn't enough.  

Hopefully I won't get downvoted just for letting people know about this. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Man formerly prosecuted for killing cop and cop's friend posts crime scene photos of victims on Facebook </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-08-31 18:22:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Man formerly prosecuted for shooting cop and cop's friend posts crime scene photos of victims on Facebook </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-08-31 18:21:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Man fractures penis after taking sex supplement </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-08-31 13:15:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [NSFW] Man fractures penis after taking sex supplement (who knew an article without photos could be NSFL?) </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-08-31 13:14:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Farther wears skirt in solidarity after 5 year old son teased for cross-dressing </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-08-31 12:47:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Father wears skirt in solidarity after 5 year old son teased for cross-dressing </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-08-31 12:46:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Guy nearly suffocates after wrapping himself in box and mailing himself to girlfriend </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-08-30 17:12:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Hiker who violated quarter-mile rule for grizzly bear killed/eaten after photographing it for 8 minutes </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-08-30 14:25:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Hiker who violated quarter-mile rule for grizzly bear killed/eaten after photographing it for 8 minutes. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-08-30 14:24:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Researchers: Chocolate each day may keep strokes away </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-08-30 12:29:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> TX rape defendant vanishes during trial </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-08-30 12:24:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> 100 year old driver hits 11 near LA school, including 9 children </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-08-30 12:22:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
