<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject8628</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-18 17:57:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Never had udon noodles. Looks delicious  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-18 16:16:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Beautiful.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-18 16:14:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That will make a great scooby doo mystery. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-05 18:41:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Better than investing in a bank, buy gold. Buy some every month. Even the smallest amount will work.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-05 17:39:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The one where you must take a train to reach the witches. Can't remember the name.

Edit - it's called train http://www.creepypasta.com/train/ </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-05 17:27:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Noroi  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Why are Indians so nerdy? I'll tell you why. We were invited to a "festival celebration" and the welcome session was about Vedic Mathematics!!!! </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-04 13:59:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-02 13:34:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Behind those hair, are tiny earphones playing punk rock  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-01 16:06:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Who farted. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-01 16:05:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Wtf is that? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-01 16:05:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Haha. I was watching Scooby doo just now. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-31 16:16:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Eaten with Honey. I have to try that. 
I doubt I will find that style of pizza here. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-31 15:17:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> OML. I can haz one , no?? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-31 15:16:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If you ate this, what did the ancient mariner eat????? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-31 15:15:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Awesome. Bravo  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-31 15:14:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What's a mountain style deep dish?? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-31 15:14:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Eat it.......Swiftly </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-31 15:12:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Looks a bit cocky  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-31 15:12:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Can you do neon? I heard it's a fad these days  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-31 15:11:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thos are some huge fries  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-31 15:10:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Indian food....... Mmmmmm. Great shot. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-31 14:17:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This is a very engaging account of events. I relaly liked it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-24 17:11:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yes. That's correct way to write. I love that series. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-24 08:08:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Until they take 500 and actually buy books, Ian not biting. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-24 08:05:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yours was the red one? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-24 08:04:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Not a lot of that happening. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-22 20:49:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Taken from yamishi bai. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-29 15:38:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's called gada in Hindi or mace in English. It's a weapon. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-29 15:37:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That is the most amazing thing I have seen all week. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-29 15:37:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Your nana is kool. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-29 15:37:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Lol, brilliant  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-24 14:05:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I know. I live in Bagis  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-23 21:24:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Sdermalm's natives are hipsters </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-19 13:42:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Please narrate. Thanks !!! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-16 20:36:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Oh mine mine. :)
And glwyc !! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Incident on the highway </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-16 20:28:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> 
The first thing that came to my mind when I decided to write this incident was that maybe I should just let it be. Forget it. After all, it has been more than 12 years. But then, I thought to share it.



I live in a big city up in northern India and yes, its crowded and yes the traffic sucks. It was 2003 and the winter was settling in. For those of you who do not know much about northern India, I can tell you that it can get pretty cold up here. 



I was 20 years old back then and had just landed a great job with a very good company. I was a technical support guy working for a company based out of US. This meant that I ended up working graveyard shifts. And truth be told, I loved it. It gave me the freedom to be out of home at night and do what I liked doing best, helping people and having fun at job. More so, because I wasnt the only 20 year old there. The entire building was full of them. So naturally, there was fun and excitement and I really did like working there.



I lived in the city but the job was at the, what was then called a satellite town. Mostly because it was still not developed enough to be a city but was close enough to the city. Since this was mainly rural setting and mainly because majority of the workforce worked in graveyard, the company provided us with transport. These company cabs would pick us up and drop us back to our doorstep. The cab would be routed to pick up people in the same area and then drop them back too. Pretty sweet deal that was.



Anyways. I had already spent a few weeks working and had made quite a few friends. As a routine, at the end of our shift, before we took our cabs back to home, all team mates would get together the cab area before moving towards home and discuss days gossip over some chai.



Days passed on and on. I remember that on this one dreary, overcast, foggy winter night, I was waiting in my cab for other cab mates to come so that we could be on our way. It must have been 3 AM. I was tired and wanted a good warm bed. As I lived furthest, I was usually the last one to be dropped. I didnt like it but I couldnt do much about it.  I waited and finally one by one they all came and we were on our way. The cab driver who was new started talking about himself and how he moved in from a distant village to this town last week and was happy driving a cab. 



With all the small talk happening, we moved swiftly on the highway until we met a traffic jam. Great, just what I needed. It has started to drizzle and traffic jam was nowhere near over and soon we came to a standstill. We all waited impatiently for the next few minutes when I decided to get out of the cab and get some air and see whats holding us. A friend and a common partner in crime agreed and we both got out and started walking towards ahead. We soon realized that the reason was an accident ahead and that this would take us more than an hour to cross. It wasnt a serious accident but a crane was needed to pull the vehicle out and the way was blocked.



We came back and told everyone much to their despair. Now, everyone who has been to India says the traffic is bad. Well it is. It is also like water. It flows. If something is stuck, people find a way around it. Customary to most cab drivers, our driver also got down and flagged a cab going down the other way. They two driver chatted and he came running back stating that the other guy has told him about a shortcut on the other side of the highway. We agreed and he quickly drove down the median and took the U-turn, cut across the other lane and we were now heading into the bylanes of small settlements that lie strewn across the highways.



A few minutes had passed and we soon realized that the driver does not know the way and that he was confused. Not to our help, it starting pouring. I guess monsoon gods were against us that day too. It was still 12 years ago to GPS wasnt too common and none of the phones had it. 



We soon turned onto what looked like a deserted road with no street lights. One of the guys in the cab then said this was the old highway was abandoned because of design faults and that it had led to many accidents. It ran parallel to the new one but was hidden from sight because of the settlements.



The driver was trying to navigate through the potholes and was driving not too fast. Wed been driving for 5 odd minutes now and just then two things happened. It felt like something had hit us from behind and we heard a shout. It wasnt too loud not too feeble. It was more of a shriek that came for further behind us. A shriek of fear. I was sitting next to the driver and turned back instantaneously. From the corner of my eye, I caught a glimpse. A glimpse of something. Something womanly.



There were 3 girls in the cab with us and at first I thought one of them had screamed but then I rejected that thought because I knew all of them and I knew it couldnt be any of them. The driver was a bit shaken since it was no fault of his and someone had hit him from behind. He got out in the downpour and went back to see the damage. From the light of his cell phone, the driver checked but to his satisfaction, didnt see any visible damage. I also got down along with my cab mate and had a look. Three of us agreed that there was no damage and this thought what could have it been. We came back inside and concluded that we may have hit a pothole or something and that the shriek may have been from an animal nearby. We called it a coincidence and drove along.



However, I knew that this wasnt the explanation I was going to believe. I have had a few experiences in the past that were unexplainable and this was becoming one of those. I knew that I had seen a womanly figure as soon as I had turned at the sound of that shriek. And I sensed that everyone else felt the same. 



We still had a long way to cover but the rain had stopped. To cheer everyone up I turned on the radio and a we moved along. We were still on the old highway but the driver had not picked up any speed because the fog had settled in after the rain. Just then, it happened again. Another hit and another shriek. This time more announced and much more closer. This wasnt good and I knew something was wrong. When youve spent all your life in a country like India where religion, superstition are a way of life and no matter how much you try not to believe them, you come across things that make your rethink. 



At this time, all three of us, except the ladies, got out of the cab and went to inspect but some good thinking on the drivers part, he kept the engine running. We got out and knew this time it was different. This time, we saw the damaged bumper. It had been bent quite so to suggest that it had been hit badly. It was dark outside but we could still make out the blood that was on the corner of the bumper. We knew we had hit someone. But we hadnt gone more than 10 feet after the hit but we couldnt see any anyone around lying or hurt. At this time, the driver of the cab asked both of us to sit inside the cab with the ladies. He wanted to go further down the road to check but he had an intuition that this could turn bad if this was a trap of some kind to stop and rob unsuspecting people. We followed his advice and came back inside while he went to check.



What happened next has lived with me forever since. We all waited for the driver to come back. Not soon after, he came running back. Crying and white as if the blood has drained from his face. He had blood on his hands. More than he had before. He was terrified and his survival instincts had kicked in and without delay, he drove away fast. He kept going and we kept asking him what had happened. He didnt answer any question but kept crying and kept saying just one think Sahab, picche mat dekhna which meant, DO NOT look at the back though the rear window. All this while he himself kept looking at the rear view every other second.



After driving like a few minutes, we finally came back on main highway and a sense of safety came upon us. The well-lit highway gave us the much needed settling of the nerves. Seeing that the driver had calmed down a bit, I asked him to stop at the next gas station.



Once at the station, the driver broke down completely. Seeing a grownup man crying like a child was not a sight we 
were expecting but we calmed him as much as we could and he told us what had happened.



He said, when we walked down the road to check for any injured person, he heard a laugh. A laugh of a woman. He said, that she was on the side of the road just laughing. She was pretty and dressed up as a newly married Indian girl. With her red dress and her jewelry and all her makeup. He asked her what she was doing alone at this hour on this abandoned road. At this she stopped laughing and started moving towards him. When she came close enough he could see that..that her feet were turned backwards. He saw her face has changed to a grotesque, deranged face of an old woman.



At this he started running. He ran as fast as he could to reach the cab. And when he asked us not turn back and see, he wanted to save us from seeing the old lady that was following our cab, even at the high speeds at which he drove. In his words, she was right behind our cab all the time.

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
