<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject5571</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-10 19:37:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> As I had previously said, I had no evidence to back it up, just went to Berlin and heard it from a bunch of guides. Based on people's reactions there's clearly misinformation going out there. Much of the information over seen recently has said it's Turkish so yeah. Man people get pissed about food. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-10 18:51:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This website may not be the most accurate but the American Invention of the dish is fairly well documented, check it out online. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-10 17:10:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Is that real? I mean I've heard of Walt Disney doing it but is it something you can practically do without millions? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Redditors that wrote a will in their twenties, how did you feel after doing it? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-10 16:58:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-10 16:42:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I heard this from a few different tour guides while in Berlin, I had never heard of the origins in Bursa but you could be right, I must check it out, thanks! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Redditors that made a will, did it put your mind at ease or simply make you worry about things more? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-10 16:40:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-10 16:00:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The Donor Kebab was invented by a Turkish man living In Berlin using Turkish Ingredients. The wrap was added to the meat and vegetables simply because the food had become very popular with drunks late at night (shocking) and to avoid drunken customers breaking any more dishes, the owner found it easier to enclose the food in a wrap and send them on their way.

Although it is largely associated with Turkish food and sold by Turkish owners, the Donor Kebab is generally accepted as originating from Berlin.

Personally I think that you can get ingredients from all over the world to make any number of dishes but it takes its significance from the culture in which it developed, which in this case was the US. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [Serious] What has been the most successful argument for the existence of a higher being or afterlife? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-10 13:31:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> TIL that spaghetti and meatballs was invented in America and not Italy. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-10 13:11:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-10 09:25:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I thought it was called life </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-09 22:01:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> My bad I didn't read your comment properly. I get ya! And yes it is shocking the amount of influence that our expectations can play on a students life. I often look back at my own teachers (some of whom I actually work with now) and wonder how it might have influenced things. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-09 21:38:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> As a teacher I can honestly say it's not our knowledge. We don't know how kids are going to turn out. That's the problem. We have to, despite years of experience telling us a student will grow up a certain way, there's a chance they won't and we may be responsible for sending them on the wrong path all because of our bias. This is a big factor in why minority children perform poorly. Teachers expect them too. But we're not all bad. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-09 19:49:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Well no, it's not prophecy. The more important aspect of this idea is that you need to believe in yourself. Sounds corny but it works. Don't settle for a box in any old alley. Choose your alley. Maybe live in  car. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-09 19:47:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I think I can't, I think I can't, I think I can't.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-09 18:39:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yes that's actually the bigger problem. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-09 16:57:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You are correct. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-09 15:48:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> As an English Lit and EFL teacher in Ireland I completely agree. I've found that it is often the students own negative beliefs about themselves that we have to fight the most. Great to hear this sort of thing more. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> TIL that wearing a head guard in boxing and other combat sports is unsafe and is slowly being phased out. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-09 15:11:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-09 14:54:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Conversely see the Pygmalion Effect. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> TIL of the Golem Effect, the principle that we essentially meet the negative expectations held by those superior to us such as management, teachers, parents etc. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-09 14:53:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> TIL fans of Heavy Metal and Classical music have similar personalities. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-08 05:21:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> TIL that having an American or British passport could get you killed in a terrorist attack. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-08 05:07:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-08 00:41:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I thought that was a stand alone film no? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-08 00:41:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Really? How would you justify such an unjustifiable belief? Magic surely. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-08 00:36:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> As a teacher, the honest answer is that whether you get good grades or perform poorly, you can find yourself pretty much anywhere in life. 

Poor grades can sometimes simply be a result of a system that benefits certain types of people and not because you're stupid. I've known people who've failed academically and are now very happy and successful having applied themselves later on in life.

Similarly, you can get good grades and still end up getting fired, or homeless, the economy may turn, people may leave you. The only thing you can ever truly do is apply yourself to everything you do, the pride in your work and develop dreams that will make you happy in life and when life screws you over (which it will from time to time) stand up, brush yourself off and start again. As long as you've tried your best you can always hold your head up high in life. 

Try to achieve good grades, but if you don't, dont worry, try something else. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What sequel/prequel was better than the original film? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-08 00:26:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Has there ever been a sequel/prequel that was better than the original? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-07 22:54:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Where's the best place to stay in Rome? Ideally close to the sites and with a Bar? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-04 22:27:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-04 20:11:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> For a start, teachers and management generally do not like travellers. I've experienced a lot of different schools and in  every staff room the inappropriate comments and jokes about travellers are plenty full. Yes some teachers are fine but it's a very difficult thing to witness. This affects how they are treated in class and the children are aware of this. They know they are hated, I can't imagine wanting to send my kids to an Irish school if if was a traveller parent. Educational difficulties are also widely ignored with traveler students and they don't receive the help that government bodies and studies have shown they need. Traveller culture, history and language is also not welcomed or expressed in schools. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The body of an elite Chess Player </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-03 20:51:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-03 08:53:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Where did you get them? Could you share the link? They look fantastic! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> To any War Veterans, how do you view the idea of "neutral" countries like Ireland in light of current threats to global security, Is it justified? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-03 03:21:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> To any War Veterans, do you take issue with so called "neutral" countries like Ireland when it comes to dealing with global security threats. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-03 03:11:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-02 06:14:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Trying to get out there at the moment for just that reason. Not a big traveller but I don't want to regret not doing it while I had the chance! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-02 06:12:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I have never heard of anything like this suggested being rolled out in Ireland but it sounds fantastic. We did a bit of that in training but that's it. I think there are too many in the profession that are afraid of being judged on their performance which is insane when you realise that every other job has some forms of performance reviews. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [Serious] Estranged redditors, how do you cope long term with having no contact with any relations or a traditional family? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-02 06:08:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-02 06:05:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You're even younger than me, way to make me feel old on this thread. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-02 06:03:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Just starting to notice that now. Not the best feeling in the world. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-02 05:53:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Teaching. We continually preach to our students to be open minded and look at education as a lifelong endeavour. In reality many teachers look unfavourably at any sort of change to our profession and fail to attend even the most basic continual professional development courses. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-02 05:50:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I took drama for a while as a kid. One day during lunch break I was messing with a friend and I ended up soaking him pretty bad with water. The drama school director happened to catch us and gave out to me. Over the next few weeks he'd repeatedly tell me to bring me father in so he could talk to him. I was terrified I was in trouble so I kept fobbing him off until I eventually quit. Turns out they wanted me for an advertisement and needed dad's permission. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Over 30 year olds, what did you not appreciate about your 20s until you were much older? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-02 05:41:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [Serious] What do schools need to do? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-01 05:42:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hey, I'm a secondary school teacher in mayo. I can't say I'm connected to the travelling community because that would be a lie but I as a teacher I have a lot of respect and time for travellers, I'm quite close to the lads I train with. I would like to know, going forward, what ye would like from teachers and the education system for your kids? I ask this because I know the system is biased and doesn't treat traveller families fairly. Genuinely looking for advice as a young educator who doesn't have a lot of experience but wants to learn. Cheers. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-01 00:48:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thanks! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-01 00:48:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I might do that! Thanks for the advice! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-01 00:45:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> She didn't for the first year. Took a while. Apparently they're not a great breed regarding housebreaking. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-01 00:44:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I agree with Mr Sydney. Whippets are typically like cats when it comes to cleaning. I hear guys aren't as clean (I have a female) but that's just anecdotal. Don't worry really. It's normal! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-01 00:35:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Not yes.
Not no.

It depends on age, a young whippet doesn't have as much padding as an adult. However whippets feet are quite soft normally.

If it was on a rough ground over a long time then that might have done it. But...

Ask your vet. If a dog bleeds from its feet it's a problem full stop. It's not normal. But don't beat yourself up over it. Whippets are one of the most peculiar breeds around. These things happen. Ask your vet, they're the expert. Good luck, everything will be fine! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-29 22:12:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Awesome, thanks for the advice! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-29 15:57:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thanks! We don't mind the whole "it's a lot of work" thing because she's a whippet so she already a ton of work. But what's the deal dehydrators? As in do they all work on the same principal or should I be on the look out for one that uses a specific process? Never used one so to me it sounds like a vastly complicated device! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Raw food treats? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-29 15:13:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm not a big fan of giving our whippet, Sky, treats during the day but I find it great for training. I haven't come across any raw food treats that aren't pretty packaged, Ide rather make them myself but don't know where to start. I could freeze small portions of her regular food but that wouldn't really last because when they melt they'd just go everywhere again. Any help would be really appreciated! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-29 15:11:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> My whippet sky had issues with her digestion since we got her as a pup a year ago. We literally tried everything, antibiotics, specialised pet food, treatment for colitis. Nothing worked and she was loosing weight and bleeding from her anus quite badly. Then we switched to raw on a last ditch attempt and intant success. Would never go back to anything else. Hope everything works out for ya! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-26 16:10:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It was like the worst withdrawl from caffeine. I just remember headaches and like above, upset sleep patterns. As long as you're following your doctors advice re: how to quit, for me it was halving then quartering the dose but yours could be different, you'll be fine.

The clearest feeling was that of a cloud being lifted and feeling more like me again. Drink water and try some herbal remedies for the sleep in the meantime. You'll be fine  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-21 01:52:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Robin Williams: 24 hour photo and Mrs Doubtfire. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-21 01:32:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Just scrolling through and saw this comment. Very sorry to hear you lost someone one loved. Look after yourself, hope your doing ok! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-21 01:28:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Glenn from the walking dead. The real death. Apart from the fact that he was such a pure and kind character, he was my main reason for watching because everyone else seems to spend the season going through an existential crisis. It also killed the show for me. Haven't watched it since. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> ELI5: Why does hot water freeze faster than water at cooler temperatures? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-18 11:53:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> She wouldn't get up so we just had to make the bed around her </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-18 11:49:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Why do Android phones only download updates when you unlock them as opposed to the inactive periods when they're not being used? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-08 19:44:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Why do Android phones only download updates the second that you unlock it as opposed to when I'm not using it? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-08 19:28:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-05 00:06:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I don't know how you get Harvey to sit like that beside the tree, Sky would be up on that like a cat! Cute little guy! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-05 00:02:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Ah I see, thank you. And no, we live in the west of Ireland. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-04 22:42:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What's an AWC breeder? To be honest we got her from a breeder in Wicklow and although we did our research I don't know how reputable the process was. For our next whippet were going to go with a more well know breeder in Ireland.  Live and learn I guess. Why do you ask?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [Advice Request] How do you deal with estrangement long term? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-02 01:59:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm new to this forum and was looking for advice with regards to dealing with estrangement long term.  I'm at a point now where I'm moving on with life, I'm happily married as of this year and estranged about two years properly.

What I find hard is the idea of being very much alone. In a sense I feel as though I lack identity or roots. U often envy my wife's relationship with her family and I find myself caught in a contradiction. I wish I had some one that I could call family, someone who (and I know this is selfish) is just for me. At the same time I don't want that from my parents.

How do you cope with this in adulthood?

Note: I have attended counselling and dealt with a lot of issues but got to a point with them where they simply said "well this is kind of how it is for you now" </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-01 21:40:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thanks! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-01 21:39:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Good advice, I think I'll go with that, cheers! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Are there any helpful sites regarding Le Canne? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-30 14:26:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I've been practicing Assaut for a few years now and would like to take up Canne, are there any links you know of that provide any guides or instructions? Any help would be greatly appreciated. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Advice Needed: How long can a BARF mush meal last when refrigerated? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-30 14:01:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> My whippet is going to be Kennelled for a few days over the weekend and I've prepared her food (minced beef, bone, offal and veg) and sealed them in plastic bags in the fridge. Realistically how long can that food last as I know the Kennel doesn't offer raw food. I also can't give her regular food as she has colitis and kibble makes her bleed. Any advice would be greatly appreciated. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Sky's gotten into the spirit of things early </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-16 21:37:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-16 20:50:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Awesome </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Our little Sky. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-15 18:43:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-14 02:43:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> To be honest in not a uniquely Irish thing, although I do it myself. It's a habit formed by cultures that had a large amount of poverty. A lot of Asian countries share the same practice if bringing fruits and vegetables from home with them. Originally it was something we brought over out of neccesity but in modern times its more of a cultural habit. You don't see it with other western countries because they didn't have the same level of widespread poverty as we did. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-09 02:02:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> We're used to her pooing like 10 times a day so we're looking forward to a change. Cheers for the advice! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-09 02:01:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I didn't know about the fasting, I don't think is have the willpower either. Cheers! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-09 01:59:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Just about to order my first load, cheers for the advice! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-08 13:05:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> OK so a lot of recommendations for the BARF diet, definitely going to look into that, do you notice that they poop less in the BARF? I know it sounds odd but our poops really often and I heard the raw diet makes them deface less, could be hearsay though. Cheers for the advice! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-08 13:00:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm unfamiliar with the BARF diet I must look in to it. So you would alternate days with veggies and meat or simply include vegetables on certain days. This sounds really interesting though, cheers! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-08 12:58:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> We live in the west of Ireland. We've only recently started to look into raw foods as an alternative so I'll take a look at some of the stockists in our area. I guess my biggest concern is making sure she gets a balanced diet. Also have you found they defacate less with the raw diet? Ive heard anecdotally thay it does. Cheers for the advice! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Raw food diet: Any experience with this in Whippets? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-07 22:49:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Our 1 year old Sky has colitis and my wife and I are trying to find alternatives to the food she is on at the moment. We're looking for some advice regarding what sort of foods a whippet would require if you're using the raw food diet and perhaps what to avoid.

Edit: I've never seen such a change in Sky since we have put her on the BARF. Her colitis is clearing up, she's actually eating her food and she's in all round better condition. Thanks everyone! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-19 17:36:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thanks for the advice, I'll definitely try the white noise at night! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Advice: Foster with Abandonment Issues </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-16 09:25:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> My wife and I have just fostered a 4 year old male greyhound and he has some awful abandonment issues, howling and pacing at night and he shadows us everywhere during the day. Our 1 year old Whippet doesn't seem to give him much comfort and the foster group didn't have much info on his past.

Any advice on how to make him more comfortable would be great!

Edit: I know that there is an adjustment period but I've had dogs before and never experienced anything like this. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-01 13:38:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Passable. I've to take the course to get my grade up to Higher C. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Teachers who transitioned from Post Primary to Primary </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-01 12:06:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm currently a Post Primary teacher in Ireland considering making the move to Primary education. What have been some of the positive and negative aspects of your transition? Bear in mind I'm an English teacher so used to quite a heavy workload. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-22 18:23:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That's okay, the apartments contain noise pretty well but it's good to be aware of that, thanks for the advice! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-22 18:21:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The separation anxiety is a big thing for us, hopefully this will help her feel more at home. Thanks for the advice! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-22 18:20:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> A lot of people have said the male and female combination works best too, thanks for the advice!  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-22 18:19:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I guess you're right about the puppy stage not being over yet, but I think it's worth the effort. Also I'm going to use the "potato chips" line again. Thanks for the advice! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Should we get a second Whippet? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-21 21:50:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> My wife and I live in Ireland and currently own a year old female. We have done the research and are happy to get a second for us and we believe for company for our current Whippet. We live in an apartment which has as much space as your typical house and we live across from a field where we run her every day.

My question is this. Do we need more space for a second Whippet? She spends most of the day sleeping to be fair and gets plenty of exercise.

We are also wondering whether we should wait for her to get older. Our Whippet is nearly a year and the pup would be three months, should our Whippet be older? 

So ar we have followed all the advice and would really like a second but we also don't want to act irresponsibly. Any advice? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-18 01:42:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> My wife and I had the same problem with our ten month old. She would chew wires and pee around the house. The advice we received was that Whippets are more comfortable and less stressed in a smaller space. We keep her confined to the kitchen (door open to the back and toys out) and don't let her in the rest of the house. The kitchen  is quite small too. So far we've seen a big improvement from when she had access to other rooms. 

Other small tips that we found helpful:

- Don't make a big deal about leaving, especially if you have a routine before you go (keys, coat etc. ) if a Whippet with separation anxiety notices these are signs your leaving it can cause stress.

- Make sure you're cleaning pee with non-amonia or bleach products. It may act as a marker. Detol spray works for us.

- Have talk radio on in the background.

- Leave something in the room that smells like you.

Best of luck! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-03 17:08:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thanks for the advice,  know she's intolerant to poultry, and I agree IBD might be too general of a statement. I'll look into a specialist here in Ireland. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Advice: Iritable Bowel Syndrome in Whippet </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-02 17:03:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Looking for some advice. Our 9 month old Whippet has been recently diagnosed with canine IBD. We're unsure of the cause. Up till now she has had really loose and bloody stools and the hypoallergenic food has helped.

Does anyone know of foods or treats for Whippets with this. I don't really want to do the while trial and error with her because it takes top much of a toll on her digestive system. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-02 13:45:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thanks I would've had to go back for it later. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-02 13:33:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You know you're Irish when you spent a whole summer trying to beat Metal Gear Solid in one go because you had no memory card. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-02 13:25:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-02 13:13:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That Deep Heat wasn't actually De-Peat </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-02 04:20:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If something you did made someone else think you were bi or gay when you ctually weren't, would you then be bi or gay?

Your version of heterosexuality may be different to another man's. That doesn't mean his is less valid. I hate the idea of dressing in women's clothing but I don't begrudge men doing and I know that straight men do it too. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-02 04:09:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I admire your point about believing in treating people nicely. I'm White and Irish so like you (I am only assuming) that you're not part of a group that has been overly stigmatised as of late.

Just because you're not xenophobic or racist doesn't mean you're not doing something wrong. I lived a lot of my life with the belief that because I feel everyone is equal I couldn't put a foot wrong.

We need to educate ourselves about the realities of other cultures or groups and assuming that you know all you need to know about cultural sensitivity is a mistake. Someone who is very clued in on LGBTIQ issues may know very little on Aboriginal issues etc. It's not beong politically correct. It's about educating yourself. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-02 03:57:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I know that my best friends father isn't his real dad. His biological father left when he was really young and his stepfather has been there for most of his life. He hates the man, hes even stolen from him, but he  never let on to any of us the truth. We only found out one day when another friend's mother let it slip in passing. To this day no one has ever spoken to him about it. I guess it feels wrong knowing it without his permission. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-02 03:47:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I think we have to consider two things here (no kids but hope to in the future).

1. What we consider "adult content" shifts from.generation to generation and even then is largely subjective based on culture or family. Sex was a big threshold in my family and wasn't talked about at all before a certain age when I had the talk, Sex scenes would be skipped over all the time. My friends' family considered homosexuality to be an "adult" concept and as a result never heard of it until about 5th class.

2. We should accept that parents cannot properly censor most of the content their children take in on a daily basis. When I was a kid I heard about adult stuff from my friends in hushed tones. Nowadays your average music video or reality TV show is far more explicit.

As a teacher I think honesty is the best policy, don't shield your children from these things because you can't. Get out in front of it. Let them know what is realistic, what is appropriate and they will come to you in time with questions. Avoid the issue or make it taboo and you're creating a problem. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
