<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject8814</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> TIL a study found that 95 percent of corrupt Chinese officials had illicit affairs and 60 percent kept a mistress </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-09-08 20:33:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> TIL one researcher gave schizophrenic children LSD   psilocybin, sometimes both, to allegedly good effect in the 50s and 60s </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-08-17 18:59:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-08-13 20:21:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> From the site: "Last summer I took a sacrament I think the literature refers to as toad slime. In this particular experience  its a nine minute, uh, moment... I turned into a very large black woman. I was surrounded by beings who were children  all suffering, hungry, frightened, sick. I found myself opening my arms to draw them all into myself. At the same time I was both gagging on it all, and in absolute ecstasy, the ecstasy of just being part of the total dance of life, not looking away from anything."
 
--Ram Dass, Notes from a Psychedelic Revival Meeting </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> TIL that when "spiritual teacher" Ram Dass smoked toad venom, he thought he'd "turned into a very large black woman" and was "surrounded by beings who were children--all suffering, hungry, frightened, sick." </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-08-13 19:57:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-08-12 20:50:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Here's the study, linked to in the story: http://journals.plos.org/plosone/article?id=10.1371/journal.pone.0134152 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Scientists have described the first social octopus </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-08-12 20:40:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-15 18:28:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Can it just be listed as "Biology"? I've submitted to r/science before and not had to choose a flair, is this a new rule? Thanks much. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Coffee beetles' guts contain 14 bacteria that can survive on pure caffeine, allowing them to withstand toxic levels of the stimulant </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-15 15:19:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-25 00:40:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> They also receive little public attention since they've abandoned their consumer product lines and made much of their fortune making aniline dyes in the late 1800s / early 1900s. Source: http://www.nytimes.com/2013/01/12/opinion/a-cycle-of-contamination-and-cancer-that-wont-end.html </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> TIL BASF is the world's largest chemical producer and was founded 150 years ago </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-25 00:37:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-16 23:49:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's described more on the wiki for snubnosed eels: https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Snubnosed_eel

"In 1992, two snubnose eels were discovered inside the heart of a 395 kg (871 lb) shortfin mako shark (Isurus oxyrhinchus) landed at Montauk, New York. The two eels, both immature females, measured 21 and 24 cm (8.3 and 9.4 in) long and had fed on blood, with histiological evidence suggesting that they had been there long enough for arteriosclerosis and hyperplasia (indicative of circulatory obstruction or toxicity from metabolic wastes), and tissue regeneration to occur." </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> TIL that eels can burrow their way into a shark's heart </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-16 19:35:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Google is testing huge internet balloons in an enormous freezer </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-15 19:40:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
