<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject1966</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-08 02:11:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The Baron smiled at me, the bright light overhead reflecting off the slime on his yellowing teeth. His skin was tinted orange, his hair bleached; long and luxurious white robes flowed down his body, masking his true shape and size. Perhaps he was a lean, towering, giant of a man. Perhaps he was as a crone, his back misshapen and body frail. Regardless of what he was, his army of Crakors had caught me. My hands were cuffed to the pipe behind me. I managed, with effort, to stand, to face him at eye level.

"You're a monster, you know that? You slaughtered them- all of them, and for what? To capture a damned Prince? My father isn't even dead, you dolt, much less willing to pay a ransom for me. So what's your game?" I let my voice rise steadily, threw in an edge and a growl as I went. I'd learned a thing or two in Downtown Theater. If I put on a good enough show, maybe he'd shit himself and let me go without a fight. 

Wishful thinking. My mind was already crafting a plan B and C, knowing damn well A wouldn't work.

"My game," the Baron asked. He smiled, his hands folded around a silvery staff. Power was flowing off it, invisible to the naked eye but strong enough to burn my skin, even from a good six feet away. "is not one of diplomacy. Your father is a cruel man, my Prince; he was beaten bloody by your grandfather, disciplined and hardened until nothing but contempt for the world remained. He sees only war, and until now, has had no reason to believe he could be stopped."

I pressed my back against the pipe I was chained to; the Baron was drawing closer, and the intense heat from his Relic was beginning to burn. "If it's not about diplomacy, then what is it!? Why'd you take me and not my father? Why me, and not the heir to the throne? Roderick would be the next in line- if you sought to cripple the Kingdom, why would you go for the lesser Prince?"

The Baron hesitated, frowned, licked his lips. "You sound so certain that Roderick is fine- that he himself isn't already dead."

My heart stopped for a moment, before I saw the lie in the Baron's eye. "Impossible. Roderick is kept at Father's side, day and night. He's being groomed for the throne as we spea-" 

The Baron's grin returned. I'd stumbled into the answer.

"And if Roderick is being groomed by Father... it stands to reason his rule won't differ all that much."

The Baron patted my shoulder. "There we are. Naturally, Roderick is turning out to be a fear mongering, bloodlusting little prick in the side of the betterment of the World. You're all but dead to your father anyway, my Prince. When was the last time you saw him with your own eyes?"

I thought about it. 

"Christmas, almost a year ago. He's forced me to stay in the Sister Palace ever since."

"He'll never know you're gone; not until you turn up at his doorstep with an army in tow."

I stared at this man, wide eyed... And then that stare turned into a glare. Treason. "And where in the nine fucking Hells am I to find an army willing to die for me? You expect me to take on the Kingdom- all fucking twelve of the realms- and usurp my Father's throne? Are you insane?"

The Baron laughed.

And laughed.

And laughed. And then he hefted his Relic into the air and drove the sharp end through my chest. It burned; the wound cauterized as he drew the mystic weapon back out. I gasped for breath as my vision returned. 

"I just might be, boy, but I'll not be taking no for an answer... Will you be a Puppet King for me?"

I drew in a ragged breath, turned my eyes up to his, and spat. "Never."

The Baron leaned in close, until his nose was touching mine. His breath was sour, drenched in wine. "That answer will change, once you come to understand true insanity." He rose to his full height, turned away from me, and tapped the Relic three times on the ground. "Send in the Bison Fucker," the Baron boomed. 

He left the room with six long strides; the mechanical doors whirred shut. Somewhere behind me, another set of doors opened. I tried to twist myself around the pipe to see, but could only barely make out a large, blood-soaked knife, bobbing up and down through the air.

"Buffalooooo," came a twisted, broken voice. It sounded like a man, but with the curiosity and innocence of a child... "Buffaaaaalooo," he called again. His voice had gone up a few octaves; I could practically hear his heart beating as adrenaline built up in him. His naked feet slapped wetly on the ground, a sharp sting touched my right arm, a harsh grip crushed my throat, and suddenly a faceless man was staring into my eyes, an eternal, lipless grin pressed against my mouth, saliva dripping down onto my shirt. He was hungry, his face had no skin, and his knife was digging into my right arm. It burned just as intensely as the Baron's staff; it was a Relic.

"Buffalo!" The Faceless Man screamed, and he carved a chunk out of my arm. "Buffalo, Buffalo," one of my fingers was between his teeth, blood sprayed onto his pant legs. "Buffalo, Buffalo, Buffalo, Buffalo-" with each utterance of the word, the Knife dove into my stomach, lopped off an appendage, carved a new symbol into my skin and muscle and bones.

"Buffalo," the Faceless Man said, one final time. He gripped my head and slammed it into the pole. Just as consciousness began to flee, I saw the Faceless Man retreating. The Baron had returned.

This wasn't the end.


----

((I know I stretched the rule a bit. Apologies.)) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-24 04:54:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Reich* </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-11 05:10:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> the knife presses into coro's arm, pinches at the flesh, draws out a little bit of blood. the brown coat is smiling maliciously, his eyes alight with some hellish flickering feelings. the brown coat has had coro here for days, since before the council invoked the mutual morals act.

what the council had not anticipated was this; the enemy did not need to kill to win. they only needed to have greater numbers. the enemy simply captured its foes, broke them, diced up the unnecessary bits and left the rest hanging in a room somewhere, getting fed the absolute minimal nutrients by machines. not a single human was being killed; they were just being removed from the battlefield.

coro, however, was not a human being. coro was a divine, and the brown coat knew it. his blade drove deeper into her arm, poked at the bones, scratched at the runes inscribed on them. coro bit her lip, focusing all of her power on keeping the ichor from flowing. if it flowed...

"Of course, you'll know exactly the reasoning," the brown coat said. "It only takes a drop, and then any mortal creature transcends, takes on a totally new biological makeup. Just one drop, dear, and it can all be over."

coro yelped as the knife drove home, piercing her arm bone and letting the golden ichor flow free.

'the council,' she cursed to herself. they'd failed to consider one simple fact.

'it is a war crime to kill another human being...'

humans may not kill humans, no; but humans could kill divines. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-17 07:49:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Red rover, red rover, please do come over.


Dead snow.


Loathe to speak, less to hear.


Angsty teens, man.


What was that for?


Snow hills.



Loathe to speak, less to hear,

Lest I whisper in my ear.

Snowy hills and great sand dunes, 

too often I find both remind me of you;

barren baroness, having made me a widower,

the snow, the sand, the trees- all i've seen, and been, and gone to to die

i find you in it all, and your face, taken in tragedy,

watch as it stays my hand. you always watch, damn you, and refuse to let me visit.

Loathe to speak, less to hear,

some nights, my mind grows queer

calls you a bitch and a whore and a monster and worse...

god, to not be in *pain.*

Snowy hills and sand dunes, and trees, and seas, these eyes've seen it all, baroness.

Shall I visit? Is it time? But no, you don't listen to the words. The pleas I give you.

You'd rather I move on and live.

Loathe to listen, not to hear.

I'll keep wandering, then.

Maybe meaning will come. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-17 07:34:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> 
Rather than a light descending from the ceiling, it was as if the light were being reflected from another room. *My* room was brighter than before, sure, but...

I looked up, taking a long moment to process just what I was seeing.

My father sat on the foot of his bed- the one I'd taken to the dump three years ago, to make room for my own- with an ice pack and tissues wrapped around his thumb. My mother sat with him, rubbing her hand up and down his back, calming him. It was like... Like staring through some sort of two way mirror, but... So... So much *weirder.*

I noted, absently, that I'd crossed the thresh-hold, and that I was now standing at the foot of my own bed, staring up. A spot of blood dripped from my dad's tissues, fell to the floor of their bedroom... And plummeted onto my neck. I wiped it away with my shirt's collar.

*Seven, Seven, One... Seven, Seven, Seven, One... Seven, Seven, One.*

My heart halted again, the feeling I'd gotten washing over me again. The image on my ceiling was gone. I was left with... An urge. An urgent urge. I heard some sort of sharp *rap-tap-rap* behind me. The door. At this hour? The urge grew stronger. I held the bat in my right hand, and with my free left hand, I reached into my pocket, groping for my phone. 

*Rap-tap-tap,* the door declared again. But not the front door, I realized; I'd never closed the front door. I turned and, to my shock, realized the bedroom door had shut itself. When the *fos'la* had I done that?

The urge. 


*Seven, Seven, One...*


I typed the first number,

**RAP, TAP, TAP**, the door was screaming now. Something was wrong, incredibly wrong, but my mind, damned as any human mind is, was twisted, confused, drifting aimlessly in space from the pot and the caffeine and the all around *strange.* I typed, my fingers flying, even as I felt myself raise the bat, even as I felt my arm muscles twitch.

*...Seven, One, Seven-Seven-Seven One, Seven-Seven*, my body seemed to be electric, impulsive jolts that were not stemming from my brain guiding my hands as they locked my phone, slammed it down on the bed, gave my father's bat a death grip, and slammed the aluminum thing into the skull of... Of...

"*Fos'la,*" I asked aloud, "what in the hell *are*-" but I didn't have time to finish, because this thing, this thing with too many eyes and too few clothes, and far, far too much free-hanging flesh, was clamoring back to its bony feet, reaching its anorexic arms down, wrapping its skeletal fingers around its flesh, ripping at it, unleashing fucking *maggots* from inside itself and onto my floor. I slammed the bat into again, and it slapped against the wall, its flesh sounding like some sort of wet trash bag. I gripped my phone, typed the final one, and hit the call button.

In one moment, the Many-Eyed Entity was clamoring towards me; in the next, I was alone in my room, with one noticeable difference.

The carpet- the one I'd put in a few months after my father's death- was now tile. 

*Seven, Seven, One. Seven, Seven, Seven, One. Seven, Seven, One.*

My mind was leaping through ideas like a frog across a freeway. Daylight streamed through the windows. My bat still hung at my side, my keys were still in my pocket. The bedroom door was open now, though. *Fuck,* I thought, and then I stopped. "*Fuck?*" The word was... Alien. I made my way back to the living room, noted the Pizza Hut box said 'Pizza Hut' again. To my shock, my car was sitting in the driveway. I reached into my pocket, used the keys to unlock it, and, hands shaking, popped open the trunk.

There sat a wooden bat and a flashlight.

*Seven, Seven, One. Seven, Seven, Seven, One. Seven, Seven, One.*

I stared at my phone. My hands were shaking. Again, I began to type. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-17 07:29:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> *Seven, Seven, One. Seven, Seven, Seven, One. Seven, Seven...*

I slammed on my breaks, my heart louder than the music I'd been blaring for the past three hours. *Bump... Bump...* 

It wasn't some strange sixth sense, or a *thing* that was physically visible, or even the peculiar number he'd left on my desk today. *Seven, Seven, One. Seven, Seven, Seven, One. Seven, Seven, One.* No, nothing that predated this sudden burst of pure *instinct* was the causation; perhaps, like some sort of odd quirk in my perception of the world's linear flow, *this was* the causation, and not of the current *effect*, but of those things which preceded it. My mind, my *foslir'ein* mind... It feels... It felt, it feels, like I've been drugged. Not like some sort of date rape drug, either. It feels like someone dosed me with LSD or... Something... Something...

That feeling. That blood-halting, bone-freezing, brain-killing feeling. *Fos, fos, bloodied **foss,*** I'm thinking. Thought. I felt.

I put my car into reverse, moving the stick slowly, methodically, as if I were learning how to drive again and my mother were sitting shotgun, white knuckles gripping the aptly, affectionately named *Oh Shit* bar, just a breath away from screaming at me to stop and let her drive instead. I turned off my lights, and I backed up until the stop sign that marked Jessa Avenue was hidden behind a row of bushes.

*Seven, Seven, One...*

Only now did I know what halted me. Only once the *thing* was out of sight, was my mind able to process it properly. There had been something... *Wrong* about the sign. Something horribly, unnoticeable-y wrong, something that I wouldn't have noticed if not for that *fos'a'* number. *Seven, Seven, Seven, One...* My road had never been Jessa Avenue, not before today. Not before the number. *Jessup Avenue.* I'd grown up here, inherited the house after my father hung himself, after my mother left him for a tragic grave. 

*Seven, Seven, One.*

I took the keys out of the ignition, popped open my trunk, got out, and shut the driver side door as quietly as I could. The hairs on the back of my neck stood on end, and I was regretting the bowl I'd allowed myself at the start of this drive. I also regretted the constant stream of coffee I'd consumed since reading those numbers; neither the pot nor the caffeine was helping my addled mind remain calm. 

From the truck, I withdrew my late father's aluminum baseball bat (a memento that doubled as protection, I used to tell myself, in case my car broke down in the middle of no where) and a flashlight, then pushed down on the trunk, applying pressure slowly and silently until I heard a soft *click.* I gave the bat a quick spin, recalling how my late mother would play 'Obi and Ani' with me back in '03, before she got bad. She'd use this deep, horrible British accent and pretend to be Obi-Wan, and I'd be Anakin, and she'd train me with these nerf swords that we painted to look like lightsabers. My dad, a B-list voice actor and casual baseball player, would put on his best Jar-Jar impression and cheer me on.

I approached the house in darkness, having turned the flashlight off after rounding the corner and using it to inspect the Once 'Jessup' sign again. Sure enough, the 'Up' had changed to an 'A'; I hadn't hallucinated again. I'd feared, briefly, that I'd fallen victim to those latent episodes they warn you about in Elementary school, where a trace of LSD crops up a decade later and drags the victim back into some horrible trip before frying their brain.

*Fos'a',* I thought. D.A.R.E was still getting to me, all these years later.

I held the bat tight in one hand, slid the flashlight into the inner pocket of my leather bomber, and fumbled with my keys. I hesitated for two heart beats, then pushed open the door whose green paint had been chipping away for years. I stood, my bat wielding hand hanging limply at my side, my other on the door knob, and stared into the most welcoming abyss I'd ever seen.

*'Ware that what fakes a limp*, Stephen King once wrote. I pulled the flashlight free of my pocket, flicked it on, and turned the beam over every inch of the living room. Empty hot-pocket sleeves, check. A half-drank can of piss-water-beer, check. PS4 left on because I'm a lazy *Fos'a'ked,* check. But then, there. The empty box of pizza, left open on the coffee table.

*Pitzae Hu'ut*, it said.

"What the foslir'ein..." My voice trailed off. Another variable, another *thing*, completely different from any memory I possessed. Pizza Hut:Pitzae Hu'ut. Jessup Avenue:Jessa Avenue. Red Wagon Suites:Nairskuel Inn. My preferred Pizza Chain, my Street, and my fucking *job.* None of them possessed the same names that they'd had. I was gripping my father's bat the same way my mother would have gripped the Oh Shit bar, when I, on a whim, turned the beam of light upwards.

Footprints.

*Seven, Seven, Seven, One...*

I led the light along the muddy trail, until it hid itself behind the hallway's wall. I made my way- tentatively- across the room, set my flashlight down next to the half empty can of piss-beer, and flicked on the living room lights. Next, I moved towards the hall, now able to see as far as my bedroom door. The footprints curved down the wall, onto the carpet, back up along the ajar white door, and disappeared into the shadows of my room. 

Where the prints touched the floor, they were not muddy. Instead, they seemed... Green. No, more than green. They were, my mind concluded, *grass.*

I flicked on the light and followed the trail, now gripping the bat with both hands. I paused for a moment, bending down to examine the grass prints. My mind was taken back more than half a decade, all the way to my first real memory. 

I was sitting in front of a pile of lego bricks, mostly ignoring them, save for one large green one, which I was slamming on the ground to the sort of rhythm only a two year old boy could hear. "*FOS!*" My father shouted from outside. He came barreling through the back door, gripping his thumb inside his shirt. "Sandra, I missed the nail again," he called. Blood was seeping through his white button up, and his mud-coated boots left a trail of large footprints on the then-wooden floor.

Staring into the grass, I noted one small splotch of red, and a chipped bit of nicotine-yellowed finger nail.

I stood, my breath caught somewhere inside of me that was not my lungs. I dared not cross the thresh hold into my room- the room that my parents called their own years ago, that I'd since moved into. Instead, I poked my father's bat into the shadows and used it to flick on the lights.

The lights- my lights, rather- did not flick on.

*Seven, Seven, One...*
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
