<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject2846</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-16 18:09:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I wouldn't watch anything else. That is such a great series. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-16 18:04:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The system is so much different, it's almost like apples and oranges. You have to be a lot more creative with a large variety of magic and sword moves in the Witcher, DS is more hack and dodge for me. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-16 17:56:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This one killed me. They were just doing the right thing. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-16 04:04:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I think Bloodborne really helped the cause. It was so fast passed and rewarded you for being aggressive, where as the souls games made you play a really defensive game. This game still has me walking around every corner with my shield, but it palso more now to run at opponents and play a faster game instead of lumbering through in the toughest armor I can find. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-15 23:04:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This is why you don't give permission to search your car. If they want it bad enough, make them get a warrant. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-15 21:13:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> TIL Johnny Depp is a time traveler </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-15 19:50:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Or, on vinyl. Ohhh goodness what a find that would be. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-14 23:17:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So real it hurts. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-13 05:15:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> 2 Meta 2 Fast 2 Furious  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-12 20:16:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Not a fan per say, but I live close so I go to games a lot. I am praying that the playoffs come to SLC, the Jazz have played a good game and I think they won't be an easy first round for the warriors. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> ELI5: The Clinton Email Scandal and why nothing is happening. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-12 17:20:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-12 07:33:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Just do it! Who cares if her parents don'the know you, it is a nice gesture! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-12 07:23:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> From what I have seen, the team just lacks a leader. All the guys on the team are basically the same age, I think the oldest on the roster is like 29 or 30 years old. My point is, they might have a core of decent players, but they don't have someone to lead them.

If I were the Jazz, I would keep Burke, Burks, and Golbert and work on finding a stronger 3 and 4. Heyward is on or off and just isn't clutch. It is embarrassing to watch him play because he can go cold in an instant and play 1/2 of the game that way. 

I can't say what the solution is, but it isn't a rookie, especially not from this draft class. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-12 07:16:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The kings are screwed in the draft anyways, I hope they don't throw it! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-12 07:03:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I agree. Just the other night the Jazz took them to overtime. The clippers on Saturday night as well. Honestly, I think the Jazz are one or two moves away from being a formidable opponent. If they could trade Hayward for a more consistent and a little older SF, they could take the division. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-12 06:54:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I am rooting for the Wolves. Jazz aren't my team, but I live In SLC and it would be fun to have the Warriors in town for a few games. Maybe the Jazz can even win one? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> With the Jazz and Rockets battling for the 8th seed with 1 game a piece left, here are the official rules for tiebreakers. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-12 06:46:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-09 16:53:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I was at a bar watching this. Utah fans nowadays hardly look up, it is just so normal for the jazz to lose the close ones. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-08 16:47:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Or how about buying the team in MyGM not being 50k VC. I love to play, but that is soooo much in game time. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-07 20:26:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Shh. Let him have this moment. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-07 15:10:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Dirty, I love it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-07 14:48:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> How about Crabbe though?! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-07 02:20:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This probably isn't true, but I can go up 19-5 in the first 4 minutes of a game, and within the next 2 minutes the lead is cut down to 3. I should dominate some teams, but it always ends up coming down to the last 30 seconds of the game. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-06 08:32:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yep. I have been on the outside too though, i totally get it. It is hard to feel it in Utah, but Mormons are a minority pretty much everywhere else that doesn't have I -15 running through it. When you grow up as one of a dozen in your school, you feel that pressure. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-06 01:57:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Utah Mormons are dicks. I live in SLC and I can't stand going to my ward because of it. I know how you feel though, it was the reverse for me in California. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-06 01:18:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Serious though, I don't feel like arguing about this right now. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-06 01:15:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You shut your dirty mouth you bastard, that's MY church. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-06 01:04:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Really though. The LDS church gets so much flak for their views, but this was huge. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-06 00:56:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It is the same thing with business owners denying insurance to cover birth control/ reproductive services. It has no effect on them, but people insist that it is infringing on their religious beliefs by paying for health insurance that covers those things. People just love to hate. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-05 23:16:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Going out and playing baseball from dawn to dusk. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-05 23:09:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Everything. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-05 19:42:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This reminds me of "trainwreck" that movie is worth it to watch if only because of lebron. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-05 08:14:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hey guys look, an optimist here on reddit' </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-05 08:12:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> A nice backyard and outdoor kitchen. Everyone has a pool. Not everyone has a pizza oven, barbecue grill/ smoker, and outdoor refrigerator to go along with their landscaped backyard and 2 tier pool. It will cost a lot, but if you live somewhere with nice weather, you will use it for years and years, like kids, grandkids and possibly great grandkids enjoying an awesome backyard. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-05 08:03:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This is actually really cool. How did you do it? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-05 06:59:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Or the kings </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-05 01:51:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Eventually I will. Although it might just be cheaper to buy a tele. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-04 22:42:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I am thinking about drilling in a new spot and running the wires down through the bridge pickup space. And yeah, if it was a more expensive guitar I wouldn't dream of doing something so major, but where it isays as cheap as it is, these are just bonuses. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-04 22:23:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I hadn't thought of that, but that might be a good idea. Will it give me something similar to a neck position pickup? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [QUESTION] Possibly modding my Les Paul Jr. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-04 20:53:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hey guys and gals. I recently received a Les Paul jr from my pops. The guitar is from the Rocksmith bundle and it plays decently after a tuning key switch, but I'm looking to diversify the sound a little. I know this is blasphemy, but I was thinking of adding a telecaster single coil pick up to the neck position. Ideas, suggestions, comments? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-25 06:10:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What can I do to get to the next level? I have played for 9 years and am finally getting to be able to play solos and more complex rhythms, but I am having trouble with my own solos and my improvisation. I sort of know my scales but not super well. What should be my first areas to attack?

Edit: I have been working on emulating ZZ Top, Clapton, SRV, and Hendrix, that is what I kind of want to sound like. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-24 18:31:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I can definitely agree to that. You have to think that there wasn't nearly as much surveillance as we have today, so finding someone would be much much harder. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-24 18:19:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I agree. I have a grandma whose father was basically a spy for the CIA. They were living in Brazil at the time and she said that on that day all of the CIA directors and higher ups were in the sky or could not be reached. She even remembers her dad leaving early and being gone all day that day. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-24 18:17:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm like 25/75 on this one. I don't think Bush was that much of a warmongerer to attack his own country, but if we had sleeper agents inside of Al Queda, it is possible that the attacks could have been funneled from the CIA to them and moved up the line. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-24 18:15:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Kurt Cobain. I honestly don't think he killed himself, and it seems like Courtney Love paid a lot of people to cover for her killing him. 

She was a tweaker though, so a lot of her peculiar actions could be attributed to that. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-24 18:03:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Honestly, it takes too much time to vote in caucuses. I have school all day, two quizzes, a group project and homework. How am I supposed to have time to cook dinner, or spend time with my wife? She is republican and I am a democrat, so it sure as heck isn't going to be at the caucuses.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-24 04:01:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> http://imgur.com/gallery/SY3rKiJ </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-23 15:10:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Good luck! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-22 16:46:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm not your pal, friend. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-22 05:33:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah it is kind of lame. I have gone from buying to selling, but never contending when I'm trying to get a coach or new staff. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-22 05:07:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Won the championship thrice, made some awesome buys and had a good off season, and Marc Spears ranked me last. Screw that guys. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-19 05:32:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Kenny Chesney??? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-11 06:46:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I love the Bucks home jersey. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-10 04:47:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Don't give up! Huskies are stubborn, but if you keep at it she will come around. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-09 23:46:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Go figure right? Might as well make the age to vote and enter the military 21 as well since 18 year olds aren't capable of making reasonable decisions.... /s </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-09 20:47:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> They are trying to do that in SLC as well. I am from California and I learned this in Walmart last night. I was blown away that they would do something like that. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> TIL in Alaska, Alabama, New Jersey, and Utah the legal age to buy tobacco is 19. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-09 19:27:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-09 10:44:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That is something Tobey Flenderson would say... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-09 07:34:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Sunsplash? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-09 05:44:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This is actually a recurrent nightmare of mine... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-08 19:23:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Take a deep breath and channel that into a ball of motivation/rage. I used to get teary eyed a lot, and then I realized that I have this fire in my stomach that I can use. It really helps when you are in front of someone who you don't want to see you frustrated. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-07 21:45:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm sorry! I lived in Provo and worked on University Ave. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-07 18:56:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> University Ave in general sucks! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-07 18:12:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Salt Lake City in the house! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-07 04:31:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> IT'S A ROCK! The pioneers used to ride these babies for miles! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-04 18:31:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's a family gatoring! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What the hell is wrong with this game? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-29 10:06:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I am manned up on the point guard and some how there is always a guy RIGHT UNDER THE FUCKING HOOP. My players can't block passes, no steals, but when I'm passing into the lane or driving it is FUCKING turnovers galore. And worse, when my team is slacking on D, I can have a wide open shot with Lillard on the perimeter, or posted up under the rim with Horford, and I can't make a fucking shot. Goodbye 12 point lead, hello down by 4 is the last 40 seconds because of some bullshit 16 point run. Honestly, the game feels rigged to keep things down to the wire and it pisses me off. I can play a perfect 3 quarters and then suddenly no one on my team can make a shot for a solid 3 minutes and I lose when I was winning the entire fucking game. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-28 22:45:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What would be a good amount of money to go to a casino with? Like, if my wife and I wanted to spend a weekend in Vegas, we would set aside money to play with, and leave our debit and credit cards in our room, so how much would be a good amount to go with? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-28 03:41:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm not entirely convinced this isn't true... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-28 03:39:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> No, the Warriors just can't shoot tonight. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-26 18:58:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If you love your job and want to keep it, don't say anything. While nothing may occur in the present, your reputation down the line could be damaged if something were to happen between you and the daughter, i.e. break ups, personal info shared with your boss, any sort of unpleasant or awkward experience. Also, could you imagine if this daughter is super vindictive and decided to accuse you of rape or something of that sort if you were to break up? Even without proof, your boss would probably side with her daughter and you would be S.O.L.

While professionally your personal life should not matter, if you happen to have a weird fetish, something else that you would rather keep personal, or even complaints about work that you share with your boss's daughter, the information is liable to get back to your boss, especially if you have a fallout. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-25 02:13:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You have come this far, you might as well cap it all with a PhD. Then you can at least have an awesome title while you pay off your soul crushing debt. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-25 02:08:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah, we took a vote. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-24 07:19:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Like 4 things of preworkout. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-24 07:15:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Did you see Jim otter in the back looking right into the camera?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-23 15:19:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> He did what to your family?! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-23 14:59:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This makes me sick. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-23 06:27:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I played firewatch a few days ago and I have been listening to it's soundtrack while I do my homework, make dinner, etc. It makes me sad, but I don't know why. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-23 01:59:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Do we get the pitchforks now, or should we grab a bite first? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-22 07:08:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [Alton Brown would like a word with you.](https://youtu.be/RllWJUvrxEY) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-21 07:29:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Watching his character made me physically uncomfortable. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-20 17:24:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Que saudade! I have only had that once and I had to split it because I couldn't finish it on my own. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-20 04:03:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It really helps the dogs look better. Kinda sad they don't do it for more. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-20 02:24:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If your owner ever needs to keep it somewhere for a week, I would be glad to watch it! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-19 23:02:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> He was adopted yesterday! When the dogs get these pictures taken, they usually go within a day or two. I usually see them too late to do anything about it though... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-19 22:58:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This is Utah humane, and they have tons of great looking dogs. Most do have issues, but nothing you can't fix with good training. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-19 22:57:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I have done the same thing. I want a husky, but I cannot be a student and have a husky at the same time. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-19 22:56:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Can we get someone on this?? This is the internet, where are the dank memes? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-19 22:55:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If Derek Zoolander *was* a dog </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-19 22:52:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Bravo! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-19 21:41:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Kenai! That's the name on the shelter page. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-19 21:19:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Enter it! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-19 20:55:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I have wanted a husky for forever! I didn't see him until he had already been adopted. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-19 20:54:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Isn't that the answer for everything? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-19 20:52:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Woot woot! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-19 20:51:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> He has already been adopted. :/ </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-19 20:50:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> He has already been adopted. :/ </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-19 19:46:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This almost reminds me of the uncle Sam poster. Haha </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> A dog at our local humane society has some sass. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-19 17:26:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-17 17:06:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> We are also fake about it. You see the outward friendliness, but there is a lot of back biting as well, usually in the home.

Source: Married to a girl from the south, get to deal with her family's drama all the time. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-17 16:58:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> As a member, this is a pretty big thing. I know they aren't advocating it, but it shows that the Church isn't close-minded to advances in medicine. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Mormon Church Urges 'Cautious Approach' on Medical Marijuana Issue in Utah </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-17 16:57:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-17 09:38:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I do not have identical children, but a close family friend did, and she has had to mark one of the boys with marker on his foot so she knows which one is which! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Where do you get your airline tickets? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-27 17:42:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm looking to travel this summer and the time is fast approaching to start buying tickets. What sites do you use? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> 3-2 defense cannot stop corner 3s? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-19 07:45:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Does anyone else have this problem? My down low guys won't kick out to even try to defend an open 3 shot, and the computer just spams this on me all day when I play offline. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [Serious] If America were to adopt a form of Scandinavian-style social democracy, would there be any discernible problems caused directly by the size of the population? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-18 08:50:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
