<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject6816</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-27 16:25:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> https://www.bloomberg.com/view/articles/2012-08-26/u-s-taxpayers-are-gouged-on-mass-transit-costs </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> U.S. Taxpayers Are Gouged on Mass Transit Costs </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-27 16:25:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-04 18:32:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Depends on where you live. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-31 22:47:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Here's what I feel would be the simplest solution. Wittle all these apps down to three:

1. **GChat**: An iMessage equivalent that defaults to RCS and all its iMessage-like features, and when the recipient doesn't have RCS capability, falls back to SMS. The majority of those I know already call Hangouts "Gchat", and it sounds natural to say "Gchat me". This would be the default texting app on all Android phones, Google could theoretically strong-arm OEMs by withholding Google Services if they don't play ball. Also, they would bundle the Gchat extension into chrome by default so even the average user would be able to answer texts from their laptop without having to know to install something.

2. **Duo**: Include a vchat button in Gchat which opens this already existing app. Keeps things simple when you just want to video chat without opening an entire texting app. Similar to iMessage vs. FaceTime.

3. **Google Teams**: Rename Hangouts to this, and make it the Slack/Skype competitor that handles enterprise chats and video conferencing. Sounds more professional than "Hangouts" but with all the robust videoconferencing reliability.

Bam, done. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-25 16:03:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  every day he breaks his arms and every night he breaks his legs. And waits for the heart attacks to put him to sleep. 

Love the spongebob reference lol. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Southern/midwestern cities don't have NIMBY culture, so they're able to build housing fast, but have weak public transit support. Coastal cities are reversed. is there any US city that's the best of both worlds? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-09 15:52:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
