<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject4589</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-18 20:10:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Aw shit this one comment is why my journey to get Reese's pieces and ice cream is going to be like a next level Bourne ultimatum style espionage  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Has anyone ever reported you for being high? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-18 19:46:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I always have this thing after I've smoked a joint when I'm walking around in public and I get very scared people are going to notice I've smoked and report me. Has that ever happened to anyone - like a shop assistant or a passerby can tell that you're stoned and decides to call the cops or campus police? What would happen if the cops came and noticed you were high even though you finished your nug? Would they be able to arrest you for internal possession or take you to your apartment and search everything? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-18 05:58:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Even after the whole David Kelly affair? It's maintained by Royal Charter - the British government has literally nothing in the Beeb. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-15 04:33:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Care to give an overview of Farage? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-10 14:21:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah, the defend budget is miniscule and the reality of the situation is that governments always cock projects up (see universal credit under IDS). The money that's being added to the deficit now is coming from a shortfall in taxes and destructive, yet electorally salient projects like help to buy.

Also Britain actually grew through brown's last budget, when the spending cuts kicked in, the economy shrank and around the time Osborne started spending again we started to see growth. What brown did in his last years in office - sway fiscally conservative bush to adopt an expansive TARP recovery programme, lead the G20 through one of the greatest disasters of all time and save an economy largely dependent on financial services from collapse was a masterclass class in leadership.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-10 04:27:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I remember seeing Ed Milliband making a "speech" in the centre of town on a scruffy wooden pallet. Of course he was surrounded by advisers and guards and personal army I reporters and cameras to show everybody how working class Ed is!

Ever seen David Cameron do that? Nah probably not, doubt you'd feel the need to brand him out of touch though. Even if security guards weren't guarding one of the most powerful men in britain like that, you'd probably laugh at him for being egged or beaten up.

Do you remember that Emily Thornburry twitter incident? I think that brings home my point more than anything. An experienced MP representing the working class baffled as to why anybody would fly the Saint George's flag. Just completely disconnected from real people. Like I said, so are the Conservatives but they don't pretend to be like that.

It was literally a picture of a house with the caption 'image from #rochester' from a politician that is known to tweet inane pictures from doorknocking - quite an abstraction you've made there. Oh and how does that somehow represent the entirety of the 100,000+ member labour movement, especially when party officially quickly denounced and fired her? 

On a more trivial note I can take barely any of the labour leadership seriously. Every time they speak I cringe. The only one I can take seriously is Chuka Umunna, at least he seems to believe what he is saying and backs himself a bit

Yeah that's a substantiated point. Thanks for contributing to the discussion with your enlightened observations! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-10 04:20:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The outgoing Chancellor leaving a note on the desk for Osborne saying "Sorry, the money's all gone - best of luck" would be funny if it weren't true.

Actually it was Liam Byrne who was a treasury minister. In spite of that, this government has still managed to borrow more in 5 years than labour did in 13 http://blogs.spectator.co.uk/coffeehouse/2014/12/in-graphs-george-osborne-fought-the-debt-and-the-debt-won/ funny eh?

I know small business owners who were forced out of business as a direct result of Labour policies, and lets not forget the heavy erosion in civil liberties that was ushered in under the "something must be done" mantra of Anti-Terror Laws, etc.

Which policies? New Labour was desperate to do everything possible for business, it facilitated employment, lowered the corporate tax bill and prevented the entire economy from diving in 2008. Anyway, you're probably talking about the global recession that hit literally every country in the west - would we have avoided it if we had George Osborne "I'll match Gordon Brown's budget pound-for-pound" or "we need to encourage risk taking" michael howard or the plethora of Tory MPs that were lobbying for less financial oversight from the FSA? Doubt it. 

As for Civil Liberties - the tories voted those anti-terror laws in opposition (Ed Miliband didn't) and this government has only gone on to nstitute secret courts, internet surveillance, gag charities and threaten to scrap the human rights act.

Can't comment on your Local MP because you didn't mention him by name. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> NYPD are proving that broken window theory is a sham </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-03 15:52:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Economist: The Green Party is a growing force in British politics; if only it was more of the world </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-12-30 16:59:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-12-28 21:42:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I think the point is the world we see on Facebook is an entirely fabricated reality where only a certain version of ourselves is presented. Yes, you can choose what you put on there (providing it can be expressed in the form of a status, a picture or a video that meets certain social expectations) but facebook chooses the way that data is presented back to us. The aim of this is to fit us into a catagory that allows marketers to target us as neatly as possible. The 'year in review' app is a way of reaffirming that catagory and saying 'these are  the important things that happened to you this year', 'this is who you are'. The more we technology advances and the more we put on social media, the more companies like Facebook will convincingly be able to own us and prod us like voodoo dolls. When the algorithm that determines all of this goes wrong and presents sensitive memories as 'highlights', the spectacle is ruined and the morbid reality - that we are slowly sacraficing our very essence to companies like Facebook and there's nothing that we can do about it is revealed. That's what makes this morbid, and I think seeing this as a 'free app' just like Facebook want us to is extremely dangerous and we owe it to ourselves to keep them to account. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-12-28 14:05:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> No its like getting pissed when someone asked to read your diary and uncaringly forced you to face repressed memories without consoling you. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-12-28 14:02:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Err facebook turns over a pretty healthy profit and it makes that money from its members. I know this is 'voluntary', but companies dont just do things for free without an ulteria motive. They have no right to shit all over people on the margins like this.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Facebook Apologizes to User Pained by 'Year in Review' Posts </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-12-28 01:08:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-12-26 05:35:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Same with the iranian ayatollah. Sure, the queen doesn't abuse the powers she technically has, but having an unelected representative holding the highest office of state without having a single vote casted on her name is fundamentally wrong... so goes the Republican argument 

I'm no republican though and the point people seemed to miss is that this instills a healthy deal of determinism in us brits, which I think explains why recognize, say the injustice of tax cuts for the wealthiest members of society at a time of austerity unlike our cousins on the other side of the Atlantic. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-12-26 05:18:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I think he framed his point badly, but it still stands. People always wants to have their cake and eat it too. In this case, they begged for the movie to get released and when Sony had the guts to heed to those demands, reddit still managed to distribute it illegally and thus deny even basic respect to Sony for its decision to put their asses on the line. People begged for marijuana to get legalized and when it finally was, they still bought illegally at street prices. People complained about newspapers putting up paywalls but didn't make adblock exceptions for newspapers that made ran on losses to get keep their content free.

Reddit complains about the public being solipsistic and self-sabataging, when the public decide to sacrafice basic liberties for counter-terrorism controls or 'boomers' voting for pension rises  without proportionally contributing back to society or middle-aged people who benefited from government grants not willing to pay taxes to keep college affordable. What redditors doesn't realize is that they exhibit a turbo-charged form of this kind of egoism when it it comes to the basic indecencies I mentioned above. 

The idea that companies will just let consumers buy whatever the hell they want AND set the price (a model being vigorously advocated on this reddit) looks ridiculous when you see the kind of mass-indulgence you get here. Sure, a few media outlets have been successful using this model while it's still a novelty but if this became an industry standard, you can be sure as hell it wouldn't work.

Obviously businesses have to stay financially viable, so when they manipulate reddit's voting system or covertly hide advertisements inside articles or abuse product placement reddit sure as hell can't complain over at places like /r/hailcorporate </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-12-25 21:23:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> States in eastern Europe have national treasures serving as head of state - imagine Steven fry or clare balding serving this role.

I think though that's it'd completely irrelevant - when people who actually make decisions have done as little as the queen to earn their titles. If the Windsors all died, our prime minister would be on the shortlist as a candidate for the next king for Pete's sake! In america, people don't tend to realize the irony of the fact that someone from either the Clinton or a Bush families are going to get inaugurated to the highest office and lecture the nation about how 'anyone can become the president some day if they have the grit and resolve and a strong belief in the American dream'.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-12-25 21:20:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Its God save the queen you daft yank! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-12-25 17:31:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's another way of taking out your own mediocrity by shitting on the poor. If you're in poverty, you have to work longer hours to pay your way through. Longer hours mean less time to cook - for middle class people that would mean eating out at  north london bars every day, but for everyone else it means ready meals and fast food. Good health is a privilege of the comfortably off in modern britain.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-12-24 20:53:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If people knew just how radical the greens were, they would be consigned to the status of the other far-left parties in Britain. I'll give you an example - the greens beat labour in a council byelection at my university. The guy had no idea what the local issues were at the time and campaigned on anti-war/populist grounds. If people knew that the greens intended to block a science park development that would create jobs for graduates in the area because huzzahh its sponsored by BAE, nobody would have voted for them. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-12-22 08:36:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If you're using a phone, VPN in and just download the channel 4 app. It's what I did (: </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-12-18 18:55:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So you were standing on the board of a ship with the embodiment of my idea right next to you as you wrote that? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-12-17 20:38:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> *figuratively  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-12-17 15:30:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I was hoping you would assume that a: I want to read a respectable, middle-class paper and b: I don't want to pay for it </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-12-17 05:33:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So does the Daily Mail's - it's the most visited news website worldwide. That says nothing about journalistic integrity though. Guardian coverage tends to have a very lefty-slant. It's not overt in the same way Russia Today or the Morning Star might be, but that makes it more deceptive. Recently I noticed how the hashtag #illridewithyou got nearly as much attention as the Sydney hostage crises itself, but in the past it has been very one sided in its economic coverage and in the israel-palestine conflict. Also, CIF is a clickbait shitshow. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-12-17 00:31:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I think we remember Piers Morgan as being worse than he actually was, in the same way you might remember a horror film as being scary then look back and laugh. If you look at the tosspots - I'm talking Rod Liddle in the Sun, James Delingpole in the Specie, Will Self in the Staggers, anyone in the mail - that have columns nowadays and the general click-batey internet era tone they write in you have to laugh at what you once thought was journalese.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-12-17 00:21:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah but the Spectator has a very weak paywall and you don't need to be registered to comment. Metafilter and SomethingAwful were always given as examples of why people that actually pay for a site are more likely to be more conscientious, original and intelligent about what they write compared to, say SlashDot or Digg. Even though that was in the internet olden days, I think they're good examples because those sites were exactly 'high brow' in the same way that the Independent or the Telegraph may be.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-12-16 23:30:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The Telegraph released details the MPs expenses scandal five years back. That's pretty good.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-12-16 22:19:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I don't think the mirror is equivalent to the express; of the tabloids its probably the nicest one. It's comment section is probably on par with CIF too. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-12-16 22:17:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah when your readers need the information to make investment decisions, your news is going to be accurate. It's a shame though that a neoliberal version of the pravda is the only way of getting decent coverage... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-12-16 20:39:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Nah it's a broadsheet, disagreeable and outright wrong at times but still informed relevant to actual news. I'm a liberal-lefty but I think it's important to read the stuff that ministers in our government read.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-12-16 20:34:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Probably, but they'll just be driven to Breitbart UK or something and get even more nutty  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-12-16 20:32:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah, enjoy it while you can - they'll stop giving free articles as soon as you get used to clearing your cache. Their [twenty-odd  social media optimisers](http://order-order.com/2014/06/18/telegraph-announce-40-new-e-jobs/) are probably monitoring this thread as we comment here :/ </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-12-16 20:23:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> /r/titlegore - I'm turning off the spellchecker on my phone now. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Now the independent and the telegraph have paywall, I'm literally have to be a guardian reader or a daily mail reader </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-12-16 19:45:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-12-15 05:47:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Nowhere does it say activists should 'ignore' immigration, just acknowledge their concerns, maybe mention that [Labour will go further than the coalition on immigration](http://www.theguardian.com/politics/2014/oct/23/labour-immigration-reform-bill-voter-concerns) and then talk about other issues UKIP rather wouldn't. Worries over 'social cohesion' ARE irrational - remember that fact that white voters in diverse communities tend to agree with UKIP less than white voters in non-immigrant communities? remember how immigrants [objectively contribute way more than non-immigrants to society](http://www.economist.com/news/britain/21631076-rather-lot-according-new-piece-research-what-have-immigrants-ever-done-us) (before you dispute this, remember that [farage himself agrees](https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=LWeL5hLKO0k)). These are objective, logical facts, but voters don't care if you mention them because they can't be persuaded on the basis of facts. If you can get a copy of it, Satre's 'Anti-Semite and Jew' explains this and I believe that the sentiments propelling UKIP are the exact same sentiments that propelled populist/fascist parties across Europe. That's not to say that the concern about immigration isn't valid, but its not something you can argue with or change people's mind on. Stop being so paranoid and susceptible to slippery slopes - levelling this minor document that against the very concept of democracy.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-12-15 05:19:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I don't think it says candidates should ignore people's concerns about immigration. It just seems to be politely saying that fears about immigration can't be argued with rationally. If your job is to win votes over, mention that Labour have acknowledges these fears but emphasise Labour's policies on the NHS and Housing - two areas, by the way that UKIP don't have a coherent stance on.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-12-15 05:14:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That's exactly what the document says - you can't out-ukip UKIP on immigration so listen to voters concerns and make sure they know about Labour's policies on housing and the NHS. Blindly pushing out party dogma without actually listening to people's concerns is anti-democratic. This is the party that expects to govern the entire country; its policies have to broadly represent the national mood - that isn't complete nationalisation of the means of production, distribution and exchange without compensation.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-12-10 00:35:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah thats another thing, Brits don't want coalition government. When the houses of parliament were rebuilt after being bombed in WW2, planners were instructed to rebuilt it in a government/opposition bench confrontational way - even though Labour, Independents etc made the UK a multiparty democracy. We want strength, not compromise - so the coalition could never work in a conventional way. The Conservatives haven't given an inch on any points of principle to the Liberal party - I do not see why it should have been the reverse. 

I don't even know why people seem to think that the Liberals were forced into accepting tuition fees - senior figures have repeatedly made clear that they regret promising to lower tuition fees but they do not regret voting for higher tuition fees. This just shows them as a bunch of middle-class tory-lite compromise merchants that would do anything to get elected. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-12-09 20:49:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Nobody voted for the lib dems because of their policies on working hours or child tax credits - they were seen as an alternative to the hollow spin machines Labour and Tory. Instead of using all their political capital to challenge the two-party consensus on things like civil liberties, drug laws and tuition fees they claimed credit for a few nice things that Tory sadomonetarists don't care about like cracking down on homophobia or lowering taxes for the low paid. The reason everyone hates them now is that they are literally a caricature of everything wrong with politics: corrupt, spineless, deceptive, spinsters  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-12-05 05:57:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Bankers, Oligarchs, Shareholders, Tax dodgers, Globalised Capitalism, The European Commission etc are all potential scapegoats for left-of-centre parties. 

Podemos in Spain and Syriza and Greece are running populist platforms that basically blames all of the above. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-12-04 03:44:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> UKIP are edging that way - they're now against the TIIP and they want to re-nationalize parts of the NHS, Farage said he sees neither left nor right but right and wrong. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-11-30 21:55:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's not like they have a rational or coherent programme of policies. The only reason to vote to vote for them is because of who they are -- and because UKIP have set the bar so low, this is the only way to talk about them. Who they are is constituted by the people that vote for them. If the most successful leader of British fascism in the past 50 years is voting for them, it certainly is grounds to dismiss them. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-11-30 03:02:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> 20 years ago we didn't have rolling news and social media. With the demand for so much news so much of the time obviously the quality had to drop. 
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-11-30 00:37:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I've seen very clever people on the left and on the right post it on facebook. People on this subreddit naturally have an anti-politician bias too and I can see it getting upvoted here just as easily. Don't pretend it's "those people" that are susceptible to this kind of behavior.

Edit: Ooop look at this http://www.reddit.com/r/unitedkingdom/comments/2np39a/out_of_650_mps_only_11_turned_up_for_a_debate_on/ </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The menace of memes: how pictures can paint a thousand lies </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-11-30 00:31:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [Political Economy] How has Sweden managed to create a sustainable social democracy, while France's social model seemingly teeters from crises to crises? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-11-28 02:13:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> With the concessions Manuel Vall is being forced to make to big business, it's pretty clear that France will *have* to make reforms to its corporatism social model if it is to remain competitive. Pretty much everything I read about France's economic woes recommends either this or unrealistic structural changes to the EU or international capitalism. 

Meanwhile, Sweden seems to have fared better than others from the great recession and meager neo-liberal reforms of the Moderate party have been rejected during the recent elections. Sweden's social model seems structurally sustainable and its position on the ease of doing business index, its credit rating reflect this. 

What's going on here - it seems to me that people in these two countries have pretty similar attitudes to society and the state. The Government has a large stake in industries in both countries and the left can claim a pretty large stake in elections? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
