<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject8764</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-05-06 22:27:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> He re-assigned Brian Scalabrine. You don't just reassign Brian Scalabrine and not expect consequences.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-05-05 06:11:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Best safety of all time.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-05-03 08:26:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Literally the only thing they wanted to avoid they let happen. Unbelievable. 
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-04-29 00:38:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> War Eagle! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-04-29 00:34:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> When hiring Quin Snyder over Bill Self is only your third worst basketball coaching decision as an athletic director, you know your record is bad. Thankfully Mike Alden lucked into Gary Pinkel.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-04-27 21:29:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Amen. Al had his issues and he lost it a bit at times, but by all indications he was a good guy and loyal to all of his players. He even paid for Derrick Thomas' funeral when he was killed years ago in Kansas City.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-04-23 04:47:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If Alden goes in the "fired coaches from Southern California" file, it needs to be Ben Howland and not Tim Floyd.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-04-20 00:00:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> He's resetting the shot clock. Mizzou's losing its top two players and while Haith had a good recruiting class coming in, it's unlikely Mizzou would have finished high next year. 

Instead of probably being fired in 2015 or 2016, he gets a seven-year contract. 

In terms of Alden sounding happy, he was the guy who hired him in the first place. Classic case of saving face and CYA. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-04-19 01:27:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This should be a simple process for Mike Alden:

1. Contact the representatives of Gregg Marshall and Shake Smart. 

2. On the 99.9 percent likelihood they say no, interview and hire Ben Howland. It would be the first time ever that Mizzou's head coach would have a Final Four on his resume. He would bring credibility to the basketball program. He wouldn't get the same superstar talent he did at UCLA, but he could do a job comparable to the one he did at Pittsburgh.  It may not be a grand slam hire, but it would be a bases-clearing double and would put Mizzou Top 3/4 yearly in the SEC. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-03-21 07:31:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Winning a division title, sucking at basketball and competing for the Fulmer Cup. Looks like Mizzou is really adapting quickly to the SEC.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-03-15 00:04:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> * Len Bias' death. 

* 1992 Duke/Kentucky post-game thread. 

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-02-12 18:02:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> 1. Missouri (obvious reasons)

2. USC - With respect to the other great programs, I think the USC coaching job is the best college football job in America. Great tradition, great weather, great academics, great recruiting area, money and in a major market. I think the job has become underrated in recent years with all the SEC domination.

3. LSU - Great recruiting area, money, tradition and I think Baton Rouge is the best "gameday" environment in the country. It's underrated among SEC jobs.  

4. Florida - Very similar to LSU. 

5. Oregon - Beautiful part of the country, money and they have the "cool program" buzz with a lot of recruits nationwide.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-01-12 23:54:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> A couple:

- What if James Franklin was healthy all season long? Perhaps Mizzou beats South Carolina.....but perhaps that injury helped Mizzou for next year, too. Mauk gained valuable experience, so the injury worked both ways. 

- What if Georgia beats Auburn and the first Auburn miracle doesn't happen? Football is a game of match-ups and while I think Alabama was just as good as Auburn was, I think they may have been a better match-up for Mizzou in the SEC title game. Preparing for Auburn's offense in six days was a tough chore and they were the hottest team in the country at that point. Plus, looking back at how OU and Texas A M threw the ball on them, Mizzou's passing game could have been tricky for Alabama. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-01-08 06:17:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Going to do my best without spoiling it:

1. Lack of a follow up on one of the important plot elements in Season 7. You'll see when you get there. 

2. The introduction of too many new characters. Having watched several TV shows, I can't remember one that introduced as many new characters as Dexter's final season did. 

3. It never had the feeling of a final season. This was especially important about a guy who's hiding a major secret. There was no urgency like there was in the final episodes of The Sopranos, for example. 

Sorry if that's vague, but you requested no spoilers.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-01-07 23:48:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Ah, that was the year when Illinois and Kansas --- two teams Mizzou beat --- made the BCS over a 12-2 Tigers team. Good times! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-01-07 19:22:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This coming from the guy who hired Mike Tice as an NFL head coach.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-01-07 06:49:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Bad Luck BCS....has best year ever in its final season.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-01-07 06:27:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Bo Pelini exhibiting a great sense of humor may be a bigger miracle than any of the stuff Auburn pulled out this year.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-01-05 23:07:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Since they couldn't land a giant fish, I would have hired James Franklin instead. Strong's a solid coach, but Franklin would have killed it in that state.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-01-04 21:07:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Too bad you didn't beat the Raiders. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-01-04 05:42:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Bobby Petrino back to Louisville? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-01-01 00:52:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> 1, 2, 4, 7, 5, 3, 6, 8, though 8 is really the only season I didn't like. 

I give Season 1 the edge primarily because of how it ended. It was a bit slow at the beginning, but it picked up and just gathered steam towards a great ending. I thought Season 2's ending was a cop-out and it loses a few points with me there. Still a great season. 

Compared to most Dexter fans I know, I liked Season 5 more and I think it gets a bit of a bum wrap. I understand a few of the complaints about it (how Rita is rarely mentioned after S5E1), but I liked how it changed from a "big bad" to a group of people. It was a good change-up after focusing on one big bad guy.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-12-31 19:00:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Trading a coach and having him beat my team the next year in the Super Bowl. Oh wait.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-12-30 19:47:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The "College" episode of The Sopranos. One of the first of several outstanding episodes of the show.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-12-30 19:28:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I don't know (or think) if they should go in this direction, but Mike Shanahan would be a pretty good fit with all of that offensive talent in Detroit. Since Rex Ryan survived with the Jets, I think this is the only fired coach scenario that would work.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-12-30 18:04:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This might be the happiest I've ever been about another team's firing. It's criminal how much Schwarz and that coaching staff wasted the talent there.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-12-29 23:19:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Good call....one of the most underrated coaching jobs this season. Many thought the Jets were a two-to-four win team entering the season.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-12-23 17:30:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Detroit. If he gets fired, I think Rex Ryan would be a perfect fit there. That team has some very nice pieces.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-12-23 17:27:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I really don't think DA gets fired unless Jon Gruden is waiting in the wings. In that case, it's really hard to blame Mark Davis if he does pull the trigger.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-12-20 07:30:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Wait for basketball season.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-12-17 06:11:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Maybe there's a way to do a Godfather II like deal where half of the season is based on flashbacks/prequel stuff and the rest is in the present. Find a way to connect them, ect.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-12-17 05:57:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Exactly. That game was the reason why I was scared of Auburn so much leading to the SEC title game.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-12-17 02:31:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I fully admit that this is based on being a Mizzou fan....but the whole immediate "conference is overrated" argument you hear if the best conference teams aren't traditional powers. There was a lot of talk this year about the SEC being overrated because of Mizzou and Auburn playing for the SEC title. If Auburn was called LSU or Alabama and Mizzou's resume came from a team called Florida or Georgia, there would have been no talk about the SEC being overrated. 

And for what it's worth, let me defend the Big 12 here: Just because Baylor was the Big 12 champion doesn't mean the conference stunk. They were a really good team and Briles is one of the best coaches in the country. Again, if Oklahoma or Texas had done what Baylor did this year, there would have been more "BCS national title" contender buzz about them.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-12-16 07:35:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Way, way too many to pick from:

1. Fifth Down vs. Colorado.
2. Flea Kicker vs. Nebraska. 
3. South Carolina.

All of those happened on the same end of the field in Columbia. That stadium needs an exorcism.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-12-16 07:32:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Root for Mizzou, but was pulling hard for Snyder to win a title that year. That play left me kind of sick.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-12-16 07:28:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> There were some bad losses in the 1980's and 1990's, but Kansas State just absolutely annihilating Mizzou 66-0 stands out. K-State was up 42-0 at halftime and honestly, the Wildcats could have put up 90 that day if Bill Snyder wanted to.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-12-15 01:28:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I think the timing of all this indicates that Mack Brown just didn't want Nick Saban to replace him. Wow.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-12-09 22:54:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I agree, but the one possible angle for a competitor like Saban is winning a national title at three different schools. That would be one of the most unbreakable records in sports. The only guy who'd have a realistic shot at it is Urban Meyer, but he's not leaving Ohio State unless the NFL calls. 

While Alabama is a great job and the best program in the country right now, Texas is one of the few jobs where a coach can compete right away. Saban would have that program competing for a national title by year two.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-12-03 21:10:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> There's a list of 7-10 episodes I really like the best, but I'll just stick with two of them.

1. "Born Free," the Season 1 finale. While I had a feeling Rudy/Brian was the ITK, I did not see the brother twist coming (Didn't read the books). Lithgow's performance as Trinity was the best, but I enjoyed Brian's story better. The interactions between the two brothers as Deb laid on the table was great. Then, Dexter killing Brian and exhibiting emotion for the first time in the show was fantastic too. Everything about that episode was great. 

2. "Hello, Dexter Morgan." In my opinion, the ending to the episode is the greatest scene in the series. The cat and mouse game between the two killers was awesome and it was great to see Dexter finally outsmarted by someone. The final few episodes of the season were terrific, but this one was my favorite.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-12-02 18:21:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Franklin should wait for the Florida job to get open. I'd hate that he would still be in the SEC, but Florida's the better fit for him IMO.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-11-28 09:02:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Not bad, but I actually liked Season 5 and I would only change one big detail: Deb should have pulled the curtain in the season finale and discover who the vigilante killers were. I think that moment started the decline of Dexter, at least compared to the first four seasons. 

Deb finding out there would have solved a few of the remaining issues many have with Season 5. 

- It gives Lumen a perfectly legitimate reason to bail on Miami rather than "losing" her dark passenger. Deb, who sympathized with the rape victims throughout the season, let's her go for this reason and she disappears forever.

- It doesn't tie everything neatly into a bow. The cliffhanger could be Deb debating on what she does with Dexter.

If I could make one major change, it would have been this one. It also eliminates the Season 6 we got and this alternate Season 6 could have been the final season with perhaps a different ending.

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-11-24 09:48:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I believe the Drug War should be brought to an end and all drugs should be legalized. The prohibition of drugs creates a lot of the violence we see in larger cities. The federal government has turned the drug trade into a big business. In addition, addicts are often forced to steal or rob homes/businesses to satisfy their habits, creating even more crime and more victims. It's a negative domino effect that's been created by government and law enforcement. 

I say legalize drugs, regulate them and use a good chunk of the money to fund drug counselors that can help drug addicts.  It's time to stop treating non-violent drug offenders as criminals and treat them as people who have a disease, similar to how we treat alcoholics now. 

You would have less violence on the streets, you would have significantly fewer prisons in America and you'd save billions of dollars on a federal program that does not work. And oddly enough, the addicts would be the greatest beneficiary as they could acquire their drugs in a safer manner and not jeopardize the lives of others. 

I'm not sure how unpopular this is, but each time I talk to one of my liberal or conservative friends about this issue, I get eye-rolls and strange stares in return.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-11-21 02:39:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I would have preferred them trading Miggy Cabrera, personally.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-11-19 03:18:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Good point. Thanks for the reminder of that! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-11-18 19:28:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm wondering if the guy is connected to the Senator or someone else from the CIA/federal government that's hostile to Saul.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-11-17 08:55:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> At his peak, I'll still take Dan Marino over any other quarterback I've ever seen. The cannon arm, the quick release and the lack of fear in his decision making. 

He put up 2010-13 numbers in 1984 and he crushed the production levels of other quarterbacks.

It's sad that this whole "you need a title to vindicate your career" garbage has been shoved down everyone's throats courtesy of ESPN and other sports outlets. Marino only had one 1,000-yard rusher during his Dolphins' career. During his 17 years, Miami only had four Top 10 defenses in that same stretch. 

On top of that, he played in an era where the quarterback position wasn't protected to the extent by officials that it is now, and cornerbacks were allowed to be physical with wide receivers.

Rod Woodson remarked that Dan Marino would have thrown for 100,000 career yards if he played in this era. I don't know if that's true, but the point is valid. 

He was a great quarterback and has become criminally underrated because of this championship obsession NFL media and fans have.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-11-12 19:25:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Michigan State/Kentucky: Just rooting for a great basketball game. I love Tom Izzo and a Kentucky win would make the SEC look good come tournament time, especially if my team is on the bubble. 

Duke/Kansas: Duke because they're not Kansas.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-11-06 22:06:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> There were still Blockbuster stores? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-11-04 19:30:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> While I agree with those who hope Incognito doesn't play another down against, I'd love also to see an angry Ndamukong Suh go against Richie Incognito.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-11-04 01:34:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I liked The Phantom Menace and I think some of the complaints lobbed about that film could be applied to the original trilogy as well. Not saying it's better than those three, but the flaws of the classics are overlooked at times.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-11-03 07:11:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Jon Stewart and The Daily Show. Don't agree with his politics, but I do respect his ability to ask tough questions --- tougher than those you'll see on Fox News, MSNBC or CNN. I also like Colbert because his character is an excellent parody of that blowhard Bill O'Reilly. 

And while I'm on entertainment related issues, politics never enters my mind when it comes to movies or music I consume. I don't care that Tom Hanks and Leo DiCaprio are Democrats: If I'm entertained by their movies, I usually will go see them or check them out on DVD.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-11-03 02:05:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The timeline might be part of it. Season 3 doesn't pick up immediately after the Season 2 finale. 

Plus, my theory is that Lockhart is a grand puppet-master in some way. There's something off about him in my opinion. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-11-01 06:20:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This could be a stretch, but how about Thad Matta for one of those jobs, especially the Duke/UNC jobs? While Ohio State's a great program, Duke and North Carolina are a step up. Matta's only 46 and he's been to two Final Fours. He's also a great recruiter.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-10-30 20:02:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Corey Tate! Seriously, that was a great game. I miss the old building.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-10-29 22:15:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> One team I haven't seen mentioned on here is the 1998 North Carolina team with Vince Carter, Antawn Jamison and Ed Cota. That was a great team that I thought would roll Utah in the 1998 Final Four and then beat Kentucky in the finals.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-10-29 22:13:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That '97 Kansas team is the best KU team I've ever seen --- and obviously, they've had a lot of them as my Tigers can confirm. Mizzou beating them that year was a borderline miracle. 
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-10-29 05:11:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> In this postseason, the Red Sox have won games started by David Price, Max Scherzer twice, Justin Verlander and Adam Wainwright twice. Quite a run.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-10-26 23:22:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Whether it's Democrats bashing Ralph Nader or Republicans bashing Robert Sarvis or Ross Perot, it's always pathetic when the two major parties blame a third-party candidate for a loss. The two parties have a monopoly on money and media coverage. They have no disadvantage against a third-party candidate. 

Plus, Ronald Reagan crushed Jimmy Carter in 1980 with a moderate Republican (John Anderson) running as an Independent candidate. Also, Harry Truman won in 1948 even with the Democratic Party splitting in three. 

If a Democrat or Republican is good enough, he or she wins the day. They need to stop crying in their beer when a third-party candidate does well.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-10-25 21:41:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I like and respect the Tea Party of 2009 and 2010. They began as a small government and lower taxes movement that was not necessarily worried about social issues or issues like pot. 

But somewhere along the way, some of the Christian conservative types hijacked it. I can't point to when it happened --- maybe during the GOP primary season for the 2012? Now, some in the Tea Party have a litmus test on some issues like abortion and gay marriage. 

To me, it started off as a Libertarian grassroots effort that was then hijacked by the Michele Bachmann's, Sarah Palins and Ted Cruz' of the world.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-10-25 02:00:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Living in Kansas City during his coaching stint, Todd Haley was never too popular even during the season the Chiefs won the AFC West.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> CareFirst says 76,000 customers will lose current coverage due to Obamacare </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-10-24 20:36:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-10-24 05:32:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> While I don't like the emphasis on Dana, I still think there's going to be a payoff at some point with her storyline. I'm not sure what it is, but after the plot twist on Sunday, my faith has been restored in the writers.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-10-23 03:58:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> A few:

1. Ryan Leaf --- While I didn't think he would be as good as Peyton Manning, I thought he would have a good career. Having taken Washington freaking State to the Rose Bowl, I thought San Diego had a QBOTF for sure. 

2. Darren McFadden --- Injuries have hurt, but I thought he'd be a stud in the league. He was one of the very few Raiders first round picks I loved and it hasn't worked out yet. 

3. Matt Ryan --- I didn't think he was worthy of a high first round pick. I was very wrong.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-10-23 03:45:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> On the good side: Russell Wilson. Living in the Midwest, I saw all of his games at Wisconsin and he reminded me of Drew Brees. I didn't think he would be this good this fast, but I thought Seattle stole him in the draft. 

In predicting a "bust": Robert Gallery and JaMarcus Russell. I HATED both of those picks at the time as a Raiders fan and they proved me right.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-10-23 03:40:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Here to say this one. In retrospect, it's amazing how much Baltimore improved during the year and how they peaked at the absolute right time. That Chiefs team is one of the worst five teams I've seen in my life (from 1985-on).  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-10-22 21:06:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I honestly believe that if Jon Stewart and Stephen Colbert had White House press credentials, they'd ask the toughest questions out of anyone in the room.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-10-21 02:32:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If Josh Freeman plays lights out tomorrow against the Giants, Schiano shouldn't make it to the end of the week. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-10-17 08:19:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm 28 and I became a Libertarian in my college years. The "all college kids are all wild, hippy liberals" is one of the more inaccurate stereotypes out there. But what turned off students to the GOP was its anti-gay marriage stance and stuff like the Patriot Act and Drug War.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Libertarianism is spreading on our college campuses. An unusually large number of politically-minded, frustrated students, who refer to themselves as the "liberty movement." </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-10-17 08:09:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-10-16 04:13:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So basically, this whole thing was just a dog and pony show. Terrific. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-10-14 19:12:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Another thing forgotten is how good the Marlins were and how loaded that roster was. 

Pudge Rodriguez was in his prime and he dominated that postseason. Mike Lowell and Derrek Lee were great that year. Oh, and if that line-up wasn't enough, there was a young 20-year-old player by the name of Miggy Cabrera in it. Josh Beckett and Dontrelle Willis (before injury) were great on that staff. 

The Cubs still should have won that series, but the Marlins weren't some fluky team that came out of no-where.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-10-14 18:08:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Too bad there wasn't a Game 7 for the Cubs to redeem themselves.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-10-13 08:47:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Freeman is still just 25 years old. He had a 25-6 touchdown-INT ratio just a few years ago. Heck, even last year, he tossed for 27 touchdowns. He's played for two disastrous head coaches in the NFL (three if you count Ron Prince at K-State). With good coach, he can still be a pretty good quarterback.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-10-13 05:28:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Josh Freeman is going to be a steal for Minnesota.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-10-13 04:45:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Two that stand out in my lifetime (since '85):

1. Rams vs. Titans: Rams were the classic Cinderella team and Tennessee was under the radar all year due to a 14-2 Jacksonville team in their division. 

2. Cardinals vs. Steelers: The Steelers were not a surprise, but the Cardinals were.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-10-13 04:38:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Good prediction I was laughed at for: I thought Pittsburgh would finish below .500. Barring a big turnaround, that one's looking decent at the moment. 

Bad prediction: I picked the Giants to win the NFC East. Not so much.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-10-11 21:19:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Following the history of third parties, there needs to be either a charismatic candidate (Teddy Roosevelt in 1912), big money (Ross Perot) or an issue that unites many Americans (the anti-slavery movement leading to the Republican Party's creation). Big money is invested in the two parties, so that's out. While I respect Gary Johnson and will vote for him in 2016 again, I don't see him being the type to capture America's imagination. 

I think Libertarians need to unite and push the issue of the debt. While many issues are important, the debt is something that does concern younger people (I'm 28). One of the dirtiest secrets of the GOP winning the House in 2010 was the fact social issues played little role in the win. The message of "liberty" is nice for those like us, but most Americans don't vote based on philosophy. They're middle of the road. I think Libertarians have to find a way to craft a message of fiscal responsibility that resonates with voters.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-10-10 22:24:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Magic Johnson's my favorite player of all-time, but this is good news. Magic's analysis was terrible and Doug Collins was my favorite analysis when he was doing work for NBC. Good upgrade.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-10-10 02:36:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> While I liked the plot twist and was stunned at the ending, part of me always wished Rita would have found out about Dexter.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-10-07 21:58:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah, that year was stacked. Fiennes deserved it, though.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-10-07 19:40:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Ralph Fiennes should have won for his portrayal of Amon Goeth in Schindler's List. Fiennes was amazing in that movie.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-10-07 02:37:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> He outplayed a quarterback who's arguably in the middle of the greatest stretch of quarterback play in NFL history. On another note, if Tom Brady or Peyton Manning were sacked in the manner Romo was on the play before, it's a horse-collar penalty. 

Tough break, but Romo played one of the best 10 games I've seen a quarterback play. That last pass doesn't eliminate that.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-10-06 09:19:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The 2002 Elite Eight game against Oklahoma. Gilbert, my second favorite Tigers player ever, had his version the John Starks game. Mizzou also missed several free throws and still only lost the game by six points. 

If Mizzou wins, they play a very beatable Indiana team with a chance to play for the national title. Plus, it gets the Final Four monkey off of our program's back. 

While the '09 Elite Eight loss to UCONN stung, UCONN was a great team and Mizzou had a great run. Losing to a conference rival in an Elite Eight game stings far more.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-10-06 08:57:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's probably one of Pinkel's better road wins. Dominating a decent SEC team on the road is a nice way to open up the conference season and give the football program some good momentum. After a bad season last year, eight to nine wins is doable, which most around the SEC didn't expect. 

Murray against Mizzou's secondary terrifies me. Mizzou's offense is good enough to compete against UGA. Bet the over.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-10-06 07:32:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Matthews knew about Dexter from the beginning. I thought Season 8 would have revealed that for sure, especially the fact that Matthews consistently helped both Dexter and Deb throughout the series because of his relationship with Harry. I thought they were going down this path when he brought Vogel in on the season opener.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-10-03 17:06:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Well, I guess the Democratic Party can create jobs after all.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-09-28 20:24:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> There were a handful of missed opportunities. I didn't like the cop-out ending in Season 2. Deb should have found out at the end of Season 5. I thought Brian as Dexter's ghost would have been interesting path for the last half of Season 6, but nothing. 

However, LaGuerta's death essentially having no impact on Season 8 was unforgivable for the story. Season 7 was a pretty good season IMO with an ending that naturally set-up a shit-storm for Dexter and Deb in Season 8. However, that did not happen. Season 8 should have picked up immediately where Season 7 ended. Instead, we had new characters and an underwhelming "Big Bad" for the final season. 

Despite the flaws of the first seven seasons, there was still a great opportunity to end the series on a high note. However, they dropped the ball on LaGuerta's death.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
