<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject4121</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Jeff the Brotherhood at Forecastle. Louisville, Ky </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-21 04:41:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-13 08:42:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Then why am I feeling so down? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-10 03:19:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Mary Poppins must have let her prison issued umbrella get away from her. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-19 21:44:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> haha. Give me liberty or give me meth! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-19 20:48:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Red Flags are among us. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Did the gov't have Macaulay Culkin kill all of the Madea's in order to distract us long enough to sneak TPP through? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-19 20:25:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-08 09:10:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Pedal of Honor......I love that game! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-07 18:58:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thanks for all the replies! They have been very helpful. You Tucsonians are alright. ;)  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-07 18:01:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> By the end of the year I'll bet he is their starting quarterback. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-06 08:10:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Sold! I had a tough day today trying to find good bourbon. I knew it would be difficult but shit! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-06 06:23:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thanks! Hopefully I should easily avoid them since I really hate sticks. Look at em being all smug and just laying on the ground or connected to a tree. Get your own life, sticks! Am I right? Geez. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-06 05:41:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Ah, got ya. Thanks for the heads up. I have noticed that your guys traffic has no flow and it takes what seems like forever to get somewhere. I already am having issues with the snowbirds or q-tips as my gf calls them. They are old, blind, metal torpedoes. It is just like that South Park episode. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-06 05:29:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I agree and disagree. You see the current brand of the far right. I do think it would get bad enough that people would be forced to finally get their head out of the sand.  You see everyone in the streets protesting about racism and inequality. Just image if people realized the government is puppeteering this in order to divide and concur the masses, thus making us easier to control. They are having us fight amongst ourselves about race in-between stories of people changing genders and articles about what celebrity looks fat in a bikini in order to distract us from the fact that laws are being pushed through that continues the destruction of our country. I think people would wake up and start going after the real criminals. I would hope so anyways. If not.....I heard New Zealand is nice. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-06 04:55:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Awesome! Thank ya much! That shit looks awesome and is exactly what I'm talking about. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-06 04:54:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I did mention the evil Monsanto. I said that Obama passed a measure making them infallible. I don't get the "lost all credibility" thing, but whatever man. Thanks for thinking I had some to begin with! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-06 04:53:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thanks! Way ahead on the shaking thing. The NOPE is strong in this one. Ha </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-06 01:50:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I respectfully disagree but I understand where you're coming from. The little remaining anarchist in me though would vote far right in that scenario just so it would get so bad the people will revolt and force actual change. By selecting evil, on any scale, it only perpetuates more evil. So I would just write in Bernie in the general if it came down to it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-06 01:44:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Now thats what I mean! I'm on 12th St. for a couple more days until I move into the house. I will try it for sure! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-06 01:21:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Ha. Thanks for the advice. If I were to head to California though, it would be Northern California. :-) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-06 01:20:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Libertarians aren't libertarians anymore though. Now a days they're just re-branded Tea Partiers. Real libertarians acknowledge the usefulness of government as long as it stays small and not intrusive. Libertarians now just wanna overthrow the government because a half-black man is in office. So if you vote down the line libertarian, just for lack of a better option, it could produce some pretty shitty results. So get to know your local independent candidates. You might have a lot in common with some of them. Either way, this starts local. Know your local politicians personally and what they stand for in order to get the right people in office. That's how you get your vote to count. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-06 01:08:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thanks man/woman! I don't know though. I'm from Louisville and people are very kind there. It still has its southern charm even though it's a progressive city. Unfortunately, most of the rest of Kentucky makes people think all of Kentucky is shitty. The rest of our Kentucky, outside of Louisville, is like your Phoenix or Scottsdale. Ha </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-06 01:01:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Awesome! That does help. Thanks for the reply! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-06 00:54:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I am an individual that is not affiliated with any party. I say far left because it's easier for people to understand what I mean when I say that, having never met someone. I am obviously against all the NSA bullshit. I am for universal healthcare, marriage equality, tax hikes for the wealthy and most other things on a "socialists" agenda. I am simply stating that even though I hate what our government is, I understand that aspects of government are essential for the population. And that there is no-one that I would cast a vote for other than Bernie because everyone else is just evil like always. I'm also not naive to think the Bernie would have a huge impact as president since the problem starts locally. We need to get the right people in office at the local level to change anything but at least it would be a start in a positive direction. Basically, I hate Obama a lot but not because he is black like some redneck asshole. I hate him because of all the fucked up deals he has made while people's backs were turned, worrying about Jenner's dick or what not, i.e. making Monsanto infallible, trying to push TPP forward, extending the patriot act, drones, defender of troops staying in the middle east to secure the opium trade, etc etc etc. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-06 00:06:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's OK. I've been training. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-05 23:46:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Nice! Am I allowed to just call them squabs and eat them?

Edit: The pigeons, not the dogs. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-05 23:43:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Sorry, I don't fully understand your question. Are you saying that because things have been shitty for the last 20 years how can I still be to the left since there's been a "democrat" in office the last 7 years? If so, if you didn't realize, Obama is a conservative (w/ moderate capabilities) republican. The right has become so far out there that moderate ones are misdiagnosed as a democrat. Don't get me wrong, I hate democrats and republicans alike but I also realize that some government(not the current one for sure) is necessary, just as long as the boundaries aren't crossed(as we are way past that).  We are screwed until corporate money is gone from elections and we do away with the two party system. I don't know if this answers your question or not and if it didn't then simply put.... It's extremely easy to keep a far left stance at 33. And to answer the last question you had...my vote is with Bernie Sanders or no one. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-05 23:21:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thanks. I'll have to check it out. I went to Mi Nidito last night. It was pretty decent. The Chile relleno was the best thing I had there. Not very impressed with the menu but overall decent. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-05 23:16:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You sir, take an upvote. They are amazing guys as well as musicians. That's what they like to be told anyways. ;) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-05 23:13:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That's what the girlfriend is for. Well....that and many other things....well some things </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-05 23:12:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Nice. That's comforting, anyways. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-05 21:42:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah. Unfortunately, I don't have the qualifications to be a fluffer. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-05 21:33:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Right on. I'm sure this is a big argument but where in your opinion is the best place to have authentic Mexican food. By authentic I mean chopped up organs straight off a grilled pig onto a handmade tortilla with a squirt of lime and cilantro authentic. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-05 21:25:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thanks! I drink tons of water anyway, granted it's usually mixed with bourbon, so that shouldn't be a problem. I am aware of the shit show that is Maricopa Co and Scottsdale. My gf has always said that the rest of Arizona gives Tucson a bad name and after reading what all has taken place over the last decade or more, I can see why she says that. I am an avid fan of the outdoors and have been up Mt. Lemon once before. It is beautiful. What is the music scene here like? Is it like most southwestern cities or is there more of a independent feel here because of the college demographic?  I would guess scuz rock, people who used to love Sublime and still do, and the rest like Los Lobos. Hopefully I am wrong. Ha </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-05 21:16:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I am from Louisville so I am very aware of the disdain for out of towners. I will do my best to be the least douchey I can be until one day, I too, can hate people that just moved here. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-05 21:14:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Well...I love dogs, I don't mind a little tang to my water and I prefer not to drive so as a pedestrian, I will be on the lookout for crafty turn arrows. Thanks! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> I am 33 yrs old, faaaar left, from Kentucky and just moved to this beautiful city. Tell me about it. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-05 20:16:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-03 18:19:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> How else do you mow a tree? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-02 22:20:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> No, it's uncool to pick up 11 year olds at candy parades. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-01 05:54:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Awesome! Welcome to the 19th century along with the middle east and eventually america. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-31 23:32:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I get that but if our country is to have any chance of being unfucked then we have to do away with the 2 party system. My point was that the republican brand name isn't what it used to be. It is now just a group of redness trying to out douche each other for profits. The democrats aren't much better. The government does nothing but throw polarizing issues at the masses in order to keep them arguing and distracted while the government slips out the back door and accepts deals that are detrimental to this country. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-31 18:11:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> We don't need a governor who appeals to the republican party at all. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What's a pirates favorite type of fish? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-31 17:20:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> GAAAARRRRRRRR!!!

Edit: I beat ya guys to it. Ha </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-31 15:35:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> She needs a nose reduction. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-31 13:20:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Luckily it didn't matter since I signed a PTA. He sentenced me to 3 years but my PTA said I couldn't serve more than 16 months. So with good time taken into account, I served a total of 14 months (December 13th 2001- February 14th 2003).

Edit: He/They definitely wanted to make an example out of me, however. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-31 03:57:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You're very welcome. Indeed, it was. As I was being led down the neon lit hallway, amongst the United States vs. My Last Name signs every two feet, I could see the judge just glare at me. Good thing I signed a PTA. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-31 02:02:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I was in for selling MDMA. I was a 4421 which was a Legal Service Specialist (paralegal) and worked for JAG. I worked for the judge who sentenced me and was at his house the previous Thanksgiving. It was awkward to say the least.   Military prison in Japan is weird in a lot of ways. In some ways it was better than civilian jail (food, day jobs, hygiene, ...) and in some ways worse (military regimen, solitary confinement, visitation, only that shit ass Armed Forces Network on the tv, ...) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-30 23:20:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I did 14 months in a military prison in Japan. It's been 12 years and I still always have to sit with my back against a wall. That and I eat and drink everything as fast as I can. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-28 15:59:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Take away the sword in The Sword in the Stone </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-28 15:56:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> A rubber band gun. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-28 00:35:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Fracking?  Frapping? Frap Attack! Duck. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-26 13:50:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> " Hell hath no fury like a woman's scorn for Sega." </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-26 03:57:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Talk about "Ribbed for her pleasure". </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-16 16:47:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> A "teaser pony" if you will. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-11 17:54:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I sincerely drought it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-11 17:51:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Give me liberty or give me meth! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-09 18:19:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Who gives a flying fuck? This is just more polarizing bullshit. MLK Jr. did so much for human rights but who fuckin' cares?! That sum ova bitch copied a couple sentences. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-05 00:09:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So you're saying she'll win? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-04 12:23:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> He looks more like Christina Ricci. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-03 16:45:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I think you mean, spitful. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-18 16:09:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'd still boink her! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-16 18:05:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Nothing like blurring a hamster decapitation and not a human one at the hands of ISIS. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-11 01:27:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> In fact it is no one's cup of tea. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> I like my comedy how I like my milk..... </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-10 17:57:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> dry. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-10 02:01:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Looks like you're in the military. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-09 01:05:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This is the same person. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Have you seen Jesus's abs?!! </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-05 16:56:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> He must be doing that Cross-Fit workout! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-05 07:08:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Started liking bottoms now I'm queer. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-30 15:47:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> One can be both. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-29 19:26:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I thought Philip Seymour Hoffman was dead!? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-29 17:45:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm sorry.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-29 17:35:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> When you're Reich, you're Reich! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-28 05:45:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Cranberry computer Taliban milk </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> AHH, Schlitz! </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-27 21:40:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-27 13:43:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I still like the guy but he did that on purpose. He's done plenty enough press conferences to know the mic was on. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-27 00:48:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's like that scene in Donnie Darko. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-25 19:17:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Ha! Yeah, a little more manish though. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-25 18:22:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Down on the beach. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-25 18:17:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Because pouring superglue in a woman's stink crevice isn't safe anywhere. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-25 16:21:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> She looks like one of Joseph Smith's old wives.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-20 20:26:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Is this why religious people say that they are made in god's image? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Fifty Shades of Grace </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-20 20:14:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-10 23:52:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Never forget 9/12 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-10 18:41:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's the the ol' long kahn.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-08 06:49:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What a moron! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-26 14:17:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's simply trial and error.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-24 14:20:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Banana for scale! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-18 13:25:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's funny how they had to add "Male" to immigrants. Stigma much? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-17 09:43:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Looks more like an Oscar Mire Wiener to me. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> When did cartoonists drawing for animated shows start drawing a 4 fingered hand and why does it continue to this day? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-09 00:14:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Ways to explain better? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-05 16:41:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I get in fight with my girlfriend all the time about this and it drives me crazy. She received the MMR vaccine in the Army then developed Chron's disease. The Army subsequently kicked her out for it. So she very adamant that vaccines fucked her up. I have argued the normal talking points as to why vaccines are essential but I am at a loss for words now. How do I explain better or have her come away from the dark side? It is very difficult to talk to her about this because it is something that will always negatively affect her and she sees it as the vaccine having a direct correlation between her and Chron's disease. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [Just a status symbol] </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-24 15:53:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Just a status symbol. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-24 15:43:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Little to a lot </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-12-21 16:20:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Are there any decent U.S. $5 minimum deposit sports betting sites? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What to do? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-10-08 05:22:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I am visiting your fine city for All Souls and staying in a hostel downtownish. Was wondering if anyone can be so kind as to give me some non-tourist suggestions of what to do.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Humbling </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-08-14 04:59:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Buttshroom </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-08-11 21:48:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> A little help please. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-07-22 02:53:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> My friend posted this pic of her as an infant with her dad for Father's Day.....he was way ahead of his time. Happy Father's Day to all of us who deserve it! </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-06-15 20:02:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> James Vincint McMorrow -- Cavalier Live on Kexp [Soul] </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-03-27 02:48:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Does anyone know if our great city has any 9/11 Truth meetings that go on? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-12-21 02:35:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What is the craziest/most impressive self project you have accomplished using only the internet? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-10-14 22:28:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Kishi Bashi everyone </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-03-14 02:41:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What are Jonny Clearwaters Adam Bomb capsules? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-03-14 01:08:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Any weird I-70W road trip suggestions? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-02-13 00:45:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> I-70 suggestions </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-02-13 00:24:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Finalized finishing touches on road trip!! I am going I-70W through Missouri and Kansas till I get to Colorado then Moab, Utah and settling in Tuscon, AZ for a little bit. Anyone know of anything awesome, fucked up or any awesomely weird roadside attractions I can check out while there? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Why I shouldn't be allowed at Media Day. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-10-23 04:14:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Who needs a pinky,brain? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-10-16 05:38:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> It's my Reddit day of birth and I'm the fat ,hairy one. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-07-26 12:01:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
