<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject8925</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2011-03-13 08:19:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I wish I had a good movie to recommend that portrays mental illness accurately! So many movies do it incorrectly. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2011-03-13 08:15:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm a sophomore at the University of Minnesota - Twin Cities. I'm studying political science with a minor in social justice. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2011-03-13 08:11:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> No, but the previews skeeved me out. Mental illness as a romantic comedy plot device is a tad offensive to me. Soundtracked with indie pop! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2011-03-13 08:09:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I meant AMA, don't even worry.

I no longer have manic episodes, so yes, I am not bipolar. I went through intense therapy for two years to calm my mania. I miss it, sometimes.

Starting at the age of nine, I became convinced that God was talking to me, and that my family was demonically possessed. I would have periods of violence and attempt to hurt my parents and my little brother to exorcise them. When I was 12, I swallowed half a bottle of Tylenol in an attempt to join God in heaven. My father, who is bipolar himself, enrolled me in therapy. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2011-03-13 08:00:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> He's pretty excellent. Last night I was walking across campus when I realized that I needed to jump off the bridge across the river right. now. I immediately sat down on the ground and texted my friend to come and get me. This is a fairly regular occurrence - my suicidal urges are incredibly strong. 

My thoughts are alternating between thinking about how I could possibly hurt myself here and knowledge that I don't actually want to hurt myself, it's just the crazy talking. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
