<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject6069</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-20 21:17:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> And their definitions, legally speaking, vary greatly from country to country. Additionally the method of collecting data (such as whether individual instances are counted separately or if reports count equally as convictions do) and cultural factors surrounding reporting play a role. So yes, in order to make specific claims, those terms do need to be defined and those factors do need to be taken into account on a case by case basis when comparing statistics between countries. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-20 21:11:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The contention about the definition for sexual assault is an extrapolation made by the person who posted the links, and nothing is said about whether the definition of sexual assault has also been broadened - it does not appear in any of the quotes they sourced. So no, it does not directly address it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-20 21:05:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [Sweden is the "rape capital" of Europe mostly because they collect data differently than most countries.](https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Rape_in_Sweden#Swedish_rape_statistics) For example, data is collected right when it is reported, not when it is verified to have occurred, so any incidents that are later overturned are still counted as rapes. And if a woman says she was raped by her husband every day for a year, Sweden counts that as 365 rapes while other countries typically count it as a single instance. The legal definition of rape is broader in Sweden than elsewhere, and there is not as much of a taboo around reporting as elsewhere. That is why there is such a disparity - not because it's vastly more common in Sweden. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-20 19:06:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So the headline gives a quotation, but the quotation never appears in the article and is never credited to anyone. Beyond that, if a staff member goes out an publicly derides their boss in the way that this guy did, it's entirely reasonable to demote them. Can we please remove independent.co.uk as a valid source on this sub? It's as bad on the left as breitbart is on the right! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-20 08:24:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Another post, another dodge. No justification for the claim that the march is opposed to women having the right to choose who they vote for. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-20 08:10:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  If you don't want to be written off as stupid at this point you'll have to answer some very basic questions.

Is this the internal monologue you've been ignoring this entire time? Listen to it! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-20 08:08:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Dude, no. Barring someone from attending a march is IN NO WAY equivalent to the disenfranchisement involved in removing their right to vote for whoever they want to and we BOTH KNOW that's a ridiculous thing to try to claim! Jesus christ! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-20 08:05:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> We both know you didn't come anywhere close to starting to back up your claim, at all. Just put it simply for me: how is telling people they can't come to a march telling them they can't vote for whoever they want to? How does any of what you've said even approach justification for the claim that the purpose of the march was to remove the option of voting for whoever anyone wants to? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-20 08:00:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> No... it really, really isn't. It's telling them they can't come to a march, not saying they *can't* choose to vote for whoever they want to. How in the hell is it removing their choice of who to vote for? Instead of justifying your earlier overstatement of the facts, you just go one step further in overstating the facts. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-20 07:57:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This isn't how a discussion works - you don't answer a question by asking someone else to prove a point first. If you can't back up your claim, just say so and we can move on. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-20 07:50:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  The women's march was against women having the freedom to vote for whoever they want.

Again, that's what I'm asking you to justify. How was the march *against women having the freedom to vote for whoever they want*? Telling pro-life people not to come is not that. Telling Trump supporters not to come is not that. Even punching female reporters is not that (also I haven't heard of it - what are you referring to?). Telling people they don't have the freedom to vote for who they want is advocating for that freedom to be actually taken away - no examples of which you've provided, and certainly you haven't demonstrated that that's the core, organizing principle of the march. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-20 07:19:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> OK, so you just won't answer the actual question, that's fine. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-20 07:18:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Well the headline was "DHS weighed Nat Guard for immigration roundups" and the up to 100,000 officials in 11 states number (which is in the article, not the headline though) comes from the number of National Guard members who would be eligible to participate in the 287(g) program, allowing state and local officials (and National Guard members if this memo were put into action) to act as immigration authorities. The memo directs the head of ICE to seek out and pursue all opportunities with state and local jurisdictions to enact the 287(g) measures. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-20 06:50:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That was a bigly fuckup - probably three, but unquestionably two, of those heavy duty shots were unnecessary. Mario slowly slunk in there instead of ending it quickly. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-20 06:30:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm going to the first comment of yours that I replied to so we can get back on track and you can explain it, since you've just been dodging it instead:

 The women's march was against women having the freedom to vote for whoever they want.

This is the contention I've been asking you to support. The march was not arguing that women *can't* vote for whoever they want to. It had plenty of advice on who people *should* vote for, but to say it was *against the freedom to vote for whoever they want* is a completely disingenuous overstating of the facts.

AP: you should go ahead and [read the actual AP report](https://apnews.com/5508111d59554a33be8001bdac4ef830). It says:

 DHS spokeswoman Gillian Christensen declined to say who wrote the memo, how long it had been under consideration or when it had been rejected.

How was the author miscredited to make it seem worse when the author of the memo was never mentioned in the report?

 A DHS official described the document as a very early draft that was not seriously considered and never brought to Homeland Security Secretary John Kelly for approval.

So as you said, it was a low-level memo. The AP report doesn't say otherwise. [Here is the memo itself - it has lots of numbers, but I don't know what numbers you're saying it doesn't have, please clarify.](https://www.documentcloud.org/documents/3467508-Trump-National-Guard-Draft-Memo.html) Again, everything you say the report doesn't say, it does say. So labeling it fake news and false exaggeration is inaccurate. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-20 05:59:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> First paragraph - again, explain how turning away pro-life groups means they are saying people can't vote for whoever they want to...

Second - the results were within the margin of error for the aggregate polls. It was statistically unlikely that Trump would win but unlikely is not impossible, as we see every day when unlikely things happen. The AP report simply said that DHS considered the option of using the National Guard, which is true. There was an early draft memo on the option. This is the problem with calling all reporting, polling, and news that you don't like "fake news" - it is almost always the case that the report is actually accurate and that more was read into it than it actually says by people who want to freak out and claim there is a false news epidemic. Another example: when Trump called CNN fake news for reporting on the fact that he and Obama were briefed on the existence of the Steele dossier. That was something that actually happened - that was not fake news. They were briefed, and that's what CNN said happened. 

Third - now we're in anecdote country so I'm going to just let that go. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-20 05:23:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Two guys, one with blue shorts and one with black, are fighting in a cage. There's an audience there. A couple of people are explaining what's happening. There's also a ref there. There's a small HUD that shows the time and the score. There's a big M in the middle of the mat. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-20 05:21:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You could look into JKF, the moon landing, and Tower 7, or you could just google intergalactic-psychic-vampire-pedophile-politicians and skip all the stuff in between. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-20 05:15:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Anyone know how Cyborg Santos's dome is doing these days? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-20 05:06:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> First paragraph - still wondering where you're getting the idea that a movement representing women's rights means it's against women being able to vote for whoever they want to, as you claimed.

Second - really hard to parse what you're saying - all we've seen from Trump is consequences for lying? He hasn't faced nearly high enough a price for all the lying he and his administration do. Also wondering what you mean by the media lying its ass off to prevent his election - can you elaborate?

Third - Why would you presume I or anyone else thought it was a perfect system prior to this election? I have felt for years that ranked choice voting would lead to more representative outcomes and have wondered since Bush vs Gore whether or not the EC makes sense in the modern media world. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-20 04:59:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I have no doubt that it was his clumsy speech that created the issue. But that's why it's worth thinking about what the fuck you're going to say before you say it - perhaps even carefully planning a speech and making some digressions from it on points that you really want to emphasize. Fact is, he brought up "last night in Sweden" without specifying anything about it, and then listed cities like Brussels and Paris and Nice where terror attacks have happened. This really would be no big deal at all if he was just Donald Trump, rich guy making a speech. But he's the fucking president. The things he says matter very very much for that reason alone, and this style of speech where he just gets up and rants and raves is dangerous. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-20 04:54:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Exactly right. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-20 04:43:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Holy shit, so we put my Fox News watching, half baked idea spouting uncle in charge of the country </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-20 04:39:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So he's a valley girl now </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-20 04:38:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> He's like a smart person </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-20 02:55:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Wouldn't the last thing they would want to do be indicating that Trump is "one of their own?" If ever there were a person I'd think the Republicans would hang out to dry it would be Trump. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-20 02:54:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  Cohen travel to Prague is indicated

 Cohen coordination with Flynn is indicated.

I missed when that happened - last I saw was that stupid picture of a passport - what's the scoop </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-20 02:35:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Very excited </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-20 02:33:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Personally I was about to go bully but I reconsidered </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-20 02:33:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Mutually Assured Bullying </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-20 02:32:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Joe Martinez is not new, he does occasional events and has done for some time, since before the sale. The commentator is doing a very solid job. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-20 02:31:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yep, ? and Anik </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-20 02:30:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So did Carla bully her or something? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-20 02:13:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The \#3 ranked strawweight in the world, ladies and gents. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-20 00:49:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> At the very least their voices are different enough that you can tell who's talking </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-20 00:48:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If you're in the States you can watch the FP prelims on fightpass, but will have to switch to FS1 for the rest.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-20 00:46:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's excusable, their guy lost - and they weren't booing during the interview, so np by me </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-20 00:43:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That was slick </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-19 23:26:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Due to an insanely busy work schedule I decided to read a short book, or rather, collection of stories. It was **Clarkesworld: Issue 124** - a monthly publication featuring short sci-fi. It had six or seven stories and a few non-fiction articles. Although the stories were mostly interesting, I discovered that I'm not a huge fan of sci-fi short stories. One of the joys of sci-fi is getting to jump into a weird world that's different from our own due to technological advances, in much the same way that fantasy is cool because magic changes things. In short form, though, you barely get used to the rules before the story is over. The gears shift too quickly. I thought I might like it because I'm a big fan of short horror, but it was not to be. Still, it's really cool that these stories are available in print each month.

This week I will have the time to read **Authority** by Jeff Vandermeer. I started it last week and I'm not as gripped by it as I was by **Annihilation**, but that may change. The spooky, mysterious facility and the mystery of the former director is intriguing, but the family backstory is less so. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-19 21:38:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I guess triggered has completely lost all meaning now. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-19 18:44:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This is the problem with Trump though. He says things in such a vague and undefined way that people can say "he meant X" when he might have meant Y or Z. People on both sides of the issue can do it because he is so fucking imprecise that it's basically a Rorschach test.  He doesn't specify "what happened in Sweden last night", and then goes on to list several cities where there were terror attacks. It is pretty easy to see why people would read that as him implying there was a terror attack. He most likely does this intentionally so that people can take whatever they want from it. If he were simply running a business that would be one thing - but the president sets agendas nationally and internationally and clarity is extremely fucking important in that arena.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-19 18:31:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm willing to bet there were plenty of people sitting around saying things like "our grandparents fought *real* X or Y" during the rise of past fascistic governments, and look where it got them. The great part about our system is that we get to voice our opposition to where our government is headed. We get to start heading it off at the pass instead of letting it flourish. Personally I feel that focusing on the incompetence of Trump's administration, and his betrayal of the working class that put him and the rest of the Republicans in office, is going to be a far more effective technique in unseating him.

I am pretty much on your side about the Milo shit, the protests get him more notoriety. He would not have been on Bill Maher without that bullshit. Saying the women's march is against women being able to vote for whoever they want is disingenuous and goofy though. And when people cite the popular vote victory it is typically to demonstrate that Trump doesn't have a mandate, or to suggest that we ought to consider reform in our system of voting, both fair points to raise.

We have seen explicit threats and table setting from Trump to silence free speech with the force of the government through a concerted campaign to discredit any journalistic outlets that dare to question him, and he is, after all, the president, so what he says has a hell of a lot more weight than some gutter punk antifa at Berkley. We are still in the very early days of his administration so those threats are incredibly worrying and need to be monitored.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-19 18:12:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Oh yeah that was those precious few days where /r/the_donald tried to convince Trump to solve the Flint water crisis and he did nothing about it and they eventually moved on, I remember that </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-19 15:57:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'd be stunned if you weren't leaving out tons of context that would explain those bans. You didn't *just* say people should be able to camp on public land, did you? You didn't post "lol" in a vacuum. Got the actual posts that got you banned handy? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-19 15:53:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's a support sub and dissenting views will be banned. It started as somewhat satirical but tons of genuine supporters joined and now it is what it is. If I'm missing something, enlighten me. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-19 15:51:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's unbelievably easy to get banned. Just get into a mild disagreement about an issue. For example, voice support for sanctuary cities, say you're opposed to the wall, etc. Get into a reasoned debate with someone and play devil's advocate to your positions. If a mod notices it, you will be banned. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-19 07:16:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> ...I noticed you still haven't provided a source for those claims... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-19 07:14:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> He's like a smart person </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-19 07:13:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> But it was three different people and they're all idiots, so... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-19 07:12:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I tried to watch the rally today but I didn't even make it to the part where Trump got on stage. It was a truly bizarre event. The guy prior to Melania described Trump as the "next president" of the United States as if the campaign was still on-going. It was a completely needless and strange affair. I had to bail when Melania started reading a prayer. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-19 06:45:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> To be honest if you haven't been banned from the donald and you post there on a semi-regular basis, that says plenty - the fact you're able to go into those other subreddits to argue with people speaks well of them and very poorly of the donald.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-19 06:35:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Seriously - this dude is choosing defending Nazis as his hill to die on. I hope he's making these impassioned pleas for actual decent people and not just actual Nazis. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-19 06:33:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm not sure what the right answer is but I'd be willing to bet people were having this appeasing attitude towards the rise of the Nazi party in 1930s Germany too. There is a reason Nazi is essentially a slur and Hitler is the go-to example for a horrible person. It's because they're horrible people and they care not a lick for your reason and empathy.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-19 00:51:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Of course it's sad. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-19 00:44:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> wut </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-19 00:44:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Come back when you finally realize you shouldn'ta </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-19 00:42:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> ...the joke being that Trump gave his opponents nicknames with that exact structure: descriptor, name. And it sure worked for him! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-18 23:52:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> /r/titlegore  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-18 23:22:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I don't think many people would analyze the specific primate selected to deride Trump, either </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-18 23:19:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Think about it though... somehow our money knew Lincoln would be president before he was even born... money can predict the future... [8] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-18 23:07:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Uh... he *chose* to run for president, didn't he? It's a position of service, one for which you are expected to make many sacrifices. By no means was he required to run for president. He chose to, was elected, and now every decision he makes will be rightfully scrutinized as a potential conflict of interest because he was not patriotic enough to divest. He could have just sat on his laurels and made money through his business if that's what he wanted to do. Now he is the employee of the American people and we deserve better than a greasy self-enriching person making decision on behalf of our entire country in ways that will directly financially benefit him. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-18 23:01:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah it's the family size that is adding up not the fact that 2 of them live in downtown friggin' New York City and he flies down to a resort every weekend and his sons travel the world doing business deals with security on the taxpayers dime... nothing to do with their lifestyle choices, purely the size of the family amirite </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-18 22:58:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Perfect description - Greasy Donald is what they should have called him way back in the primaries </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-18 22:52:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  Melania is just as bad as Donald.

nah. but she is bad. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-18 22:45:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> How crazy would it be to spend money that has your own face on it... [7] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-18 22:44:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Anyone know what his little pep rally tonight is costing us? A completely needless event for which we have to pay travel and security costs, among plenty others. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-18 21:09:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's only a problem if you are using reign in the most restrictive sense. Reign is a pretty flexible term that comes up often when discussing a powerful person. CEO's are described as reigning over their companies and yet they are still accountable to their boards in many cases. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-18 20:50:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Not yet </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-18 20:48:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> At the same time, free reign makes just as much sense </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-18 18:51:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Fucking incredible </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-18 18:50:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> dicghazi </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-18 18:48:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> *standing ovation* </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-14 22:07:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Looks like I played myself. Read George Soros, bailed on the rest, revealed myself to be a goober </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-14 21:43:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> At this point there is an accusation that Trump and his administration have ties to Russia and colluded with Russia during the campaign. We now have evidence that a member of his team *did* communicate with Russia and lied about it. Now we have an undeniable basis for an investigation, which might involve Trump and his team having to testify and actively *prove* that they were not involved. This is different than a criminal trial. It's a congressional investigation. It's not innocent until proven guilty because it's not a court room - it's an interview under oath where congresspeople try to ferret out the truth. The rape analogy does not apply. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-14 21:39:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I gotta tell you that bringing up George Soros un-ironically makes most people roll their eyes and move on without reading the rest of the post. People have made such a supervillian boogeyman out of George Soros that it's a punchline at this point. I'm still waiting on my Soros checks for the political activism I've been participating in lately. Come on George, pay up! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-14 21:37:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yes let's recognize that Obama betrayed his promise of transparency and get better about holding our leaders to account now and in the future. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-14 18:50:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  - An excerpt from the memoir "Ravings of a Teenage Edgelord" </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-14 18:48:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It started out as a way to describe legitimately fake news - things that literally did not happen but were posted to facebook as headlines and often with links to sites that were designed to look legit, but weren't. It was then co-opted to describe journalistic mistakes, poor reporting, misleading headlines, and in its final stage, things that people just don't like. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-14 18:45:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I had a feeling this was bullshit when I saw it posted on /r/the_don. It was just the clip saying it was refugees in France but with no way of actually verifying that information. Fake fucking news, man. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-14 17:13:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Out of curiosity which intel are you referring to? Intel about the sanctions? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-14 15:56:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> No, you just littered our White House and presidential cabinet with filth instead.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-14 15:55:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The sentiment is much appreciated.

*BUT* unfortunately our president mainly interacts with other heads of state, and those are the people who will determine our fate as a nation. The lower we sink, the less interested people will be in working with us. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-14 15:45:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Looks great, thanks! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-14 14:46:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Reminds me of the doctor's letter about how Trump is the healthiest person ever to run for president. No fucking subtlety or shame in these people. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-14 14:40:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The media and the intelligence communities should be doing the jobs they were established to do, and that's all they are doing. It's not about them being mad because they were insulted. It' about them seeing us heading in a very dangerous direction and doing their best to report on it and reveal the truth. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-14 14:35:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Bad mindset - even if some of them are it is way too easy to write off and ignore the group if you have that mindset. Treat them as if they are actual people because the majority are. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-14 07:53:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Best part is that earlier today they linked a CNN article on this topic claiming it was fake news - but that was *before* the resignation. Now there are people in comments pointing it out to them. Good popcorn. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-14 07:52:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [8] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-14 07:51:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Kellyanne seems to have dodged the conflict of interest bullet since Flynn dove right in front of it with this story. If I had to guess - Miller is next. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-14 07:50:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The Denial is real </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-14 06:51:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Awesome </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-14 05:44:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Flynn was not a part of the president's national security team as Trump was not the president yet. That's why.

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-14 05:43:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Ahem... /r/conspiracy, NOW IS YOUR TIME TO SHINE! There is an actual fucking conspiracy happening at the highest levels of the government! Where the fuck are you? Oh, that's right - you got cucked by the donald. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-14 05:39:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> They have posted several memes about how the courts blocked the immigration order - but the memes imply that the courts are like, an opponent who is acting out of malice, not a legal institution performing its function. It is fucking bizarre over there. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Therapy by phone? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-12 04:53:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hello,

I have long thought that therapy would be very beneficial to me due to extremely high levels of stress, bouts of loneliness due to travel, and several other reasons. Since I travel so much it would not be feasible for me to keep solid appointments with a therapist in person. Does anyone have recommendations for services that are affordable and offer therapy by phone? Thanks! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Professor Sage </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-25 01:50:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Any interest in a weekly /r/52in52 podcast? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-11 00:23:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This popped to mind while I was showering today - is there any interest in a weekly podcast discussion of that week's book? I have only recorded some (very) low-key podcasts mainly for my own entertainment in the past, but I think it could be fun. I'm envisioning a discussion of the book where people can connect and chime in if they'd like, a section where we highlight some reviews of the book (professional reviews or funny ones from amazon), bring up some of the points mentioned by users in the discussion thread, maybe some information on the author... any interest and / or thoughts on other sections that could be good in podcast form? I would very much to host and/or help get something like this off the ground! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Bradbury's hand-drawn map of Green Town </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-05 14:35:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Incessant Fundraising - Strongly considering Cancelling my subscription </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-04 15:00:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Is anyone else feeling this way? It permeates every conversation that TYT has these days. I get that they're trying to make a ton of money for their investigative reporting teams, but there's a reason NPR only does periodic fundraising drives and then just has occasional mentions about donations in bumpers between shows. That reason is that it drives the listeners insane to *constantly* hear about donations and fundraising. It seems like that's all TYT has really focused on over the past few weeks, and considering they still want to raise $1.4 million more, it doesn't seem like it will be ending anytime soon. This makes me want to cancel my membership for at least a few months until this ends. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [Image/GIF] Two American Heroes salute the flag at Pride 32 </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-08 05:36:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> 52 books: my highlights and lowlights </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-06 05:23:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> First of all, thanks to this sub for keeping me on-track - I lurked throughout the year and picked up some great recommendations. Instead of a full list, I will just give five highlights and five lowlights. Well get the bad out of the way first - these arent necessarily the worst books I read this year, as I rated most of them 2 stars, and read several one star books - but they were the most disappointing compared to my expectations. I promise you I am not trying to be edgy by hating on popular books - I read several popular books that I enjoyed quite a bit this year. Anyways, on with the lists!

**LOWLIGHTS:** 

**Ready Player One** ** by Ernest Cline - I loved the first 50 pages of this book - it hooked me hard. But I quickly grew tired of the endless lists of references - they started to seem less like an interesting stylistic choice and more like a total bore. I could hardly handle the parts that just describe our hero playing a video game or reenacting a movie - that was about as uncompelling a storytelling device as I can possibly imagine. It had its moments, and a very strong opening, but on the whole I was very let down.


**Dark Matter** ** by Blake Crouch - Another highly-compelling sci-fi concept that wasnt explored in enough depth. The central narrative severely limited the scope of this story, which could have been boundless and infinitely (literally) interesting, but instead felt very confined by the characters choices. It also explained several fairly well-known scientific concepts (Schrodingers Cat, the Multi-Worlds Theory) in the way that Crichton does - but the concepts werent out there enough to work the way that Crichtons books tend to. It felt elementary. Its also called Dark Matter, and they explain what Dark Matter is in the book, but Dark Matter has seemingly nothing whatsoever to do with the book. 


**Good Omens** ** by Terry Pratchett and Neil Gaiman - It felt rambling and tangential, and more than any other co-authored book that Ive read, it felt like two people wrote it. Maybe it just isnt my type of humor, but I just didnt enjoy it all that much.


**Fear and Loathing in Las Vegas** ** by Hunter S Thompson - It seems to me like this is a book I would have absolutely loved while I was in college. Part of the point was that these guys (sort of) realize that theyre assholes at the end of the book, but it didnt make reading about them being assholes for a couple of hundred pages any more enjoyable. I do think back fondly on the mushroom trips Ive taken and on (some of) my drunken escapades with friends - but we were nowhere near as shitty as these two are, so its tough to get on board with them. Some of the writing was quite good though.


**The Man in the High Castle** ** by Phillip K Dick - To be honest I just found it dreadfully boring.

**HIGHLIGHTS:**


**Infinite Jest** by David Foster Wallace ***** - This one was very much about the journey, a 3-month one for me. I can see why this book has a reputation, but in all honesty, it was a much more enjoyable book than I would ever have expected simply by virtue of the fact that it is often absolutely hilarious and frequently prescient and insightful. It is also extremely confusing and seemingly tangential for about the first 200 pages - the pieces dont start to click together for days and days worth of reading. But once they do click its a pretty amazing feeling, and the pieces fit together better and better as you begin to understand what youre reading and get further into the book. The sections about addiction and alcoholism were especially meaningful to me, as I had recently quit drinking and was struggling with that myself. I will absolutely reread this someday.


**Lolita** by Vladimir Nabokov ***** - Some truly excellent writing. I found it to be a very alarming experience to get seduced by Humberts eloquence and comedy, drifting into sympathizing with him as I read, then only later remembering oh shit, hes a rapist and pedophile. The writing was absolutely top-notch. As disturbing as the implications of the book are, and as creepy as I felt reading it in public (which I did only once, for that very reason), it was a hilarious, tragic, and discomfiting ride.


**Mans Search for Meaning** by Viktor E Frankl ***** - Incredibly powerful first-hand account of what it took to survive a concentration camp. Makes you take a seat and think wow, my life *really* isnt all that bad after all. Ever since my decade-long crying drought ended during the first 5 minutes of Up, I have been more and more sentimental as time goes on, and I will admit that I shed a few tears during this book at some of what I was reading. It is seriously fucked, what people went through, and a lot of survival just came down to random chance. The second half of the book details the mindset Frankl used to mentally cope with what he was going through, and its very applicable to everyday life. Essentially, having a purpose, a reason for being, is what keeps people going. Without purpose, direction and motivation evaporates and people faded to dust in the camps - but with a purpose in mind, its far easier to deal with what life throws at you.


**The People in the Trees** by Hanya Yanagihara **** - The first half of this book was such a different experience from the second half. You are treated to an anthropological exploration of an incredible, strange culture, and theres a mystery afoot. Then, all of a sudden shit starts to get weird. And from there on out it gets weirder and more depressing and disturbing until the end, which is completely devastating. 


**The Beach** by Alex Garland **** - An incredible character portrait - a book where I wasnt fully sure what was going on until 250 pages in, when things started to click and I realized this character I was reading about - all the weird things he had done that I had excused because I was seeing them from his point of view - was something different than what I had been thinking of him as. I was also a big fan of *Ex Machina*, which Garland directed, and *Enslaved: Odyssey to the West*, a game which he wrote. Hes directing a film adaptation of *Annihilation*, another book that I greatly enjoyed this year, so Im excited for that to come out in 2017.


Fittingly, I am finishing out the year by reading **The Sixth Extinction** by Elizabeth Kolbert. This year seemed set on periodically shooting a fire extinguisher at my sense of what is right and just in this world, so why not read about mass annihilation to close it out!

Edit: Just in case anyone is curious, I do have a standardized way of rating books - it's entirely based on my own opinion/evaluation of course, but it helps ensure that my ratings are based on the same criteria and not just an impulse:

Is it a book? +1

 - By virtue of being a book it gets a point.

Is it interesting? Up to +1

This can mean entertaining, informative, intriguing - basically, how much did it capture my interest? Score can be 0, 0.25, 0.5, 0.75, or 1 - the higher the better.

Quality Writing? Up to +1

How strong was the writing - was it consistent across the book or were there weaker sections? Did the plotting make sense? Did the writer seem to achieve whatever their goal seemed to be with the book? Was there anything particularly memorable about the writing style? Etc.

Message? Up to +1

Did the book leave me with something to think about? This is important to me, but might not be to others.

Extra: -1 to +1

This is to build in wiggle room if something was especially great or especially terrible, or if something truly stood out about the book (in a good way or a bad way). In order to get a 5 a book has to be especially great in some way to get the extra +1.

So I just have a spreadsheet with each of those slots on it, and I type my numbers in, then round up or down depending on what the number is to get my star rating for the book. Pretty simple! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
