<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject8625</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-09 12:45:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You did this reddit haha with all your trump brainwashing memes </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-08 08:52:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Did he end up finding the ninja turtles </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-08 02:41:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Reminds me of farcry 4,  shotgun fixes everything  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-07 18:24:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Finish her  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-06 14:20:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Isn't it more comfortable to have your hands under the blanket  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-05 09:38:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Dam that dog been lifting  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-02 18:19:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Is this guy trying to loose more teeth  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-02 18:17:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That cake is more soup then sponge </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-02 18:06:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I can't seem to stop watching hahaha </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-01 18:50:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hate to see what happens when the cameras aren't rolling </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-01 09:02:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Take it out the pan and place the pizza on a rack this should cook the bottom,  make sure to cover the top with foil.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-01 07:58:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> There goes my plan of diving into water to avoid a jaguar chasing me </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-01 02:27:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I don't think the AI world is ready for clients wishing to talk to a lawyer.  AI work on past data,  like any computer system you put crap in you get crap out.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-01 02:25:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I wouldn't even brother raising this as a legal issue/s,  but more as a life lesson. 

Could you get fired legally?  Probably,  depends on the documents you signed and terms and conditions you had to adhere to. 

Should you demand a reference? No,  search the term "wilful damage",  getting fired was the best outcome for you.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-31 07:18:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Do you even lift bro?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-31 03:05:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hope their flea and tick treatments are working  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-29 07:31:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thank God those pants stayed one  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-29 03:58:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> How many times has the dog stepped on his junk hahaha  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-29 03:55:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If a butterfly can defeat a koala how they going to survive in the wild  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-28 04:22:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Did anyone else the read the neighbours comment,  "he had nice pants"  lol </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-28 04:18:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You could go down the company secretary or consultation route if you have a background in commercial. 

If you are a peoples person you could try getting a legal related software/service sales job for  infotrak or  practice management software provider. 

You also have the academia route,  but be prepared to undertake more study and forced to churn out well researched legal based papers. 

The law recurtiment market is expanding as more hr companies are trying to make their money. 

Then you have countless opportunities as a inhouse legal counsel. 

Maybe have a look at beyondlaw.com.au,  a law degree is quite universal these days so I guess the sky's the limit  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-28 00:19:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I second this is a great write up :)  I would assume you would rely heavily on referrals for work.  How did you build a strong referral network?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-27 19:37:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Bill you are home!!!  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-27 19:36:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Just cut out some eyes and costume done,  she looks like those pumpkin head guys from goosebumps  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-27 19:34:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Man urban development has ruined the humble parking bay </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-27 19:29:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If I had a cricket ball hurdling to me I would be ducking for cover... Those things can kill </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [AMA REQUEST] Exotic car sales person </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-27 16:44:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What is the most expensive car you sold? 

What are your typical customers like? 

What are the commission like? 

What car do you drive? 

How did you get into the industry? 

What Supercar is the best daily driver? 

Do most people pay cash or finance?

How many cars do you sell a year? 

What is the biggest insider secret to get the best deal while buying a Supercar like a Ferrari,  Lamborghini, etc?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Lawyer awakes from surgery </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-27 15:20:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> And can't see see anything,  he yells out for the nurse. 

He hears the nurse come running in, and asks "What's wrong?" 

The lawyer replies,  " I came in for a knee operation and now I am blind!  I am going to sue you,  the hospital,  the doctor,  the..."

Before he can finish the nurse removes the bandage covering the lawyers eyes. 

The lawyer yells, "Why the hell did you cover my eye!"

The nurse answered, "There's a fire across the street, and we didn't want you to think you had died." </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Why are lawyers so expensive? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-27 15:09:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Because presidential campaigns aren't cheap </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Gangster vists a lawyer </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-27 06:25:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> A gangster sets up a meeting with a lawyer. 

The gangster asks the lawyer,  "How can I get away with murder?" 

The lawyer replies,  "I don't know".

The gangster asks the lawyer,  "How can I get away with armed robbery?" 

The lawyer replies,  "I don't know".

The gangster asks the lawyer,  "How can I get away with drug trafficking?" 

The lawyer replies,  "I don't know".

The annoyed gangster says to the lawyer, " Well what the hell do you know? "

The lawyer looks down at his watch and smiles,  and then says" That your bill will be $2,000". </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-27 03:48:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The real question is why do some many people have bears as pets?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-26 08:20:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Why do old videos always make things seem miniature?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-26 08:19:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Where's the devil horns?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-26 08:16:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Try doing that with piano or cheese string </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-26 06:30:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thank you so much for your answer :)  in the four years of running your firm what the biggest hurdle you have come across? 
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-25 18:37:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I hope that cub is actually part of the family and not being taken into the woods against their will </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-25 18:31:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Would you look into buying a firm to expand or offer different area? Or would you rather grow your existing practice?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-25 05:08:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Apparently that string is around $3000 haha

https://lawyerist.com/44691/how-much-it-really-costs-to-start-a-law-firm/ </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-25 04:50:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Out of curiosity more than anything.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Cost to start a suburban law firm </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-25 02:53:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I am curious to find out how much were your law firm start up cost? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-24 15:43:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I think you are better off having a consultation with a lawyer.

Many things to be considered such as the payment liabilities,  your personal circumstances,  the regulatory aspects,  and overall the legality behind actually buying and transferring the debt. 

If I was you speak to your accountant, who may be able to refer you to a suitable lawyer who specialises in such areas.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-24 15:33:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I don't see a real issue why you can't undertake the bachelor of law option. A JD does cost more per year than a LLB,  but in QLD they are both seen equally as I have heard.  But most people opt for a LLB as the course material is slightly easier (apparently) and the cost are significantly lower. 

Overall it is more a personal thing in Australia,  whereas in the USA a JD is more pronounced than a standard LLB. 

I believe there was an article on lawyers weekly recently summing up the real differences. 

http://www.lawyersweekly.com.au/news/19739-law-dean-slams-juris-doctors-as-problematic </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Do most magistrates come from a criminal lawyer background? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-21 08:23:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm trying to understand the pathway that lawyers/barristers take to become a magistrate.  Would love it if anyone can enlighten me on the pathway. :)  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-19 14:15:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> There is another course that turns law students into psychopaths haha god so much to learn  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-19 14:12:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thank you do much :D those images really put it into the structure into perspective  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-19 13:40:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I am feeling like I need all the help I can get haha apparently I am at the bottom of the learning curve and that learning torts is apparently turning students into psychopaths  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-19 13:38:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Do you use a yes no answer tree?  

For example for non fatal offences (e.g. Common assualt,  etc)  I found that using a flowchart that ask if the physical elements are available,  then consent and so then end up with the most suitable offence.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Exam Flowcharts </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-19 09:07:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hi all,

I would like to know if anyone here used flowcharts during their exam, and is there any structure or examples commonly used?

Would you advise someone to create a flowchart for a criminal law QLD exam and is there any examples of that particular subject? 
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
