<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject5492</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Dont call it a rebuild  Benning explains Canucks moves </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-06-28 00:25:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Kevin Allen steps down as The Professional Hockey Writers Association's President. Scott Burnside new President. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-06-27 17:14:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Stastny wants to see whats out there, will test market </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-06-25 15:20:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Which team underachieved this season, but will bounce back next season? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-06-24 21:24:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> How was your weekend? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-06-16 15:51:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> How do you feel about tie clips? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-06-04 02:46:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So i currently have an internship at a pretty big company. I have silver tie clip that I like a lot and wear it with my outfits. Although, I seem to be the only one wearing one, from what I can tell. Our dress code is shirt, tie, slacks and dress shoes so to me adding a tie clip doesn't seem too out of place. But I do feel that it might be a bit tacky/show-offy.

What do you guys think? Or do you have any opinions on them? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> My high school bully is now coming to my college. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-05-31 02:44:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This really put a damper on things.

So I was browsing around my school's sports website (I'm on the lacrosse team, so I was wondering if any news about us was up). There was a post about the incoming recruits for the football team and I decided to give it a look. Scrolling down the list mindlessly, one name caught my eye and as soon as I saw it my heart dropped. It was the douchebag that bullied me all throughout high school.

This guy abused me mentally and physically. I was originally cut from the JV team in HS and he made fun of me for it everyday, he also called me names relentlessly. I was also a total loser so it was pretty easy for him to pick on me. He is around 6'3 250lbs and I'm only 5'9 175, so easily he shoved me around, hit me and knew that there was nothing I would do.

I hate his fucking guts, he made me miserable. Ever since college, I have never been happier, I have tons of friends and being on the lacrosse team is a dream for me, and something I strived for. I am a completely different person than in high school. But now he is going to be here, and it is quite a small school and I will easily see him at times. I know some of you might say that he is may of matured or whatnot, but trust me, if he gets that chance he will just bully me again. He is crazy, and I'm pretty sure not all there in the head. At times he would act like my best friend, then all of the sudden snap. He would relentlessly bully me, follow me around, shove me if he saw me, the works.

I am honestly scared to see him at school. I don't know what will happen. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Reddit, what's on your bucket list? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-01-20 20:06:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Blue Jackets' Comeau out 4-6 weeks with MCL sprain </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-01-10 17:43:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Game between Carolina Hurricanes, Buffalo Sabres rescheduled for Feb. 25 </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-01-09 18:31:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> This was my car one year ago today, after my near-fatal car accident. Happy to be alive! </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-01-08 21:40:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> I survived a near-fatal car accident a year ago today, AMA! </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-01-08 21:10:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> First off, i'll explain the whole story in the comments if someone asks, because it is quite long.

Basically, a year ago today I was coming home from a basketball game, hit black ice, spun out and crashed into tree going 45 mph. Doctors told me, I'm lucky to be alive and they don't know how I survived. So, go ahead, AMA!

Here's a pic: http://i.imgur.com/w7WzXdd.jpg </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Let's hear your Olympic predictions! </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-01-08 20:59:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Nabokov out 2 weeks with injury. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-01-08 17:32:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Dan Bylsma is now the Penguins All-Time Winningest coach. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-01-08 06:58:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What is a song that can instantly put you in a good mood? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-01-04 04:27:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What is the best song that has come from a TV/Movie soundtrack? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-01-04 04:15:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [Serious] What do you need to get off your chest? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-12-23 01:29:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Time to open up reddit. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Caps put Neuvirth (lower body) on IR </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-12-02 17:10:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [WP] A man is slowly sinking into insanity. Write his inner monologue. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-11-29 03:58:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Think American Psycho-esque. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Reddit, tell me a story? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-11-28 01:23:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Funny or sad, stupid or serious, real or fake. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> This is the 2nd time in 3 weeks I tried to drunk drive. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-11-19 06:21:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I don't know what it is. I don't want to die but I think it's that if I do, then I know people will care about me. A lot of my childhood and teenage years I was bullied and didn't have a lot of friends, this turned me cold and emotionless. Now that I'm in college and nothing from my past is with me, I have a lot of people who care for me but I still can't comprehend it. I don't think I'm suicidal but I think I'm insane.

Each time I've had people talk me out of it and make sure that I knew that I was special. It's helped but there is still just something there. Something that makes me want to get behind the wheel and risk it all.

I've also been getting more fucked up at parties, last Saturday I snorted vodka to feel a rush. I've been getting trashed and that has just worsened my intentions. Right now I am a mess. I've considered talking to a therapist. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What is a good beginner DAW to use? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-11-18 18:16:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So obviously I want to get into making trap, but the DAW's listed in the FAQ are somewhat confusing. Are there any simple ones I can use or can someone give be a 101 on some of the DAW's you use? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Does anyone know of any good websites that will show you upcoming concerts? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-11-18 17:47:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So me and some friends have been trying to go to a show for a while but we haven't really had much luck in finding shows. We have only found big artists listed, which we would love to go to but are no where near us or sold out. So does anyone know of a website that lists a lot of shows or anything? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Jets' Slater out indefinitely with sports hernia. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-11-07 22:32:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Glencross out six weeks with MCL sprain </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-11-07 18:34:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Leafs Sign Jerred Smithson </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-11-06 23:49:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> How are your rookies doing? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-10-10 03:09:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I know we have heard plenty of some (MacKinnon, Hertl). But how are they all panning out? Do you think they'll stay with the club all season? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> /r/nfl, What happened to "one of the top qb's in the league" Matt Schaub? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-10-09 22:07:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Elias in for Devils, Neal questionable for Penguins </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-10-03 22:17:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Jets sign 13 first-rounder Morrissey to entry-level deal </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-10-03 21:20:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Preds Forsberg (lower body) to miss first two games of season </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-10-03 21:18:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Redditors in a relationship, have you ever had one day where you and/or your SO have acted like you were single? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-09-25 00:19:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Basically have you or your SO gone a day where you were "single" and did whatever you wanted? Tell us about it. Throwaways are welcome. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> College party tips. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-09-09 03:15:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm gonna make this short and simple. I just started college, and have been going to parties, but haven't really found a girl yet. Questions:

How do I get a girl to dance with me?

How can I get her away from the group?

How can I tell if a girl finds me attractive in, let's say, the first minute or two?

How can I get my drunk friend from hitting on every woman there, and possibly getting hit?

Thanks ~~boys~~ men. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> If for one time, the NHL decided to induct current players into the HoF, who would be in next year's class? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-09-07 23:11:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Just a little something to think about. Basically if the NHL decided for next year's HoF class they would include current players, which would be voted in. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> 30 Greats/30 Days: Mario Lemieux Post is now up! </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-09-05 23:06:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hey guys so about 2 hours ago I posted my Lemieux write-up for /r/hockey If you haven't seen it yet, go check it out.

http://www.reddit.com/r/hockey/comments/1lsycp/30_greats30_days_mario_lemieux/ </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> 30 Greats/30 Days: Mario Lemieux </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-09-05 21:38:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> First of all I would like to apologize for my lateness and the confusion and disarray surrounding this post. I just started college so the last week has been hectic and I haven't had a chance to finish up. I hope you all enjoy this as much as I did making it. If I missed anything, I'm sorry, with a ton of information I had to make it as short as I could.

I'd like to thank /u/Blobbles890 for setting up this whole thing up and /r/penguins for their help with the biography and highlight section.


**30 Greats/30 Days: Mario Lemieux**
________________________________________
**Position: Center**
________________________________________
**Drafted: 1st Overall, 1984 NHL Entry Draft**
________________________________________
**Teams:**
*Pittsburgh Penguins: 1984-1997; 2000-2005*
________________________________________
**NHL Stats:**

*GP: 915*

*G: 690*

*A: 1033*

*P: 1723*

*PIM: 834*
________________________________________
**NHL Playoff Stats:**

*GP: 107*

*G: 76*

*A: 96*

*P: 172*

*PIM: 87*
________________________________________
**Career Awards and Recognitions:**

* 	Hockey Hall of Fame  1997
* 	Stanley Cup champion  1991, 1992
* 	Olympic gold medalist  2002
* 	Hart Memorial Trophy  1988, 1993, 1996
* 	Art Ross Trophy  1988, 1989, 1992, 1993, 1996, 1997
* 	Conn Smythe Trophy  1991, 1992
* 	Lester B. Pearson Award  1986, 1988, 1993, 1996
* 	NHL Plus/Minus Award  1993
* 	Calder Memorial Trophy  1985
* 	Chrysler-Dodge/NHL Performer of the Year  1985, 1986, 1987
* 	Dapper Dan Athlete of The Year  1986, 1989
* 	Lester Patrick Trophy  2000
* 	Bill Masterton Trophy  1993
* 	NHL All-Star Game MVP  1985, 1988, 1990
* 	NHL First All-Star Team  1988, 1989, 1993, 1996, 1997
* 	NHL Second All-Star Team  1986, 1987, 1992, 2001
* 	NHL All-Rookie Team  1985
* 	CHL Player of the Year - 1984
* 	ESPN Hockey Player of the Decade  2000
* 	ESPY Award NHL Player of the Year  1993, 1994, 1998
* 	Lou Marsh Trophy  1993
* 	In 1998, he was ranked number 4 on The Hockey News' list of the 100 Greatest Hockey Players, the highest-ranking French-Canadian player.
* 	Inducted into Canada's Walk of Fame in 2004.
*	His #66 has been retired by the Pittsburgh Penguins, Team Canada, and Laval Titan.
* 	In 2009, he was made an Officer of the Order of Canada "for his contributions as one of hockeys most gifted players, as an inspirational role model and mentor, and for supporting charitable initiatives through the Mario Lemieux Foundation".
* 	Played for Canada in the: 1983 World Juniors (bronze), 1985 World Championships (silver), 1987 Canada Cup (Won), 2002 Winter Olympics (Won), and 2004 World Cup of Hockey (Won)

 **Pittsburgh Penguins Franchise Records / Achievements**

* 	Career Leader in Games (915), Goals (690), Assists (1,033), Points (1,723) and Seasons (17)
* 	Single Season Records for Goals (85), Assists (114) and Points (199)
* 	Captain between 1988-90, 1990-91, 1991-94, 1995-97, 2001-04, and 2005-06
* 	Longest goal streak (12 games)
* 	Longest point streak (46 games)

**Mini-Biography:**

Mario Lemieux was born on October 5th 1965 in Montreal to Pierrette and Jean-Guy. Lemieux started practicing hockey at the age of three in his basement and eventually his father built a rink in their front yard so he and his brothers could play.

At the age of 15, Lemieux was drafted by the Laval Voisins of the QMJHL (Quebec Major Junior Hockey League). He had declared he would break records, and that is exactly what he did. During the 1983-84 season, Lemieux broke the season record for points with 282 (133 goals and 149 assists). In his last game of the season Mario needed 3 goals to tie Guy Lafleurs goal record. He ended up scoring 6 goals and adding 6 assists in a 16-4 victory.

The Penguins selected Lemieux with the 1st overall pick in the 1984 NHL Entry Draft. Lemieux had said that he would play for any team that picked him, but because the Penguins and Marios agent had not agreed on terms for a contract, when his name was called Mario refused to shake hands with management and also did not put on a Penguins jersey. Despite the conflict a contract would be agreed upon and Lemieux started the season as a Penguin. He made his first appearance on October 11th, 1984 against the Boston Bruins. On his first shift, Lemieux would steal the puck from future Hall of Famer Ray Bourque and score on his first shot. During this season Lemieux would be named to the NHL All-Star Game and go on to be the first rookie to win MVP honors. Lemieuxs rookie campaign was tremendous; as he had posted 100 points and went on to win the Calder Trophy as the NHLs top rookie.

The next few seasons Lemieux kept up with his crazy point production and in 1988 won his first Art Ross Trophy (top point producer) with 168 points. During this year he would also collect the Hart Memorial Trophy as league MVP. In the 198889 season, Lemieux led the league with 114 assists and 85 goals for 199 points. Lemieux finished the season a close second to Wayne Gretzky in voting for the Hart Trophy, and set several milestones and records in the process, becoming the second player to score 70+ goals in two seasons, the fourth player to score 50 goals in 50 games, and the only player to score 13 shorthanded goals in one season.

During the 1992-93 season, Lemieux scored a goal in his first 12 games and was on pace to possibly surpasses Gretzkys single season goal and points records. This was until he made an announcement that shocked the hockey world. On January 12th, 1993 Mario Lemieux told everyone he was diagnosed with Hodgkins Lymphoma. Lemieux underwent aggressive radiation treatment and missed two months of the season. On the day of his last radiation treatment, Lemieux flew to Philadelphia to play against the Flyers, where he scored a goal and an assist in a 5-4 loss. Before the game Lemieux earned a standing ovation from Philadelphia fans, which just goes to show how much he meant to the game. Even with missing two months Lemieux would score 160 points and beat out Pat LaFontaine for the scoring title. He also went on to earn the Bill Masterson Trophy and Pearson Trophy.

During the 1993 season, Lemieux experienced many back problems and underwent back surgery for a 2nd time. After the season Lemieux would take a leave of absence to recover from his treatment. He would return for the 1995-96 season. During that season he again led the league in scoring with 69 goals and 92 assists, and became the 7th player to win 3 Hart Trophies and the 4th player to win 5 Art Ross Trophies. The next season Lemieux again led the league in scoring with 122 points, and also announced this would be his last season. When he retired Mario Lemieux was the only player to average more than 2 points per game. On November 17, 1997, Lemieux was inducted into the Hockey Hall of Fame and also becoming the ninth player in history to have the mandatory three year waiting period waived.

In 1998, the Penguins were in trouble financially and the threat of moving or folding the team was very real. At this point, Lemieux offered to buy the team. Years of deferred salaries, adding up to $32.5 million, had made him the Penguins' largest creditor. He proposed to convert $20 million of his deferred salary into equity, enough to give him controlling interest. He also promised to keep the team in Pittsburgh. The U.S. Bankruptcy Court gave preliminary approval to Lemieux' bid on June 24. Lemieux later said that he would have put in a bid even if he had not been owed the deferred salary. The NHL's Board of Governors approved his application for ownership on September 1, 1999. Two days later, the court gave final approval to Lemieux's reorganization plan, allowing him to formally assume control. This made the then-retired star the first former NHL player to become majority owner of his former team. Lemieux assumed the posts of president, chairman and CEO of the Penguins.

In 2000, Lemieux decided to make a comeback into the NHL and on December 27th played against the Toronto Maple Leafs, where he would score a goal and add 3 assists. Despite playing in only 43 games Lemieux scored 76 points to finish 26th in scoring and finish the season with the highest points-per-game average. On December 23, 2002, during his afternoon radio show in Pittsburgh, host Mark Madden said he would donate $6,600 to the Mario Lemieux Foundation if the hockey great ever scored off a faceoff. That very night, the Penguins played the Buffalo Sabres in Pittsburgh and Lemieux, who was aware of the challenge, made good on it when he scored the game-winning goal right off a faceoff during the third period. On January 24, 2006, Lemieux announced his second and permanent retirement from professional hockey at the age of 40. This followed a half-season in which he struggled not only with the increased speed of the "new NHL" but also with atrial fibrillation, which caused him to experience irregular heartbeats. Also, Lemieux remarked that" I can no longer play at a level I was accustomed to in the past, possibly another reason for his leave.

Nowadays, Mario Lemieux is still owner of the Penguins Organization and has brought them back to the top of the league. He also founded the Mario Lemieux Foundation to fund medical research projects. He and his wife, Natalie, along with their 4 children; Lauren, Austin, Stephanie, and Alexa reside in Sewickley, Pennsylvania.

P.S. We have the same first name...tehe.
________________________________________

**Highlight Reel:**

[5 goals in 5 ways](http://www.youtube.com/watch?v=EJNpoIi8OWg)

[End to End Goal vs North Stars](http://www.youtube.com/watch?v=pEdgiPEDa8w)

[Lemieux to Crosby](http://www.youtube.com/watch?v=MGZID3mxYAY)

[Game vs Flyers after cancer treatment](http://www.youtube.com/watch?feature=player_detailpage v=FxHXcx8jJ0Q t=97)

[Goal vs North Stars](http://www.youtube.com/watch?v=P0OCTC03Vzo feature=youtu.be)

[Faceoff Goal](http://www.youtube.com/watch?v=sZiCx0vfRKo feature=youtu.be) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Great win tonight. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-09-01 04:22:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> We played hard all game, even when we were up big. Wheeler had a solid game and everyone stepped up. Amazing hitting from the guys and solid defense. Even though our chances of a playoff spot are slip to none we should still be proud of the team. Great game and congrats to Matt Den Dekker on his first MLB hit. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> 30 Days/30 Players: Brooks Orpik </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-08-31 16:54:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> **DAY 16: BROOKS ORPIK #44
PLAYER SUMMARY**


Born September 18th 1980 in San Francisco, CA, Brooks Orpik (Brooksy) currently plays defense for the Penguins. Orpik started off his hockey career by playing for the Nichols School in Buffalo, NY then heading over to Massachusetts to play at Thayer Academy. Although never playing in the CHL Orpik went on to play for Boston College for 3 years winning the Hockey East Championship twice(1999 and 2001) and the NCAA Mens Ice Hockey Championship in 2001.

Drafted 18th overall by the Penguins in the 2000 NHL Entry Draft, Orpik spent a year with the Baby Pens before in the 2002-2003 season was called up and has been with the Penguins ever since. In his first full season Orpik played in 79 games, registering 1 goal, 9 assists and 127 penalty minutes. In 2008 he signed a 6-year deal worth $22.5 million that will expire at the end of this upcoming season. Along with Evgeni Malkin, Orpik wears an A on his sweater to represent alternate captain.


**STATS**

**Career Stats**


| Stat  | Regular Season  | Playoffs  |
|:-----:|:----------:|:------------:|
| GP |  631|       87
| Goals |  11|  1  
| Assists  |108  |   12     
|Points|119|13
|+/-|35|-5
|PIM|688|88

**12/13 Season** 

| Stat  | Regular Season    | Playoffs   |
|:-----------:|:------------:|:------------:|
| GP      |    46     |     12  
| Goals|    0|  1  
| Assists    |        8|   1     
|Points|8|2
|+/-|17|2
|PIM|32|10




**BENEFIT TO THE TEAM**

Not only is Orpik a hard-hitting gritty defenseman, he is also a leader in the locker room. His play on the is always physical and he tires opponents down with his checking. He doesnt back down and do whatever he can. Although in recent years he has lost some of his touch he is still a valuable player on and off the ice. He is a leader in the locker room and a force on the ice.

**HIGHLIGHTS**

* ["The Shift"](http://www.youtube.com/watch?v=XpBXdefDulU)
* [Huge hit on Daniel Paille](http://www.youtube.com/watch?v=NwdHmuiJZyw)
* [OT winner against Islanders](http://www.youtube.com/watch?v=g-x91Snvs6I)

**FINAL THOUGHTS**

Brooks Orpik has played for the Penguins all his life and myself, like many of us hopes to see him retire that way. There has been speculation of moving him in order to make the cap. Although we do not know what will happen we know what Brooksy provides. Most likely playing on the 2nd and 3rd pairings and PK, Orpik will still be a tough defenseman to play against and along with Scuderi will be the veteran leadership the defense needs.

P.S. Sorry about the weird formatting.
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Team Canada: Lines for 2nd walkthrough </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-08-26 20:10:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The Specktators - Miss Me </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-08-22 02:56:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Which is the better conference going into the season? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-08-22 00:44:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Basically, which conference do you think is stronger? Has better teams? etc.. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What is something you wish to experience in your lifetime but won't? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-08-21 03:05:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [Serious] What is the worst thing you have ever done? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-08-15 03:40:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Might be good to use a throwaway. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> First time smoking alone at my home. Couldn't of gone better. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-08-14 21:54:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Key   Peele: The Great Start Program </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-08-13 02:45:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What is a food you hated as a child but love as an adult? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-08-13 02:02:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Tips for living in a triple and overall party hall? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-08-13 01:31:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I got roomed with 2 other people which means we will have a triple. I wanted to know if there were any tips I should know about and if it is any different than just a double? Also, the building I will be living in is the notorious party dorm on campus. Like anyone else I love a good party but how can I make sure I don't get sucked into the scene when there will be parties all around me? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> I'm a tad late to the Civ 5 party but still... </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-08-06 20:44:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Wilkes-Barre/Scranton Jersey for sale or trade. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-08-06 01:13:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I have a Wilkes-Barre Scranton Jersey for sale or trade. It is a Large(fits like an XL) and has a fight strap in the back.

Here is an album: http://imgur.com/a/S1d3a#6K7aYiC[1]

Sale: $40-$50
Trade: Another Jersey (M or L) or t-shirt (L)

Comment if you have any other questions. I'm also posting this to /r/HockeyClassifieds   so I will be taking the best offer from either site. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [Gear] Wilkes-Barre/Scranton Blank Jersey-Sale/Trade </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-08-06 01:03:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I have a Wilkes-Barre Scranton Jersey for sale or trade. It is a Large(fits like an XL) and has a fight strap in the back.

Here is an album: http://imgur.com/a/S1d3a#6K7aYiC

Sale: $40-$50

Trade: Another Jersey (M or L), T-shirt

Comment if you have any other questions. I'm also posting this to /r/penguins so I will be taking the best offer from either site. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Bastille - Flaws </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-08-04 19:37:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Having a temporary implant. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-08-02 05:10:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It is a temporary crown on an implant. Not a temporary implant. Sorry.


So I have a question about my temporary crown on my implant. I got it today and it will be on for 2 weeks until my permanent one is ready. So on Saturday me and some buddies are going camping. This will include kayaking, rope swinging into a lake and cliff jumping. I was just wondering, would by implant pop out from any of this. Like when hitting the water would the pressure and subsequent biting down make the crow loose?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Possible meetup at a game? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-08-02 04:57:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So /r/hockey has been talking about meetups and it got me thinking that we could do a meetup at a game one day if enough people are willing to go. Now the date isn't set but it would most likely be a Saturday game. What do you guys think? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Happy Birthday Geno! </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-07-31 17:32:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Girls love. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> /r/hockey 30 Greats in 30 Days </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-07-29 20:04:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So I have volunteered to do the /r/hockey 30 Greats in 30 Days thread for the Pens. Lemieux is our great. Now I could do this myself and put all of my opinions in it but I wanted everyone to be included. So you guys are going to help me, I want this to be the best post of them all and I can't do that without all of you. I want everyone's opinion on this, not just mine.

So the categories that I want you guys to help me with are:

Rivals: This can be a team or player, we can have as many as we want.

Career Achievements: Obviously a lot of will go on here, many of them without discussion, but if you feel like there should be something listed here that is significant let me know.

Highlight reel: I want to see all of Lemiuex's greatest moments in this thread. We can have as many as we want so go crazy.

Extra Information: Anything else you feel is significant.

Like I said, I could do this all by myself and only put in my 2 cents but I wanted to get everyone involved so this can be the best 30 Greats in 30 Days post of them all.

Here is the original post: http://www.reddit.com/r/hockey/comments/1ja9ki/30_greats_in_30_daysupdate/ </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Today is my birthday and I turned 18, AMA. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-07-28 20:03:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This birthday sucks so far. I've had 3 people(not including my parents) actually say happy birthday to me, I think everyone has forgotten. On top of that I'm sick so I can't go and do anything. I figured reddit could cheer me up. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What is the biggest sports scandal/conspiracy theory? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-07-26 00:17:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Good Guy Eric Young. Not sure if you all have heard of this. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-07-25 18:40:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> All class from Eric Young. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-07-25 05:34:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That was a great thing Young did after he stepped on Hudson's ankle. I have never seen a player run up and help a player he injured. Young seemed generally concerned for Tim. Even when he was being carted off, Young was over there talking and making sure everything was good. I have never seen a player do that. Now I haven't been able to watch a lot of Mets, since Dish Network hates them, and ESPN just pisses me off but that was the first time I have seen that.

Stay classy, Eric Young. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Cypress Hill-It Ain't Nothin' ft. Young De (Album: Rise Up) </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-07-24 21:22:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> JagrWatch2013: 99% likely to sign with Devils. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-07-21 17:09:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Redditors who know/love to cook, what is your favorite meal to make? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-07-20 03:10:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Reddit, what is your favorite memory? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-07-19 23:07:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Please be specific. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> EA has finally stopped caring. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-07-19 19:32:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> If given the chance to go back and change one moment in your life, would you take it and how would you change it? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-07-19 06:56:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Also please include what the moment and original outcome were. Funny and serious responses are all welcome! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Oh, so that's what Reed does. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-07-19 06:37:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
