<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject4010</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Any good YouTube channels that speaks about Half-Life lore? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-08-25 13:41:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Title says it </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Any good YouTube channels that speaks about Half-Life lore? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-08-25 13:20:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-08-20 21:15:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I know, but allot doesn't. Most have the real canon. + playing as a citizen/rebel gives allot of insight on how things were :p </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Need help with the lore/story of half life for an assignment </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-08-20 14:31:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I need to know how humanity lived, got around, where everything was during the half life 2 games and some time before that. I've played allot of HL2RP so I have some knowledge on how everything was but it would help tremendously if I could get some hard facts on the topic.

The assignment is find a problematic situation in absolutely anything inside the media, books, movies, games, etc. I chose the situation that civilians deal with in the half life universe since it sort of reflects how many people was treated during WW2 and the lore is amazing as f*ck. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-08-20 10:47:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Mirrors Edge, Half Life and Portal games </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-08-17 19:34:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Well since the fantastic four reboot bombed, Kate Mara could play Captain Marvel in the MCU since we never got a real name other than 'U.S. Marshall'... (+ the badge she had looked like it was from shield i think) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Is Mafia 3 going to be similiar to GTA 5 in some ways? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-08-17 15:40:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> At the end of the trailer we see 3 more characters pop up behind the main one, could these be playable characters like Trevor, Franklin and Michael or just tied into the story characters?

Would we be able to edit cars and upgrade them in garages set in the sixties?

Is there going to be online version like in GTA 5 where we can buy houses, have garages, do different missions with our 'family'(crew)? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-08-15 01:04:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This would be similiar to lavabending where they would have to heat up the sand and create glass, perhaps lavabending is the same as metalbending where it could be learned but it would take training to master it. Then later on they somehow manage to heat up sand to glass (like earth to lava) and manage to control glass. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [No Spoiler] What other kind of special/rare bending abilities could exist in this universe? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-08-14 01:14:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> We have lavabending and flying, metalbending is more common and lightning is in the same league. So what else can there be?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-08-08 20:17:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Exactly, the reason the 3rd Sam Raimi spiderman movie and the last TASM2 movie was so horrible was because Sony interfered too much in the production. Hell Raimi wanted sandman and volture (and introducing eddie brock for spider man 4) instead but Sony said no, interfered, and we got a rushed venom story and an unwanted goblin story.

Would rather have seen Tranks first version of the movie than when FOX came and ruined it... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [No spoiler] Since fantastic 4 reboot had allot of mixed reviews, will there still be a sequel? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-08-08 19:23:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The movie was both good and bad, but got allot of negative reviews and some positive. A lot of problems behind the set too.

But I think a sequel with the right director could redeem it. The cast is great, loads of good stories to take from and to just make a better movie. Think I heard that Singer was going to direct the second movie, which could be a really good choice for the franchise seeing how he did with the X.Men franchise.

I don't want another reboot with a completely new cast since the movie might not have met up to the expectations. I would rather want the same, extremely talented cast members to make a great sequel, and seeing how this movie was topping it wouldn't be that hard. Please, we don't want a new spiderman reboot incidence! D: </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-08-08 17:49:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> PC </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-08-08 17:42:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I don't think a rocksteady SUPERhero game would go well, like superman, wonder-woman, green lantern, etc. It would kinda get too OP and the character wouldn't even be in the same danger as a non superhero. That's probably why the Arkham series worked so good since it a normal guy with tons of gadgets. Think Green Arrow would fit perfectly since he's most likely already in the Arkham-verse and the game mechanics could just flow over to this. Upgrade able arrows, different kind of tech you get throughout the story. Like the DC showcase of Green Arrow would be awesome in a rocksteady game. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [No Spoiler] Why don't I have the Batgirl DLC even though I have the season pass and everything? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-08-08 17:27:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I finished the game 100% not long after the game was released. So I decided to start playing the DLC (Which have been released by now) but when I go and check the DLC doesn't show up anywhere in-game or when I check for updates on the game, not even as an option to download. I purchased the premium deal with the game and season pass so I should have it, but I don't. Help? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-08-07 17:14:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That unmasking didn't make much sense yeah, but the impact would be much, much more better and intense with Tobey instead of using a completely new actor... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-08-07 14:59:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah well we've figured it out. But still adult version in a tv-series would be awesome, not the graphical novel stuff. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-08-07 03:43:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> She broke the cycle, she couldn't remember the past lives and since the spirit world went back into the physical world the cycle kind of ended. (I think) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [No Spoiler] Would anyone else be completely for a new Avatar series with the old Team Avatar as adults? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-08-07 02:58:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Since The Legend of Korra kinda made it impossible for more Avatars coming along, the adult versions of Aang   Co would be the best way to make a new series.

***http://orig07.deviantart.net/1b0f/f/2012/170/e/d/avatar_after_by_gingashi-d540342.jpg*** </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Would anyone else be completely for a new Avatar series with the old Team Avatar as adults? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-08-07 02:47:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Is anyone else annoyed and disappointed that Marvel/Sony chose to reboot Spider-Man again? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-08-07 00:41:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Personally I'd want them to cast Tobey back in the role, he was great as Spidey and much better than Garfield in my opinion. + The way they are putting Spider-man into the MCU just seems wrong and completely rushed. By using Tobey they could make a much bigger impact with the reveal of Spider-man since it's someone we've already seen through 3 movies. (We would also get back J.K.Simmons Back as J. Jonah Jameson, ain't that a reason enough..)

Also here's a link explaining more in depth why they should bring back Tobey: http://moviepilot.com/posts/2015/02/28/why-marvel-should-bring-tobey-maguire-s-spider-man-into-marvel-cinematic-universe-2739119?lt_source=external,manual

And a Youtube Video that compares the new and old: https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=u63-R9NCbXU </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-08-06 22:35:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yup, Would be awesome/best if he'd be recast into the MCU.. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [AMA Request] Tobey Maguire </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-08-06 22:32:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> **My 5 Questions:**

1. Have Marvel contacted you about potentially re-starring as Spider-Man again?
2. Either yes or no on nr.1, would you want to star as Spider-Man again?
3. Do you and Leo have regular conversations and hang out often?
4. What would be your dream movie role in any genre? (Also what superhero would you have played instead of Spidey?)
5. Do you like fishsticks?

**Public Contact Information:** https://twitter.com/tobeymaguire </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-18 02:53:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thank you so much, now I can finally scratch that itch :D </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [REQ] Need help finding a movie, no idea when its from or who is cast. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-18 02:43:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I remember it vaguely from many years ago, back in the beginning of the 2000's I think (I'm only 18).

Okay so I think it was a horror/sci-fi movie. It was on a boat during a storm and on the boat there was a machine(s) that slowly took over the crew by taking their bodies and putting a robotic skeleton inside. Not like in terminator but like the flesh looked like it was literally put on, you could see parts of the body where the shoulders, elbows, neck, pelvis, etc would be robotic while the rest was normal body parts made of flesh that most likely just covered the mechanical beneath.

I remember one scene where I think (remember my memory of this movie might not be exactly how the movie goes) the captain sort of sacrifices himself or goes to where the main machine is to talk or something. I remember him standing in a dark room looking at something with a sort of almost finished robot with human parts on it being assembled/rotating, I think the room was filled with dead human parts and robot parts as well. And that's about it. As the title says I have no idea who plays in it or when its from, I could guess and say its from the 90's/early 2000's but that's it. (Well other than the captain was played by a grey bearded guy at the time.)

This is only a faint memory I've had in the back of my head for at least 10 years now and I really wanna figure out what this movie is called. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-18 00:58:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If you're up for drama, Whiplash.

If you're up for action, Kingsman.

If you're up for creepy, Nightcrawler.

All of them are great movies but of those three the best one would be depending on what kind of movie you wanna watch. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> If Terminator Genisys used Christian Bale and Anton Yelchin as John Connor and Kyle Reese would the movie been better? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-18 00:54:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I liked the last two terminator movies, they had their moments, especially with Salvation showing us the post-apocalyptic world.

Don't get me wrong by the title, I liked the new movie but the casting seemed wrong to me. Personally I'd like the cast from Salvation to pop up again through the windshield, Bale did an awesome performance of John Connor and Yelchin even looks like Michael Biehn from T1 (well now atleast). + It would officially tie in TS with the franchise, and tbh Jai Courtney and Jason Clarke really didn't fit the roles in my head... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-06 19:09:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Am I the only one that thought genisys was awesome af? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> ELI5: Does anyone know how or what kind of program people use to make models for the workshop on steam? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-02 00:25:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Been wondering this for a while now actually, I've made some models in the PAC 3 add-on for Garry's mod but been wanting to make those models into actual models.

PAC 3 is (shortly explained) a model merger/editor, like you could shrink down bones in the upper torso of one model, then do the same with the legs of another model, bone merge those two and you got a new model with parts from both models.

The models I've built in PAC 3 has been used for Half Life 2 Roleplay characters I created, here's the result.

***Example 1 (Citizen edition):*** http://i.imgur.com/b6SEREU.jpg

***Example 2 (Summer Rebel Edition):*** http://i.imgur.com/UanCSWG.jpg

***Example 3 (Winter Rebel Edition):*** http://i.imgur.com/jINdP5G.jpg

***This last one is another character, smaller version of DOG from HL2:*** http://i.imgur.com/8EDtC9i.jpg </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-30 14:49:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Remember laughing at something Joker said:

"There once was a gal named Oracle,

expert in things technological.

But in a fear toxin bind,

she blew her own mind,

and sadly that's not metaphorical!"  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> So what do you want Rocksteady to do next? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-29 23:17:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Personally I'd want a Green Arrow game where he's like in the DC Showcase (https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=cVRiADlDEig). The character would be awesome and could be put in the arkhamverse since we've seen Queen Industries almost everywhere in the games. + they could make some awesome gear with the arrows and have sidekicks like red arrow/arsenal like they did with Robin.

My second choice is to continue the current series with Terry McGinnis. Could fit in with the end of Arkham Knight and continue on years later in Neo-Gotham with an Old Bruce Wayne helping out this new upcoming batman. Could be awesome to see both new and maybe old villains, could also expand it to a new trilogy where we get to play more and more of gotham. (The current Gotham with the Miagani, Bleak and Founders Island. The Arkham City and the Origins Gotham and lastly the Gotham we see on land and not on an island that hasn't been accessable before.) I also saw someone post an epic name for it: ***Batman: Beyond Arkham***

Would not want a Superman game though, wouldn't be the same without the use of gadgets and would be too much OP. But hey if its done right it could work but currently I wouldn't bother with it. + He does exist in the Arkhamverse, Lex Luthor, metropolis has even been mentioned and some thugs saying things like; "That'll teach him. Who the hell does he think he is anyway? Superman?" and the "You know the only thing that's missing is if that freak from Metropolis flew in here." </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-29 21:52:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You gotta finish every sidequest and get every riddle on every island, airships, Arkham Knight HQ and the Panessa studios.
Watch the videos from this guy:
https://www.youtube.com/user/NukemDukem/videos
Or you could just find and interrogate everyone that shines green :p </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [MAJOR SPOILER] Could anyone explain the ending? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-29 21:45:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So after getting every riddle and beat the Riddler and every other sidequest you get the final ending with the knightfall protocol. Wayne manor blows up and Bruce obviously faked his death. What didn't make much sense to me was the stuff that happened after this, rich family that gets robbed like the Waynes and we see a Batman like figure up on a rooftop which turns into a giant bat symbol. SO could anyone explain this? Like how that could happen or is it just Batman using fear toxin? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> so Batman was in the series (sorta) </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-29 15:22:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Don't remember exactly what episode but it was the one where Iris is moving out and finds Barrys old backpack. When Barry looks in it he takes out a comic book with Batmans face all over the cover, it's only for a split second tho. If anyone would find a pic of it that'd be great :D </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [SPOILER] Had an idea on how season 2 will play out. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-22 18:39:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Okay so, I recently re-watched the last 6 episodes of the first season and I think I've figured out a way everything could fit together with each other and make sense.

***SPOILER ALERT***

So when Barry goes back in time to stop Eobard (Reverse Flash) killing his mom we see his future self stopping him. Or do we? Let me explain. We got the past you Barry that gets carried away by future Barry, the one that came back to stop Eobard. Then the current Flash that we see in the series going back to safe his mom. And last we see the future Flash that's going back to stop Eobard. Also what we've gathered of information in the series we know that since that incident there have been two different timelines/universes, so who is from where? Young Barry is in both and grows up to be the flash in both timelines. The Barry that lost his mother is there. But the future Flash and Reverse Flash is from the original timeline, the one where Barry and Iris gets married and his mom lives. Eobard is also from that original timeline but crosses over to the alternate timeline when he kills Barrys mom.

So how does this fit into the next season? Well out of all this and what has happened in the series (mostly the ending) I'd say that the next season would actually start in the original timeline. But then how could the future Flash know that he should stop the current Flash to save his mom in the past? Easy, since the current Flash ran into the black hole in the sky it could perhaps patch onto the original timeline. Like how Cisco had memories of Wells killing him, everyone in the original timeline could remember what happened to the changed timeline (Barry growing up with Joe and Iris, Eddie and Iris in a relationship, Barrys father in prison, etc). So then we see how Barry in the original timeline remembers or gets memories from the alternate timeline, which then he knows he must stop alternate universe Flash to save his mom.

Further speculation on why this can happen is that Tom Cavanagh is returning to the series 2nd season. Well we saw that the original Wells died and that the Reverse flash got vaporized out of existence (Literally). So how could he return? Also easy answer, he would play the original (Not going to secretly kill you) Wells in the ORIGINAL unaltered timeline. He could get memories of how he died in the alternate one and help out the flash as actual Harrison Wells (That'd be awesome tbh). Eddie Thawne in the original timeline could also get some heavy memories of how he died/sacrificed himself.

Final thing I wanted to explain. The reverse flash return, or reappearance, or pre appearance? We could see him in the original timeline as Eobard Thawne, maybe get some back story on why he and Flash is mortal enemies other than "they just are". + We could see Matt Letscher actually play the role for more than 2 seconds. Also to add on this to make it more mind blowing, how did Eobard find out about Barrys identity? Last easy answer is that he learned it from those memories of the alternate timeline.
(They wouldn't have to get every memories from the alternate universe but just the most important (due to obvious reasons as Eobard obviously not knowing everything that would happen in the alternate universe that would happen.), aka Barrys identity, Eddies and Wells death, Barrys mom death. etc)

Give feedback on how this could or could not work in all this.
  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> If Gabe announced anything on any E3s he would die </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-21 19:52:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Imagine it, walks out on the platform starts talking about different ways to change the gaming industry again. Then starts bringing up a new orange box, first Portal 3, then Left 4 Dead 3 and lastly Half Life 3. The screams from fans will simply explode our lord Gabens eardrums, people from China will wake up in the middle of the night all like wtf was that. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> So since ME:C is a free roaming world will there be a online version as well? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-17 17:12:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Title says it, would be awesome to create your own character and roam the world parkouring everywhere with friends. Something like GTA 5 online where you can do missions with friends aswell. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-05 20:48:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> With the current building system you could maybe put down a triangular foundation... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-05 10:50:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Well atleast I have the achievements to prove I've played through the entire game. I've re-installed the game and it launched fine, except now I can only play the intro of the game and then it crashes each time. Any ideas? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [Suggestion] Underwater diving gear/clothes </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-04 22:30:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Title says it (mostly atleast). This could be a cool thing when dealing with base design and how you could interract with them, could bring the entire gameplay from land and into the sea.

Okay so PROS:

 - You could have an entire base underwater, make it harder to raid.

 - It would be hard to spot. (Unless they make the water transparent in the future.

 - You could live under water with the diving gear.

 - New defences could be added like a water mine or sharks(npc animals ofc)

CONS:

 - It could be REALLY hard to get to and possibly life threatening for you to get in if you don't have your gear on.

 - Furnaces wouldn't work (Obviously but perhaps a sort of airlock could make the inside of the base be full of air while the outside would be water.

 - Weapons are useless. (Unless they added something to add on weapons to make them available under water, that is if they ever plan on bringing more things to the under water levels.)


Maybe have caves under water that has airpockets in them, where the entrance is full of water and the rest is livable. Could also make it easier to raid these bases if there was a diving gear or something to breathe beneath water. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What are the names of every item? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-04 15:54:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This is bugging the hell out of me, I've got 9/10 tools and 26/28 clothes and so on and I can't figure out what those last pieces of items could be. Does anyone know what every item is in a categorical list? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-03 22:00:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah I noticed the same after a while. Went to check the server I was playing on the next day and every chest had their locks on, then an hour later they didn't. Sometimes when I opened them I could hear the little *beep* sound even if the codelock wasn't shown, sometimes it didn't. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [Help!]All my saves on the new order is gone! </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-03 21:58:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I've played through both the new order and got abselutely everything you could get from it, perks, collectables, achievements, everything! That was when it came out, and now that I have played through The Old Blood and gotten everything I wanted to play through The New Orders storyline again. Now I find that every extra collectibles I found is gone, deleted, can't even go into chapters as it looks like the first day I bought the damn thing.
Edit: Now a new problem is happening. I started from the beginning of the game and lasted up to when the plane crashes into Deathheads compound. The screen is black and then it crashes. Now when I re-launch the game i barely get past the Bethesda logo before it crashes. Help? ;-;
Sidenote: I built a new pc between then and now, so the game has been played on 2 computers total. Not sure if that has to do with anything. Anyway, anyone got an idea why this is? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [BUG] Code locks randomly disappearing? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-01 21:20:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Noticed that most of my code locks on my chests disappeared after an hour or so, anyone else having this bug or? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
