<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject7608</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-25 17:54:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thanks so much for the ideas! I really like the points system and the timer one! Will definitely use them </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-15 05:23:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Ha.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-08 23:23:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Because I was drunk and thought, "holy fuck he looks like Kellin Quinn"

Looks nothing like him.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-20 17:05:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> MirandaSings. 
If she can be famous, so can a can of peas.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-08-04 04:54:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If I could redo it, I definitely would go with something slightly longer.  But that's just me personally.  I cut all of mine off simply because it was way too hot outside and I couldn't take it anymore...not exactly the best thought process </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-08-04 04:35:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I got a pixie cut about a year ago, and it was great for the first month or so, but I never realized how much work it would be.  I didn't have time to keep it up and looking nice, and I didn't really think it looked good on me anyway, so I'm growing it out.
Worst. Process. Ever.  
There's a mullet stage.  It's unavoidable.  I didn't want to believe it, but it is unavoidable.  My only advice is to be ABSOLUTELY sure you want to cut it, because once you do, your comfort zone is gone (at least for me, it was).  It was weird because people were looking at my face, which sounds weird too, but trust me it's a feeling lol.  
In short, just be sure it's what you want.  If you don't know for sure, go to your stylist and get a slightly longer but still short cut.  If you're still itching for a pixie, go back a few weeks later!  Doing that would've helped me realize I didn't want the cut, and it could help you realize the same or help you realize that you do want the cut. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
