<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject4091</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-19 21:00:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I guess I'm a little late for this but I've been wanting to post this.
Last year I decided to apply to some top art/fashion university. Was on leave of absence on my current school prior to this. The reason being, I'm burned out since it was a course I'm not really interested in and I felt like I'm not learning anything new anymore so I thought I'd work a while.

Anyway, Last year I started processing my application, also worked on developing my portfolio. I understand form very well but I have very little experience in constructing clothes myself. Because of this I decided to leave my office part time job and focus on my business instead--buying and selling macs.

Processing was going alright, submitted my portfolio, and then it was time to wait for the results!

I have been open to my friends and specially my family about this. I was well aware at this point that I wouldn't be able to support myself with my money but some family said they'd help.

Then I got the results. I got in to Central Saint Martins!!! I couldn't believe it! I was a block away from the house when I got the results and I couldn't contain the joy. I was running, jumping, on my way home, couldn't wait to tell my girlfriend, my parents, my friends, the good news. I was one of the happiest moments of my life.

Now, having done the hard part, it's time to work on accommodations, tickets, and most importantly, VISA.

So paying for these hurt my business a lot. And I must admit it's something that I've overlooked. It wasn't long until I had to use my capital too. "Don't matter, my uncle will help me," I thought. Finally, I had to take care of my tuition fee and VISA. They require us to pay for the tuition for the entire year, as for the visa, a huuge chunk of money is required for maintenance. Overall I needed 30,000GBP.

A little background to my aunt and uncle. They're pretty well off. They're known to be very helpful, esp, financially, but never to that scale. But also, they kinda don't believe in art. I personally think of my aunt as sort of a dream killer; her kids were forced to take degrees that they didn't like.

At first my aunt and uncle sounded like they would help. They asked for a breakdown of expenses. The next time we talked I gave them, then my aunt asked for printed docs after I've explained to her everything. Fair enough, I've printed hundreds of pages, brought them to her and finally she told me, "you couldn't even finish your course here. how are you gonna finish your studies there?"

I understand that it was my fault too. I just wished they said "no" earlier.

I'm practically broke now, my savings gone, feeling lost, and is becoming somewhat self destructive.
Edit: Since we have different school systems in the UK. I had to dropout off my college </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-18 17:31:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Ill try this later </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-17 17:39:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm too ambitious yet too lazy to fulfil my illusions of grandeur. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-17 17:20:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I wanted to be an astronaut. I am now a brick. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-17 16:55:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Romanian </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-17 15:04:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Mayors and councilmen in 2 different places </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-17 14:54:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> /r/jailbait? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-17 14:52:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> My family is involved in politics. Dad, a couple of uncles, and me, have ran for several positions on different times. Some still currently in position. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-17 14:47:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> clicking of tongue </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-17 13:56:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> read this in italian accent :)))) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-16 18:30:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Happened during college. On an humanities(?) class, we had a photography project and the professor wasn't clear about the submission. This lead to a couple of my classmates submitting later than everyone. However, based on his instructions, (I can't remember exactly) they are technically on time.
He rejected their projects and I couldn't help but argue with his decision. I tried to tell him calmly that he should reconsider since it wasn't very clear. He started to raise his voice and tried to turn the whole class against me.
The argument ended when he asked the 2 students if he was right to reject their projects. They nodded. Pussies

The rest of the term was hell. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-16 14:29:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I was pretty content with this [wallpaper](http://imgur.com/jcg7VZz) I made till I saw your vid.

Then I made this opened version and used [Multipicture](https://play.google.com/store/apps/details?id=org.tamanegi.wallpaper.multipicture) to transition between [open and closed](http://imgur.com/a/OXrkX)

I think now I'll be using yours tho </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-15 18:19:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Apologize for potatoquality, my phonecamera isn't what it used to be. Taken near back in april

what a wordsmith. you have to finish it! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-15 17:42:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> i imagined my **** sobbing, actual tears. what's wrong with me? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-15 17:38:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> bruh. waddup? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-14 13:51:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I read this in an erotic way... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-10 21:39:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> try to configure your tools? try to create a brush that would match the behaviour of your style on paper. also, experiment with overlays. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-10 21:31:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> personally, i'd hold the pencil further from the point and just let it sorta glide on the paper. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-09 16:28:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Im waiting for my dad's condition to stabilize so i can give mine as well. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-03 00:25:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I was never hit by a lightning but im also quite immune to electricity. I wonder if it developed during childhood. I used to play around electronics and had the occasional shocks. I remember it being stronger then. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-02 23:55:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Reminds me if that doctor who episode...

Mommy? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-31 17:59:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [i had to](https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=l7iVsdRbhnc) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-29 09:48:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This makes me happy somehow </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-24 19:18:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I can't believe no one has said it yet.

For the glory of satan of course. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-14 15:18:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Back at it since PoGo isn't officially released in my country yet. My only regret is not submitting any structure close to my place. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-20 11:52:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> bollywood at it's finest! love em :D </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-07 20:03:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> but but but... you are what you eat. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-07 19:31:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> damn it man </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-07 19:26:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I like your style. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-27 15:19:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Worked with stunningly beutiful people and there's an entire spectrum of them as there is for everything. I know one in particular who had a terrible childhood, grew up to be extremely kind but would snap to a total psycho. Another one was both beaut and smart but is completely unaware of her beauty. I wouldn't say I got bored. After a while they became like everybody else, like I got immune to their physical charm.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-24 11:49:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's okay. Sometimes I use words I don't know just to sound metamorphosis. :) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-24 05:04:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> ten. ten ten thousand. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-24 05:03:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> god damn it Nancy </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-21 12:59:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> damn it! I want one </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-21 11:27:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> you forgot to mention you had morning wood

This is your GF's mother. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
