<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject9239</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-13 15:56:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Sailor take warning! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-13 15:09:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Just because you can't see it doesn't mean it's not there. You believe in air don't you? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-10 16:29:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Oh, you mean those EPA people that are closing coal mines and putting thousands of WV people out of work? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-07 13:57:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Not surprised. When I built my first computer in 1992 there were tables full of CD ROM's. CD players were new and I had the first one on my PC in the neighborhood. I checked out the table with software for kids and there were only a few to pick from. But the table for adults was stacked high with smut. I had no idea what a big industry PC porn was until then. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-04 15:07:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This series was very tedious. I think the 14 books could have been condensed in to 5.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-04 14:45:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I remember wearing those shorts! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-03 16:41:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> "Vote Hillary" </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-03 16:31:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Clinton INTERROGATED! Not interviewed. They only interview for jobs. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-03 05:22:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Three hours of lying Hillary. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-02 14:59:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Looks like a paper feeder tray for a printer. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-30 14:24:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> When I'm with my grand-children and people think I'm the Dad. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-30 14:07:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'd pick three of my six grandchildren. We all like to explore and kids are fun. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-29 15:05:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> LOVE Rose Byrne. You'd never know how funny she is with those sad eyes. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-29 14:54:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This is not writing, it is printing. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-28 17:37:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The Alaskan wilderness. That's where all the caribou are. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-27 16:06:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's not so much a religion as a way of life. Like Islam. I read L. Ron Hubbard's "Dianetics" back in the 1970's and looked at it more like a self help book. Scientologists have no personal freedom. Their whole lives are dictated by the policies of those in control. And it's hard to quit. They record all your sins early on in your indoctrination, and use that against you if you try to leave. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-27 06:14:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Could be IBS. And you wouldn't think it's funny if you had it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-26 18:53:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> We have the same here in Northern Virginia. I'll never give it up to the one season a year crowd. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-26 16:04:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Due to missionary position. Hitting head on bed headboard every night. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-26 15:11:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Boy, if Ansel Adams ever saw this he'd start taking color photographs. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-25 14:09:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Oh, so you want to be like Venezuela? Britain and the U.S. are on the right track. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-24 18:25:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I have a small brown bat that lives on my balcony during the summer. I  put its guano in my flower pots. It helps keep the mosquito population down. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-24 15:20:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So great for the sovereignty of Britain. Now if we can just save the U.S. from Democrats. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-21 16:35:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Any sandwich with that squeezed out guacamole they have in a plastic bag...so disgusting. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-17 18:27:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Reading and comprehension are quite different. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-13 16:27:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I wonder if he can write out the U.S. Constitution by memory. I would bet he can not. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-13 14:31:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The reality is much different then this liberal drivel. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-13 14:12:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> And you must be a millennial drone still living with your parents. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-13 13:15:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Ronald Reagan was our third greatest President, after Washington and Lincoln. He was the worlds greatest leader by lifting more people out of poverty then any leader in the history of mankind. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-13 05:28:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Oh please...enough with the Nixon bashing. You have a president now that has screwed up this country so bad they'll be commenting on it for a hundred years. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-13 05:22:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Except for accountability. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-13 05:21:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Don't know what he's angry about. He's the cause of all the unrest in our once great country. This is the fundamental change he promised. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-11 15:08:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I worked for a Theatre group in the 70's, and the answer then is no. Most theatres had one screen. They used arc projectors with positive and negative electrodes burning to make the light. That's why film would burn up if the projector jammed. They use lots of electricity. The projectors each had their own chimneys to vent the heat. Projection rooms were always hot. When we'd get only a few people for a film, the manager would apologize and refund their money. Just not cost effective. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-11 14:57:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Why do people say Democratic Party instead of Democrat Party? They are the least democratic of all the parties. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-10 17:02:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Has to be a movie. No way sissy pants Damon could defend himself. He would have wet his pants and died of shame.
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-28 14:36:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Think about it. One of them dies. Not so much fun then. I knew a young couple that while they were having sex she experienced a burst bubble brain aneurysm. They had their first child just three months earlier. A tragedy for all. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-27 14:52:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I was listening to a radio program when a woman remarked about the "Deer Crossing" signs. She said she didn't understand why they put deer crossing signs on busy roads, that they should move them to less congested areas. Yeah, deer can read, right? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-19 21:54:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Because of the first amendment of the Constitution. Ever read it? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-17 18:22:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> No way this will happen. A Socialist will never beat a Capitalist in this country.
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-16 17:49:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I don't understand this remark. There are hundreds of fascist totalitarian socialists that can be found in many failed countries. How is he any different?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-16 17:43:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Of course it's going to cost a lot. There's a lot of Commie's out there, especially in the White House. Defense of the country is in our Constitution. Look it up. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-09 16:07:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Fantastic! Isn't it awesome not having to go to the bathroom as often?! And of course no more "urges" to stop for a 12-pack. I stopped drinking alcohol in April 1987. Most people comment I look ten years younger than my age. I think it's because I stopped drinking. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-02 14:35:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Let me clear this up.
Democrats: Are now Socialists that believe in a system where all property is controlled by a small group of individuals. They determine what the common good will be and force everyone else to comply.
Republicans: Believe in Capitalism, a system where people keep what they earn and trade voluntarily for what they need. Individuals are left to pursue their own agendas so long as they don't directly harm others. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-22 16:06:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Because He is, was, and will always be. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-08-08 01:14:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If you have to ask someone else then you should not vote. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-19 04:06:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Truly I say to you, disrespect God and you will find yourself outside closed doors. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-18 03:14:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Remember when wearing your Sunday best meant the finest clothes you owned? What happened to dressing well out of respect for God? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-18 02:54:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The one who posted this picture. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-18 02:08:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Or maybe a snail darter. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-16 05:14:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Any chance you can lend her to the U.S. National Art Gallery? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-13 20:51:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You're sick </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-13 13:18:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> "Proven",your standards are pretty low if you believe that. To each his own. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-13 05:26:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You couldn't pay me to see those two "actors" in anything. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-12 01:31:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Awesome  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-08 19:27:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> She can leave asap as far as I'm concerned. Spoiled prissy brat. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-07 02:25:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The Great Escape  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-24 19:05:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Meh, her age is showing and she's too PC. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-16 05:05:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Ah, my dream girl. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-03 04:15:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Sick. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-02 21:27:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So beautiful. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-26 01:01:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Because the Earth is dynamic you will have periods of warming and cooling. Man-made global warming is a myth, so wake up. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-23 05:25:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> A willfully ignorant electorate. They're destroying all what makes the U.S. great. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-20 02:44:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Unbelievable number of boot licks out there. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-16 15:08:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Man made climate change is a myth people. Go take a geology 101 class .  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-13 21:15:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Steven is right and Amy is a slut. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-12 02:49:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Meanwhile Socialism has been a huge success, Not! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-11 17:45:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Looks like alyca to me. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-09 04:58:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Which is why I began listening to country music in the 80's! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-06 01:25:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The U.S., of course. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-05 21:30:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Their country. The last two elections demonstrate that the voting majority are morons. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-02 04:34:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Good start. Practice makes perfect. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-02 02:23:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Wow! Like candy for the mind. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-01 05:24:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> My mother listened to the fight from the radio in her bedroom. I heard her crying when her favorite, Liston, went down. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
