<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject1073</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-10 03:47:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So you're going to ignore the whole thing where you were completely ignorant of your candidate's basic proposals, huh?  Okay.

First, the operative word is "did," not "does."  Trump did appeal to more voters.

Second, the operative term is "working-class," not "middle-class."  The working-class used to be middle-class when Democrats supported Unions and worker rights in reality, not merely in a two-line blurb on a website.  

Finally, Trump did appeal more to the working-class because he told them what they wanted to hear while Hillary ignored them.  You can cry that he was lying all you like but it doesn't change what did happen.  He won on the backs of the working-class because Democrats have effectively abandoned them for corporate sponsors.

So now you know that Trump is a liar who will sell out the workers the moment he reaches the oval office.  Did that really surprise you?  Hillary did it the moment she started her campaign. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-10 03:36:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So you know Hillary's position on a minimum wage better than she does.  Got it.  Maybe if she had hired you as her pollster, she would have won since your numbers are better than hers.

And I never said Trump would increase wages because he won't.  He'll be a complete shit-show and I didn't support or vote for him.  That doesn't make anything you're writing correct.  It just makes Trump a shit-show. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-10 03:27:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I can't make any informed comment about the Democratic party in Missouri, but the Dems on the national level have been giving Unions the cold shoulder in favor of corporate donations since 1992 and the DLC at least. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-10 03:25:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'll believe what Clinton's campaign said on this one.
http://www.huffingtonpost.com/entry/hillary-clinton-12-minimum-wage_us_55ba7988e4b0b23e3ce1f307

and from her own site...
https://www.hillaryclinton.com/feed/middle-class-needs-raise-heres-how-hillary-clinton-plans-do-it/

How can you try to tell others what to believe when you don't even know your candidate's basic platform?

Clinton supported a minimum wage instead of a living wage and that's a fact.  Trump supports getting rid of it but the working class is more concerned living wage jobs than promises of sub-standard wages that might be a little higher than they were. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-10 03:11:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Being pro-worker doesn't mean being anti business, but it does mean being anti-exploitation.  That is the line that has been crossed by New Democrats like Hillary, Wasserman, Brazile, and others.  Healthy workers means healthy businesses.  The advent of the middle class in this country went hand in hand with the Unions and businesses were never so profitable.  The destruction of the Unions led to lost jobs and wages, international mergers, and the general decline of American prosperity.  At least coincidentally, it also corresponded with the decimation of local family businesses that weren't Union.  Probably because of tightening household budgets and incoming non-Union mega stores sucking profits out of communities.

Nothing I heard in Sanders' message was anti-business, but it was anti-exploitation. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-10 03:00:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You're right.  The working class should have taken what they were given and not get out of line.  Who do they think they are, anyway? /s

On a serious note, it would be good if you even knew your candidate's positions.  She did not support a $15 minimum wage, she wanted $12 and only because people like Bernie made it popular and she had to respond without upsetting her donors too much.  She specifically opposed raising it to $15.  Other than that, she was mostly silent on working class issues.

Oh yeah!  Workers also might want to get paid a little more than entry level wages for the work they do.  How presumptuous! /s </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-10 02:35:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So what exactly did I exaggerate?

As for the rest of your comment, it's been less than 24 hours since the election was decided and there's already neo-liberal propaganda trying to put the blame on pro-working class Dems.  If you want to castigate anyone, look in the mirror or go snip at them.  Those of us who have been saying this could happen a year ago need to make our voices heard or jump to a new party. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-10 02:31:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You're right.  We need more Democrats willing to tell the working class to pull themselves up by the bootstraps and learn new careers.  Without pay or assistance, of course. /s

Do you even care that you sound like Romney and Bush? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-10 02:29:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The country just elected a city liberal who recently changed his "core" beliefs.  I don't think the problems is where the candidate comes from and I don't think conservadems are the answer.  Bernie would likely have won last night as he was pulling the same constituency that usually votes Democratic but put Trump over this time.  

We need to return to being the pro-worker party of FDR, not the pro-wealth party of Clinton and Blair. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-10 02:23:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> And maybe you'll learn what comes of snide arrogance once President Pence takes over in 8 years.  If the "Democrats" continue blaming everyone but themselves, that's where we're headed. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-10 02:20:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Or we could run a candidate who actually does care about workers.  Sounds crazy but it just might work!

Also, the problem isn't being establishment, the problem is what the establishment currently supports.  It's not us. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-10 02:18:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah, he's a liar.  So is Hillary.  I guess lying about helping was better than lying about taking enemy fire or rigging the primaries.

Maybe if we hadn't run a known liar who bragged that coal miners were going to be out of jobs against Trump, we'd have a Democratic President elect and Senate right now. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-10 00:46:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It never does. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-10 00:45:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> A very strong minority of them voted for the candidate who at least gave lip service to their concerns.  It looks like that was enough. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-10 00:43:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Exporting jobs has been a bipartisan pursuit, which only Sanders and Trump have seriously criticized.  The DNC stole the primary for Hillary so we got Trump.  

I hope everyone is thanking the DNC for their efforts.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-10 00:41:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That's fine, keep excusing the New Democrat policies of corporate welfare, free trade, and deregulation and see if anything changes in the next election. 

And by the way, Clinton supported nearly all of those things you mentioned and would have continued to do so in the White House.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-09 20:09:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> And do what?  Millennial-bash them?  

Maybe it would be better to ask why they found it impossible to vote for Clinton and learn something......

NAH!!!! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-09 20:03:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Clinton took only 51% of the Union vote.  This is what destroyed her in Michigan, Wisconsin, and Pennsylvania where Union support still clings to life.  She thought she had this demographic locked down but they largely abandoned her because she (and the Democratic party) largely abandoned them.

The Democratic party either needs to get back to its roots of supporting the workers or step down so that another party can rise.  

All the corporate money in the world couldn't save this extremely flawed candidate. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-09 18:26:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hillary underperformed with her "base" of blacks, hispanics, and women.

This MUST be the fault of those dastardly Berniebros! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-09 17:48:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's too bad that Krugman spent his time during the primaries distorting Sanders' economic plans while glossing over the problems with Clinton's proposals that he had said wouldn't work years ago.

Maybe he could have helped to save all of us from this situation, but he was too busy sucking up to the Anointed One.

Basically, Krugman's a hack who helped get us to where we are today.  Hard to give him, or his Nobel medal, much credence after that. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-16 05:35:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> But it's always completely clear-cut when a white person is the victim.  Got it. /s </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-15 18:40:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I suppose all the cases of white cops murdering unarmed black people means nothing because it doesn't fit your narrative. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-15 16:55:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I don't know how some people manage to live with so much fear in their lives. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-15 05:03:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'd be embarrassed to admit being so childish that I didn't comprehend the need to compromise in order to avert a geopolitical catastrophe like a Trump presidency.

As a Bernie supporter who plans to vote Green I'm still disgusted with the apparent children I was recently aligned with. Bernie did the right thing.  Those throwing tantrums are giving true progressives a bad name. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-15 04:54:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Why was the ethnicity of the attacker was so important to you?  Neither the title or the article mentioned race but that was the major point you pulled from it. What makes you think race had anything to do with the attack? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-20 00:05:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Gotta love the ageist smear.  I guess it's alright to suggest that Hillary pushes for wars when it's "that time of month" then, right? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
