<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject2372</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-08-21 20:20:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I don't know how I didn't think of that, thank you! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Good books about the transition from the mesolithic era to the neolithic? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-08-21 20:13:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-08-13 12:13:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thanks for your response,

Having had a look at the application procedure I do have a few more questions. I see you have to apply right off the bat with a topic and hypothesis for your thesis. Is this completely nailed down or is it a more fluid arrangement, evolving as you do further research? On a related note, do you have to select a particular location to focus on from the get go or does this also evolve with your work?

I've drummed up some ideas after looking at the criteria for acceptable thesis proposals that I wouldn't mind firing off an ex-student. Could you give me your opinion on a couple if I dm you the broad strokes? Also maybe some advice on the kind of sample work they're looking for from your portfolio? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Is anyone here studying for the RIBA Part 2 at Cambridge? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-08-09 20:11:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm interested in applying as I hear its more focused on written work than most Part 2 courses. However, I would be interested in hearing current/former students opinions how well rounded they feel the course is. How well do you feel it prepared you for the working world? Although I really enjoy writing, my main hesitation is that with the commitment to write four 5,000 word essays and a 15,000 word thesis that there would be less time to develop the practical skills necessary in working life after I graduate. Do the other aspects of the course successfully balance it out? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Good (preferably free) online resources for learning Grasshopper from scratch? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-08-09 18:55:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I just did a search on here and the only posts I could find were a little out of date. Can anyone recommend some stuff that's a little more recent? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Has anyone here done the RIBA Part 2 at Cambridge? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-08-08 17:55:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm interested in applying as I hear its heavily writing based, which I enjoy and is my strong suit, but would be interested in hearing former students opinions how well rounded the course is. How well did you feel it prepared you for the working world? My main hesitation is that with the greatly above average commitment to write four 5,000 word essays and a 15,000 word thesis that there would be less time to build the practical skills necessary in working life after I graduate. Do the other aspects of the course balance it out? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-08 01:53:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> How about a new reaction series on people that really shouldn't be trying to make it in that rap game. For starters:

 nbsp;

[Oxfordshire's Finest, Gubby and Crew](https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=uPCEd2JTIFY)

 nbsp;

[The silver fox of the Newark casino scene, A. Samuels](https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=Tjvlrf0OM3M) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
