<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject9714</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Blank Check Company Manufacturer Charged With Fraud </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-21 19:02:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Trump Campaign Paid Trump's Companies Over $500,000 In August </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-21 17:20:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Brilliant! </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-21 16:09:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What Owning a Ramen Restaurant in Japan is Like (2016) </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-21 15:57:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> For Clinton, attacking Trump may not be enough - "Clintons objective is twofold: To lift her sagging approval ratings as well as build trust in her agenda and earn a mandate that could help her, should she be elected, govern in a divided Washington." </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-21 14:49:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> For Clinton, attacking Trump may not be enough - "Clintons objective is twofold: To lift her sagging approval ratings as well as build trust in her agenda and earn a mandate that could help her, should she be elected, govern in a divided Washington." </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-21 14:22:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Christian Laettner Reaches Deal to Repay Investors - "Former Duke basketball star had been involved with real-estate developments across the country" </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-21 12:37:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The progressive case for Hillary Clinton is pretty overwhelming </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-20 21:18:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Elizabeth Warren Just Eviscerated the Wells Fargo CEO - "You should resignYou should be criminally investigated." </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-20 20:07:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> An Organic Chicken Farm in Georgia Has Become an Endless Buffet for Bald Eagles - "Dozens of the raptors crash White Oak Farms each winter to dine on its fields of pasture-raised poultry. With little recourse, the farmers are racing to adapt." </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-20 19:36:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Trump used $258,000 from his charity to settle legal problems - "Donald Trump spent more than a quarter-million dollars from his charitable foundation to settle lawsuits that involved the billionaires for-profit businesses, according to interviews and a review of legal documents." </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-20 18:24:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Trump used $258,000 from his charity to settle legal problems - "Donald Trump spent more than a quarter-million dollars from his charitable foundation to settle lawsuits that involved the billionaires for-profit businesses, according to interviews and a review of legal documents." </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-20 18:23:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The difference between Barack Obama and Donald Trump in two photos? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-20 16:53:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Scooter found in Cheltenham </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-20 14:11:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> New York Times editor on Trump: We will call out lies - "Now, the most traditional American media outlets have also abandoned journalistic diplomatese in their coverage of Republican candidate Donald Trump, and are reaching for new ways to flag the word lie." </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-20 14:00:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Apple patents bold new innovation  a paper bag </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-20 12:52:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Apple patents bold new innovation  a paper bag </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-20 12:50:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Mike Pence: A Running Mate With Baggage - "Focus on Trump draws attention away from governor's record in Indiana" </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-20 12:49:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What the World Gained from Those Who Suffered Under Mother Teresas Care </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-20 12:47:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Venezuela Crises Compound as Oil Industry Falls Into Disarray - "Venezuelas petroleum industry, whose vast revenues once fueled the countrys Socialist-inspired revolution, underwriting everything from housing to education, is spiraling into disarray." </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-20 12:09:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Venezuela Crises Compound as Oil Industry Falls Into Disarray - "Venezuelas petroleum industry, whose vast revenues once fueled the countrys Socialist-inspired revolution, underwriting everything from housing to education, is spiraling into disarray." </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-20 12:09:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Donald Trumps law-and-order approach wont make us safer - "What the Republican candidate doesn't get about fighting crime." </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-19 19:22:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Five Second Rule for Food on Floor Is Untrue, Study Finds </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-19 16:14:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> It's Sunday </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-18 16:34:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> https://i.imgur.com/PKzv4dX.jpg </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> This Question on a Math Test is Really Homophobic (Also, I Solved It) </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-17 14:56:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> CBC: Voters Must Stop Trump in His Tracks - "Members of the Congressional Black Caucus on Friday urged voters to reject Republican presidential nominee Donald Trump after the billionaire businessman finally acknowledged that President Barack Obama was born in the United States." </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-17 14:55:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Trump: Stop Regulating Poisoned Dog Food - "Trump complained the FDA food police dictates whats in dog foodbut that same FDA pulled 11 poisoned chow brands off the shelves in the last year." </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-16 20:01:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> This is were they keep 'em </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-16 16:11:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Jose Berrios Is Tipping His Pitches - Good detective work </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-16 15:58:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The Laws of the Church Have No Place on Your Flesh, Declare Irish Women in Powerful New Video - "In Ireland, abortions are prohibited by law and women caught obtaining one can face up to 14 years in prison." </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-16 15:34:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Another Trump staffer acknowledges the truth of Obamas birthplace - layering it with a number of falsehoods </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-16 12:59:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> In a hungry Venezuela, buying too much food can get you arrested </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-16 12:38:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> In a hungry Venezuela, buying too much food can get you arrested </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-16 12:38:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Muslims pray toward Qibla, the direction of Mecca. This concept makes no sense unless Allah thought earth is flat. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-15 15:24:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Your Detox Diet is a Sham </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-14 14:39:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Thanks Obama. The evolution of a meme that defined a presidency. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-14 14:30:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Thanks Obama. The evolution of a meme that defined a presidency. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-14 14:29:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Georgia officials were set to approve a new mosque  until an armed militia threatened to protest </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-14 13:46:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> A big majority says Trump is unqualified for the presidency. How much will that end up mattering? - "In October of 2008, a Newsweek poll found that 55 percent said Palin is not qualified to step in as president." </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-14 13:40:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> A big majority says Trump is unqualified for the presidency. How much will that end up mattering? - "In October of 2008, a Newsweek poll found that 55 percent said Palin is not qualified to step in as president." </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-14 13:38:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The national media is talking about Trumps racist campaign. Thats good for Hillary Clinton. - "...its becoming increasingly clear that the Clinton campaign has one major strategic goal: to get the national media to talk about Donald Trumps bigotry and his racist campaign as much as possible." </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-13 16:48:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The national media is talking about Trumps racist campaign. Thats good for Hillary Clinton. - "...its becoming increasingly clear that the Clinton campaign has one major strategic goal: to get the national media to talk about Donald Trumps bigotry and his racist campaign as much as possible." </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-13 16:47:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> "Senate Republican strategists are increasingly worried that the near absence of TV ads from Donald Trumps campaign in key battlegrounds will do irreversible harm to already difficult races." </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-13 14:34:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Trumps campaign says hes given tens of millions to charity, but offers no details and no proof - "The Washington Post has spent the past few months searching for evidence of that kind of personal donation, without much success." </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-13 14:26:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Record new U.S. military aid deal for Israel to be signed in days: sources - "The United States and Israel have reached final agreement on a record new package of at least $38 billion in U.S. military aid and the 10-year pact is expected to be signed within days" </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-13 12:35:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Polls show many  even most  Trump supporters really are deeply hostile to Muslims and nonwhites </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-12 20:49:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Polls show many  even most  Trump supporters really are deeply hostile to Muslims and nonwhites </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-12 20:48:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Wells Fargo Exec Who Headed Phony Accounts Unit Collected $125 Million </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-12 18:13:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Wells Fargo Exec Who Headed Phony Accounts Unit Collected $125 Million </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-12 18:12:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> CIA Director Pushes Back On Trump Claims About Intelligence Briefings - "We dont comment on policy. We dont give policy recommendations," Brennan added. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-12 15:46:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Attention! </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-12 15:14:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Utah Professor Slams Mother Teresas Sainthood: Rejecting Reality is Not Reason to Rejoice </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-12 15:06:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Ireland Doesnt Want Apples Back Taxes, but the Irish Arent So Sure </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-12 12:08:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Ireland Doesnt Want Apples Back Taxes, but the Irish Arent So Sure </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-12 12:07:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> How Breakfast Became a Thing - Breakfast is the most important meal of the day. What you may not know is the origin of this ode to breakfast: a 1944 marketing campaign launched by Grape Nuts manufacturer General Foods to sell more cereal." What did people eat before cereal came out? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-12 11:44:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> https://priceonomics.com/how-breakfast-became-a-thing/
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Pumpkin Spice Lattes May Send You to Hell </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-11 22:18:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> University of Oregon scrubs name of KKK leader from building - "The University of Oregon has finally decided to remove the name of a KKK leader from one of its campus dormitories." </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-11 17:16:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Report: Wikileaks' Syria Docs Exclude Email On $2B Transfer To Russian Bank-"Wikileaks in 2012 published emails from Syrian government officials obtained by hackers, but the website did not include an email noting that the Syrian regime transferred more than $2 billion to a state-owned Russian bank" </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-10 15:54:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Kings Road, 1960s [396x650] </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-09 16:12:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> When Will New York City Sink? - "Even locals who believe climate change is real have a hard time grasping that their city will almost certainly be flooded beyond recognition." </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-09 15:45:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> DFL Petitions Minn. Supreme Court To Remove Trump From Ballot - "The filing  submitted to the court Thursday night  argues that the Minnesota Republican Party failed to nominate alternate presidential electors, during its party convention last May." </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-09 15:10:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Minnesota DFL asks state Supreme Court to order Trump, Pence removed from ballot - "The party's petition asks that the secretary of state be forced to remove Trump and Pence from the ballot, saying the process that put them on it broke the law. " </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-09 12:07:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Gary Johnson asks: 'What is Aleppo?' - "Libertarian presidential nominee Gary Johnson on Thursday shocked the hosts of MSNBC's "Morning Joe" by seeming to not know what the Syrian city of Aleppo is." </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-08 14:42:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Why Hillary Clintons perceived corruption seems to echo louder than Donald Trumps actual corruption. - "Hillary Clinton seems more tainted than Donald Trump, even though she isn't. Why?" </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-08 14:24:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> IRS Impeachment Debate Latest Example of House GOP Infighting - "... House Republicans debate whether they should vote to impeach IRS Commissioner John Koskinen, members are also wrestling over when its appropriate to skirt traditional legislative procedures and take matters into their own hands." </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-08 14:22:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Donald Trump is still as much of a birther as he ever was - "Birtherism hasn't been a big part of Donald Trump's 2016 campaign. But that's largely a matter of emphasis -- not any actual change in his position." </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-06 16:45:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Dallas Morning News: Trump 'does not deserve your vote' - "But what does it mean to be a Republican today? With Donald Trump as the party's new standard-bearer, it's impossible to say." </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-06 16:31:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Ohio School Districts New CEO Cuts Creationism and Intelligent Design from Science Curriculum - " Krish Mohip says that the Districts science curriculum will match the science standards promoted by the Ohio Department of Education. And that means no faith-based pseudoscience." </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-06 16:03:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Morning Flight </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-06 15:29:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Reid Readies for the Home Stretch - "In last months, Senate minority leader aims to link GOP colleagues to Trump" </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-06 15:23:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Heres a tale of two scandals. Guess which one will get more play? - "Yet somehow, stories about Donald Trump that dont have to do with the latest appalling thing that came out of his mouth dont raise questions in the same way." </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-06 14:35:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> In Japan </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-01 15:40:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Trump Staff in Secret Conservative Group - "The Southern Poverty Law Center acquired a membership directory for the Council of National Policy, an ultra-secret conservative group, and Donald Trumps campaign manager Kellyanne Conway and his campaign CEO Steve Bannon were listed as members." </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-01 15:35:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Trump Staff in Secret Conservative Group - "The Southern Poverty Law Center acquired a membership directory for the Council of National Policy, an ultra-secret conservative group, and Donald Trumps campaign manager Kellyanne Conway and his campaign CEO Steve Bannon were listed as members." </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-01 15:34:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> A Tax Expert Takes Tim Cook's EU Letter Apart Point By Point </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-01 13:46:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Oklahoma Man Says Library Ad Featuring Muslim Woman is Illegal Promotion of Islam </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-01 13:43:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> How Congress Makes Regular Taxpayers Foot the Bill for Oil Pipeline Fat Cats - "A terrible law, a phantom tax and a captured regulator mean that big businesses are forcing you to pay their taxes without even knowing it." </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-01 13:31:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Authorities: Would-be Minnetonka bank robber demanded money, then an interpreter </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-31 19:43:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The Trump Files: Donald's Petty Revenge on Connie Chung - "Donald Trump knows that a mere insult sometimes isn't enough for a journalist he doesn't like." </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-31 15:13:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Challenger's Poll Shows Statistical Dead Heat With Issa - "An internal poll conducted for California Rep. Darrell Issa's Democratic opponent shows Doug Applegate within three percentage points of the long-time Republican lawmaker." </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-30 19:11:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Former models for Donald Trump's agency say they violated immigration rules and worked illegally </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-30 19:05:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> "How a mayors campaign to keep a Jesus sign brought discord to a God-fearing East Texas town." </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-30 15:40:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Mitsubishi says overstated mileage for more vehicle models - "...more of its vehicle models were involved in a mileage cheating scandal than initially stated, and that it would temporarily stop domestic sales of affected vehicles and compensate owners." </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-30 15:13:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Just need a little nudge to get started... </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-30 15:11:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> As its proxies advance in Syria, Turkey warns Kurds to pull back </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-30 15:10:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Vladimir Putin arrested at Publix </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-30 14:53:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Abandoned in Iraq: Inside Two Soldiers' Harrowing Escape - "The true story of U.S. soldiers left for dead in Iraq, their epic battle for survival, and the military cover-up that kept them silent  until now" </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-30 12:13:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Abandoned in Iraq: Inside Two Soldiers' Harrowing Escape - "The true story of U.S. soldiers left for dead in Iraq, their epic battle for survival, and the military cover-up that kept them silent  until now" </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-30 12:12:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The Twilight of Fox News - "As pay TV slowly declines, cable news faces a demographic cliff. And nobody has further to fall than the merchant of right-wing outrage." </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-30 12:05:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The Twilight of Fox News - "As pay TV slowly declines, cable news faces a demographic cliff. And nobody has further to fall than the merchant of right-wing outrage." </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-30 12:04:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Iranian government appreciating their Olympians. However, Kimia Alizadeh the first female Iranian who won a medal isn't there. WTF! </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-28 15:40:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Arizona: Latino Group Launches Campaign, Ads Against 'Trumpublicans' - "Donald Trump has made clear time and time again that he's campaigning for the presidency on the backs of Latinos and immigrants," said Huerta. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-26 15:25:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Saudis and Extremism: Both the Arsonists and the Firefighters - "Critics see Saudi Arabias export of a rigid strain of Islam as contributing to terrorism, but the kingdoms influence depends greatly on local conditions." </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-26 15:16:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Saudis and Extremism: Both the Arsonists and the Firefighters - "Critics see Saudi Arabias export of a rigid strain of Islam as contributing to terrorism, but the kingdoms influence depends greatly on local conditions." </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-26 15:15:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [SV] Today I weight 177 lbs. The last time I weighted 177 was back in high school. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-26 14:42:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> My goal is to get my % body fat to around 12%.  I am almost there.  I started keto 3 years ago and bf % was around 40%.  I weighted 253 and had about 90 lbs of fat on my body.  WTF!!  Today, I have about 20 lbs of body fat.  Cheers!!

The key for me is to stop listening to other people.  I experiment to find what works for me, and follow the results.  If something doesn't work, I stop doing it and change things up.  The key is to keep insulin low for a period of time.  It would be great if a person could measure insulin levels at home, but that is not possible right now.  Oh, well.  IF and fasting for 3-5 days works very good.  I would not be able to do that without being on keto.  The hunger would drive my brain crazy.

Carl Franklin and Richard Morris of the 2 Keto Dudes podcast are great to listen too.  These guys are down to earth and keep keto real. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Pennsylvania House of Representatives set to give Americans United a lot of the states money. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-26 12:40:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Private Immigrant Detention Firm Gave $45K to Trump Fundraising Group - "The GEO Group operates more than five dozen facilities nationwide" </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-26 12:36:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Republican Party of Minnesota forgot to put Donald Trump on Minnesota ballot, scrambling to fix it </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-26 12:18:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [Science] A false alarm on red meat and cancer - "Two large trials have tested for evidence and the WHO ignored both of them, writes Gordon Guyatt" </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-26 12:06:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> http://www.ft.com/cms/s/0/42259e20-92b5-11e5-bd82-c1fb87bef7af.html?siteedition=intl
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Trump campaign operative suggests Clinton will die during first year in office - "John E. Jaggers, the Maryland and Northern Virginia state director for Trump's campaign, continued the Republican campaign's unfounded attack on Clinton's health during a Moms 4 Trump rally in Loudoun County." </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-24 18:23:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Poll: Murphy Pulls Ahead of Grayson, Rubio Trounces Both - "Florida survey also shows Hillary Clinton with large lead in presidential race" </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-24 14:57:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> From the South Pole to the science section: How ice becomes knowledge - "Up close and personal with a new core of very old Antarctic ice" </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-24 14:53:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The Hottest Pepper in the World - Consuming the Carolina Reaper is kind of like eating molten lava. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-24 14:38:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Prophecy: God Sent Donald Trump to Wage War Against Destructive Spirits </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-24 14:34:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Glenn Beck And The Burden Of Being God's Watchman - "So now he is claiming that his audience has been prepared to reclaim America if Donald Trump is elected president and becomes a strongman and a dictator." </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-23 20:35:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Exploring the Gap Between When the Gospels Were Written and the Oldest Copies We Have </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-23 14:38:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The Fake $400 Million Iran Ransom Story - The money was a real debt and had to be paid at some point, but the United States exploited the timing so Iran didnt delay freeing its hostages. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-23 14:25:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The Fake $400 Million Iran Ransom Story - The money was a real debt and had to be paid at some point, but the United States exploited the timing so Iran didnt delay freeing its hostages. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-23 14:24:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Trump's kids are cashing in on his campaign - "Republican Donald Trump has so far paid $7.7 million in campaign contributions to his own companies and children, according to a filing with the Federal Elections Commission" </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-23 13:20:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Donald Trump Jacked Up His Campaigns Trump Tower Rent Once Somebody Else Was Paying It - "Office rent soared in July after Trumps campaign began accepting donor contributions." </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-23 13:17:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Donald Trump Jacked Up His Campaigns Trump Tower Rent Once Somebody Else Was Paying It - "Office rent soared in July after Trumps campaign began accepting donor contributions." </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-23 13:15:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Clinton's lead in NC elevates Senate race - "Democrats see an opening to win a Senate seat in North Carolina amid the electoral turmoil caused by Donald Trump." </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-22 16:23:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Ratings Change: 7 States Shift Toward Clinton in Electoral College - "Donald Trump appears to be drowning in the wake of the conventions." </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-22 15:59:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Cops Without Guns Dominate as London Awaits 'Likely' Attack - Officers in England and Wales fired just seven bullets in the year between March 2015-16. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-22 14:33:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Brand Over Brain   Religion Over Brain - "...with branding people can come to believe their own religion is the best one in the world, the true one. " </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-22 12:26:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Campaign Ads No Longer Rely on 'Mansplaining' - "But gender roles persist, with men often still used as voice of authority" </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-22 12:22:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> YouTube Atheists Sue Christian Film Company Over Multiple Frivolous DMCA Complaints </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-19 16:06:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Weird </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-19 16:02:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> "Hillary Clinton told the FBI that former Secretary of State Colin Powell recommended on two occasions that she use a private email account for unclassified communication, sources told NBC News early Friday." </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-19 15:48:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> "Hillary Clinton told the FBI that former Secretary of State Colin Powell recommended on two occasions that she use a private email account for unclassified communication, sources told NBC News early Friday." </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-19 15:47:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> "Hillary Clinton told the FBI that former Secretary of State Colin Powell recommended on two occasions that she use a private email account for unclassified communication, sources told NBC News early Friday." </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-19 15:46:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What A Clinton Landslide Would Look Like </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-18 13:28:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> I'm Gonna Punch You in the Head for Jesus </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-16 19:44:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> LOL: https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=PHXkkhGDiCQ </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> North Carolina Hires One Of Americas Most Expensive Attorneys To Defend Voter Suppression - "Defending the indefensible is hard." </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-16 18:30:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> North Carolina Hires One Of Americas Most Expensive Attorneys To Defend Voter Suppression - "Defending the indefensible is hard." </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-16 18:29:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Jesus doing magic </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-16 15:49:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> https://i.imgur.com/zJQh0gE.jpg
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Trump addresses ISIS threat to West, but blood spilled every day in Syria, Iraq </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-16 14:34:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [Science] Help move forward on research on ketogenic diets for cancer </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-12 13:56:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This is a good hypothesis to test:

https://experiment.com/projects/part-2-can-low-carbohydrate-ketogenic-diets-inhibit-cancers
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Cannes Mayor David Lisnard Bans Burkinis on City's Beaches - "Mayor David Lisnard cited that tragedy and subsequent attack on a northwest France church in an ordinance forbidding swimwear that doesn't respect "good morals and secularism."" </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-12 13:49:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Dixie Chicks singer: GOP hypocrites over Trump - "I get banned for not liking Bush and now Trump can practically put a hit out on Hillary and he's still all over country radio! Hypocrites!" </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-11 20:24:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> "A group of prominent "Never-Trump" Republicans is calling on the Republican National Committee to divert resources from presidential nominee Donald Trump and instead shore up efforts to maintain GOP majorities in Congress." </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-11 20:22:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> From Dr. Jason Fung - I found happiness </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-11 16:27:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Trump: 'Is There Something Wrong' With Calling Obama 'Founder Of ISIS?' </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-11 16:17:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Trump: 'Is There Something Wrong' With Calling Obama 'Founder Of ISIS?' </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-11 16:16:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The U.S. will rearm Saudi Arabia to the tune of $1.5 billion as airstrikes resume in Yemen </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-11 16:03:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The U.S. will rearm Saudi Arabia to the tune of $1.5 billion as airstrikes resume in Yemen </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-11 16:02:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Ronald Reagan's Daughter Blasts Trump's 'Verbal Violence' - "I am the daughter of a man who was shot by someone who got his inspiration from a movie," the post begins, referring to the 1981 assassination attempt on President Reagan by John Hinckley, Jr. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-11 14:11:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Checkmate!! </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-11 13:59:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> https://i.imgur.com/eVOeQQj.png </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> If you are lost and need to find direction in this world... </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-10 19:43:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Google Maps can help. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Kepler's "Alien Megastructure" Star Just Got Weirder - "Bizarre Tabbys Star shows an overall dimming trend, further confusing astronomers" </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-09 19:41:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Kepler's "Alien Megastructure" Star Just Got Weirder - "Bizarre Tabbys Star shows an overall dimming trend, further confusing astronomers" </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-09 19:40:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Alligator gets a taste of stupid </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-09 18:05:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Twitter Mocks Trumps Affinity For Phrase 'Many People Are Saying' - "Trump frequently relies on this vague construction both to promote his own products and to air far-fetched conspiracies while distancing himself from the source." </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-09 15:35:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Buster Posey (No Nosey) sliding into third base </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-09 15:23:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Portugal Wildfires Force Hundreds to Evacuate Homes, Hospital - "A major forest fire in Portugal's Madeira Islands destroyed at least six homes and forced the evacuation Tuesday of more than 400 people from homes and a hospital, officials said." </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-09 14:42:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Are the Aliens Trying to Extinguish an Entire Star? - "It's surely too early to say what their motivations might be....but a paper posted this week to the arXiv pre-print server makes it all too clear that aliens are attempting to destroy an entire star." </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-09 13:54:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Are the Aliens Trying to Extinguish an Entire Star? - "It's surely too early to say what their motivations might be....but a paper posted this week to the arXiv pre-print server makes it all too clear that aliens are attempting to destroy an entire star." </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-09 13:53:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> In Rare Q   A, Clinton Calls Trump "Xenophobic, Racist, and Misogynistic" </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-09 13:41:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Trump tweet blames Clinton emails for Iranian nuclear scientists execution </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-09 13:25:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The 20 best nicknames for Donald Trump (so far) </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-08 17:52:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The System Really Is Rigged, Just Not In The Way Donald Trump Thinks - "In 2012, Democratic candidates outperformed Republican candidates nationwide by more than a full percentage point." </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-08 15:03:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Central New York Humanist Groups Billboard Will Remind Atheists Theyre Not Alone </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-07 16:12:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Don't tell anyone </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-07 15:49:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Thandie Newton - an anomaly </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-07 15:09:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> https://i.imgur.com/ymf4gAt.jpg </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Poll Shows More Now Prefer Democrats Control Congress </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-05 15:46:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Mayor Who Once Gave God a Key to the City Arrested for Allegedly Playing Strip Poker with a Minor </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-05 14:36:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Reid Says Clinton Will Win Georgia - "Minority leader is also confident Democratic nominee will carry Arizona" </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-05 14:34:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Nate Silver @ 538 Now Cast has Hillary's odd of winning the election if today @ 91.5%. Cheers!!! </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-05 14:28:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> http://projects.fivethirtyeight.com/2016-election-forecast/#now
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Trump's Presidential Campaign Has Stifled Traffic to His Hotels and Casinos - In blue states, share fell 20 percent versus July 2015 </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-05 12:59:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Inside Ark Encounter, the Life-Size Noah's Ark Theme Park That Will Save (Some of) Us All - To our mind, Trollinger said, its hard to think of a message Jesus would like less. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-04 19:39:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> This Video Shows Two Christian Pastors Using the Exact Same Personal Anecdote - "As Barrett explained it, he was invited by a university group to debate an atheist on the existence of God. He was given less time to speak than his opponent, but he outsmarted them with this argument: ..." </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-04 16:32:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Fewer and fewer Americans vote with religion in mind - "...for the growing ranks of nonreligious voters in this country, the biggest question isnt how the DNC could so clearly favor one candidate over another in the primaries. Instead, its Whats so bad about being an atheist?" </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-04 16:07:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Landmark Secular Resolution Passed at DNC - "The above resolution, making quite a statement about religion and politics while recognizing the value and importance of the nonreligious demographic, was passed at the DNC by the LGBT Caucus of the Democratic Party." </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-04 16:03:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Mike Pence Breaks With Trump to Endorse Paul Ryan - "I strongly support Paul Ryan, strongly endorse his reelection," Pence said in an interview with Fox News. "I believe we need Paul Ryan in leadership in the Congress of the United States..." </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-04 13:24:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> FBI took months to warn Democrats of suspected Russian role in hack: sources - "The FBI did not tell the Democratic National Committee that U.S officials suspected it was the target of a Russian government-backed cyber attack when agents first contacted the party last fall" </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-03 14:01:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Dr. Jill Stein: Keep Your Kids Away From Wi-Fi Because It Might Hurt Their Brains </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-02 20:06:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Dr. Jill Stein: Keep Your Kids Away From Wi-Fi Because It Might Hurt Their Brains </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-02 20:05:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Obama Declares Trump 'Unfit' to Be President - "President Barack Obama called Donald Trump "unfit" and "woefully unprepared" to be president on Tuesday, his strong comments yet against the Republican presidential nominee." </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-02 18:26:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Setting the Bodys Serial Killers Loose on Cancer </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-02 18:07:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Good Help Is Hard To Find </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-02 14:09:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Who Eats Fried Chicken With A Fork?!! </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-02 14:08:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Air Force Mother Confronts Mike Pence Over Donald Trump's 'Disrespect'  Gets Booed - ""Time and time again Trump has disrespected our nation's armed forces and veterans  and his disrespect for Mr. Khan and his family is just an example of that," Catherine Byrne, the mother of Raymond Harmon" </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-02 13:51:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Koch Brothers Plan Another $4 Million in Senate Ads - "The Koch brothers have refused to spend on behalf of Donald Trump, instead pouring their resources into Senate races." </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-01 19:59:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Crazy talk found in the bible </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-01 18:29:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> http://imgur.com/a/IlrUc </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Olympic executives cash in on a Movement that keeps athletes poor </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-01 18:12:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [Science] Cancer   The Ketogenic Diet  Dr. Colin Champ </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-01 17:28:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=Lj3h9G2tec8
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What we know about Donald Trump and his taxes so far - "Heres a look at what we know about Trumps taxes: He did not pay any (or nearly any) income taxes at least five times in the past 40 years." </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-01 13:51:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Swaledale - Happy Yorkshire Day! </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-01 12:13:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> In Her Nomination Speech, Hillary Clinton Took God Out of the Motto and Embraced Science - She said "Our countrys motto is e pluribus unum: out of many, we are one. Will we stay true to that motto?" </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-29 18:04:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Was Ben Carson Right About Hillary Tied to Lucifer? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-29 15:26:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Trump and Russia: Even Historians See No Precedent </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-29 15:20:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> There is No God - A watermelon confirms </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-29 12:46:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=ZCL4dXUtblg </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What sparked the Cambrian explosion? - "An evolutionary burst 540 million years ago filled the seas with an astonishing diversity of animals. The trigger behind that revolution is finally coming into focus." </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-29 12:26:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> "Donald Trump, after hearing speeches at the Democratic convention this week, said Thursday he wanted to "hit a number of those speakers so hard, their heads would spin."" Why is Donald Trump so intemperate? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-29 12:19:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Chandra Levy murder: Charges dropped in retrial - "The US Attorney's Office said it had dismissed the case against Ingmar Guandique, an El Salvadorean immigrant." </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-29 01:02:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> We asked Bernie die-hards inside their Philly tent city: What now? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-29 00:54:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Terminix Offers to Pay $87M to Delaware Family Sickened at Virgin Islands Resort - ".. it would pay $10 million in fines and restitution for using the banned chemical methyl bromide  a highly noxious and odorless gas  at units at the St. John resort where the family was vacationing in March 2015." </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-28 19:59:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Bryan Cranston: Black Voters Are Being Silenced at the Polls </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-28 19:15:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Bryan Cranston: Black Voters Are Being Silenced at the Polls </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-28 19:14:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Why Cereal Has Such Aggressive Marketing - "Ads by the chicken lobby may convince people to eat a bit more chicken, but an avalanche of Tony the Tiger ads can get tens of thousands of children to eat Frosted Flakes every morning for years." </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-28 14:11:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> TV Ratings: DNC Beats RNC by Nearly 5 Million Viewers in Night 2 Final Numbers </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-28 13:36:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> TV Ratings: DNC Beats RNC by Nearly 5 Million Viewers in Night 2 Final Numbers </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-28 13:36:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Christian Preacher Proselytizes Outside CERN (But No One Seems To Be Listening) </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-28 12:38:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Donald Trump Challenges Russia to Find Hillary Clintons Missing Emails - "Donald J. Trump said Wednesday that he hoped Russia had hacked Hillary Clintons email, essentially sanctioning a foreign powers cyberspying of a secretary of states correspondence." </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-27 18:22:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Georgia Man Who Won $3M Lottery Pleads Guilty to Funding Crystal Meth Ring </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-27 16:58:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Venezuela opposition calls for demonstrations amid recall tensions - "Venezuelans will be taking to the streets Wednesday  once again  in hopes of forcing authorities to set a date for a presidential recall that could determine the fate of the troubled nation." </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-27 16:18:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Father of USA Freedom Kids Considering Suit Against Trump - "The father of viral video stars 'USA Freedom Kids' says he plans to sue Donald Trump's campaign over a compensation dispute." </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-27 16:02:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Watch out! We got a #bada55 over here! </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-27 15:26:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Your Expert Guide To Beta-Alanine - Beta-Alanine and Carnosine can help increase endurance during exercise </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-26 19:41:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> After Wasting $60 Million, the Iraqi Prime Minister Has Finally Banned Fake Bomb Detectors </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-26 19:27:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
