<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject4227</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-28 20:03:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Its not about saving to get a new job. First off just because you quit doesn't mean they wont find someone else to fill your position and put the same mandates through. Second off some of these people support these changes. You're forgetting that trump still has approval ratings of ~40% and a lot of those people are very loyal to him. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-28 18:06:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Cause everyone except for judges in this scenario can be quickly fired and replaced. That's the only reason anything gets done. The non 1% needs the money they get from these jobs but the 1% does not need those people. They can easily find replacements as there are plenty of people dying for a livable income.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-28 17:57:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Wait... so to talk about the harm of Marijuana he gathered the Bureau of Alcohol, Firearms, and Tobacco? This can't be real life. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-28 17:43:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What do these people think they can drink money? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-28 17:43:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Cause this just comes down to corporations profits. In a capitalistic society if there is room for more profit it only makes sense to take it. A majority of corporations are only concerned with how much they can return to their stock holders. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-28 17:36:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I don't get how Trump can run a campaign about cutting costs and excess spending then try to pump more money into the military. It literally doesn't make sense. This article states how the U.S is in marvels of Russia's and China's new military strength. Yet if you take both of their military budgets, combine them and double it you still don't reach the U.S. spending. We need to cut this budget at very least down to 500b and junk all these old weapons were trying to use. We constantly stock pile as if were going to war tomorrow and not only is it costing us billions its also eliminating the economical bump we used to see from war (which republicans historically count on). Our military is over inflated and pumping more money into it will solve absolutely nothing. The U.S that Trump is always talking about that was so great, relied heavily on Science and Immigration (illegal or not). Trying to make the U.S great without those two is like trying to eat soup with a knife. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-28 16:22:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> No it is not in New Jersey. Any one who says its in New Jersey is a liar. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-28 16:08:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I assume long term as in "its cheaper to park this here then try to break it down and get rid of it". </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-27 19:53:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That's exactly what I was thinking. Apparently in congress incompetence is a job requirement.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-27 19:45:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah but why would they ever pay attention to an Obama press conference.... they're just members of congress not concerned citizens. /s </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-27 19:10:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I remember reading that and I was just dumbfounded. Mcconnell tried to blame Obama saying he did not notify congress of the ramifications of this bill. Even if you ignore his veto of the bill as a notification that there might be something wrong; this means that either Mcconnell and a majority of the congress did not read the bill or they did not understand the bill. He might aswell of held up a sign saying "I AM NOT QUALIFIED FOR MY JOB!". </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-16 22:03:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's almost like we've been taken over by the mob....... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-16 21:58:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I wanna see them try to eat that money when the country is in turmoil. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-16 21:55:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That was the most nonsensical ramble that I've ever listened to. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-16 21:00:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Rule number 1: Always Double Down! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Talk About Safe Spaces! </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-16 20:21:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-16 18:52:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Can we please stop naming scandals ----gate?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-16 18:41:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Dude these are usually back breaking menial jobs requiring tons of labor and effort. Most of our homeless veterans are either mentally ill or physically incapable of doing these jobs. And on top of all that these jobs pay barely livable wages. Giving these jobs to Vets who have already put their lives on the line for our country would be cruel and disheartening.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-16 18:29:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah i don't doubt that robots will take these jobs but there will always be a place in America for cheap labor. Its what we were basically founded off of. Very few Americans want to be doing these back breaking menial jobs because they don't pay well, but they need to be done! This is one of the main reasons I don't understand Republicans. How can someone be against illegal immigrants and against increasing the minimum wage for citizens? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-16 18:22:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Chaffetz is just one of Trumps puppets who refers to himself in the Third person and has a twitter handle of "Jason in the house" lol. Dude is a clown who will get nothing productive done in his position. We need to look more at the people handing down orders. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-16 18:14:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Nahhh... I dont think it would take longer than a month. Shelf life for fruit is relatively short and demand is pretty high. Finding new workers to pick fruit for the pay that would keep farms profitable would be pretty difficult if you're trying to use American Labor. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-16 18:06:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah good luck finding American workers that will work for the same pay. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-16 18:06:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I know that's what I'm saying. A one day strike will have little impact. You'd notice and be begging for immigrant labor to come back if it lasted a month rather than a day. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-16 18:04:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The real issue here is that the republican party is more interested in party politics than protecting our country.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-16 18:00:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You wouldn't notice till probably a month in when your supermarket puts up signs saying either "Due to a shortage x is unavailable" or the price of the product just doubles. Unless you go to a restaurant that usually has immigrant cooks (most) then you'll just be wondering why your meal is taking so long. Cheap labor is actually vital to the united states and Americans don't want to work for those wages so you have to find immigrants who will. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-16 17:47:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Holy shit its up to 27,411 signatures! That's so close to the 930,936 signatures on the petition for Trump to release his tax returns!!! SIGN THIS NOW! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
