<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject695</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-12-08 02:54:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I wish they would make another one. I'm not sure if I would want it to be 8-bit, though.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-12-07 21:19:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> For the record, I think Obama has been terrible on all of these.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-12-07 20:54:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Cool, same here. There are several elements of libertarianism that I agree with such as defense spending, military intervention, the war on drugs, privacy and civil liberties.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-12-07 04:25:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I don't have a problem with individuals choosing to do this. I just would not want a society run like that. I'm a Socialist, so, of course I would support entitlement programs:-)  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-12-06 22:28:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This proves that they tend to be very judgmental and prefer to give money only to those that they personally deem to be worthy of the money.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-12-06 21:47:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Then how exactly do they care? Also, if they don't want to help people who are struggling to make ends meet, when do they care them? It is a fact that Republicans think empathy has a liberal bias.

 http://www.psychologytoday.com/blog/the-human-beast/201210/why-liberal-hearts-bleed-and-conservatives-dont

 http://www.sj-r.com/x726818012/Ann-Coulter-To-liberals-empathy-just-means-political-power
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-12-06 20:16:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> And once that baby is born, they don't give a fuck about you or the child.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-12-03 08:35:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The Truth is Out There  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-12-03 02:07:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Kind of shady to me.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-12-01 09:20:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> No, I didn't bring it up to my cousin personally. That would have been rude. I brought it up with my sister and used my cousin as an example.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-12-01 07:00:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thank you all for your honest answers.  I think I understand both sides of the issue, better now:-)  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-12-01 06:49:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Wow, I did not realize that it is so debatable. I made the mistake of  asking a female family member why doesn't my cousin, who just gave birth to a set of twins, never has breastfed. They are her fourth children within a span of six years. I practically was told to mind my own business!  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Why do so many women buy formula instead of breastfeeding their infants? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-12-01 05:57:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-11-30 06:42:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The Canyons by Paul Schrader.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-11-28 11:37:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Does he mind that you call him a midget? I thought they hate that:-)  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-11-28 11:19:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Stay away from spicy food if your digestive tract is that sensitive.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-11-28 05:06:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Wow, thanks!  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-11-28 04:38:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Source, please?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-11-28 02:50:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You imbecile, there are hypocrites in every ideology, including yours.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-11-28 02:10:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Not everyone knows English. Maybe there are immigrants who are trying to buy a family member something nice and they end up with a fucking empty box because some douche took advantage of their language barrier.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-11-27 00:00:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thanks for being candid. If I may ask, how old are you now and how young were you when you realized that you are a pedophile?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-11-26 11:37:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I haven't seen his penis yet, so this is not confirmed.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-11-26 09:10:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I need to see her receipt from Wounded Warrior Project. I doubt she ever donated to them. This phony needs to be exposed.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-11-26 08:42:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thanks. I had a hunch that it would be in Columbus but than I thought  possibly Cincinnati, too.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-11-26 06:36:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Since I'm from Ohio, I would like to know which city.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-11-26 05:43:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I think you spelled Florida wrong.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-11-26 04:06:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Do you even live in Ohio? I didn't vote for DeWine in 2010 but I think he is doing due diligence and I probably will vote for him next time.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-11-26 03:29:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> TIL Wire coat hangers are not just for abortions.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-11-26 02:49:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Even this blue dude? 

http://31.media.tumblr.com/543a3ae64cde0a14d4c516e05df37582/tumblr_mw8kx91NH91rl3565o6_250.gif </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-11-25 02:26:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Come on, you aren't fooling anyone, we know that is you, Mitt Romney.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-11-25 02:11:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If she was hot, you should have told her that your dick is a gypsy.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-11-23 03:16:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Why did Patton Oswalt apologize to your asshole friend? He sure as hell didn't need to do that. He must be a real gentleman.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-11-21 11:44:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The killing in Uteoya is what confused me about Norway because I thought bullshit like that only happened here.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-11-21 11:38:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I thought of it being on par with how the gang on Seinfeld reacted to Susan's death. 

Kramer: Poor, Lilly </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-11-21 11:29:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I remember hearing about that slaughtering and it reminded me of the insane people in the U.S. who killing and committing massacres. Another thing I forgot to mention is that there are laws to prevent insane people from buying guns but there are so many flaws. First, there are a lot people who are mentally ill but never got help, so, they are not in the system when there is a background check. The mental health system here is a goddamn joke because of lack of funding and people who can get help, don't go because they think they will be judged unfairly (turned down from a job, etc.). Second, background checks only apply to gun shops but not to gun expositions or online meaning any nut job can make a purchase. 

If you have any other questions, let me know!  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-11-21 10:28:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> TL;DR: Politicians are easily corrupted/influenced by lobbying firms and their money. They get people to support guns by playing off their fears and unrest. 

Ay yi yi, where do I even start? It is a complicated mess created by powerful gun lobbyists (National Rifle Association, Gun Manufacturers of America, American Legislative Exchange Council) who gave monetary contributions to the campaigns of politicians (Democrats and Republicans) in hopes of getting pro-gun laws passed.

The gun enthusiast crowd loves to cite that the Second Amendment to the U.S. Constitution gives them the right to have as many guns as they want. The poorly worded amendment says that a well regulated militia consisting of free citizens will be able to keep and bear arms that shall not be infringed upon. Keep in mind this was written in 1791 when there were fears that the British might try to start another war after American Revolutionary War ended in 1783. In my opinion, the keywords in the amendment are "well regulated", which means the government can limit gun usage. But gun fanatics do not share this view. They proclaim that all citizens should be able to own any kind of guns and their view ultimately won. 

Politicians and gun associations continued to get support for looser gun laws by playing off people's fear of  communist invasion during the Cold War and fear of ethnic minority groups. People were told they need to stockpile in case of a nuclear war. White people (I am white, myself) were (still are?) afraid that minorites were taking over the country in the 1960s and felt they needed to protect themselves in cities where riots took place. Gun supporters argued that ordinary citizens needed to be armed because the police will not be there until after something bad happens. This is why we have the gun laws that we have today. The funny thing is that less people own guns now for the first time in decades but the people who love guns are buying more than ever. 

Currently, the truth is that the vast majority of Americans want more restrictions on guns, but no new laws to regulate the use of high capacity assault weapons will be passed because most members of Congress are in bed with the gun lobbyists. Getting rid of these politicians is another whole story of how broken our system is. 
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-11-21 08:35:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thanks for explaining that to me. I guess I was misinformed.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-11-21 06:16:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I never thought of that episode as being particularly dark, I thought it was hilarious.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-11-20 10:43:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I meant aren't the gun laws similar to America's. Or, am I confused with another country?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-11-20 05:25:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> We all are so very proud of you.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-11-20 05:24:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> And don't Norwegians love their guns just as much as Americans do?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-11-19 11:48:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I don't care what the writers or anybody else says, that's what I'm going with, too.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-11-19 07:28:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I bet you have stories about some of the photos that you have seen.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-11-17 06:56:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That pisses me off, too. I take my frustration out on it by stabbing it several times with utensils.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-11-15 07:33:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I apologize if this has already been posted, but this my favorite thing ever from C-SPAN.                                   https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=whlzFWwVv98 feature=youtube_gdata_player


 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-11-05 04:00:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You are the one who smeared the shit, aren't you?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-11-04 06:40:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> How so?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-11-04 00:59:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What, are you eleven?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
