<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject7316</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-07 20:13:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [Olivier] Climate certainly plays a role, but this can be indirect: for example, bats in temperate climates hibernate in the winter, while some tropical bats migrate to find food according to dry/rain seasons. Viruses will likely be affected by movement and physiological changes in bats. We are also studying the effect of climate along the Eastern coast in Australia, to see if the timing and frequency of Hendra virus spillover events can be linked to climatic factors.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-07 20:11:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [Raina] There are many way to study bats and viruses. One is to lay plastic sheets under bat colonies --we can collect urine from the sheets and use genetic techniques to identify viruses in the urine. Another way is to catch bats in mist nets and take blood and urine samples from individuals and then analyze the samples with diagnostic techniques to identify viruses or antibodies to viruses.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-07 20:09:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [Raina] It is about understanding the ecology and epidemiology of viruses in bat populations so we can predict and prevent spillover. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-07 20:07:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [Raina] Good question about rabies. Although a number of our coauthors work on rabies, we decided to focus on the emerging pathogens as we know so little about them in bats. We thought that it would be useful to propose strategies for understanding their dynamics in bat populations, given the focus on Ebola etc. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-07 20:07:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [Olivier] We share your concern: our research actually aims at finding solutions that protect both people and bats. There are very good reasons to protect bats, not only out of regard for the natural world, but also because they play important ecological roles which are crucial to humans. Insectivorous bats are the most efficient and natural insecticide, and fruit bats are important pollinators. 
We believe that controlling disease can be better achieved by reducing contact between wildlife and people or domestic animals, and, when possible, using vaccines (there is now an efficient Hendra vaccine for horses in Australia). </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-07 20:03:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [Raina] That is an interesting question. I found this reference to the etymology of the word 'vampire': https://www.jstor.org/stable/2709546?seq=1#page_scan_tab_contents. According to Wikipedia, vampire bats were only recently associated with vampire folklore (they were discovered in Sth America in the 16th century): https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Vampire#Vampire_bats
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-07 20:01:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [Olivier] Bat genetics and genomics is an active area of research. I'm not aware of evidence of virus integration, but these are early days. Genome sequences are starting to reveal unusual features of immune systems in bats, which might account for their ability to tolerate virus infection. We're also using bat genetics to assess geographic variations within single species: the less variation there is across large areas, the more migration and mixing must be taking place, which helps spread viruses. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-07 19:57:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [Raina] bats provide important ecosystem services https://www.bu.edu/cecb/files/2009/08/Kunz-et-al.-Ecosystem-Services_ANYAS-2011.pdf. Fruit and blossom bats pollinate forests and disperse seeds. Insectivorous bats suppress crop pets and an interesting study recently showed that they also suppressed pest-associated fungus of corn http://www.pnas.org/content/112/40/12438.full Their ecosystem services may be worth billions and billions worldwide. If we eliminate bats the consequences could be devastating to our natural and agricultural systems. Also, bats are amazing creatures with incredible adaptations such as the ability to fly thousands of kilometers in search of nectar. Loss of these species would be as tragic as losing tigers, pandas, or elephants.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-07 19:55:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [Olivier] Some microbes are very good at infecting multiple host species, while others become very specialised and infect a single species. These can be seen as alternative strategies favoured by evolution under different conditions. But in addition, a spillover event requires a suitable contact, even indirect, between two host species. We think that part of the reason for the increasing number of emerging diseases in recent decades is because human populations are growing rapidly and encroaching into wildlife habitats.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-07 19:49:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [Olivier]


1. The difficulty varies greatly among bat species and environments. In Africa, large colonies (sometimes 1 million bats) form every year and then disperse again, and they're very difficult to track. A good monitoring programme was put in place in Australia, collecting urine on large plastic sheets under roosts, allowing virus detection. So we can get reasonable estimates of the prevalence of viruses in particular bat species, but it's hard to tell exactly how many bats carry the virus. But sometimes we cannot detect the virus even though bats have antibodies that indicate they have been infected recently. It could be that the virus is present in small numbers in bats and not always shed.

2. Culling bats has been advocated by policymakers and politicians in several countries, but scientifically it's not a good solution. First, it's very hard to carry out: bats fly away as soon as you try to shoot, catch or smoke them, so you're just moving the problem to a different location. This can easily worsen the problem, especially if stress increases shedding of viruses (which is likely). Second, bats provide very important ecological services, from pest control (insectivorous bats) to pollination and seed dispersal (for fruit bats). So the longer-term cost would outweigh the short-term benefit. We are working on alternative solutions, which can involve vaccines and reduction of bat-human contacts.

3. There is currently a large research effort on WNS, including the use of models. The problem is different because WNS has a lethal effect on bats, unlike the viruses we're studying. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-07 19:48:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [Raina] See our earlier posts about bat immunity. As far as I know bats have T-cells see here http://www.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/pmc/articles/PMC4276934/ 
Also see the links on earlier posts. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-07 19:45:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [Raina] I don't know why the bighorn sheep is associated with the tweet! I also work on infectious diseases that affect the conservation and recovery of bighorn sheep and perhaps they found the image on my research website! http://bzndiseaselab.org  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-07 19:39:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [Raina] See my answer to one of the earlier questions regarding bat immunology. I'll also add to my answer: some recent work by Michelle Baker's group at CSIRO in Australia found that bats have a high baseline level of innate immunity. She eloquently describes the paradoxes of bat immunity in a popular press article here: https://theconversation.com/why-bats-dont-get-get-sick-from-the-deadly-diseases-they-carry-55012.
The conservation issues are real and important. Bats are critical for healthy landscapes. We also show that culling and dispersal, in some situations, may make virus spillover worse. Some nice work by Dan Streiker on vampire bat rabies also predicts that culling could make things worse: http://rspb.royalsocietypublishing.org/content/279/1742/3384.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-07 19:32:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [Raina] Marburg virus has been isolated from bats on a number of occasions. CDC has done some good viral ecology work on Marburg virus, showing that it persists in populations of Rousettus aegyptiacus bast in Uganda. Ebola has not been isolated from bats, however, there are many lines of evidence that suggest that bats are reservoirs (widespread antibodies in bats, successful infection of bats with Ebola in the laboratory without seeing disease, epidemiological connections between bats, seroprevalence and disease, and discovery of Ebola RNA in bats). </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-07 19:31:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [Olivier] This question received a lot of attention during the latest Ebola outbreak in West Africa, where the consumption of bat bushmeat was quite common, and bans were rapidly put in place. However, the evidence is still scarce. Before the outbreak, my PhD student Alexandra Kamins carried out a detailed survey of bat bushmeat in Ghana, which unravelled a major trade business across the country. We think that consumption of bat bushmeat, which is usually thoroughly cooked, poses limited risk of infection, unlike hunting and butchering activities. However, we didn't find any evidence of exposure to bat viruses in hunters in Ghana.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-07 19:26:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [Raina] Bats are getting some bat publicity with all the talk of viruses. However, we think that human activities are contributing to spillover -- for example, in Australia, flying foxes (fruit bats) have lost much of their native forest habitat since European settlement, and are increasingly using urban and peri-urban areas for feeding, thus increasing their contact with horses (the intermediate host of Hendra virus). These bats are important pollinators, as their distribution shifts into peri-urban areas we are losing the important ecosystem services they provide. We need to find solutions that allow bats to continue to migrate and pollinate native forests, and such solutions may also decrease the risk of virus spillover. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-07 19:19:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [Olvier] Nipah virus is the best example. This virus was first identified following a major outbreak that spread across pig farms in Malaysia, and killed pig farmers and family members: https://www.cdc.gov/vhf/nipah/
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-07 19:17:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [Raina] You are correct. There is no documented spillover of Hendra virus directly from flying foxes to humans--all cases have had a horse intermediate host. Nipah virus, similarly spilled over from bats to pigs and then humans, but is now understood to also be directly transmitted from bats to humans through drinking contaminated date palm sap in Bangladesh. Our paper in PLOS NTD examines the dynamics of these viruses in bat populations. When the prevalence of virus (proportion of bats infected) is high in bat populations, the risk of spillover can also be high --whether this is spillover to horses grazing in paddocks, humans drinking date palm sap, or humans entering a cave with Marburg infected bats. The research methods needed to understand viral prevalence in bat populations are similar in all of these systems. The research needed to understand the human behavioral and immunological aspects of spillover is, however, specific to each system (e.g., horse grazing behavior for Hendra virus, human date palm sap consumption for Nipah virus in Bangladesh, etc.). </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-07 19:16:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [Olivier] 1. As far as we know, bats seem to tolerate most of the viruses that have been studied recently in relation to spillover. Rabies and related viruses, which kill any infected animal within days, are not always lethal to bats: some of them survive and develop protective immunity. White Nose Syndrome, which is caused by a fungus, is one of very few diseases of bats known to cause a substantial toll on populations. My colleagues have recently reviewed historical records of large mortality events in bats around the world, and very few seem to have been caused by disease: http://onlinelibrary.wiley.com/doi/10.1111/mam.12064/full

2. Persistence of viruses within bats is a hypothesis under investigation, as discussed in our paper (see link at the top of this page), but evidence is still limited, due to practical constraints.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-07 19:09:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [Raina] I think it is important to put the danger in perspective. We are all full of microbes, and the air we breathe is full of microbes from many other species. Every time we pat our dog or cat we are exposed to microbes. But very few of these microbes cross species barriers and cause disease. Probably because we have very effective immune barriers to pathogens. There is also growing evidence that early exposure to pathogens may be beneficial. But I do agree, the more you know about the scary but rare pathogens, the more it clouds our perception of the real risk of infection.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-07 19:04:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [Olivier] There are a few known examples, and probably many unknown cases. Nipah virus in South-East Asia is transmitted from bats to pigs, and the closely related Hendra virus in Australia infects horses. Transmission is thought to occur when bat urine contaminates drinking water for animals in fields. Hendra is lethal to horses, while Nipah causes less severe disease in pigs. MERS coronavirus, which is probably spread by Rousettus bats, infects camels. Ebola virus has caused deadly outbreaks in gorillas, and is seen as a major threat to endangered apes in Africa. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-07 19:00:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [Raina] Peter Piot's biography "No time to lose: a life in pursuit of deadly viruses" is a fascinating account of early exploration into the ecology and epidemiology of Ebola and HIV and other infections. I could not put it down! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-07 18:55:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [Raina] There is a growing understanding that bats may have an unusual immune system that allows them to carry viruses without experiencing disease. Their special immune responses may be a consequence of adaptations for flight. Bats must increase their metabolic rate up to 16 fold to fly (compared to birds who increase metabolic rate two fold). To deal with high metabolic rates bats must deal with the byproducts of oxidative metabolism. Recent work suggests that they evolved mechanisms to deal with oxidative stress that also happen to help them deal with intracellular pathogens, such as viruses. Another hypothesis that we described recently is the "flight as fever" hypothesis -- that bats increase their body temperature during daily flight, and this may drive selection for lower virulence pathogens (fever is a mechanism the body uses to fight pathogens). </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-07 18:52:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> 1. [Olivier] Only bats in temperate regions hibernate, and these tend to carry fewer diseases. Research from our colleagues in Colorado has shown the hibernation may help rabies virus (which is found in a small number of bats) persist in bat populations through the winter. White Nose Syndrome, which affects only bats, is thought to exhaust bats' energy during hibernation, but I'm not up to date with the latest research on WNS.

2. [Olivier] Before going beyond "the obvious" variables, we need to estimate them properly, which is not easy when dealing with animals that can fly over long distances in inhospitable regions. We try to combine different sources of information on populations (density, migration patterns, reproduction, all of which vary seasonally) and individuals (age, health, presence of antibodies indicating current or past infection...). Disease transmission itself is particularly hard to measure, as we can only detect it after the fact.
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-07 16:10:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [Olivier] The identification of a disease "reservoir" is a long and uncertain process, it's a real whodunnit! For Ebola, the virus has been found in a small number of animal species, including apes and bats, so they're our usual suspects. If not the virus itself, we can find antibodies in some bats, which show that these animals must have carried the virus at some point and survived. And there is also anecdotal evidence that the latest Ebola outbreak in West Africa started in a village where bats were roosting, and the "index case" is thought to be a child who may have come in contact with a bat soon before getting sick. For Marburg, Hendra and Nipah viruses, the evidence is much clearer. I recommment reading David Quammen's excellent book "Spillover" to find out about these. 
We and others are now studying African bat species to understand how they respond to and transmit these viruses, so that we can better estimate the risk to people, but it's not an easy task, as you can imagine. I don't do fieldwork myself, but my colleagues wear appropriate personal protective equipment (gloves, face masks) when handling bats, depending on the species. And they get vaccinated against rabies before starting field work, as a precautionary measure. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> PLOS Science Wednesday: Hi Reddit, were Raina and Olivier and we conducted a review assessing the spillover dynamics of four common viruses with bat reservoirs and outlined a research agenda based on our findings  Ask Us Anything! </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-07 14:15:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hi Reddit,

My name is [Raina Plowright](http://bzndiseaselab.org/) and I am an Assistant Professor of Epidemiology at Montana State University. I use field, lab and modeling approaches to understand how pathogens persist in wildlife populations (especially bats) and spill over to humans. And my name is [Olivier Restif](http://www.infectiousdisease.cam.ac.uk/directory/or226@cam.ac.uk) and I'm a Lecturer in Epidemiology at the University of Cambridge. I use mathematical models to track the spread of microbes within their hosts and across populations. In particular, I'm trying to find out how the ecology of African bats may contribute to their ability to spread viruses.

We recently published a paper titled [Transmission or within-host processes driving pulses of infection in reservoir hosts](http://journals.plos.org/plosntds/article?id=10.1371/journal.pntd.0004796) in [PLOS Neglected Tropical Diseases](http://journals.plos.org/plosntds/).

We examine the dynamics of emerging bat infections within their reservoir host populations. We argue that understanding the mechanisms that drive pulses of excretion of viruses such as Hendra, Nipah, Ebola and Marburg viruses, is essential to predict or manage spillover risk. We outline an ambitious multidisciplinary research agenda that would allow better management or even prevention of spillover.

We will be answering your questions at 1pm ET (10 am PT) -- Ask Us Anything!

You can follow Raina on Twitter at [@rainamontana](https://twitter.com/rainamontana) and Olivier on [@BugsWormsNBats](https://twitter.com/BugsWormsNBats). </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-01 15:46:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Niels here: yes, this is indeed possible. For example, in research genetically engineered viruses that contain snippets of RNA or DNA that match part of host plant genes of interest can be used to infect these plants to manipulate the expression of these genes. 

Fascinatingly, naturally occurring viruses sometimes also contain sequences in their genome that match host plant genes. In some of these cases viruses use this similarity to subvert host plant immunity by "silencing" the expression of plant defense genes. 

As long as the genetically engineered information does not target genes that are necessary for the plants well-being and the virus itself does not cause severe symptoms in the plant, genetic information can be delivered via a "mild" virus without harming the host plant. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-01 15:33:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Niels here: symbiosis is a catch-all concept for relationships that could be described with more detailed terms such as commensalism (no benefit to either partner), mutualism (both partners benefit), parasitism (one partner benefits at the expense of the other, but does not kill the other immediately) or predation (one partner benefits at the expense of the other after killing the other). In many cases species relationships could be in or switch to either status dependent on the genotypes of the partners and/or the environment. In the case of the plant-virus-pollinator interaction in our paper, the relationship between the virus and susceptible plants seems to show signs of mutualism when pollinators are present, but parasitism (in favour of the virus) when pollinators are absent.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-31 22:23:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Niels here: thanks for your interest in our work! John Carr's laboratory at the University of Cambridge will continue studying plant-virus-pollinator interactions in collaboration with Beverley Glover's laboratory. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-31 19:28:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Niels here: Dank je! De boys van HBR zijn bij dezen ook vereeuwigd in het archief van deze sessie  :) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-31 19:18:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Niels here: work led by a fellow co-author, Jack Westwood, shows that the same viral gene contributes to both enhanced pollinator attraction and increased drought tolerance in CMV-infected plants: http://www.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/pubmed/23083401 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-31 19:13:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Niels here: thank you for your interest in our work! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-31 19:12:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Niels here: these people are on it!
- http://news.psu.edu/story/271399/2013/04/02/research/ozone-masks-plants-volatiles-plant-eating-insects-confused
- http://horticulture.oregonstate.edu/node/308 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-31 19:02:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Niels here: thanks for your interest in our work! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> PLOS Science Wednesday: Hi Reddit, were Niels and Nik, and we propose that cucumber mosaic virus repays its hosts luring pollinators to infected plants and increasing seed production and pollen export  Ask Us Anything! </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-31 14:30:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hi Reddit,

My name is Simon Niels Groen and I am post-doctoral fellow at New York University. My research focuses on plant-microbe-insect interactions. I am joined by Nik Cunniffe, a [University Lecturer](http://www.plantsci.cam.ac.uk/directory/cunniffe-nik) in the [Department of Plant Sciences](http://www.plantsci.cam.ac.uk/) at the University of Cambridge and co-author on the PLOS Pathogens [article](http://dx.doi.org/10.1371/journal.ppat.1005790). Niks research focuses on developing mathematical models of how plant diseases spread, evolve and can be controlled.


We recently published a paper titled [Virus Infection of Plants Alters Pollinator Preference: A Payback for Susceptible Hosts?](http://dx.doi.org/10.1371/journal.ppat.1005790) in [PLOS Pathogens](http://journals.plos.org/plospathogens).  Cucumber mosaic virus, an important pathogen of tomato, causes plants to emit volatile chemicals that attract bumblebees - bumblebees are important tomato pollinators, but do not transmit this virus. We propose that under natural conditions, helping host reproduction by encouraging bee visitation might represent a payback by the virus to susceptible hosts.


We will be answering your questions at 1pm ET -- Ask Us Anything!


Dont forget to follow Niels and Nik on Twitter [@simoncgroen](https://twitter.com/simoncgroen) and [@nikcunniffe](https://twitter.com/nikcunniffe). </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> PLOS Science Wednesday: Hi Reddit my name is Hunter Underhill, and I discovered a new way to use circulating tumor DNA to improve cancer diagnostics and disease monitoring  Ask Me Anything! </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-24 14:30:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hi Reddit,

My name is [Hunter Underhill](http://healthcare.utah.edu/fad/mddetail.php?physicianID=u0977727) and I am an Assistant Professor in Pediatrics at the University of Utah. My research focuses on the non-invasive detection, diagnosis, and monitoring of malignant solid tumors.

I recently published a study titled ["Fragment Length of Circulating Tumor DNA"](http://dx.doi.org/10.1371/journal.pgen.1006162) in [PLOS Genetics](http://journals.plos.org/plosgenetics/). Detection of cell-free DNA derived from tumor cells (i.e., circulating tumor DNA) against the background of naturally occurring cell-free DNA from healthy cells has proven challenging. This has been particularly difficult in non-metastatic solid tumors as circulating tumor DNA has been heretofore indistinguishable from normal cell-free DNA except for the occurrence of mutant alleles that commonly occur at a frequency below detection limits. Our study found a distinct size difference in DNA fragment length between circulating tumor DNA and cell-free DNA. We were subsequently able to exploit this difference in fragment length size to enrich samples for circulating tumor DNA. This finding may provide the opportunity to substantially improve the sensitivity of detecting circulating tumor DNA and broaden the clinical utilization of circulating tumor DNA for diagnosing and monitoring cancers.

I will be answering your questions at 1 pm ET -- Ask Me Anything! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> PLOS Science Wednesday: Hi Reddit, were Susanne and Michael and we recently published a literature review in PLOS NTDs that showed countries that targeted the snail host are more successful at reducing or eliminating schistosomiasis  Ask Us Anything! </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-17 14:00:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hi Reddit,

My name is [Susanne Sokolow](https://profiles.stanford.edu/susanne-sokolow) and I am a disease ecologist and a Research Associate at Stanford University.  My research focuses on feedbacks between health and the natural environment.  I have studied a variety of diseases, most recently, human schistosomiasis, a neglected tropical parasite and a disease of poverty.

My name is [Michael Hsieh](https://smhs.gwu.edu/hsieh-lab/) and I am a physician scientist and an Associate Professor at George Washington University. My research focuses on how microbes and the host immune system interact in the urinary tract, including during urinary tract infections and urogenital schistosomiasis, which is infection by the parasitic Schistosoma haematobium worm.

We recently published a paper titled [Global Assessment of Schistosomiasis Control Over the Past Century Shows Targeting the Snail Intermediate Host Works Best](http://journals.plos.org/plosntds/article?id=10.1371/journal.pntd.0004794).  This publication reviewed the scientific literature on various strategies to control schistosomiasis (human infection with parasitic Schistosoma worms), and indicated that countries which targeted the snail host for these parasites tended to be most successful at reducing or eliminating this worm.

We will be answering your questions at 1pm EST. Ask Us Anything!

And dont forget to follow Michael on Twitter [@perforin](https://twitter.com/perforin). </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> PLOS Science Wednesday: Hi Reddit, its PLOS Ecology Community Editor Jeff Atkins joined by the five Ecology Reporting Fellows, and were answering questions from #ESA2016 about a ONE article modeling anthropogenic impacts on California wildfires  Ask Us Anything! </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-10 14:13:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hello Reddit,

Im [Jeff Atkins](http://blogs.plos.org/ecology/2015/11/12/new-editor-introduction-jeff-atkins/), an ecosystem ecologist, a Postdoctoral Scholar at Virginia Commonwealth University and a [PLOS Ecology Community](http://blogs.plos.org/ecology/) Editor. Todays PLOS Science Wednesday comes live from the Ecological Association of America (#ESA2016) annual meeting in Ft. Lauderdale, FL, a conference bringing together some 3000 practicing ecologists all this week. Im joined for this AMA by our five [PLOS Ecology Reporting Fellows](http://blogs.plos.org/ecology/2016/08/08/2016-plos-ecology-reporting-fellows-at-esa/), all early career ecologists, to talk about a PLOS ONE [article](http://journals.plos.org/plosone/article?id=10.1371/journal.pone.0153589) featured in the [PLOS Ecological Impacts of Climate Change Collection](http://collections.plos.org/eco-climate-change) which looks at effects of human activity and climate change on wildfires in CA.

Titled [Incorporating Anthropogenic Influences into Fire Probability Models](http://journals.plos.org/plosone/article?id=10.1371/journal.pone.0153589) by Michael Mann   colleagues, incorporates human activity and demographics into forecasting fire probabilities, showing reductions in model uncertainty and highlighting the human contribution to the increased prevalence and occurrence of wildfires.  Here is my [blog post discussing these findings](http://blogs.plos.org/ecology/2016/05/12/playing-with-matches-incorporating-human-activity-into-wildfire-forecasting/).

Because the theme of how anthropogenic (human) influences are changing ecosystems is the main topic of this years ESA were also happy to take your questions on any related topics  Ask Us Anything!

Dont forget to follow us [@PLOSEcology](https://twitter.com/plosecology) and [@JeffAtkins](https://twitter.com/atkinsjeff)!

We will be back at 1 pm ET to answer your questions, ask us anything! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> PLOS Science Wednesday: Hi Reddit, my name is Ken Tape and I recently published a PLOS ONE study showing the moose habitat expanded into the tundra during the 1800s, likely due to global warming and climate change  Ask Me Anything! </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-03 14:30:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hi Reddit,

My name is [Ken Tape](https://research.uaf.edu/researchers/8707?width=900 height=500 iframe=true ajax_request) and I am a Research Scientist at the [University of Alaska Fairbanks](https://www.uaf.edu/). My research focuses on the effects of climate change on the landscape, including its soils, vegetation, and wildlife.

I recently published a study in [PLOS ONE](http://journals.plos.org/plosone) titled [Range Expansion of Moose in Arctic Alaska Linked to Warming and Increased Shrub Habitat](http://journals.plos.org/plosone/article?id=10.1371/journal.pone.0152636). The goal of our study was to examine the factors contributing to moose's range expansion across the Alaskan Arctic during the 20th century. We accomplished this largely by estimating available moose habitat -- tall shrubs along rivers and streams -- during the late 1800s. We showed that moose habitat was greatly reduced during the 1800s, when moose were absent from the region. We think that warming increased moose habitat and caused its range expansion into the tundra.

I will be discussing the study and answering questions at 1pm ET. I look forward to your questions! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> PLOS Science Wednesday: Hi reddit, were Nick, Jenna and Fumiaki, and we contributed research to the new PLOS Medicine special issue on diabetes prevention -- Ask Us Anything! </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-27 14:00:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hi Reddit,

My name is Nick Wareham and I am Director of the [MRC Epidemiology Unit](http://www.mrc-epid.cam.ac.uk/) at the University of Cambridge. My research focuses on the genetic and environmental determinants of type 2 diabetes and the translation of epidemiological knowledge into preventive action. I also served as a [guest editor](http://collections.plos.org/s/diabetes-prevention-special-issue-guest-editors) on the PLOS Medicine special issue on [Diabetes Prevention](http://collections.plos.org/diabetes-prevention). I also wrote the editorial entitled [The Clinical and Public Health Challenges of Diabetes Prevention: A Search for Sustainable Solutions]( http://journals.plos.org/plosmedicine/article?id=10.1371/journal.pmed.1002097)  in which we discuss how diabetes is driven by rapid economic development and how attempts to deal with a public health problem by clinical approaches to prevention will be unaffordable and unsustainable in many countries. We focus on the need to develop effective and sustainable public health interventions for the prevention of type 2 diabetes that can be implemented in both resource-rich and resource-poor health care systems.

I am joined by Fumiaki Imamura and Jenna Panter, two scientists at the [MRC Epidemiology Unit](http://www.mrc-epid.cam.ac.uk/) at the University of Cambridge, who also contributed research to the [Diabetes Prevention](http://collections.plos.org/diabetes-prevention) issue of PLOS Medicine.

Jenna is a Senior Research Associate in the MRC Epidemiology Unit. Her research focuses on examining patterns and determinants of change in physical activity and evaluating environmental and policy interventions to promote activity. Jenna recently published an article titled [Cycling and Diabetes Prevention: Practice-Based Evidence for Public Health Action](http://journals.plos.org/plosmedicine/article?id=10.1371/journal.pmed.1002077) in [PLOS Medicine](http://journals.plos.org/plosmedicine/) in which the authors discuss the findings from a linked paper by [Rasmussen and colleagues](http://journals.plos.org/plosmedicine/article?id=10.1371%2Fjournal.pmed.1002076%20) on changes in cycling and risk of developing type 2 diabetes. In the article, the authors highlight the need to conduct rigorous evaluations of interventions to promote physical activity which will provide evidence about how researchers can create a genuinely population-based public health strategy for the prevention of diabetes and other chronic diseases.

Fumiaki is a Senior Investigator Scientist at the MRC Epidemiology Unit. His research focuses on effects of dietary components and behaviours with a risk of developing type 2 diabetes. Fumiaki recently published a study titled [Effects of Saturated Fat, Polyunsaturated Fat, Monounsaturated Fat, and Carbohydrate on Glucose-Insulin Homeostasis: A Systematic Review and Meta-analysis of Randomised Controlled Feeding Trials](http://journals.plos.org/plosmedicine/article?id=10.1371/journal.pmed.1002087) in PLOS Medicine. I am also a co-author of a study published by the EPIC-InterAct Study in the PLOS Medicine, [Association of Plasma Phospholipid n-3 and n-6 Polyunsaturated Fatty Acids with Type 2 Diabetes: The EPIC-InterAct Case-Cohort Study](http://journals.plos.org/plosmedicine/article?id=10.1371/journal.pmed.1002094). In the two studies based on published trials and the Europe-wide observational investigation, respectively, Fumiaki and colleagues indicate that fat commonly present in vegetable oils is good to reduce the burden of type 2 diabetes in many countries.

We will be answering your questions at 1pm ET  Ask Us Anything!

Dont forget to follow us on Twitter [@JennaPanter](https://twitter.com/JennaPanter), [@fumimamu](https://twitter.com/fumimamu) and [@mrc_epid](https://twitter.com/MRC_Epid). </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> PLOS Science Wednesday: Hi Reddit, we're Jessie Abbate, Carmen Lia Murall and Christian Althaus, and we developed a mathematical model showing the sexual transmission of Ebola could prolong the epidemic in West Africa -- Ask Us Anything! </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-20 14:00:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hi Reddit,


We are Jessie Abbate, Carmen Lia Murall, and Christian Althaus, infectious disease researchers collaborating between France (Research Institute for Development), Switzerland (University of Bern), and Germany (Max Planck Institute). Collectively, our work focuses on the epidemiology, ecology, and evolution of pathogens, including human viral infections.


We recently published a study entitled [Potential Impact of Sexual Transmission on Ebola Virus Epidemiology: Sierra Leone as a Case Study](http://journals.plos.org/plosntds/article?id=10.1371/journal.pntd.0004676) in [PLOS Neglected Tropical Diseases](http://journals.plos.org/plosntds/).


Recent observations show that Ebola virus can remain active and transmissible in sperm for up to 9 months, meaning patients can remain infectious after they recover from the initial symptomatic phase of the disease. We developed a mathematical model to study the potential impact of sexual transmission on the size and duration of Ebola outbreaks such as the 2013-2016 epidemic in West Africa.


Using the epidemiological data from Sierra Leone as an example, we found that despite very few additional cases, sexual transmission from survivors could extend the duration of the epidemic substantially, allowing cases to continue popping up throughout 2016 and highlighting the need for care providers to stay alert for this possibility.


We will be responding to questions from 1pm EDT (10 am PDT) -- Ask Us Anything!




Dont forget to follow us on Twitter [@jessieabbate](https://twitter.com/jessieabbate) [@cl_murall](https://twitter.com/cl_murall) [@c_althaus](https://twitter.com/c_althaus). </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> PLOS Science Wednesday: Hi Reddit, were Jorge Ahumada and Lydia Beaudrot, and we used camera traps to monitor mammal and bird populations in 15 protected tropical forests, further establishing the importance of standardized monitoring for conservation  Ask Us Anything! </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-13 14:03:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hi Reddit,

My name is Jorge Ahumada and I am the executive director of the [TEAM Network](http://teamnetwork.org) at [Conservation International](http://www.conservation.org). I completed my PhD in [Ecology and Evolutionary Biology](https://www.princeton.edu/eeb/) at Princeton University, where I studied the reproductive strategies of neotropical wrens. I am interested in applying mathematical models to solve applied conservation problems, and Ive worked on the impacts of climate change on disease and biodiversity, incorporating the effects of temperature and rainfall on models of disease-transmitting vectors and more recently on the use of camera traps for monitoring vertebrates.

My name is Lydia Beaudrot and I am a Michigan Fellow and Assistant Professor at the University of Michigan in the [Department of Ecology and Evolutionary Biology](https://lsa.umich.edu/eeb/). I previously worked in the Moore Center for Science at [Conservation International](http://www.conservation.org/projects/Pages/Betty-and-Gordon-Moore-Center-for-Science-and-Oceans.aspx). My research focuses on how people and the environment affect mammals and birds in tropical forests.

We recently published a study with several colleagues in [PLOS Biology](http://journals.plos.org/plosbiology) titled [Standardized Assessment of Biodiversity Trends in Tropical Forest Protected Areas: The End Is Not in Sight]( http://journals.plos.org/plosbiology/article?id=10.1371/journal.pbio.1002357). Protected areas, such as National Parks, are very important for conservation, but surprisingly we have not known whether protected areas keep wildlife populations from declining. Our study used infrared-activated cameras placed in 15 tropical forests around the world by the TEAM Network and found that these protected areas have not had widespread wildlife declines recently, which is better news than previous studies have suggested.

Read more about our research[Conservation: Good News from Animal Selfies](http://blogs.plos.org/biologue/2016/01/20/conservation-good-news-from-animal-selfies/) on Biologue at PLOS Blogs.

Follow Conservation International on Twitter [@ConservationOrg](https://twitter.com/ConservationOrg).

We will be answering your questions at 1pm ET -- Ask Us Anything! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> PLOS Science Wednesday: Hi Reddit, were Courtney Lane-Donovan and Joachim Herz, and in a PLOS ONE study we examined how a high-fat diet effects levels of ApoE isoforms in mice, which are known to impact Alzheimers risk  Ask Us Anything! </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-06 14:00:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hi Reddit,

My name is Courtney Lane-Donovan, and I am an MD/PhD student in Neuroscience at the [University of Texas Southwestern Medical Center](http://www.utsouthwestern.edu/) in Dallas, Texas. Im interested in the underlying biology of neurodegenerative diseases (e.g., Alzheimers disease) and finding new molecular mechanisms that could be targeted for future drug development.

My name is [Joachim Herz](http://profiles.utsouthwestern.edu/profile/13165/joachim-herz.html), I am a Professor of Molecular Genetics and Neuroscience with a specific interest in lipid metabolism and the mechanisms of neurodegeneration and therapeutic approaches that Courtney has mentioned.  My claim to fame is that I was Courtneys MD/PhD mentor.  In the meantime, our roles seem to have reversed, as I have the feeling that I am the one who is learning more from Courtney each day.

We recently published a paper titled [High-Fat Diet Changes Hippocampal Apolipoprotein E (ApoE) in a Genotype- and Carbohydrate-Dependent Manner in Mice](http://journals.plos.org/plosone/article?id=10.1371%2Fjournal.pone.0148099) in [PLOS ONE](http://journals.plos.org/plosone/).

Alzheimers disease affects 1 in 8 individuals over the age of 65. The risk of developing Alzheimers disease is increased by lifestyle factors, including a high-fat Western diet and high cholesterol, as well as genetic risk factors. Our research is centered on one of the most common genetic risk factors: apolipoprotein (ApoE). Individuals who have the e4 isoform of ApoE (ApoE4, about 15% of the population) have a three-fold increased risk of developing Alzheimers. ApoE has many roles in the brain, including cholesterol transport and neuronal function.

In this study, we looked at the effect of a known lifestyle effect  high-fat diet  on levels of ApoE in the brain in mice expressing the different ApoE isoforms. We found that while the diet reduced levels of brain ApoE in mice expressing ApoE3, it did not affect the levels in mice expressing ApoE4 or mouse ApoE.

We will be answering your questions at 1pm ET -- Ask Us Anything!

Edit: Hi, everyone. We are signing off for now. Thank you for inviting us and for your great questions and discussion on Alzheimer's, ApoE, and diet!  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> PLOS Science Wednesday: Hi Reddit, were Roslyn Dakin and Suzanne Amador Kane. We published a study in PLOS ONE assessing the physics behind displays of courtship from male peacocks  Ask Us Anything! </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-29 13:04:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hi Reddit,

Our names are Roslyn Dakin and Suzanne Amador Kane. We study animal behavior and vision.

Roz is a postdoctoral fellow in zoology at the University of British Columbia. She studies bird courtship, mating behavior, and flight. Suzanne is a biological physics professor at Haverford College. Her research focuses on how physics influences animal behavior.

Along with coauthors Owen McCrossan, Jim Hare, and Bob Montgomerie, we recently published a study in [PLOS ONE](http://journals.plos.org/plosone) titled, ["Biomechanics of the Peacock's Display: How Feather Structure and Resonance Influence Multimodal Signaling"](http://journals.plos.org/plosone/article?id=10.1371/journal.pone.0152759).

When peacocks try to impress females, they fan their feathers and vibrate them at a very high rate, causing the eyespots to hover against an undulating, shimmering background. We explored the physics of this display. We found that the individual feathers move as standing waves. Furthermore, the peacocks tail as a whole has a resonant peak frequency matching the vibration frequency of the display (about 25 times per second). This indicates that the tail is well-suited to perform the display efficiently. However, when we studied individual peacocks in the field, we found that individuals with longer feathers used slightly higher frequencies on average, suggesting that the display may reveal a males capacity to generate muscular force. Its still an open question as to how (or if) this display influences the female, her perception of the peacock's iridescent colors, and how she chooses a mate.

We are excited to answer your questions at 1pm ET. Ask Us Anything!

Also, be sure to watch a video on [vibrations of peacock feathers](https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=voPTJ9KKsoY) and our [lab experiments](https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=yTfk5Izepfo) from this study. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> PLOS Science Wednesday: Hi Reddit, I'm Professor Damien Keating and I discovered gene RCAN1 is linked to blood sugar problems in both Type 2 Diabetes and Down Syndrome -- Ask Me Anything! </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-22 14:00:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hi Reddit,


My name is [Professor Damien Keating](https://www.flinders.edu.au/neuroscience/lab_molecular.html) and I am a cell physiologist at Flinders University in the School of Medicine. My research focuses on understanding how cells release chemical signals to each other and how this relates to certain diseases such as diabetes.


I recently published a paper titled [A Syntenic Cross Species Aneuploidy Genetic Screen Links RCAN1 Expression to -Cell Mitochondrial Dysfunction in Type 2 Diabetes]( http://dx.plos.org/10.1371/journal.pgen.1006033) in [PLOS Genetics]( http://journals.plos.org/plosgenetics/).



In this study we wanted to identify what might drive pancreatic beta cell dysfunction and reduced plasma insulin in type 2 diabetes (T2D). If those beta cell changes dont happen people dont develop T2D. We tackled this in a different way by looking at diabetes in Down syndrome (where chromosome 21 is triplicated), as beta cells in individuals with Down syndrome show the same defects observed in T2D beta cells. Using a screening approach combining Down syndrome mouse models and human T2D beta cells, we arrived at a single lead candidate, RCAN1. We then provided functional evidence that increased RCAN1 expression causes defects in beta cell mitochondrial function and insulin release that are observed in T2D beta cells. We hope this will provide a platform to examine whether affecting RCAN1 function or expression could have positive influences in T2D.



I look forward to chatting with you all on this topic from Australia. I will be answering your questions at 1pm ET -- Ask Me Anything!



Dont forget to follow me on Twitter [@dj_keating](https://twitter.com/dj_keating). </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> PLOS Science Wednesday: Hi reddit, were Mahdad, Lucy and Gabriele. We found several different effects of HIV-1 infection on anti-TB immune response, presenting new implications for treating patients with TB and HIV infections  Ask Us Anything! </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-15 13:50:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hi Reddit,

My name is Dr Mahdad Noursadeghi. I lead a research group in Infection   Immunity at [University College London](http://www.ucl.ac.uk/), in which we try to discriminate between human immune responses to microbial infection that protect us from those that cause disease. We focus our efforts on tuberculosis (TB), HIV and the role of macrophages.

And my name is Dr Lucy Bell. Im a researcher in Infection   Immunity at [University College London](http://www.ucl.ac.uk/). My research explores the impact of HIV-1 infection on immune responses to other infections, such as TB, using methods ranging from in vitro macrophage co-infection experiments to human experimental challenge models.

And my name is Dr Gabriele Pollara. I'm a postdoctoral clinical research fellow at [University College London](http://www.ucl.ac.uk/). My work focuses on understanding the nature of protective immune responses to TB infection. My main methodological interests are the use of transcriptional modules to deconvolute biological information from whole genome transcriptional datasets.

We recently published a paper titled [In Vivo Molecular Dissection of the Effects of HIV-1 in Active Tuberculosis](http://journals.plos.org/plospathogens/article?id=10.1371%2Fjournal.ppat.1005469) in [PLOS Pathogens]( http://journals.plos.org/plospathogens). We aimed to investigate whether HIV-1 infection changed the anti-TB immune response in vivo in patients with active TB, by using the tuberculin skin test (the TST, also known as the Mantoux test) as a challenge model. By analysing biopsy samples taken from the site of TSTs, we found several effects of HIV-1. In early HIV-1 infection, we found diminishment of an immune response component that usually helps prevent harmful inflammation. In more advanced HIV-1, we found almost complete absence of any anti-TB immune response, except for activity which is normally part of our defence against viruses. In a third group of patients, in whom active TB only became apparent after starting treatment for HIV-1, we found that most immune responses had recovered to normal levels, but that one particular response sometimes associated with asthma and allergies was exaggerated.

Our results provide new insights which may help explain why HIV-1 positive patients have a substantially increased risk of active TB, and which may inform the development of new treatments for HIV-1/TB co-infection.

We will be answering your questions about our research, TB and HIV at 1pm ET. Ask us Anything!

Dont forget to follow us on Twitter:  [@mnoursad](https://twitter.com/mnoursad), [@LucyCKBell](https://twitter.com/LucyCKBell), [@gpollara](https://twitter.com/gpollara), [@innate2adaptive]( https://twitter.com/innate2adaptive).

And check out our [research group website](http://www.innate2adaptive.com/). </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> PLOS Science Wednesday: Hi Reddit, my name is Emily Bucholz and I published a study in PLOS Medicine studying the impacts of being underweight after a heart attack, Ask Me Anything! </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-08 14:00:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hi Reddit,

My name is Emily Bucholz. I am a pediatric resident at [Boston Childrens Hospital](http://www.childrenshospital.org/) but did my doctorate at [Yale School of Medicine](http://medicine.yale.edu/). My doctoral research focuses on sociodemographic and clinical predictors of life expectancy after heart attacks. I am particularly interested in how risk factors for the development of coronary heart disease affect long-term survival after heart attacks.

I am the lead author of a study recently published in PLOS Medicine titled [Underweight, Markers of Cachexia, and Mortality in Acute Myocardial Infarction: a Prospective Cohort Study of Elderly Medicare Beneficiaries](http://journals.plos.org/plosmedicine/article?id=10.1371/journal.pmed.1001998). In this study, we studied over 50,000 Medicare beneficiaries to examine the effect of underweight on survival after heart attack. We used two techniques (adjustment and stratification) to disentangle the effects of low weight from comorbidity and frailty, which can also lead to weight loss and poor health outcomes. We found that being underweight was an independent risk factor for higher short- and long-term mortality after heart attack. There are several potential explanations for these findings including decreased physiologic reserve, lower rates of guideline-based therapies, and genetic predisposition. Regardless of the mechanism, we conclude that strategies to promote weight gain after heart attack -- both in the hospital and after discharge --are worthy of testing.

My co-authors were Ms. Hannah Krumholz and Dr. Harlan Krumholz. I will be answering your questions at 1pm ET -- Ask Me Anything! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> PLOS Science Wednesday: Hi reddit, my name is Nicholas Money and I published a paper in PLOS ONE which showed mushroom spores act as nuclei for raindrops using environmental electron microscopy -- Ask Me Anything! </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-01 12:30:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hi Reddit,



My name is [Nicholas Money](http://miamioh.edu/cas/academics/departments/biology/about/faculty/money/index.html). Im a biologist at Miami University in Oxford, Ohio and specialize in the study of fungal growth and reproduction. I am fascinated by the extraordinary mechanisms of spore discharge in these organisms that include high-velocity spurts, exploding gas bubbles, and a catapult that launches mushroom spores.




I am the senior author of a 2015 paper in [PLOS ONE](http://journals.plos.org/plosone) titled, [Mushrooms as rainmakers: How spores act as nuclei for raindrops](http://journals.plos.org/plosone/article?id=10.1371/journal.pone.0140407). A couple of years ago I was struck by research by atmospheric chemists that suggested that 50 million tons of fungal spores are ejected into the atmosphere every year. This made me wonder whether the mechanism of drop expansion that powers the discharge of mushroom spores could be reactivated once the spores were airborne. If this happened in clouds, it could play a significant role in the condensation of water and stimulate rainfall. The PLOS ONE paper reports experiments that offer a proof of concept using environmental scanning electron microscopy. This work was co-authored by my doctoral student, Maribeth Hassett, and long-term collaborator Mark Fischer, a physicist at Mount St. Joseph University in Cincinnati.



I'll be answering questions at 1pm ET -- Ask Me Anything! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> PLOS Science Wednesday: Hi Reddit, we're Nick and Cori Ruktanonchai, and we published a paper in PLOS Computational Biology on how mobile phone data can target malaria elimination efforts -- Ask Us Anything! </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-25 14:00:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hi Reddit!

Im [Nick Warren Ruktanonchai](http://www.flowminder.org/people/nick-ruktanonchai), a postdoctoral research fellow at the University of Southampton. Im interested in understanding how people move, which helps us predict when, where, and why some people become exposed to areas with infectious diseases. And I am [Cori Warren Ruktanonchai](http://www.southampton.ac.uk/geography/about/staff/cr2m14.page), a PhD student in Geography   Environment at the University of Southampton--as you may have noticed by the names, I also happen to be Nicks wife! Im interested in using spatial statistics to better locate pregnant women, mothers and newborns at risk of adverse health outcomes.

We recently published an article titled [Identifying Malaria Transmission Foci for Elimination Using Human Mobility Data](http://journals.plos.org/ploscompbiol/article?id=10.1371/journal.pcbi.1004846) in [PLOS Computational Biology](http://journals.plos.org/ploscompbiol/), mapping where people got malaria based on their travel patterns.

We combined data from 1.19 million mobile phones in Namibia with a map of malaria prevalence to predict areas where the most people get infected. We hope that by targeting these hotspots, elimination efforts can both send help where it's most needed and reduce transmission nationwide.

Call and text locations from mobile phones are a great tool for knowing where people have been. At [Flowminder](http://www.flowminder.org), weve used mobile phone data to not only help governments and NGOs predict the spread of disease, weve also used it to understand how people move after catastrophes, including a [PLOS Medicine paper](http://journals.plos.org/plosmedicine/article?id=10.1371/journal.pmed.1001083) on the 2010 Haiti earthquake and a [PLOS Currents paper](http://currents.plos.org/disasters/article/rapid-and-near-real-time-assessments-of-population-displacement-using-mobile-phone-data-following-disasters-the-2015-nepal-earthquake/) on the 2015 Nepal earthquake.

Well be answering your questions at 1pm ET -- Ask Us Anything!

Dont forget to follow Nick on Twitter at [@nruktanonchai](https://twitter.com/nruktanonchai) and Cori at [@cwruktanonchai](https://twitter.com/cwruktanonchai). Also, the Flowminder Foundation can be found at [@flowminder](https://twitter.com/flowminder), and the WorldPop Project at [@WorldPopProject](https://twitter.com/WorldPopProject)! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> PLOS Science Wednesday: Hi Reddit, we are Florian Markowetz and James Breton. We published a paper in PLOS Medicine showing resistance to cancer treatment may be related to the heterogeneity in the tumor, which has implications for drug effectiveness  Ask Us Anything! </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-18 13:53:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hi Reddit,

My name is Florian Markowetz and I am a cancer researcher at the University of Cambridge in the [Cancer Research UK (CRUK)](http://www.cambridgecancer.org.uk/) Cambridge Institute. My lab and I try to understand how genetic variability between and within patients leads to differences in cancer progression and outcome.

And my name is James Brenton and I am a senior group leader at the CRUK Cambridge Institute, where I study the functional genomics of ovarian cancer and lead on translational studies in the clinic as a medical oncologist at Cambridge University Hospitals.

We recently published a paper titled [Spatial and temporal heterogeneity in high-grade serous ovarian cancer: a phylogenetic reconstruction](http://journals.plos.org/plosmedicine/article?id=10.1371/journal.pmed.1001789) in [PLOS Medicine](http://journals.plos.org/plosmedicine). The main hypothesis that we were trying to test was whether the magnitude of intratumoural heterogeneity in a patients ovarian cancer was a predictor of their outcome. For this, we developed new methods to parsimoniously reconstruct phylogenies using copy number profiles. We found evidence that resistance to treatment could be linked to the degree of genetic heterogeneity in the tumor. The more heterogeneous a tumor is, the more likely is it that the patient becomes resistant. Our study is small, but it identified what could be one of the key reasons why drugs stop being effective after some time.

We are looking forward to exploring this topic further with you and will be answering your questions at 1pm ET -- Ask Us Anything!

You can find out more about me (Florian) and my research at my [labs webpage](http://www.markowetzlab.org) and on my blog [Scientific B-Sides](http://scientificbsides.wordpress.com). And dont forget to follow me on Twitter [@markowetzlab](https://twitter.com/markowetzlab).

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> PLOS Science Wednesday: Hi Reddit, my name is Ben Lopman, and I am lead author on the new PLOS Collection featuring research on global burden and economic costs of norovirus, and prospects for vaccine development -- Ask Me Anything! </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-11 14:12:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hi Reddit,

My name is [Ben Lopman](http://blogs.cdc.gov/safehealthcare/authors/ben-lopman-ph-d/) and I am an infectious disease epidemiologist with Division of Viral Diseases at the US Centers for Disease Control and Prevention (CDC). My research focuses on the epidemiology of diarrheal disease and, specifically, its viral causes.

I am a lead author on recently published PLOS Collection titled [The Global Burden of Norovirus   Prospects for Vaccine Development"](http://collections.plos.org/norovirus). This collection explains why a norovirus vaccine is so important and focuses on some basic science and public health questions that need to be addressed in order to pave the way for a vaccine.

Noroviruses are estimated to cause over 200,000 deaths every year globally. And, all added up, they cost over $60 billion worldwide each year due to health and societal impacts. Noroviruses can cause severe disease among children, the elderly and other vulnerable populations, such as patients in hospitals or residents in nursing homes, places where outbreaks often occur. Better control strategies, including vaccines, are needed, and, thankfully, are under development.

I will be answering your questions at 1pm ET -- Ask Me Anything! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> PLOS Science Wednesday: Hi reddit, were Neelesh Patankar and Malcolm MacIver, and we published a paper in PLOS Biology showing a mechanically optimal method of swimming evolved independently in vertebrate and invertebrate swimmers  Ask Us Anything! </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-04 13:08:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hi Reddit!
 
My name is Neelesh Patankar, and I am the Charles Deering McCormick Professor of Teaching Excellence and Associate Chair of the Department of Mechanical Engineering at Northwestern University. Following my Ph.D. in Mechanical Engineering at University of Pennsylvania, I was a post-doctoral associate with Prof. Daniel D. Joseph at the University of Minnesota until 2000. I then joined the Department of Mechanical Engineering at Northwestern University as an Assistant Professor in 2000, and have been a Professor since 2011. My research area is developing computational methods for immersed bodies in fluids, applying computations to problems in biology (fish swimming, esophageal transport, rat whiskers), and designing textured surfaces for non-wetting, super-wetting, or anti-icing properties.
 
And my name is Malcolm MacIver, and I am a Professor with a joint appointment in the Department of Mechanical Engineering and Department of Biomedical Engineering at Northwestern University. I completed my Ph.D. in neuroscience at the Beckman Institute of Advanced Sciences and Technology at the University of Illinois, and my post-doc in mechanical engineering at the California Institute of Technology in Pasadena, joining Northwestern in 2003. My research includes the mechanical and neural basis of animal behavior, particularly the intersection of information harvesting and biomechanics, utilizing a variety of approaches spanning behavioral analysis, computer simulations, robotics, neurobiology, and mechanics.
 
We recently published a [paper](http://journals.plos.org/plosbiology/article?id=10.1371/journal.pbio.1002123) in [PLOS Biology](http://journals.plos.org/plosbiology) examining how diverse groups of aquatic animals, including vertebrates and invertebrates, evolved independently to exhibit a mechanically optimal method of swimming. Using computational modeling, measurements, and a robotic fish, we demonstrate that this best way to swim maximizes propulsive force and speed. There is some small amount of variability around the optimum in the many species we measured, but that variability is always within a relatively small zone where the decrease in performance is less significant. Our result touches on a long standing debate within biology about whether evolution is largely about chance, or about necessity. If we were to rewind the clock and restart evolution, would we get the same animals, or different ones? For example, birds evolved wings, and so did insects, but their last common ancestor did not have wings. This suggests that an aerial animalon any planet with earth-like atmospheremight have wings. The idea that evolution is therefore more about necessity than chance due to these kinds of repeated patterns is referred to as convergent evolution. One of the unique contributions of our work is that we can quantitatively show where the optimum exists, while it has proven difficult to do so for other examples of convergent evolution.

**We will be answering your questions at 1pm ET  Ask Us Anything!**
 
[@NeeleshPatankar](https://twitter.com/NeeleshPatankar), [@malcolmmaciver](https://twitter.com/malcolmmaciver) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> PLOS Science Wednesday: Hi reddit, my name is Dr. Nina Kraus and I found preschoolers auditory language processing parallels early language development, which would allow for early intervention for language disorders  Ask Me Anything! </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-27 14:04:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hi Reddit, my name is Dr. Nina Kraus and I am professor and neuroscientist at [Northwestern University](https://www.communication.northwestern.edu/faculty/NinaKraus). My research focuses on how the brain learns to make sense of sound, and the impact of this learning on our ability to communicate with one another.

I recently published a study titled ["Auditory processing in noise: A preschooler biomarker for literacy"](http://journals.plos.org/plosbiology/article?id=10.1371/journal.pbio.1002196) in [PLOS Biology]( http://journals.plos.org/plosbiology). In this study, we measured how a preschoolers brain responds to sound, using an objective biological approach my lab has developed. We found that the integrity with which preschoolers' brains processed consonants in noise paralleled their early language development, and could predict the development of their literacy skills one year out. This suggests we have an approach to identify which preschoolers will struggle learning to read long before they begin formal instruction. This is important because it would allow us to provide interventions for language disorders such as dyslexia to children before they experience prolonged challenges in school.

To learn more about my work and our biological approach, please check out our website, [brainvolts](http://www.brainvolts.northwestern.edu/). The website is a labor of love; we update it almost daily. By viewing [lab projects]( http://www.brainvolts.northwestern.edu/projects/index.php), you can gain a sense of the scope of our work. Choose the individual lab project pages that interest you most to see relevant videos, publications, and more -- do be sure to check out the friendly overview slideshow offered for each project. And be sure to check out the [demonstration of our biological approach to auditory processing]( http://www.brainvolts.northwestern.edu/demonstration.php) on the homepage, and all papers are available for download from [publications](http://www.brainvolts.northwestern.edu/publications.php).

I will be answering your questions at 1pm ET -- Ask Me Anything!

Dont forget to follow us on Twitter [@brainvolts](https://twitter.com/brainvolts).

**Edit**: Thanks all for the questions and interest. We invite you to visit our [website](www.brainvolts.northwestern.edu) to keep up-to-date with our work, and please explore all the resources we have there! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> PLOS Science Wednesday: Hi Reddit, were Eric C. Leuthardt, Joshua Shimony, and David Tran. We discovered the blood-brain barrier stays open after laser ablation surgery, creating opportunities for glioblastoma treatment, as described in PLOS ONE  Ask Us Anything! </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-20 14:17:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hi Reddit,

My name is Dr. Eric C. Leuthardt and I am professor of neurosurgery at [Washington University](https://wustl.edu/). My research focuses on brain computer interfaces, advanced brain mapping and the development of new medical technologies. And my name is Joshua Shimony and I am an Associate Prof. of Neuroradiology at [Washington University School of Medicine](https://www.mir.wustl.edu/). My research focuses on advanced MRI imaging and its clinical applications. And I am David Tran, the chief of neuro-oncology in the department of neurosurgery at the [University of Floridas College of Medicine](http://med.ufl.edu/). My research focuses on understanding the mechanism of cancer progression and on developing novel therapeutic approaches to cancer.

We recently published a study titled [Hyperthermic Laser Ablation of Recurrent Glioblastoma Leads to Temporary Disruption of the Peritumoral Blood Brain Barrier](http://journals.plos.org/plosone/article?id=10.1371%2Fjournal.pone.0148613) in [PLOS ONE]( http://journals.plos.org/plosone). We found that a laser system commonly used to kill brain tumors has an additional and significant benefit: It creates a temporary opening in the blood-brain barrier  a natural barrier thats normally efficient at blocking out chemicals and bacteria  to allow the passage of chemotherapy and immunotherapy drugs into the brain, for up to six weeks. This discovery could lead to new treatment protocols for glioblastoma, a very aggressive brain cancer thats highly resistant to standard treatment.

**We will be answering your questions at 1pm ET  Ask Us Anything!**
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> PLOS Science Wednesday: Hi Reddit, we are Lisa Jones-Engel, Stacey Schultz-Cherry, and Christopher Small. We published a study in PLOS Pathogens demonstrating new evidence of the role of primates in the ecology of Astroviruses that can also infect humans  Ask Us Anything! </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-13 13:45:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hi Reddit,

My name is Lisa Jones-Engel and I am a Senior Research Scientist at the [University of Washington](http://staff.washington.edu/ljengel/teammonkey/lisa.htm). For nearly two decades my research team has focused on the infectious agents that are transmitted at the increasingly porous human-primate interface in Asia.

And my name is Stacey Schultz-Cherry and I am a Full Member (Professor) at [St Jude Childrens Research Hospital](https://www.stjude.org/directory/s/stacey-schultz-cherry.html) where my research focuses on the pathogenesis of influenza virus and enteric viruses, like Astroviruses, especially in high-risk populations. 

My name is Erik Karlsson and I am a Postdoctoral Research Associate at [St Jude Childrens Research Hospital](https://www.stjude.org/) where my research focuses on host factors, especially nutrition, that affect the pathogenesis and evolution of influenza virus and enteric viruses.

My name is Christopher Small and I am the Head Data Scientist at [pol.is](https://pol.is/home) a startup applying data visualization and machine learning to making sense of large scale conversations. I also do distributed systems and web app development consulting as ThoughtNode Software. Before all that, I worked with Erick Matsen at [Fred Hutch Cancer Research Center](https://www.fredhutch.org/en.html), studying metagenomics and molecular viral epidemiology. 

Astroviruses are leading causes of diarrhea in children under the age of 2, immune-compromised populations and the elderly. You can get them from infected people but also through contaminated food and water. They also appear to be causing encephalitis in high-risk populations. Although we knew that Astroviruses were found in lots of different birds and animals, we never thought human viruses could infect animals or vice versa. We thought infections were species-specific (i.e. only human viruses could infect humans). That changed in 2009 when we began finding viruses in humans that were genetically more similar to animal viruses.

Thats where our recent publication titled [Non-Human Primates Harbor Diverse Mammalian and Avian Astroviruses Including Those Associated with Human Infections](http://journals.plos.org/plospathogens/article?id=10.1371/journal.ppat.1005225) in [PLOS Pathogens](http://journals.plos.org/plospathogens/) provided important new data. For the study, we sampled 879 urban, temple, captive and wild primates in Bangladesh and Cambodia. We found that 8% of primates were infected with diverse mammalian and avian Astroviruses, including those previously only known to infect humans. Clearly this exemplifies One Health and how infectious diseases of humans can impact animals we contact and potentially vice versa.

We will be answering your questions about primates and Astroviruses at 1pm ET -- Ask Us Anything! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> PLOS Science Wednesday: Hi Reddit, were Drs. Yamey, Morel, Hotez, Kruk, and Swaminathan. We wrote the PLOS Grand Convergence Collection, which outlines a path for achieving dramatic global health gains by 2035  Ask Us Anything! </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-06 13:30:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hi Reddit,

We are Gavin Yamey, Carlos Morel, Peter Hotez, Margaret Kruk, and Soumya Swaminathan, global health researchers who co-authored the [PLOS Grand Convergence Collection](http://collections.plos.org/grand-convergence). In the Collection, we show how strategic investments in research and development, as well as aggressive scale-up of health-care delivery systems to implement existing health tools and services, can lead to a dramatic reduction in the global burden of disease by 2035. The collection focuses on five conditions that disproportionately affect the worlds poorest people: HIV/AIDS, tuberculosis (TB), malaria, maternal and child mortality, and neglected tropical diseases (NTDs). Our introductions are included below.

My name is [Gavin Yamey](http://globalhealth.duke.edu/) and I am a Professor of the Practice of Global Health and Public Policy at Duke University. My research focuses on large scale questions in global health, such as the best ways to finance and deliver global health interventions. And my name is [Carlos Morel](http://www.dndi.org/about-dndi/friends-of-dndi/carlos-medicis-morel/) and I am the Director of the Center for Technological Development in Health (CDTS in its Portuguese acronym) at the [Oswaldo Cruz Foundation (Fiocruz)](http://portal.fiocruz.br/en/content/home-ingl%C3%AAs), an institution with headquarters in Rio de Janeiro affiliated to the Brazilian Ministry of Health. My research focuses on the role of translational sciences in developing new tools for the prevention, control and treatment of NTDs.

We recently coordinated a special collection of nine papers across three PLOS journals [PLOS Biology]( http://journals.plos.org/plosbiology/), [PLOS Medicine](http://journals.plos.org/plosmedicine/), [PLOS Neglected Diseases](http://journals.plos.org/plosntds/) called [Grand Convergence: Aligning Technologies   Realities in Global Health](http://collections.plos.org/grand-convergence). Grand convergence means reducing infectious, maternal, and child deaths down to universally low levels. [The Lancet Commission on Investing in Health](http://www.GlobalHealth2035.org) showed that grand convergence could be achieved by 2035 provided that new health technologies are discovered and delivered to those who most need them. Additional Collection authors and AMA participants are introduced below.

My name is [Margaret Kruk](http://www.hsph.harvard.edu/margaret-kruk/) and I am an Associate Professor of Global Health at the [Harvard T.H. Chan School of Public Health](http://www.hsph.harvard.edu/). My research focuses on the quality and responsiveness of health systems in low and middle income countries. My contribution to the Collection was a [PLOS Biology](http://journals.plos.org/plosbiology) paper titled [Transforming Global Health by Improving the Science of Scale Up](http://journals.plos.org/plosbiology/article?id=10.1371/journal.pbio.1002360). In the paper, we advocate for increased policy and implementation research in order to produce generalizable evidence on what works to implement successful health interventions at scale. We also propose a priority research agenda to support the goal of reducing infectious, child and maternal mortality rates and supporting universal health coverage in low and middle income countries.

My name is Peter Hotez and I am Dean of the [National School of Tropical Medicine at Baylor College of Medicine](https://www.bcm.edu/education/schools/national-school-of-tropical-medicine) and founding editor-in-chief of [PLOS Neglected Tropical Diseases](http://journals.plos.org/plosntds/). My contribution to the Collection was a [PLOS NTDs ](http://journals.plos.org/plosntds/) paper titled [Eliminating the Neglected Tropical Diseases: Translational Science and New Technologies](http://journals.plos.org/plosntds/article?id=10.1371/journal.pntd.0003895), where we summarize some of the key challenges in translational science to develop and implement new technologies to successfully eliminate NTDs globally.

My name is Soumya Swaminathan and I am Secretary of the Department of Health Research for the [Ministry of Health and Family Welfare in India](http://www.mohfw.nic.in/), and Director General of the [Indian Council of Medical Research](http://www.icmr.nic.in/). My research focuses on pediatric and adult tuberculosis, epidemiology and pathogenesis, the role of nutrition, and HIV-associated TB. My contribution to the Collection was a [PLOS Medicine](http://journals.plos.org/plosmedicine) paper entitled [Translational Research for Tuberculosis Elimination: Priorities, Challenges, and Actions](http://journals.plos.org/plosmedicine/article?id=10.1371/journal.pmed.1001965).  We argue that achieving the WHO End TB Strategy will only be possible through the development and rapid uptake of new tools, including rapid point-of-care diagnostics, safe and shorter treatment of latent TB infection and disease, and an efficacious TB vaccine, combined with efficient health systems and care provision, and actions on the social determinants of TB. We advocate for enhancing research along the full spectrum, from basic to implementation, and strengthening research capacity, particularly in low- and middle-income countries severely affected by the TB epidemics, is crucial for TB elimination.

We will be answering your questions at 1pm ET -- Ask Us Anything!

You can follow us on Twitter [@cmmorel](https://twitter.com/cmmorel), [@gyamey]( https://twitter.com/GYamey), [@mkruk](https://twitter.com/mkruk), [@PeterHotez](https://twitter.com/PeterHotez), and [@doctorsoumya](https://twitter.com/doctorsoumya). </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> PLOS Science Wednesday: Hi Reddit, were Michael Emerman and Lucie Etienne, and our PLOS Pathogens research looks at the role of host genes in preventing (or not) cross-species transmission of viruses related to HIV  Ask Us Anything! </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-30 14:15:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> PLOS Science Wednesday: Hi Reddit, were Michael Emerman and Lucie Etienne, and our PLOS Pathogens research looks at the role of host genes in preventing (or not) cross-species transmission of viruses related to HIV  Ask Us Anything! </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-30 13:31:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hi Reddit,

We are Michael Emerman and Lucie Etienne. [Michael](http://research.fhcrc.org/emerman/en.html) is a Full Member at the [Fred Hutchinson Cancer Research Center](https://www.fredhutch.org/en.html) in Seattle, WA, and [Lucie](https://lsetienne.wordpress.com/) is an Assistant Professor at the [International Center of Infectiology Research](http://ciri.inserm.fr/en/) in Lyon, France. Our research focuses on the evolutionary battle between viruses and their hosts with an emphasis on viruses such as HIV.  We study how viruses evolve to infect new hosts by neutralizing some of the host defense proteins.

We recently published a paper in [PLOS Pathogens](http://journals.plos.org/plospathogens) entitled [The Role of the Antiviral APOBEC3 Gene Family in Protecting Chimpanzees against Lentiviruses from Monkeys](http://journals.plos.org/plospathogens/article?id=10.1371/journal.ppat.1005149). In this study, we wondered why chimpanzees are not infected by more viruses like HIV since they eat many monkeys that harbor similar viruses, called SIVs. We found that a protein in the chimpanzee called APOBEC3G may protect them from infection because the SIVs from monkeys are not capable of overcoming its antiviral effects. The actions of APOBEC3G and its interactions with the viral proteins also help understand better the ancient origins of HIV.

We will be answering your questions at 1pm ET -- Ask Us Anything! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> PLOS Science Wednesday: Hi Reddit, my name is Wan Yang, and I developed a forecast system that predicted the timing and magnitude of flu epidemics in Hong Kong -- Ask Me Anything! </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-23 12:20:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hi Reddit,


My name is [Wan Yang](https://sites.google.com/site/wanyangblog/), and I am an Associate Research Scientist at Columbia Universitys [Mailman School of Public Health](https://www.mailman.columbia.edu/). I use mathematical and statistical methods to study how infectious diseases (e.g. influenza and Ebola) spread through populations and develop methods to predict them.


My colleagues and I published a paper, ["Forecasting Influenza Epidemics in Hong Kong"](http://journals.plos.org/ploscompbiol/article?id=10.1371/journal.pcbi.1004383) in the journal [PLOS Computational Biology](http://journals.plos.org/ploscompbiol/). Hong Kong has a humid subtropical climate and is a known global epicenter for flu. Unlike the U.S., where flu is seasonal, the timing of flu outbreaks in Hong Kong and similar climates is highly irregularmaking prediction particularly challenging. Using data from 1998 to 2013, we developed two forecast systems for Hong Kong. We were able to predict the timing and magnitude of flu epidemics and the 2009 pandemic with accuracy near that achieved for the U.S.http://cpid.iri.columbia.edu/ Our findings suggest that forecast of irregular infectious disease epidemics (e.g. the flu epidemics in Hong Kong) is possible.


I will be answering your questions at 1pm ET, AMA!

EDIT: Hello, everyone! I'm gonna start answering questions now :)

EDIT: Thanks everyone for the great questions!  I had a great time answering them.  Now I'm signing off.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> PLOS Science Wednesday: Hi Reddit, my name is Pedro Afonso and I recently published a paper in PLOS ONE that showed changes in sea surface temperature can predict whale shark habitat use patterns  Ask Me Anything! </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-16 13:15:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> PLOS Science Wednesday: Hi Reddit, my name is Pedro Afonso and I recently published a paper in PLOS ONE that showed changes in sea surface temperature can predict whale shark habitat use patterns  Ask Me Anything! </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-16 12:09:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hi Reddit,

My name is Pedro Afonso, and I am a senior researcher at the [Institute of Marine Research]( http://www.horta.uac.pt/intradop/index.php/contactos-topmenu2-180/65-utilidades/personal-pages/1406-pedro-afonso) and MARE - Marine and Environmental Sciences Centre, both based at the [University of the Azores](http://www.horta.uac.pt/). I recently published a paper in [PLOS ONE](http://journals.plos.org/plosone) entitled [Dynamics of Whale Shark Occurrence at Their Fringe Oceanic Habitat](http://journals.plos.org/plosone/article?id=10.1371/journal.pone.0102060), where we investigated the patterns of occurrence of whale sharks over the mid north Atlantic ridge. Using 16 years of observational data from a pole-and-line fishery across the Azores and GAM models, we investigated the spatial and temporal patterns of whale shark occurrence in relation to oceanographic features. Our study found that whale shark sightings in this oceanic region increased sharply in 2008, and that sea surface temperature helps predict whale shark occurrence in the region. Our research also showed that the Azores are at a thermal boundary for whale sharks, which can help explain the post-2007 increase in sightings and has further implications in the face of climate change.


I will be taking questions at 1pm ET  Ask Me Anything! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> PLOS Science Wednesday: Hi Reddit, were Albert Ko, Manoel Sarno and Hugo Ribeiro, we published a study in PLOS NTDS showing the Zika virus may be linked to stillbirth and other adverse outcomes in addition to microcephaly  Ask Us Anything! </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-09 13:15:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> My name is Albert Ko and I am a professor at [Yale School of Public Health](https://publichealth.yale.edu/people/albert_ko.profile) and a collaborating researcher at [Fundao Oswaldo Cruz, Brazilian Ministry of Health](http://portal.fiocruz.br/en/content/home-ingl%C3%AAs). My research focuses on identifying solutions for health problems that have emerged as a consequence of rapid urbanization, social inequity and the growth of slum settlements and I am part of a team that has been investigating the outbreak of microcephaly in the city of Salvador, Brazil. Today I am joined by Dr. Manoel Sarno, the lead investigator on the study and doctor at the State Department of Health in Bahia, Salvador in Brazil; and our colleague Dr. Hugo Ribeiro, associate professor of Pediatrics at [Federal University of Bahia School of Medicine](https://www.ufba.br/), chief of the Fima Lifshitz Research Center at the University Hospital at Federal University of Bahia and also the executive director of Roberto Santos General Hospital, in Salvador, Bahia in Brazil.


We recently published a study, entitled [Zika Virus Infection and Stillbirths: A Case of Hydrops Fetalis, Hydranencephaly and Fetal Demise](http://journals.plos.org/plosntds/article?id=10.1371/journal.pntd.0004517), in [PLOS Neglected Tropical Diseases](http://journals.plos.org/plosntds). This study, conducted in Brazil, detected Zika virus in a stillborn fetus that had developed hydrops fetalis, a condition characterized by abnormal accumulation of fluid, and severe central nervous system defects including microcephaly. The case provides supportive evidence for a potential link between Zika virus and brain defects.  In addition, the findings suggest that the virus may affect other tissues and may lead to fetal demise. Given the recent spread of the virus in the Americas, systematic investigation of spontaneous abortions and stillbirths may be warranted to evaluate the risk that Zika virus infection imparts on these outcomes.


This study and more Zika research can be found in the [PLOS Zika Collection](http://collections.plos.org/zika).


Well be answering questions at 1pm ET (10am PST, 3pm in Brazil) -- Ask us anything about the Zika virus, its recent emergence in the Americas, and its potential association with congenital defects. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> PLOS Science Wednesday: I'm Alexander Suh, my paper in PLOS Biology evaluates the evolutionary signature of modern birds and discovered extreme degrees of complex conflict at onset of the big bang of modern birds, when speciation of birds began rapidly after dinosaur extinction  Ask Me Anything! </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-02 13:15:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hi Reddit,

My name is Alexander Suh and I am a postdoctoral researcher at [Uppsala University](http://katalog.uu.se/profile/?id=N12-1893_1) in Sweden. My research focuses on the evolution of birds and their genomic parasites, such as transposons and viruses.

We recently published a study in [PLOS Biology](http://journals.plos.org/plosbiology) titled [The dynamics of incomplete lineage sorting across the ancient adaptive radiation of neoavian birds](http://journals.plos.org/plosbiology/article?id=10.1371/journal.pbio.1002224). There we analyzed the evolutionary signature of what some call the big bang of modern birds, a rapid succession of speciation events following the extinction of dinosaurs.

We used ancient retrotransposon insertions from 48 bird genomes to reconstruct evolutionary relationships, showing that most of the bird Tree of Life can be reliably resolved by our study and previous studies. However, we were surprised to find that the very onset of the big bang of modern birds harbors extreme degrees of conflict. In fact, the conflicts are so complex that they look more like a network than a tree. Our explanation for this complexity is that bird speciation in the direct aftermath of dinosaur extinction was extremely rapid, potentially too rapid to be resolvable as a single tree.

I will be answering your questions at 1 pm EST (10am PST, 7 pm CET). Ask Me About Birds, Transposons, Anything!

Dont forget to follow me on Twitter [@alexander_suh](https://twitter.com/alexander_suh) and visit my [website](http://genomicrocosm.wordpress.com). </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> PLOS Science Wednesday:My name is Dr. Sanjay Basu, I published two articles in PLOS Medicine modeling methods for preventing type 2 diabetes in India, including a hypothetical tax on sugar-sweetened beverages and assessing the effectiveness of community diabetes screenings, Ask Me Anything </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-24 13:15:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hi Reddit,

My name is Dr. Sanjay Basu, a physician and epidemiologist at [Stanford University](https://med.stanford.edu/profiles/sanjay-basu) working on the prevention and treatment of type 2 diabetes and cardiovascular disease worldwide. I recently published two articles in [PLOS Medicine](http://journals.plos.org/plosmedicine) that focus on diabetes prevention. In ["The Health System and Population Health Implications of Large-Scale Diabetes Screening in India:  A Microsimulation Model of Alternative Approaches"](http://journals.plos.org/plosmedicine/article?id=10.1371/journal.pmed.1001827) we found that large-scale community-based screenings in India are likely to produce a large number of false-positive results, particularly if using the currently available screening instruments. In [Averting Obesity and Type 2 Diabetes in India through Sugar-Sweetened Beverage Taxation: An Economic-Epidemiologic Modeling Study](http://journals.plos.org/plosmedicine/article?id=10.1371/journal.pmed.1001582) we developed an economic-epidemiologic model that found introducing sustained taxation on sugar sweetened beverages could mitigate the increasing rate of obesity and type 2 diabetes in India. We found that given current consumption patterns, the relative effect of SSB taxes would be expected among both urban and rural populations in India. This is important in light of the increasing global prevalence of type 2 diabetes; the WHO estimates that in 2014 the global prevalence of diabetes (of all types) was already 9% among adults aged 18+ years.

In recognition that a focus on prevention is critical to addressing climbing diabetes rates globally, [PLOS Medicine](http://journals.plos.org/plosmedicine) has called for papers on diabetes prevention for a special issue. Publishing research on diabetes prevention is a top priority for PLOS Medicine, but to be considered for this special issue, all submissions are due on March 4 2016. To learn more about submitting your research, [read the Speaking of Medicine post](http://blogs.plos.org/speakingofmedicine/2016/01/19/the-future-of-diabetes-prevention-a-call-for-papers/).

I will be answering your questions at 1pm ET (10am PT, 6 pm UTC)  Ask Me Anything! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> PLOS Science Wednesday: Hi Reddit, were Dr. Sarah Myhre and Kate Davis, authors of a paper in PLOS ONE that finds that oxygen declined in the ocean during the deglaciation, a period of warming with analogues to anthropogenic climate change Ask Us Anything! </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-17 13:30:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hi Reddit,

My name is Dr. Sarah E. (Moffitt) Myhre and I am postdoctoral scholar at the [University of Washington](http://ice.washington.edu/). My research focuses on understanding the consequences of abrupt climate warming to marine ecosystems. And my name is Kate Davis and I am graduate researcher at the [University of California, Davis](http://geology.ucdavis.edu/index.php). My research focuses on the use of microfossils in reconstructing past marine environments.

We recently published a paper titled [Paleoceanographic Insights on Recent Oxygen Minimum Zone Expansion: Lessons for Modern Oceanography](http://journals.plos.org/plosone/article?id=10.1371/journal.pone.0115246) in [PLOS ONE](http://journals.plos.org/plosone). Oxygen Minimum Zones are natural features in many ocean basins, where they have profound effects for marine life, which are currently expanding in response to changes in global climate. In this study, we looked at records of Oxygen Minimum Zone change during the last period of rapid climate change  the last deglaciation.

Were here to talk about how oceans lose oxygen during events of global-scale climate warming and why this is really important to marine life. Past events of climate warming reveal that capacity of ocean systems to dramatically reorganize to states that have never existed in human history. Please ask us questions about climate change, oceanography and marine ecology!

We will be answering question at 1pm ET (10 am PT, 6 pm UTC) -- Ask Us Anything!

And, dont forget to follow Sarah and Kate on Twitter to continue the conversation: [@SarahEMyhre](https://twitter.com/SarahEMyhre)   [@seavdavis](https://twitter.com/seavdavis). </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> PLOS Science Wednesday: Hi Reddit, were Dr. Claudia Denkinger and Dr. David Dowdy. We published a study in PLOS ONE modeling tuberculosis transmission in a high-population setting using different strategies for drug resistance testing  Ask Us Anything! </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-10 13:15:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hi Reddit,

My name is Dr. Claudia Denkinger and I am a lecturer at [Harvard Medical School](http://hms.harvard.edu/) and the Head of the [Tuberculosis and Hepatitis Programme at FIND](http://www.finddiagnostics.org/about/who_we_are/team/denkinger.html). FIND is a non-for-profit organization in Geneva that is working to provide diagnostic solutions for patients in resource poor settings.

And my name is Dr. David Dowdy and I am an Associate Professor of Epidemiology at the [Johns Hopkins Bloomberg School of Public Health](http://www.jhsph.edu/faculty/directory/profile/5157/david-dowdy). My research focuses on the population-level dynamics of tuberculosis - including drug-resistant tuberculosis - in high-burden settings.

We recently published a paper entitled, ["Do we need to detect isoniazid resistance in addition to rifampicin resistance in diagnostic tests for tuberculosis?"](http://journals.plos.org/plosone/article?id=10.1371/journal.pone.0084197) in [PLOS ONE](http://journals.plos.org/plosone/). In this paper, we constructed a mathematical model of tuberculosis transmission in a population similar to that of India, in order to evaluate the effects of different strategies for drug resistance testing on the future of the drug-resistant TB epidemic. We specifically looked at testing for rifampicin and isoniazid - the two most important first-line TB drugs - and we found that testing for isoniazid did not provide much additional benefit on top of testing for rifampicin. These results have been important for developing policy related to resistance testing for TB, as well as our understanding of long-term dynamics of resistance to different drugs against TB.

We will be answering your questions at 1pm EST (10 am PST, 6 pm UTC), were looking forward to the conversation! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> PLOS Science Wednesday: I'm Dr. Peter McCormick, I published a study in PLOS Biology showing that the beneficial effects of Delta-9-tetrahydrocannabinol (THC), can be separated from the negative cognitive side effects  Ask Me Anything! </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-03 13:15:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> PLOS Science Wednesday: Hi Reddit, were Ru Daros, Joo Costa, Marina von Keyserlingk, Maria Htzel, Heather Neave and Daniel Weary. We recently published a study in PLOS ONE that found dairy calves experience emotional effects when undergoing routine procedures, such dehorning  Ask Us Anything! </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-27 13:15:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hi Reddit,

Our names are Ru Daros, Joo Costa, Marina von Keyserlingk, Maria Htzel, Heather Neave and Daniel Weary. We are researchers from the [University of British Columbia](https://www.ubc.ca/) in Canada and the [Universidade Federal de Santa Catarina](http://en.ufsc.br/) in Brazil. Our research focuses on animal welfare, how to use changes in behaviour to make inferences about the quality of life that animals experience.

We recently published a study entitled ["Separation from the Dam Causes Negative Judgement Bias in Dairy Calves](http://journals.plos.org/plosone/article?id=10.1371/journal.pone.0098429) in [PLOS ONE]( http://journals.plos.org/plosone/).

Young farm animals, including dairy calves, are often separated from the dam far earlier than what occurs under natural conditions. Farms animals are also sometimes subjected to painful procedures like hot-iron dehorning. The aim of this study was to better understand the effects of these routine procedures on the emotions of animals. One way to investigate mood states is to look for evidence of judgement biases. We tested for cognitive biases in calves before and after separation from the cow and dehorning, and found diminished responding to intermediate, ambiguous stimuli (evidence of a pessimistic response) following both physical pain and social loss. This paper illustrates one approach to investigating emotional states in animals, and draws parallels in the emotional experience of physical and social pain.

We will be online at 1pm EST (10am PST), and we look forward to hearing your questions about our work!

Please also follow us in Twitter [@ubcAWP](https://twitter.com/ubcAWP). </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> PLOS Science Wednesday: Were Nicholas Heintz, Brian Cunniff, and Kim Nelson, and we recently published a PLOS ONE study showing that selective targeting of two related antioxidant enzymes causes mesothelioma cancer cells to choke on their own oxidative exhaust  Ask Us Anything! </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-20 13:30:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hi Reddit,

My name is Nicholas Heintz and I am a Professor of Pathology at the [University of Vermont Cancer Center](http://www.uvm.edu/medicine/vtcancercenter/). My research has focused on dysregulation of redox signaling in cancer cells, and how the enhanced production of reactive oxygen species (ROS) in tumor cell mitochondria can be exploited for therapeutic purposes in aggressive human malignancies like mesothelioma. My coauthors Brian Cunniff (a former graduate student in my lab), and Kim Nelson (a postdoctoral fellow at Wake Forest) are joining me for this AMA.

My name is Brian Cunniff and I am a Postdoctoral Research Fellow at [Harvard Medical School](https://hms.harvard.edu/). My research focuses on intracellular trafficking, specifically clathrin mediated endocytosis, during cell migration and tissue organization. Using cutting-edge lattice light sheet microscopy we are able to visualize cellular processes with unprecedented spatial and temporal resolution.

My name is Kim Nelson and I am junior faculty in the Chemistry Department at [Wake Forest University](http://college.wfu.edu/chemistry/). I have been part of a highly collaborative, interdisciplinary team of researchers at Wake Forest who are focused on elucidating how reactive oxygen species are produced in a regulated manner as part of cell signaling events involved in growth, cell division, and cell death. My research has focused on 1) the kinetic, biophysical, and structural analysis of features in the peroxiredoxin family of proteins that modulate their rapid reaction with peroxide and 2) the identification, visualization, and biochemical analysis of proteins that are functionally modified by cysteine oxidation in response to regulated, intracellular hydrogen peroxide production. Along with Todd Lowther, my contribution to this study was in utilizing structural, kinetics and mass spectrometry analyses to characterize the mechanism by which thiostrepton directly associated with and inhibited the activity of purified human Peroxiredoxin 3.

We recently published a research study titled [Disabling mitochondrial peroxide metabolism via combinatorial targeting of peroxiredoxin 3 as an effective therapeutic approach for malignant mesothelioma](http://journals.plos.org/plosone/article?id=10.1371/journal.pone.0127310) in [PLOS ONE](http://journals.plos.org/plosone). In this paper we show that the thiazole antibiotic thiostrepton covalently crosslinks the antioxidant protein peroxiredoxin 3, thereby inactivating its activity. Since peroxiredoxin 3 is largely responsible for metabolizing the copious amounts of ROS produced by mitochondria in human mesothelioma cells, inactivation induces intolerable levels of mitochondrial oxidative stress and tumor cell death. When paired with gentian violet, which blocks expression of another antioxidant enzyme in the peroxiredoxin 3 pathway, thiostrepton markedly inhibits tumor growth in mouse models of human mesothelioma.

This work extends our previous observations published in PLOS ONE, [Peroxiredoxin 3 is a redox-dependent target of thiostrepton in malignant mesothelioma cells](http://journals.plos.org/plosone/article?id=10.1371/journal.pone.0039404); which showed that the activity of thiostrepton is dependent on the redox state of the cell, thereby explaining the preferential effects of the drug on highly malignant tumor cells that commonly produce large amounts of ROS. Our paper, along with many other recent studies, identifies pro-oxidant therapeutic approaches as viable treatments for intractable tumors.

We will be answering your questions at 1 pm ET (10am PST, 6 pm UTC) -- Ask Us Anything! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> PLOS Science Wednesday: Hi Reddit, were Malcolm MacLeod and David Howells, and we published a paper in PLOS Biology that found an elevated average risk of bias in work from leading institutions or work published in high-impact factor journals  Ask Us Anything! </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-13 13:10:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hi Reddit,

My name is [Malcolm Macleod](http://www.ed.ac.uk/schools-departments/clinical-brain-sciences/people/principal-investigators/professor-malcolm-macleod) and I am Professor of Neurology and Translational Neuroscience at the [University of Edinburgh](http://www.ed.ac.uk/schools-departments/clinical-brain-sciences). Im interested in risks of bias in animal research, and how these might get in the way of the development of new drugs.

And my name is [David Howells](https://rmdb.research.utas.edu.au/public/rmdb/q/indiv_detail_warp_trans/12701) and I am Professor of Neuroscience and Brain Plasticity at the [University of Tasmania]( http://www.utas.edu.au/health/about-us/school-of-medicine). My research on stroke focuses on how we translate good ideas into solid bench science that might then survive the rigor of clinical trialing to provide treatments for brain diseases.

We recently published a study titled [Risks of bias in reports of in vivo research: A focus for improvement](http://journals.plos.org/plosbiology/article?id=10.1371/journal.pbio.1002273 ) in [PLOS Biology](http://journals.plos.org/plosbiology).

This study extends work across multiple neuroscience domains which highlights the risk of overestimation of the potential for translational success when studies fail to take measures to reduce the impact of bias. This study investigated whether this held true across a broader range of science and whether where the work was conducted or published influenced the risk of bias.

We already know that publications which do not describe certain design features which reduce the risk of bias (e.g. randomization, blinding) tend to exaggerate observed effects, at least in the neurosciences. We were interested to see whether this was the case more generally, and if this was different in journals with a high impact factor or in work from leading institutions. We found that nobody is doing particularly well but also that work from leading institutions or published in high impact factor journals was at greater than average risk of bias. We hope that scientists, institutions, journals, and funders will use these findings to help improve the process of drug discovery and development.

We will be answering your questions at 1pm EST (10am PST and 5am on 1/14/16 in Melbourne). Ask Us Anything! You can follow Malcolm on Twitter [@maclomaclee](https://twitter.com/Maclomaclee), and [@CAMARADES_](https://twitter.com/CAMARADES_) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> PLOS Science Wednesday: Were Christine Kreuder Johnson and Tierra Smiley Evans, from UC Davis. We developed an oral sampling technique to screen for pathogens in primates which allows researchers to samples previously missed primate populations- Ask Us Anything! </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-06 13:00:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hi Reddit! 

My name is Christine Kreuder Johnson, I am a Professor of Epidemiology at the University of California School of Veterinary Medicines [One Health Institute](http://www.vetmed.ucdavis.edu/ohi/). Joining me today is Tierra Smiley Evans, a veterinarian and graduate student in epidemiology at UC Davis who developed the primate sampling technique published recently in [PLOS NTDs](http://journals.plos.org/plosntds),  [Optimization of a Novel Non-invasive Oral Sampling Technique for Zoonotic Pathogen Surveillance in Nonhuman Primates](http://journals.plos.org/plosntds/article?id=10.1371/journal.pntd.0003813), that we will be discussing today.

CHRISTINE KREUDER JOHNSON  My research focuses on ecological processes that impact wildlife and public health. I am especially interested in finding new ways to investigate disease in endangered species and identifying One Health solutions for protecting human and animal health. Most recently, I work with a consortium of partners on USAIDs [Emerging Pandemic Threats PREDICT project](https://www.usaid.gov/news-information/fact-sheets/emerging-pandemic-threats-program) to develop global surveillance capabilities to detect infectious disease threats with pandemic potential. We focus on zoonotic viruses that spillover from animals to cause disease in humans and we work at the highest-risk interfaces around the world where new diseases are most likely to emerge.  Our published study [Spillover and Pandemic Properties of Zoonotic Viruses with High Host Plasticity](http://www.nature.com/articles/srep14830) highlights many of the epidemiologic circumstances promoting spillover, amplification, and spread of zoonotic viruses that we are investigating in order to direct interventions aimed at disease prevention.

TIERRA SMILEY EVANS  My research focuses on zoonotic disease transmission in human and non-human primate communities in Africa and Asia. I have conducted field research in Uganda, Rwanda, Nepal and Myanmar and I am particularly interested in developing non-invasive diagnostics for wildlife that can enable us to understand disease dynamics in these remote settings. Our recent [PLOS NTDS](http://journals.plos.org/plosntds/article?id=10.1371/journal.pntd.0003813) article describes a non-invasive sampling technique that involves distributing a rope for primates to chew on that can be retrieved and screened for pathogens that are present in the mouth. This method provides an alternative approach to anesthetizing wild primates to test for diseases and enables sampling of populations that otherwise would not be able to be sampled. Our methods can be applied to studies examining primates as sources of diseases that could affect humans in remote tropical settings.

Our study and its implications for public health is also discussed in a [post on the PLOS Student Blog](http://blogs.plos.org/thestudentblog/2015/09/11/wildanimals/).

We are looking forward to answering your questions at 1pm ET today  Ask Us Anything! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> PLOS Science Wednesday: Hi Reddit, my name is Jack L. Conrad and I published a paper in PLOS ONE about my discovery of a new fossil Babibasiliscus, which is the earliest known species of casquehead, also known as Jesus lizard  Ask Me Anything! </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-30 14:45:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> PLOS Science Wednesday: Hi Reddit, my name is Jack L. Conrad and I published a paper in PLOS ONE about my discovery of a new fossil Babibasiliscus, which is the earliest known species of casquehead, also known as Jesus lizard  Ask Me Anything! </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-30 13:34:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hi Reddit,

My name is Jack L. Conrad and I am an Assistant Professor at [NYIT College of Osteopathic Medicine](http://www.nyit.edu/medicine) and a Research Associate at the [American Museum of Natural History (AMNH)](http://www.amnh.org/). My research focuses on the evolution, morphology, and paleontology of modern and living snakes, amphisbaenians, mosasaurs, and other 'lizards' (Squamata). Squamates first appeared around 245 million years ago, have a good fossil record for the last 155 million years, and today include more than 9700 living species; that's alotta Squamata!

One of the most difficult problems in understanding squamate evolution is snake origins. We know that many branches of the lizard family tree lost their limbs -- there are limbess geckoes, limbless skinks, limbless cousins to the Komodo Dragon, etc. -- but we don't know from which branch of the lizard family tree snakes come. It's really become quite a headache, but also a fun area for investigation.

Studying this problem, and other areas of squamate evolution, leads scientists like myself to understanding other natural science questions and phenomena, including (but certainly not limited to): What was Earth like at various times in the past? Are there physical constraints on how big a lizard can be on land? In the seas? How did lizards move across the planet as they evolved over time?

I recently published a study titled ["A new Eocene casquehead lizard (Reptliia, Corytophanidae) from North America](http://journals.plos.org/plosone/article?id=10.1371/journal.pone.0127900) in [PLOS ONE](http://www.plosone.org/). This study described the earliest known species of casquehead, or Jesus lizard, known. Importantly, this animal lived in Wyoming when the planet was much warmer than it is now and because its modern relatives live only in the tropics, it raises questions about what might happen if our planet warmed up a few degrees.

I will be answering your questions at 1pm ET. Ask Me Anything! I love everything about reptiles and evolution. I may not have all of your answers, but I will certainly enjoy talking with you about all of your questions!

Dont forget to follow me on Twitter [@ammoskius](https://twitter.com/ammoskius). </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> PLOS Science Wednesday: Were Peter Dodds, Bill Gottesman, and Andy Reagan. We published a paper in PLOS ONE that constructed a model that can help establish an institutions gift-giving profiles and help organizations set fundraising goals  Ask Us Anything! </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-16 13:34:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hi Reddit!

My name is Andy Reagan and I am a PhD candidate at the [University of Vermont](http://www.uvm.edu). My research focuses on computational social dynamics: using big data to better understand language, happiness, and health. I am joined by Bill Gottesman, a designer and builder of [sundials](http://www.precisionsundials.com), and Dr. Peter Dodds, Director of the Vermont Complex Systems Center and a Professor in the Department of Mathematics and Statistics at the [University of Vermont (UVM)](http://www.uvm.edu). Dr.  Dodds teaches courses on the [principles of complex systems](http://www.uvm.edu/~pdodds/teaching/courses/300) and [complex networks](http://www.uvm.edu/~pdodds/teaching/courses/303) at UVM. His research covers complex systems and networks in general, with recent work focusing on social contagion, sociotechnical phenomena, happiness, language, and stories.

We recently published an article titled [Collective Philanthropy: Describing and Modeling the Ecology of Giving](http://www.plosone.org/article/info%3Adoi%2F10.1371%2Fjournal.pone.0098876)
in [PLOS ONE](http://www.plosone.org/). We found that philanthropic gifting appears to follow an approximate power-law size distribution, and detailed forms of gift-size distributions differ across but are relatively constant within charity categories. We showed how knowledge of gift-sized distributions may be used to assess an institution's gift-giving profile, to help set fundraising goals, and to design an institution-specific giving pyramid.

We will be answering your questions at 1pm EST (10am PST) on December 16 -- Ask Us Anything!

Follow Andy on Twitter [@andyreagan](https://twitter.com/andyreagan) for updates on PhD life and his black lab, Finn. Follow Dr. Dodds on Twitter [@peterdodds](https://twitter.com/peterdodds) and [visit his website]( http://www.uvm.edu/~pdodds/index.html) to learn more about his courses at UVM.

NOTE: PLOS author Bill Gottesman is answering questions under his reddit username, wgottesman.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> PLOS Science Wednesday: Hi Reddit, were Lara Aknin, Kiley Hamlin, and Elizabeth Dunn. We published a paper in PLOS ONE that found toddlers experience happiness when sharing with others, which is consistent with the findings that many people find generous acts rewarding  Ask Us Anything! </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-09 12:00:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hi Reddit,


My name is [Lara Aknin](http://members.psyc.sfu.ca/aknin) and I am an Assistant Professor of Social Psychology at [Simon Fraser University]( http://www.sfu.ca/). My research focuses on the relationship between generosity and happiness. I am [Kiley Hamlin](http://psych.ubc.ca/persons/kiley-hamlin/), and Im an Associate Professor of Developmental Psychology at the [University of British Columbia (UBC)]( https://www.ubc.ca/). My research focuses on the development of moral action and judgment in preverbal infants and toddlers. And I am [Elizabeth Dunn](http://psych.ubc.ca/persons/elizabeth-dunn/), a Professor of Social Psychology also at [UBC]( https://www.ubc.ca/). My research focuses on the factors that shape human happiness.


We recently published a paper titled [Giving Leads to Happiness in Young Children]( http://journals.plos.org/plosone/article?id=10.1371/journal.pone.0039211) in [PLOS ONE]( http://journals.plos.org/plosone). In this paper, we show that toddlers find giving treats to others more rewarding than receiving treats themselves. These findings support the idea that humans may have evolved to find giving rewarding.


We will be answering your questions at 1pm ET (10am PT)  Ask Us Anything!

NOTE: Lara, Kiley, and Elizabeth are sitting together to answer these questions and coming up with a collaborative response to inquiries.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> PLOS Science Wednesday: Hi Reddit, were Drs. Malika Ihle, Wolfgang Forstmeier and Prof. Bart Kempenaers, behavioural ecologists here to discuss the fitness benefits of love in birds  Ask Us Anything! </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-02 13:51:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hi Reddit,

I am [Dr. Malika Ihle](https://malikaihle.wordpress.com/) and I am currently a post doctorate researcher at the [University of Sheffield](http://www.sheffield.ac.uk/aps) in the UK. I conducted my PhD at the [Max Planck Institute for Ornithology (MPIO, Germany)](http://www.orn.mpg.de/en), under the great supervision of [Dr. Wolfgang Forstmeier](http://www.orn.mpg.de/409052/employee_page?c=660919 employee_id=26271) and [Prof Bart Kempenaers](http://www.orn.mpg.de/409052/employee_page?c=671278 employee_id=26312), who will both be joining me today! Prof. Bart Kempenaers is the director of the MPIO and head of the [Department of Behavioural Ecology and Evolutionary Genetics]( http://www.orn.mpg.de/2622/Department_Kempenaers); Dr. Wolfgang Forstmeier is a researcher in this department, principal investigator of the evolution of sexual behaviour in zebra finches.
We are all researching why and how female birds choose their partner, on what criteria, and also why some females are faithful to their partner while others are not.

We recently published an article titled [The fitness benefits of mate choice for compatibility in a socially monogamous species](http://journals.plos.org/plosbiology/article?id=10.1371/journal.pbio.1002248) in [PLOS Biology](http://journals.plos.org/plosbiology). We wanted to understand why female zebra finches differ in their mating preferences: do they pick compatible partners instead of high-quality ones?

We compared the reproductive success of birds that bred with their chosen partner, to the fitness of birds that were forced to pair with the chosen partner of another bird.

We found that individuals of chosen pairs had 37 percent more offspring than individuals of assigned pairs, not because they were genetically more compatible but because they were behaviourally more compatible: they were better at rearing chicks together. Individuals of chosen pairs were also more faithful to each other; females were more inclined to mate with their chosen partner, and males were more willing to invest into paternal care. Overall, it seems that each specific bird was, rather idiosyncratically, attracted and stimulated by their specific favourite mate, a phenomenon that some people might more commonly call love. In this case at least, love did have fitness consequences.

We will be answering your questions at 1pm EST (10am PST, 6pm UTC)   Ask Us Anything!

Want to read about all the interesting results in an inspiring literary form? Read the synopsis written by [PLOS Biology](http://journals.plos.org/plosbiology) editor Roland Robert: [The fitness benefits of love](http://journals.plos.org/plosbiology/article?id=info:doi/10.1371/journal.pbio.1002249).

Want to be able to explain the study to your friends, family or children? Read my [PLOSAble](https://askabiologist.asu.edu/plosable) article [Benefits of being choosy](https://askabiologist.asu.edu/plosable/benefits-being-choosy). </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> PLOS Science Wednesday: Were Tisha Wheeler and Elizabeth Mziray and were here to discuss our PLOS Collection that examines evidence-based solutions to curbing transmission of HIV and other STIs among sex workers  Ask Us Anything! </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-11-25 13:32:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hi Reddit, were Tisha Wheeler and Elizabeth Mziray, and we work at global health agencies that are leading the global response for key populations in the global HIV/AIDS epidemic.

My name is Tisha Wheeler, and I am a senior HIV/AIDS advisor for key populations at the [United States Agency for International Development (USAID)]( https://www.usaid.gov/), where I lead policy making, design, implementation, and evaluation of key populations HIV/AIDS programs. I am joined by Elizabeth Mziray, an operations officer with the [World Bank](http://www.worldbank.org/), where she supports countries in improving the efficiency and effectiveness of their HIV programs. She is the task team leader for the Banks technical support program in West and Central Africa that includes support for improving the scale, quality, targeting and coverage of HIV services for sex workers and their clients through integrated technical assistance and a capacity building program.

We are here to discuss a special [PLOS Collection](http://collections.plos.org) titled [Focus on Delivery   Scale: Achieving HIV Impact with Sex Workers]( http://collections.plos.org/achieving-hiv-impact). In our [collections overview](http://journals.plos.org/plosone/article?id=10.1371/journal.pone.0121145) published in [PLOS ONE](http://journals.plos.org/plosone) we highlight the evidence that shows protecting sex workers from HIV/STI  transmission is both necessary and feasible for controlling the epidemic. The eighteen papers published in this collection demonstrate the importance and scalability of existing interventions through four key themes: 1) epidemiology, data needs and modelling of sex work in generalized epidemics; 2) implementation science addressing practical aspects of intervention scale-up; 3) community mobilization and 4) the treatment cascade for sex workers living with HIV.

We will be answering your questions on Wednesday November 25 at 10am PST (1pm EST, 6 pm UTC)  Ask Us Anything!

NOTE: Richard Steen, first author on the PLOS Collection Overview, has joined the AMA from his medical mission in Tanzania.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> PLOS Science Wednesday: Hi Reddit, we're Dr. Bob Brewin, Dr. Lee de Mora, and Dr. Thomas Jackson, here to discuss our PLOS ONE paper investigating the potential of using recreational surfers as a means to collect sea-surface temperature data, Ask Us Anything! : science </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-11-18 18:30:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> PLOS Science Wednesday: Hi Reddit, we're Dr. Bob Brewin, Dr. Lee de Mora, and Dr. Thomas Jackson, here to discuss our PLOS ONE paper investigating the potential of using recreational surfers as a means to collect sea-surface temperature data, Ask Us Anything! </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-11-18 13:18:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> PLOS Science Wednesday: We're Drs. Albert Ko and Federico Costa; our PLOS Neglected Tropical Diseases paper examines the burden of leptospirosis, a disease that impacts urban slum dwellers and rural subsistence farmers, and projects the burden to rise with environmental conditions, Ask Us Anything! </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-11-11 14:00:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> PLOS Science Wednesday: We're Drs. Albert Ko and Federico Costa; our PLOS Neglected Tropical Diseases paper examines the burden of leptospirosis, a disease that impacts urban slum dwellers and rural subsistence farmers, and projects the burden to rise with environmental conditions, Ask Us Anything! </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-11-11 13:30:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hi Reddit,

My name is Albert Ko and I am a Professor at [Yale School of Public Health](https://publichealth.yale.edu/). My research focuses on identifying solutions for health problems that have emerged as a consequence of rapid urbanization, social inequity and the growth of slum settlements. I am joined by my colleague, Federico Costa, who is an Associate Professor at the [Universidade Federal da Bahia](https://www.ufba.br/) in Brazil. His research centers on how the ecology of the slum communities influences the disease emergence and transmission in such environments.

Federico and I recently published a study, titled ["Global Mortality and Morbidity of Leptospirosis: A Systematic Review"](http://journals.plos.org/plosntds/article?id=10.1371/journal.pntd.0003898), in [PLOS Neglected Tropical Diseases](http://journals.plos.org/plosntds). This study estimated the health burden caused by leptospirosis, a bacterial disease that is transmitted by rats, livestock and other animals in environments that lack basic sanitation. We found that leptospirosis accounts for one million cases and 60,000 deaths each year, most of which occur in regions where its impact on subsistence farmers, pastoralists and slum dwellers has been neglected. Furthermore, the burden of leptospirosis is projected to rise as the global expansion of shantytowns and climate change-associated extreme weather events create the environmental conditions for intensified transmission.

We invite you to ask questions about leptospirosis, and how changes in the worlds demographics and environment are creating new health challenges and neglected diseases which impart their greatest impact on vulnerable populations.

We'll be taking your questions  at 1pm ET (10 am PT, 6 pm UTC) -- Ask Us Anything!

NOTE from PLOS: Albert and Federico are presenting at a conference in Brazil today, and will answer questions as they are able, sometimes before or after the 1-2pm ET live chat hour.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> PLOS Science Wednesday: we're Jean-Michel Drezen, Salva Herrero, and Elisabeth Huguet. We discovered active genes derived from bracoviruses in the genomes of many moths and butterflies, which provide protection against some infections  Ask Us Anything! </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-11-04 14:15:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> PLOS Science Wednesday: we're Jean-Michel Drezen, Salva Herrero, and Elisabeth Huguet. We discovered active genes derived from bracoviruses in the genomes of many moths and butterflies, which provide protection against some infections  Ask Us Anything! </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-11-04 13:33:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hi Reddit,


My name is Jean-Michel Drezen and I am the Research Director (CNRS, French research agency) at the [Research Institute on Insect Biology (University of Tours, France)](http://international.univ-tours.fr/institute-of-research-on-insect-biology-irbi--283147.kjsp). My research focuses on symbiotic viruses associated with parasitic wasps named bracoviruses. Parasitic wasps reproduce by injecting their eggs inside caterpillars on which wasp larvae feed. Together with the eggs wasps also inject bracovirus particles that induce immune suppression and control caterpillar development, enabling wasp larvae to colonize their host.


Together with me is Salva Herrero, Associate Professor at the [University of Valencia, Spain](http://www.uv.es/uvweb/college/en/university-valencia-1285845048380.html). His research focuses on understanding the interaction of insects with their viral and bacterial pathogens. We have also with us Elisabeth Huguet, Professor at the [ University of Tours](http://international.univ-tours.fr), her research is also on bracoviruses with more focus on their impact on host physiology.


We recently published a study titled [Recurrent Domestication by Lepidoptera of Genes from Their Parasites Mediated by Bracoviruses](http://journals.plos.org/plosgenetics/article?id=10.1371/journal.pgen.1005470), published in [PLOS Genetics](http://journals.plos.org/plosgenetics). In our study we have detected in the genomes of several species of butterflies and moths, including the famous Monarch (Danaus plexippus), the insertion of active genes derived from bracoviruses. Additional results have revealed that these genes can confer a certain protection against infections with other insect pathogenic viruses. Some of the genes have been previously acquired by the bracovirus from the wasp gene pool indicating that a gene flux exists between wasps and their caterpillar hosts. We think we are only seeing the tip of the iceberg and that in fact many lepidopteran species may have acquired genes via bracoviruses.


We will be answering your questions at 1pm ET, and hope this discussion will expand our views on the topic  Ask Us Anything! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> PLOS Science Wednesday: Hi Reddit, we're Oliver Cumming, Pinaki Panigrahi,   Yael Velleman and we're here to discuss how improved water, sanitation, and hygiene (WASH) programs will impact health outcomes for women and children globally  Ask Us Anything! </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-10-28 12:45:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hi Reddit,


I am Yael Velleman, a Senior Policy Analyst for Health   Hygiene at [WaterAid](http://www.wateraid.org/us). My work focuses on the links between water, sanitation and hygiene and health, and the implications for policy and programs.


I am Pinaki Panigrahi, a professor of Epidemiology, Pediatrics, and Environmental-Agricultural-and-Occupational Health at the [University of Nebraska Medical Center](http://www.unmc.edu), and also the Director of the [Center for Global Health and Development](http://www.unmc.edu/publichealth/cghad/) at the College of Public Health at University of Nebraska. My current research focus is to study the impact of environmental exposures on maternal and child health.


I am Oliver Cumming, a Lecturer in the Environmental Health in [Department of Disease Control](http://www.lshtm.ac.uk/itd/dcd) at the [London School of Hygiene and Tropical Medicine](http://www.lshtm.ac.uk). My research focuses on access to safe water, sanitation, and hygiene and its impacts on childhood health and development.


We recently published papers in [PLOS Medicine](http://journals.plos.org/plosmedicine/) examining the impacts of water and sanitation programs on public health.


In a paper titled "[From Joint Thinking to Joint Action: A Call to Action on Improving Water, Sanitation, and Hygiene for Maternal and Newborn Health](http://journals.plos.org/plosmedicine/article?id=10.1371/journal.pmed.1001771)," Yael and Oliver, in collaboration with several UN and academic agencies and institutions, set out the case for action on water, sanitation and hygiene for improving maternal and newborn health, and provided a set of policy recommendations.


In "[Risk of Adverse Pregnancy Outcomes among Women Practicing Poor Sanitation in Rural India: A Population-Based Prospective Cohort Study](http://journals.plos.org/plosmedicine/article?id=10.1371/journal.pmed.1001851)," Pinaki and colleagues found that open defecation led to more adverse pregnancy outcomes. The study enrolled more than 600 pregnant women and researchers tracked their sanitation practice during pregnancy. Those practicing open defecation had higher number of bad pregnancy outcomes, especially preterm births. Many other concomitant factors were also studied (apart from defecation practice), and against conventional wisdom, we did not find socioeconomic status to play any role in this, but the pregnant womans education did. More research is needed to identify changes that are induced by open defecation ultimately driving an unhealthy pregnancy.


We will be taking your questions about how WASH impacts global public health today at 1pm ET (10 am PT, 5 pm UTC)  Ask Us Anything!


And don't forget to follow Yael on Twitter at [@YaelVelleman](http://www.twitter.com/YaelVelleman). </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> PLOS Science Wednesday: Hi Reddit, we're Dr. John Ioannidis and Dr. Robert Kaplan, and we're here to discuss the importance of improved reporting in scholarly research for Open Access Week  Ask Us Anything! </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-10-21 14:00:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hi Reddit,


October 15  25 is [Open Access Week](http://openaccessweek.org/) and this year's theme is "Open For Collaboration". PLOS authors Dr. John Ioannidis and Dr. Robert M. Kaplan are leading this AMA to discuss how more comprehensive reporting in scientific research can lead to more study replication, stronger statistical methods, and improvements to scientific standards, all of which are hallmarks of open access publishing.


In ["How to Make More Published Research True"](http://journals.plos.org/plosmedicine/article?id=10.1371/journal.pmed.1001747), an essay in [PLOS Medicine](http://journals.plos.org/plosmedicine), Dr. John Ioannidis examined the factors behind false or exaggerated results in research and proposed solutions for improving the efficiency and value of scientific investigation.


Dr. Robert M. Kaplan co-authored a [PLOS One](http://journals.plos.org/plosone) study, ["Likelihood of Null Effects of Large NHLBI Clinical Trials Has Increased over Time"](http://journals.plos.org/plosone/article?id=10.1371/journal.pone.0132382), which found that the number of null findings increased after the [National Heart, Lung, and Blood Institute](http://www.nhlbi.nih.gov/) adopted more transparent reporting standards.


Here is a little more information about the participants for this week's PLOS Science Wednesday AMA:


Dr. John Ioannidis is one of the two Directors of [Meta-Research Innovation Center at Stanford](http://metrics.stanford.edu/). He also holds the C.F. Rehnborg Chair in Disease Prevention at [Stanford University](https://www.stanford.edu/), and he is Professor of Medicine, and of Health Research and Policy, and Director of the [Stanford Prevention Research Center](http://prevention.stanford.edu/) at the School of Medicine and Director of the PhD program in Epidemiology and Clinical Research as well as Professor of Statistics at Stanford University School of Humanities and Sciences. Dr. Ioannidis has served as member of the editorial board of more than 20 major journals and he is also a member of the [PLOS Medicine](http://journals.plos.org/plosmedicine) and [PLOS ONE](http://journals.plos.org/plosone) editorial boards. His work has already been cited over 85,000 times in the scientific literature and there are currently more than 1,500 new citations to his work every month. His 2005 [PLOS Medicine](http://journals.plos.org/plosmedicine) paper on "[Why most published research findings are false](http://journals.plos.org/plosmedicine/article?id=10.1371/journal.pmed.0020124)" has been accessed 1.5 million times.


Dr. Robert M. Kaplan served as Chief Science Officer at the [U.S. Agency for Healthcare Research and Quality (AHRQ)](http://www.ahrq.gov/) and Associate Director of the [National Institutes of Health](http://www.nih.gov/), where he led the behavioral and social sciences programs. He was formerly the Distinguished Professor of Health Services and Medicine at [University of California, Los Angeles](http://www.ucla.edu/), where he led the UCLA/RAND AHRQ health services training program and the UCLA/RAND CDC Prevention Research Center. He was Chair of the Department of Health Services from 2004 to 2009. From 1997 to 2004 he was Professor and Chair of the Department of Family and Preventive Medicine, at the [University of California, San Diego](https://ucsd.edu/). He is a past president of several organizations, including the American Psychological Association Division of Health Psychology, Section J of the American Association for the Advancement of Science (Pacific), the International Society for Quality of Life Research, the Society for Behavioral Medicine, and the Academy of Behavioral Medicine Research. Kaplan is a former Editor-in-Chief of [Health Psychology](http://www.apa.org/pubs/journals/hea/) and of the [Annals of Behavioral Medicine](http://www.springer.com/medicine/journal/12160). His 18 books and over 500 articles or chapters have been cited more than 28,000 times. Kaplan is a member of the [National Academy of Medicine](http://nam.edu/) (formerly the Institute of Medicine).


We will be taking your questions at 1pm ET (10 am PT, 5 pm UTC), Ask Us Anything! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> PLOS Science Wednesday: Hi Reddit, We're Ben Inglis and JB Poline, and we're here to discuss methods for fMRI acquisition and analysis  Ask Us Anything! </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-10-14 14:00:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hi Reddit,


We're Ben Inglis and JB Poline, two scientists who work at the [Brain Imaging Center (BIC)](http://bic.berkeley.edu/) at [UC Berkeley](http://www.berkeley.edu/).

I'm Ben, and I am the manager and physicist at the [Brain Imaging Center (BIC)](http://bic.berkeley.edu/). My research focuses on the use of MRI to study physiology and biochemistry in the brain and my primary responsibility is to assist BIC users in acquiring good functional MRI data. I was recently interviewed for the PLOS Neuro blog in a post called ["FMRI under the Microscope"](http://blogs.plos.org/neuro/2015/01/28/fmri-under-the-microscope-an-interview-with-mri-physicist-practical-fmri/). Using my own blog, [practiCal fMRI](http://practiCalfMRI.blogspot.com), I am trying to help improve fMRI acquisition methodology anywhere, including at Berkeley, through education. The Internet is an excellent medium for sharing tips on fMRI. My hope is that by accelerating the discourse via blogs and forums like AMA we will see an overall improvement in the quality of functional imaging studies.



My name is JB Poline and my research focuses on statistical analysis methods for brain imaging and brain imaging genetics, as well as neuroinformatics. I recently published a study titled ["Orthogonalization of Regressors in fMRI Models"](http://journals.plos.org/plosone/article?id=10.1371/journal.pone.0126255) in [PLOS One](http://journals.plos.org/plosone), which explained a common pitfall when using the linear model in fMRI analyses. More generally, I am interested in the reproducibility of fMRI and neuroimaging studies.

Follow Ben on Twitter [@practiCalfMRI](http://www.twitter.com/practiCalfMRI) and follow JB at [@jbpoline](http://www.twitter.com/jbpoline).


We will be answering your questions at 1pm ET (10 am PT, 5 pm UTC)  Ask Us Anything!

UPDATE: 10 pm PT - Ben will try to answer questions through the end of Thurs 15th, assuming the guest login continues to work. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> PLOS Science Wednesday: Hi Reddit, I'm Tom Kaye, here to talk about how my team uses laser fluorescence in our paleontology research, Ask Me Anything! </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-10-07 14:20:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hi Reddit!


I am Tom Kaye, Associate Researcher with the [Burke Museum](http://www.burkemuseum.org/) in Seattle, Washington. My research uses lasers to make fossils and minerals fluoresce in ways never seen before. My team recently published a paper in [PLOS ONE](http://journals.plos.org/plosone) titled [Laser-Stimulated Fluorescence in Paleontology](http://journals.plos.org/plosone/article?id=10.1371/journal.pone.0125923) where in one example we used our system to identify the origin of a bracelet that was placed around the arm of a 6,000 year old skeleton of a girl. We also demonstrated the use of laser fluorescence to automatically sort microfossils, its ability to back light feathers preserved as carbon films and light up micro-fossils that were normally invisible under the surface. We are also taking the laser underground and using it to fluoresce and photograph cave formations at great distances!

I hope to answer lots of interesting questions at the PLOS AMA at 1pm ET (10 am PT, 5 pm UTC), and you can follow my science adventures on [Facebook](https://www.facebook.com/tom.kaye.35).

See you all soon! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> PLOS Science Wednesday: Hi Reddit, I'm Zhengquan Yu, here to talk about my recent PLOS Genetics paper that has identified the key role of a microRNA in hair loss. I'm joined by Maksim Plikus, who studies stem cell regulation using hair follicles  Ask Us Anything! </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-09-30 14:00:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hi Reddit,


My name is Zhengquan Yu and I am an associate professor at the [China Agricultural University](http://www.cau.edu.cn/). Joining me in this AMA is my colleague, Maksim Plikus from the [University of California, Irvine](http://uci.edu/), who studies the principles and mechanisms of adult stem cell regulation using hair follicle as the primary model system.



My research focuses on regulatory network of somatic stem cells in hair follicle and mammary gland. We recently published a research article titled [Post-transcriptional Regulation of Keratinocyte Progenitor Cell Expansion, Differentiation and Hair Follicle Regression by miR-22](http://journals.plos.org/plosgenetics/article?id=10.1371/journal.pgen.1005253) in [PLOS Genetics](http://journals.plos.org/plosgenetics). We describe an essential role for a highly conserved microRNA, miR-22, in regulating the regression of mouse hair follicles. We found that increasing miR-22 results in hair loss in mice due to the premature regression of follicles, and that silencing of keratin-mediated hair shaft assembly by miR-22 is a prerequisite for follicle regression. There are hundreds of microRNAs expressed in hair follicles, but most of them are not well studied. This paper highlights the importance of determining the combinatorial effects of the microRNA regulatory network in hair cycling and provides new insights into the mechanism of premature hair follicle regression in understanding the pathology of hair loss.





We will be answering your questions at 1pm ET (10 am PT, 5 pm UTC), Ask Us Anything! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> PLOS Science Wednesday: Hi Reddit! Im David Frayer, here to talk about my PLOS ONE paper that found Neandertals created jewelry from eagle talons  Ask Me Anything! </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-09-23 14:00:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hi Reddit,

My name is David Frayer and I am a retired professor at the [University of Kansas](https://anthropology.ku.edu/david-w-frayer). My research focuses on paleoanthropology, with an emphasis on later European human evolution and, most recently, on the relationship between Neandertals and the humans that followed them.



I recently published an article with three Croatian colleagues (Davorka Radovi, Ankica Oros Sren   Jakov Radovi) titled [Evidence for Neandertal Jewelry: Modified White-Tailed Eagle Claws at Krapina](http://journals.plos.org/plosone/article?id=10.1371/journal.pone.0119802) in [PLOS ONE](http://journals.plos.org/plosone). The study documents eight talons and a foot bone from the [Krapina Neandertal](https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Krapina) site in Croatia, dated at 130,000 years ago. These elements bear cut marks, highly polished areas on some talons and a dull sheen on their sides indicating that Neandertals assembled them into jewelry. These talons, along with other paleocultural evidence, provide multiple new lines of evidence for Neandertals abilities and cultural sophistication.



I will be answering your questions at 1pm ET (10 am PT, 5 pm UTC), Ask Me Anything! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> PLOS Science Wednesday: We're Laura Pollitt and Andrew Read, and we found that mosquitoes can harbor multiple infections of the malaria parasite at once and transmit a double-dose of malaria infection, Ask Us Anything! </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-09-16 14:00:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hi Reddit,


My name is Laura Pollitt and I am a research fellow in the [Centre for Immunity, Infection and Evolution](http://ciie.bio.ed.ac.uk/) at the [University of Edinburgh](http://www.ed.ac.uk/home). Joining me is Andrew Read who is the director of the [Center for Infectious Disease Dynamics](http://www.cidd.psu.edu/) at [Pennsylvania State University](http://www.psu.edu/).


Andrew is interested in applying an evolutionary approach to medical problems, a field sometimes referred to as evolutionary medicine. He has worked on various disease systems but is best known for his work on malaria where he has looked for solutions to the rising problem of drug resistance in the parasites that cause the disease and insecticide resistance in the mosquitoes that transmit the parasites.


Laura is interested in how different strains of malaria parasites interact within infections across the whole of their life cycle. In particular, what impact this has on parasite evolution and transmission.


Along with other colleagues, we recently published a study titled [Existing infection facilitates establishment and density of malaria parasites in the mosquito vector](http://journals.plos.org/plospathogens/article?id=10.1371/journal.ppat.1005003) in [PLOS Pathogens](http://journals.plos.org/plospathogens). Very little is known about how malaria parasite strains interact with each other inside mosquitoes. In this study, we show that mosquitoes that have already been infected with one strain of malaria parasites are more likely to become infected with a new strain. Moreover, the presence of an existing infection enhances the replication of malaria parasites with no obvious impact on mosquito survival.


We will be answering your questions at 1pm ET (10 am PT, 5 pm UTC).  Ask Us Anything!


Dont forget to follow Laura on Twitter [@LauraCPollitt](https://twitter.com/lauracpollitt) and the Center for Infectious Disease Dynamics at Penn State [@ciddpsu](https://twitter.com/ciddpsu). </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> PLOS Science Wednesdays: Hi, Im Stuart Kim here to talk about gene sequencing the worlds oldest people to unlock the secrets of human longevity, AMA! </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-09-09 14:00:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hi Reddit,

My name is [Dr. Stuart Kim]( https://chemsysbio.stanford.edu/faculty-profiles/kim-stuart/) and I am professor at [Stanford University]( https://www.stanford.edu/). My research focuses on genes that contribute to extreme longevity, such as supercentenarians that live to be over 110 years.

I recently published a study titled [Whole Genome Sequencing of the World's Oldest People](http://journals.plos.org/plosone/article?id=10.1371/journal.pone.0112430) in [PLOS ONE](http://journals.plos.org/plosone). [Supercentenarians]( https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Supercentenarian) are the world's oldest people, with just 17 or so alive in the United States at any time. Supercentenarians often show a remarkable delay in aging, such as one that worked as a physician in Georgia until age 103 and another that worked as a stockbroker on Wall Street until age 109. In order to begin to find the genetic basis for extreme longevity, we sequenced the genomes of 17 supercentenarians. The full genome sequences of the supercentenarians are available as supplemental data from the paper, and we hope that our data contributes to future research to unlock the secret for extreme longevity.

Thank you everyone for your questions, it was a pleasure to answer your questions. I think trying to understand the biology of aging is really interesting and I hope you find it interesting too.  I've signed off for now.

Best wishes,
Stuart Kim


 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> PLOS Science Wednesday: Hi, we're Caitlin Dunn, Deborah McFarland and Kelly Callahan, and we published a study in PLOS NTDs about how onchocerciasis (river blindness) programs helped achieve the aims of certain Millennium Development Goals (MDGs)  Ask Us Anything! </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-09-02 14:00:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hi Reddit!


My name is Caitlin Dunn, and I am a Program Officer at John Snow, Inc., a public health consulting and management organization located in Boston, Massachusetts. Joining me for today's AMA is Kelly Callahan, Director of the [Trachoma Control Program](http://www.cartercenter.org/health/trachoma/index.html) for [The Carter Center](http://www.cartercenter.org), based in Atlanta, Georgia, and Dr. Deborah McFarland, Associate Professor at [Emory University Rollins School of Public Health](http://www.sph.emory.edu/). We published an article titled "[The Contributions of Onchocerciasis Control and Elimination Programs toward the Achievement of the Millennium Development Goals](http://www.plosntds.org/article/info:doi/10.1371/journal.pntd.0003703)" in [PLOS Neglected Tropical Diseases (NTDs)](http://www.plosntds.org/). This article was a literature and data review which found that reducing the burden of onchocerciasis in highly endemic areas contributes to achieving several Millennium Development Goals (MDGs).



Here is a little bit about us:



Caitlin Dunn currently provides backstopping support to two USAID-funded health programs: a health systems strengthening program focused on improving maternal and child health outcomes in Pakistan and a program looking at data quality of PEPFAR indicators in Mozambique. This article was written as part of Ms. Dunns thesis, A Retrospective Review of Onchocerciasis Control and Elimination Program Contributions to the Achievement of the Millennium Development Goals while at the Rollins School of Public Health in partnership with The Carter Center, where she served as a Graduate Research Assistant.



Dr. Deborah A. McFarland is on the faculty of the Department of Global Health and the Department of Health Policy and Management at the Rollins School of Public Health of Emory University. Dr. McFarland has been involved in health policy, health systems and health financing issues for the past 30 years, both in the U.S. and internationally. Dr. McFarland is a current member of the [WHO NTD Strategic Technical Advisory Group (STAG)](http://www.sph.emory.edu/departments/gh/), a former member of the [APOC Technical Consultative Committee](http://www.who.int/apoc/about/structure/tcc/en/), the [Mectizan Expert Committee](http://www.mectizan.org/about/mectizan-expert-committee) and WHO TDR group on community-based interventions for NTDs.



Kelly Callahan works in program implementation towards eradication, elimination and control of specific NTDs. Ms. Callahan focuses specifically on eliminating blinding trachoma as a public health problem by 2020 in six countries. In line with this interest in the NTDs, she has published other key articles also printed in PLOS NTDs that are relevant to this topic: "[Trachoma Control as a Vehicle Toward International Development and Achievement of the Millennium Development Goals](http://journals.plos.org/plosntds/article?id=10.1371/journal.pntd.0003137)"
and "[Contributions of the Guinea Worm Disease Eradication Campaign toward Achievement of the Millennium Development Goals](http://journals.plos.org/plosntds/article?id=10.1371/journal.pntd.0002160)".



Ms. Callahan believes there are several salient points in these three articles:

     *   Given the prominence of the MDGs in the development of global health agendas, it is important to consider greater implementation of NTD strategies in achieving the MDGs (and from the post-2015 Sustainable Development Goals); and
     *   Emerging evidence shows people infected with NTDs are more susceptible to becoming infected with the big three (HIV, malaria, tuberculosis). Evidence also indicates that coinfection with one or more NTDs may adversely and exponentially affect the patient's prognosis of having one of the big three diseases.
We'll be answering your questions at 1pm ET  Ask Us Anything! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> PLOS Science Wednesday: Hi! Im Corina Logan here to talk about my research on animal cognition, specifically how birds are able to adapt their behaviors to different situations  AMA! </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-08-26 14:00:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hi Reddit,

My name is Corina Logan and I am a [Leverhulme Early Career Research Fellow]( https://www.leverhulme.ac.uk/funding/grant-schemes/early-career-fellowships) at the [University of Cambridge](http://www.cam.ac.uk/). I study behavioral flexibility in birds: their ability to adapt their behavior to changing circumstances.

I recently published a study titled [Modifications to the Aesops Fable paradigm change performances in New Caledonian crows](http://journals.plos.org/plosone/article?id=10.1371/journal.pone.0103049) in [PLOS ONE](http://journals.plos.org/plosone). My colleagues and I set out to understand how New Caledonian crows solve novel foraging problems involving a clear tube that is partially filled with water and contains a floating food reward. Dropping objects into the water to raise the water level and bring the food within reach solves the problem. We found that crows can discriminate between water volumes: they dropped more objects into the narrower tube rather than the wider tube when the initial water levels were the same in both tubes, and they switched their preference later when the wide tube became the functional option. Also, one crow appeared to inhibit attention to causal cues to learn to associate the color of one tube with receiving food in its adjacent tube.

I will be available to answer your questions at 1pm ET (10am PT, 6pm GMT) so Ask me Anything!


And dont forget to follow me (and the birds!) on Twitter [@LoganCorina]( https://twitter.com/LoganCorina). </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> PLOS Science Wednesday: Hi! Were Camilo Mora and Iain Caldwell, here to talk about our paper in PLOS Biology that investigates how plant growth is impacted by climate change  AUA! </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-08-19 14:00:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> My name is Dr. Camilo Mora and I am an assistant professor at the [University of Hawaii Manoa](https://manoa.hawaii.edu/). My research focuses on understanding the feedback loops between people and biodiversity. My earlier career was on basic ecology, but then I realized that the effects of people on various species were massive and already evident. Quantifying such impacts and their feedbacks on people represent the main topic of my latest research.


And my name is Dr. Iain Caldwell and I am a post-doctoral researcher at the [University of Hawaii Manoa](https://manoa.hawaii.edu/). I am an ecologist with broad interests in how organisms can respond to changes in their environment, including the potential consequences of projected climate changes for such organisms.


Along with several colleagues from the University of Hawaii and the [University of Montana](http://www.umt.edu/), we recently published a study in [PLOS Biology](http://journals.plos.org/plosbiology) titled [Suitable Days for Plant Growth Disappear under Projected Climate Change: Potential Human and Biotic Vulnerability](http://journals.plos.org/plosbiology/article?id=10.1371/journal.pbio.1002167). In this paper, we explored the potential consequences of projected climate changes on future plant growth worldwide, and what that could mean for various ecosystems and the people that depend on those ecosystems.


Our findings indicate that, if climate change continues as it has in the past, there could be significant global declines in the number of suitable plant growing days by 2100; with the most drastic changes affecting people in the poorest countries of the world. There is hope though; as our results also indicate that if we can curb our global carbon emissions, these changes in plant-growing conditions should be far less severe.



We will be answering your questions at 1pm ET. Ask Us Anything!


Dont forget to follow Iain on Twitter [@ircaldwell](http://www.twitter.com/ircaldwell). </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> PLOS Science Wednesday: We're Jim Hansen, a professor at Columbias Earth Institute, and Paul Hearty, a professor at UNC-Wilmington, here to make the case for urgent action to reduce carbon dioxide emissions, which are on the verge of locking in highly undesirable consequences, Ask Us Anything. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-08-12 14:00:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hi Reddit,

Im Jim Hansen, a professor at [Columbia Universitys Earth Institute]( http://www.earthinstitute.columbia.edu/sections/view/9).http://www.earthinstitute.columbia.edu/sections/view/9 I'm  joined today by 3 colleagues who are scientists representing different aspects of climate science and coauthors on papers we'll be talking about on this AMA.

--Paul Hearty, paleoecologist and professor at University of North Carolina at Wilmington, NC Dept. of Environmental Studies. I study the geology of sea-level changes

--George Tselioudis, of NASA Goddard Institute for Space Studies; I head a research team that analyzes observations and model simulations to investigate cloud, radiation, and precipitation changes with climate and the resulting radiative feedbacks.

--Pushker Kharecha from Columbia University Earth Institute; I study the global carbon cycle; the exchange of carbon in its various forms among the different components of the climate system --atmosphere, land, and ocean.

Today we make the case for urgent action to reduce carbon dioxide (CO2) emissions, which are on the verge of locking in highly undesirable consequences, leaving young people with a climate system out of humanity's control. Not long after my 1988 testimony to Congress, when I concluded that human-made climate change had begun, practically all nations agreed in a 1992 United Nations Framework Convention to reduce emissions so as to avoid dangerous human-made climate change.  Yet little has been done to achieve that objective.

I am glad to have the opportunity today to discuss with researchers and general science readers here on redditscience an alarming situation  as the science reveals climate threats that are increasingly alarming, policymakers propose only ineffectual actions while allowing continued development of fossil fuels that will certainly cause disastrous consequences for today's young people. Young people need to understand this situation and stand up for their rights.

To further a broad exchange of views on the implications of this research, my colleagues and I have published in a variety of open access journals, including, in [PLOS ONE]( http://journals.plos.org/plosone), [Assessing Dangerous Climate Change: Required Reduction of Carbon Emissions to Protect Young People, Future Generations and Nature (2013)](http://journals.plos.org/plosone/article?id=10.1371/journal.pone.0081648),
[PLOS ONE](http://journals.plos.org/plosone), [Assessing Dangerous Climate Change: Required Reduction of Carbon Emissions to Protect Young People, Future Generations and Nature (2013)](http://journals.plos.org/plosone/article?id=10.1371/journal.pone.0081648), and most recently, [Ice Melt, Sea Level Rise and Superstorms: Evidence from the Paleoclimate Data, Climate Modeling that 2 C Global Warming is Highly Dangerous](http://www.columbia.edu/%7Ejeh1/2015/20150704_IceMelt.pdf), in [Atmos. Chem.   Phys. Discussions](http://www.atmos-chem-phys-discuss.net/volumes_and_issues.html) (July, 2015).

One conclusion we share in the latter paper is that ice sheet models that guided [IPCC (Intergovernmental Panel on Climate Change)](http://www.ipcc.ch/) sea level projections and upcoming United Nations meetings in Paris are far too sluggish compared with the magnitude and speed of sea level changes in the paleoclimate record. An implication is that continued high emissions likely would result in multi-meter sea level rise this century and lock in continued ice sheet disintegration such that building cities or rebuilding cities on coast lines would become foolish.

The bottom line message we as scientists should deliver to the public and to policymakers is that we have a global crisis, an emergency that calls for global cooperation to reduce emissions as rapidly as practical. We conclude and reaffirm in our present paper that the crisis calls for an across-the-board rising carbon fee and international technical cooperation in carbon-free technologies. This urgent science must become part of a global conversation about our changing climate and what all citizens can do to make the world livable for future generations.

Joining me is my co-author, Professor Paul Hearty, a professor at University of North Carolina  Wilmington. 

**We'll be answering your questions from 1  2pm ET today. Ask Us Anything!** </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> PLOS Science Wednesdays: Hi, Im Laura Jurgens here to talk about my research on the mass death of sea species along the Pacific Coastline  Ask Me Anything! </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-08-05 14:00:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Updated post-AMA: 

Hi Reddit, 
Thanks to all of you who submitted questions, answers and insights. I wish I could have gotten to all of them and I thank you for your interest!

Laura Jurgens (tweeting @seacurious)

---------------------------------

Hi Reddit, 

My name is Laura Jurgens and I am a postdoctoral researcher at Temple University and Smithsonian Institution. My research focuses on how marine organisms, and the interacting communities they form, respond to extreme events and global change.

Together with a wonderful group of collaborators, I recently published a study titled ["Patterns of Mass Mortality among Rocky Shore Invertebrates across 100 km of Northeastern Pacific Coastline"](http://journals.plos.org/plosone/article?id=10.1371/journal.pone.0126280) in [PLOS ONE](http://journals.plos.org). In it, we describe an unusual event that killed nearly 100% of two species, a tiny sea star and a sea urchin, over a large region, following a harmful algal bloom or "red tide". We discuss why it's especially important, but often hard, to document such events, which may be increasing in severity and frequency with human-induced changes to our oceans. We also discuss how lifestyle differences between the affected species could determine how long it takes them to recover, and what that means for coastal ecosystems.

I will be answering your questions at 1pm ET. Ask me Anything!

You can also follow me on Twitter [@SeaCurious](http://www.twitter.com/seacurious). </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> PLOS Science Wednesday: Were Sten Vermund and Akhenaten Tankwanchi, we just published a paper about the impacts of brain drain or the migration of the health workforce from Sub-Saharan Africa to the United States  Ask Us Anything! </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-29 14:00:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hi Reddit, were Sten Vermund and Akhenaten Tankwanchi, we just published a paper about the impacts of brain drain or the migration of the health workforce from Sub-Saharan Africa to the United States  Ask Us Anything!

My name is Sten Vermund, and I am a professor of pediatrics and the Director of the (Vanderbilt Institute for Global Health)[http://globalhealth.vanderbilt.edu/] at Vanderbilt University School of Medicine in Nashville, Tennessee. My primary research focus is on infectious disease control and prevention in low-income countries. Joining me for todays AMA is the lead author of our work, Dr. Akhenaten Tankwanchi, a Washington, D.C.-based consultant now in the job market. Akhenaten holds a PhD in community research and action from Vanderbilt University's (Peabody School of Education and Human Development)[ http://peabody.vanderbilt.edu/]. His current research interest is on health workforce migration from Africa and its implication for development and global health policy.

We recently published a paper titled (Monitoring Sub-Saharan African Physician Migration Post-Adoption of the WHO Code of Practice: Temporal and Geographic Patterns in United States)[ http://journals.plos.org/plosone/article?id=10.1371/journal.pone.0124734] in (PLOS ONE)[http://journals.plos.org/plosone/article?id=10.1371/journal.pone.0124734].  In this study, we examined available data on physicians originating from Sub-Saharan Africa (SSA) and appearing in the AMA Masterfile with the primary aim of evaluating the effectiveness of the (WHO Code of Practice on the International Recruitment of Health Personnel)[http://www.who.int/hrh/migration/code/practice/en/] in decreasing the emigration of SSA physicians from the continent of greatest need. Our findings suggest that the non-binding WHO Code of Practice has not slowed physician emigration from SSA to the United States (U.S.). In fact, we observed an increasing trend in the number of SSA migrant physicians recruited into the U.S. physician workforce. They currently exceed the number of physicians reported in 34 SSA countries. On the heels of this large-scale migration, the recent and deadliest Ebola epidemic has further compounded the SSA health workforce crisis. This paper complements the more (extensive study)[ http://journals.plos.org/plosmedicine/article?id=10.1371/journal.pmed.1001513] we published in 2013 in (PLOS Medicine)[ http://journals.plos.org/plosmedicine/article?id=10.1371/journal.pmed.1001513] and a 2014 (commentary)[ http://www.thelancet.com/journals/langlo/article/PIIS2214-109X%2814%2970240-2/fulltext] in the (Lancet Global Health)[ http://www.thelancet.com/journals/langlo/article/PIIS2214-109X%2814%2970240-2/fulltext].

We will be answering your questions today at 1pm ET, Ask Us Anything!

Follow Akhenaten on Twitter (@Am3nhot3p)[ http://www.twitter.com/Am3nhot3p]. Sten's work can be found at (http://globalhealth.vanderbilt.edu)[http://globalhealth.vanderbilt.edu]. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> PLOS Science Wednesday: Hi! Im Dr. Todd Eckhadl, here to discuss my recent PLOS ONE paper showing that an optimal metabolic solution can be derived through the evolution of bacteria, proving our concept of Programmed Evolution  AMA! </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-22 14:33:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hi Reddit,

My name is Dr. Todd Eckdahl and I am a Professor of Biology at [Missouri Western State University]( https://www.missouriwestern.edu/). I collaborate with Dr. Malcolm Campbell and Dr. Laurie Heyer of Davidson College, Dr. Jeff Poet of Missouri Western State University, and undergraduate students studying biology and mathematics on our two campuses.  Our research focuses on using Synthetic Biology to improve metabolic engineering of bacteria for applications in medicine, energy, and bioremediation.

We recently published a paper titled [Programmed Evolution for Optimization of Orthogonal Metabolic Output in Bacteria] (http://journals.plos.org/plosone/article?id=10.1371/journal.pone.0118322) in [PLOS ONE]( http://journals.plos.org/plosone). Our approach is called Programmed Evolution and captures two concepts. First, a population of cells is programmed with DNA code to enable it to compute solutions to a chosen optimization problem. Second, the system employs the evolution of bacteria toward an optimal metabolic solution by imposing fitness defined by metabolic output. Our study is a proof-of-concept for Programmed Evolution applied to the optimization of a metabolic pathway for the conversion of caffeine to an asthma medication called theophylline in E. coli.

My collaborators and I will be answering your questions at 1pm ET, Ask Me Anything!
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> PLOS Science Wednesday: we are Sabrina Engesser, Simon Townsend and Andy Russell, here to talk about our recent PLOS Biology paper that found birds have phonemic capacities previously thought to be limited to humans, which has implications for the early evolution of human language  Ask Us Anything! </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-15 14:05:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hi Reddit,

Our names are Sabrina Engesser, Simon Townsend, James Savage and Andy Russell. We recently published a paper titled [Experimental Evidence for Phonemic Contrasts in a Nonhuman Vocal System]( http://journals.plos.org/plosbiology/article?id=10.1371/journal.pbio.1002171) in [PLOS Biology]( http://journals.plos.org/plosbiology). Through studying the vocalization of the highly social chestnut-crowned babbler, we found that these birds reuse meaningless acoustic elements in different arrangements to generate new signals. While it was previously assumed that such phonemic capacities are limited to humans, our study shows that the ability to generate basic phoneme-like structures exists outside of humans and provides insight into potential early steps in the evolution of human language.

SABRINA ENGESSER - I am a PhD student at the Institute of Evolutionary Biology and Environmental Studies at the [University of Zurich]( http://www.uzh.ch/index_en.html) in Switzerland. My work focuses on the combinatorial mechanisms vocally constrained animals apply to increase their basic vocal repertoire, and its implications for the evolution of human language. I am currently studying two highly social birds, the chestnut-crowned babbler from outback Australia and the pied babbler from southern Africa.

SIMON TOWNSEND - I am a Group Leader at the Institute of Evolutionary Biology and Environmental Studies at the [University of Zurich]( http://www.uzh.ch/index_en.html), but have recently taken up an Assistant Professorship in Psychology at the [University of Warwick]( http://www2.warwick.ac.uk/) in the UK. I am particularly interested in how and why the human capacity for language evolved. To this end, I study primate and non-primate mammals and birds in the wild and captivity to shed light on the origins of this stand-out feature of human behaviour.

JAMES SAVAGE - I am a postdoctoral researcher in the Department of Animal Sciences at Wageningen University, the Netherlands. I work on parental care behaviour, primarily looking at how parents (and helpers in cooperative systems) respond to each other when feeding offspring. I did my PhD on chestnut-crowned babbler in Australia, and currently work on great tits in the Netherlands.

ANDY RUSSELL - I am an Associate Professor in Animal Behaviour at the [University of Exeter](http://www.exeter.ac.uk/) in the UK. My research focuses on understanding the causes and consequences of cooperative breeding systems, wherein non-breeders help to rear the offspring of breeders. I have worked on meerkats and humans, but now primarily work on chestnut-crowned babblers from outback Australia.

We will be answering your question at 1pm ET, ASK US ANYTHING!
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> PLOS Science Wednesday: Hi! Im Dr. Jan Heng here to talk about a new method for predicting whether a women is at risk for threatened preterm labor  AMA! </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-08 14:14:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> My name is [Dr. Jan Heng](http://scholar.harvard.edu/janheng/home) and I am a Research Fellow at [Harvard Medical School]( http://hms.harvard.edu/). My research focuses on applying novel technologies and analytical methods to better understand disease pathogenesis and the integration of various types of data (clinical, epidemiological, genomics and proteomics) to improve disease diagnostics and therapeutics in womens health.

I recently published a research study titled [Whole Blood Gene Expression Profile Associated with Spontaneous Preterm Birth in Women with Threatened Preterm Labor]( http://journals.plos.org/plosone/article?id=10.1371/journal.pone.0096901) in [PLOS One](http://journals.plos.org/plosone). My colleagues and I discovered a set of nine genes, when combined with clinical data, could predict if a women with signs of premature labor (i.e. in threatened preterm labor) would or would not deliver a premature infant within 48 hours of hospital admission. Women admitted for threatened preterm labor are often unnecessarily hospitalized, and we wanted to develop a test that can differentiate between true and false labor so that women in truly threatened labor will receive appropriate medical care while women in false labor will receive supportive care and be discharged.

Looking forward to answering your questions at 1pm EDT. Ask me Anything!

Edit  Thank you for your wonderful contributions, I had an awesome time! I would to thank my co-authors on this PLoS publication especially Professor Stephen Lye. I would also like to acknowledge my current PI, Dr Andrew Beck and Ben Glass for supporting me during this AMA.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> PLOS Science Wednesdays: Hi Reddit, were Amy Morrison and Sarah Anne Guagliardo, here to discuss our paper that found river boats contribute to the spread of Dengue Fever in the Peruvian Amazon  AUA! </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-01 14:08:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Im Dr. Amy Morrison, and I am Project Scientist in the [Department of Entomology and Nematology]( http://entomology.ucdavis.edu/) at the University of California, Davis, but also I am the Scientific Director for the U.S. Naval Medical Research Unit No. 6 (NAMRU-6) Iquitos Field Laboratory. I have lived and worked in the Amazonian City of Iquitos, Peru for the last 17 years on a series of prospective epidemiological studies (7 large multi-year cohort studies following about 5,000 people each) to understand the role of Aedes aegypti in dengue virus transmission dynamics.


And Im Sarah Anne Guagliardo, and I currently serve as an [ASPPH Allan Rosenfield Global Health Fellow]( https://fellowships.aspph.org/programs/details.cfm?programID=2) at the Centers for Disease Control and Prevention. I recently completed my PhD at Emory University in [Population Biology, Ecology, and Evolution]( http://www.biomed.emory.edu/PROGRAM_SITES/PBEE/), with an emphasis on the ecology of infectious diseases. My doctoral research focused on how human transportation networks are responsible for the geographic range expansion of mosquito Aedes aegypti in the Peruvian Amazon. Ae. aegypti transmits many pathogens, the most important of which is dengue virus.


[Our previous research]( http://journals.plos.org/plosntds/article?id=10.1371/journal.pntd.0003033) showed that this urban mosquito is in the process of invading peri-urban and rural communities throughout the region. To expand upon this finding, we compared mosquito infestation rates in different kinds of vehicles commonly found in the Amazon, such as large barges and water taxis. We found that large barges are heavily infested with Ae.aegypti. As it turns out, these boats provide ideal conditions for mosquitoes  cargo holds in the bottom of the boats often contain puddles that serve as mosquito breeding grounds. Our findings showed that mosquitoes commonly hitch rides on barges, and that boat traffic ultimately contributes to Ae. aegypti spread throughout the Peruvian Amazon. Findings in this article illustrate how easily and efficiently dengue virus can be spread between large urban centers, and are reported in our recent article in [PLOS NTDs]( http://journals.plos.org/plosntds/), [River Boats Contribute to the Regional Spread of the Dengue Vector Aedes aegypti in the Peruvian Amazon](http://journals.plos.org/plosntds/article?id=10.1371/journal.pntd.0003648)


As dengue fever continues to be a serious global public health problem, it is essential that scientists understand the geographic distribution of its primary vector, Ae. aegypti.

We will be answering your questions at 1pm ET  Ask Us Anything!


Dont forget to follow me on Twitter [@sarahguagliardo](https://twitter.com/sarahguagliardo).
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> PLOS Science Wednesdays: Hi, were Miriam Barlow and Juan Meza, here to discuss our paper about reversing antibiotic resistance through rational treatment plans  AUA! </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-24 13:54:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> My name is Miriam Barlow and I am an Associate Professor at [UC Merced]( http://www.ucmerced.edu/). My research focuses on Antibiotic Resistance and Evolutionary Time Travel.

And name is Juan Meza and I am a Professor in Applied Mathematics at UC Merced. My research focuses on optimization and scientific computing. My role on the research team was to show how to rewind the evolution of antibiotic resistant bacteria by using mathematical models to predict the best combination of antibiotic treatments.

We recently published a study titled ["Rational Design of Antibiotic Treatment Plans: A Treatment Strategy for Managing Evolution and Reversing Resistance"]( http://journals.plos.org/plosone/article?id=10.1371/journal.pone.0122283) in [PLOS One](http://journals.plos.org/plosone). We showed how to rewind the evolution of bacteria and verify treatment options for a family of 15 antibiotics, including penicillin, used to fight common infections. This work shows that there is still hope for antibiotics if we use them intelligently.

We will be answering your questions at 1pm ET  Ask Us Anything!

Dont forget to follow us on Twitter [@Miriome](https://twitter.com/Miriome) and [@ProfMeza](http://www.twitter.com/profmeza)! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> PLOS Science Wednesdays: Hi, were Manica Balasegaram and Bernard Pcoul, here to talk about prospects for a global health R D fund to fight Ebola, Antibiotic Resistance   Neglected Diseases  AUA! </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-17 13:55:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hi, Im Manica Balasegaram, executive director of the [Mdecins Sans Frontires (MSF) Access Campaign](http://www.msfaccess.org/), where we work to increase access to essential medicines for all. I worked for years as an MSF physician in the field in several African countries and in the Indian sub-continent, where I experienced firsthand the dire need for research and development for drugs, where the market does not incentivize.

Im Bernard Pcoul, executive director of the [Drugs for Neglected Diseases initiative]( http://www.dndi.org/), a non-profit research and development organization that uses public and private funding and partnerships, spanning from governments to pharmaceutical companies, to develop and deliver treatments for neglected diseases. I started out as an MSF field doctor where I discovered the extent to which neglected populations were left behind by the vast medical advances of the past half-century.

Were here to discuss our recent article in [PLOS Medicine]( http://journals.plos.org/plosmedicine), titled [A Global Biomedical R D Fund and Mechanism for Innovations of Public Health Importance](http://journals.plos.org/plosmedicine/article?id=10.1371/journal.pmed.1001831). The paper calls for a broad framework for funding and coordinating research and development for Ebola, Antibiotic Resistance, and Neglected Diseases initiatives in low-and-middle income countries. We see investing in health as a cost-saving and lifesaving strategy, and called upon the global community to invest in a biomedical R D fund at the recent [G7 Summit]( http://www.theguardian.com/world/2015/jun/05/g7-bavaria-angela-merkel-summit-26-hours-trade-ebola-oompah) in Germany. 

Well be answering your questions  at 1pm EDT (10 am PDT, 17:00 UTC)  AUA! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> PLOS Science Wednesdays: Im Tim Brown, here to talk about the discovery of a new way mammals visually perceive changes in the time of day (including humans)  AMA! </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-10 13:56:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hi Reddit,

My name is [Dr. Tim Brown] (http://www.ls.manchester.ac.uk/people/profile/?alias=browntm) and I am a [BBSRC David Phillips Fellow]( http://www.bbsrc.ac.uk/funding/fellowships/david-phillips/)  at the [University of Manchester] (http://www.manchester.ac.uk/). My research focuses on the intersection between biological rhythms and visual processing.

I recently published a study titled [Colour As a Signal for Entraining the Mammalian Circadian Clock] (http://journals.plos.org/plosbiology/article?id=10.1371/journal.pbio.1002127) in [PLOS Biology] (http://journals.plos.org/plosbiology). In this study, we show that the brains biological clock uses information about natural changes in blue-yellow colour occurring around dawn and dusk to determine time of day. Until now, the role of colour-opponent signals and its impact on the mammalian circadian clock were untested. These findings reveal a new sensory mechanism for estimating the time of day that is available to all mammals with chromatic vision, including humans. I will be answering your questions on June 10 at 1pm EDT (10 am PDT, 5 pm UTC)  Ask me Anything! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> PLOS Science Wednesdays: Im Seth Blumberg, a physician-scientist here to talk about my study examining the measles outbreak in California and importance of vaccine coverage to prevent further measles transmission  AMA! </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-03 14:10:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hi Reddit!  My name is Seth Blumberg.  I am a physician-scientist based out of the [University of California, San Francisco](http://www.ucsf.edu) and [St. Marys Medical Center](http://www.stmarysmedicalcenter.org/index.htm). Joining me for today's AMA is Jennifer Zipprich, an epidemiologist with the Immunization Branch at the California Department of Public Health.  

SETH BLUMBERG - I am involved in research concerning the emergence and re-emergence of infectious disease.  Along with a wonderful group of collaborators, I recently published a study titled [Assessing Measles Transmission in the United States Following a Large Outbreak in California]( http://currents.plos.org/outbreaks/article/assessing-measles-transmission-in-the-united-states-following-a-large-outbreak-in-california/), in [PLOS Currents]( http://currents.plos.org). In this article, we analyze the recent outbreak of measles at Disneyland. The key question is whether or not the transmission of measles has increased to the point where it may once again become endemic in the United States.  Fortunately, we find that the transmission of measles is probably still controlled, but that vaccination remains an essential public health policy.  There have been a lot of conflicting reports on the benefit of measles vaccination, and our research helps to clarify why measles vaccination is important.

JENNIFER ZIPPRICH works with a team of epidemiologists to investigate cases and outbreaks of vaccine preventable diseases, including measles. On April 17th her team declared the measles outbreak associated with Disneyland over, however, measles is still a threat internationally and importations into the U.S. continue to occur. She looks forward to answering your questions about measles prevention and control  Ask Us Anything!  

You can address your questions to either or both of us. Well be back at 1pm to answer them.

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Robots that can adapt like animals (Nature cover article) </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-01 20:34:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Science AMA Series. PLOS Science Wednesdays: Im Jelte Wicherts, here to talk about a data simulation study published in PLOS ONE that showed why publishing everything is more effective than just publishing significant findings  AMA! </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-27 13:11:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hi Reddit, 
My name is [Jelte Wicherts] (https://www.tilburguniversity.edu/webwijs/show/j.m.wicherts.htm) and I am an associate professor at Tilburg University in The Netherlands, where I lead the Human Factors in Statistics group. Our research focuses on how researchers in the social sciences deal with the analysis of their data, errors with statistics, publication bias, and reproducibility.
I recently published a study titled [Why Publishing Everything Is More Effective than Selective Publishing of Statistically Significant Results] (http://journals.plos.org/plosone/article?id=10.1371/journal.pone.0084896) in PLOS ONE. In this article, we argue that the best way forward in science is to publish all results rather than just those that are significant. We used simulation, a data fabrication technique that is ethically acceptable because it lets us see what happens in particular circumstances, to show that publishing all relevant results leads to much better estimates of effects in the literature. Publishing these results in PLOS ONE aligns closely with the journals guidelines to not focus exclusively on novel or important results, but instead publishes sound research regardless of whether results are significant or not. **I will be answering your questions on May 27 at 1pm EST  AMA!**
  Dont forget to follow me on Twitter @JelteWicherts. 
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> PLOS Science Wednesday: Im Megan Head, an evolutionary biologist talking about the wide scope of inflation biases  called p-hacking -- in science publications  AMA! </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-20 13:16:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hi Reddit,

 My name is [Dr. Megan Head](https://researchers.anu.edu.au/researchers/head-ml), and I am a post-doctoral research associate in the Research School of Biological Sciences at The Australian National University. I am an evolutionary biologist that researches how interactions between males and females influence evolution, but I am also dedicated to maintaining integrity and rigor in the scientific process.


In line with this latter interest, I published a Perspective Article titled [The Extent and Consequences of P-hacking in Science] (http://journals.plos.org/plosbiology/article?id=10.1371/journal.pbio.1002106) in PLOS Biology. P-hacking is a practice where researchers analyze their data multiple times or in multiple ways until they get the desired result, for example, a p-value  0.05. This paper shows that p-hacking is rampant in science, but that it does not seem to influence the conclusions drawn from meta-analysis, at least in our case study of meta-analyses conducted in evolutionary ecology. The paper highlights common methods of p-hacking, and offers suggestions for how researchers and journals can prevent p-hacking. 

**I will be answering your questions at 1pm EDT (10 am PDT, 5 pm UTC), AMA!** </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> PLOS Science Wednesday: Hi Reddit, we create computational models for artificial intelligence. Ask us anything! </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-13 13:41:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hi reddit!

 We study the evolution of intelligence by conducting experiments in computational simulations of evolution. Our work not only sheds light on the evolution of intelligence in natural animals, but will also accelerate attempts to create artificial intelligence (AI). Individually, we are:


         Kai Olav Ellefsen, who recently received a Ph.D. from the Norwegian University of Science and Technology, and is currently a post-doctoral researcher at the Brazilian Institute of Robotics 


         Jean-Baptiste Mouret, who is an associate scientist at Inria (France), and previously was an assistant professor at Pierre   Marie Curie University (France), and


         Jeff Clune, assistant professor of computer science at the University of Wyoming, who directs the [Evolving Artificial Intelligence laboratory] (http://EvolvingAI.org)


Our [recent PLOS Computational Biology paper](http://journals.plos.org/ploscompbiol/article?id=10.1371/journal.pcbi.1004128) suggests that when computational brain models called neural networks are organized into modules they are better at learning new information without forgetting old knowledge. The brains of animals (including humans) are modular, which means they have many separate units, such as those for language and facial recognition. While natural animals tend to forget gradually, artificial neural networks currently exhibit what is called 'catastrophic forgetting, meaning they rapidly overwrite previously acquired knowledge when learning a new skill. We found that modularity significantly reduced such catastrophic forgetting in these computer brains.
 

For summaries of the work, please watch our [summary video](https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=6PlvyWQUQu8),  read [a story about the work in the Atlantic] (http://www.theatlantic.com/technology/archive/2015/04/teaching-a-computer-not-to-forget/389727/), or [listen to a BBC interview about the research](http://www.bbc.co.uk/programmes/p02n93fn) (the section on our work starts at 1:24).


**We will be back at 1pm EDT (10 am PDT, 6 pm UTC) to answer your questions, ask us anything!** </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> PLOS Science Wednesday: I'm Andy Farke, I was on the team that named North America's oldest horned dinosaur, AMA! </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-06 13:56:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hi reddit,

Im Andy Farke, a vertebrate paleontologist at the [Raymond M. Alf Museum of Paleontology](http://www.alfmuseum.org/) in Claremont, California. My research interests include the evolution and biology of horned dinosaurs, as well as reconstructing extinct ecosystems from the end of the Age of Dinosaurs. Im also the volunteer section editor for paleontology at PLOS ONE.

The [research article](http://blogs.plos.org/plos/2015/04/plos/%20http:/journals.plos.org/plosone/article?id=10.1371/journal.pone.0112055) Ill be talking about in this AMA is about Aquilops a newly discovered and named dinosaur who, at around 106 million years old,  turns out to be the oldest horned dinosaur (the lineage including Triceratops) named from North America, besting the previous record by nearly 20 million years. No bigger than a bunny rabbit, its also incredibly small (for a dinosaur) and cute. So, after finding only a skull how did we figure this out? Come to our PLOS redditscience AMA and youll find out.

Here are two posts I wrote on my PLOS blog about this research, the first introducing [Aquilops](http://blogs.plos.org/paleo/2014/12/10/aquilops-hello/) and [then telling the story](http://blogs.plos.org/paleo/2014/12/11/assembling-aquilops-paper/)  of how our team assembled this paper.

Find me on Twitter: [@andyfarke](http://twitter.com/AndyFarke)   Ill be back at **1pm EDT (10 am PDT, 6 pm UTC)** to answer your questions, ask me anything! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> PLOS Science Wednesday: We developed Open-Source, 3-D Printed Laboratory Equipment, AUA! </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-29 13:42:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hi Reddit!

We are [Tom Baden](https://tombaden.wordpress.com) and [Andre Maia Chagas](https://www.mendeley.com/profiles/andre-maia-chagas/), and we are neuroscience researchers at the Centre for Integrative Neuroscience (CIN) at the University of Tbingen, Germany. We are also part of [TReND in Africa](http://trendinafrica.org), a scientist-run NGO aimed at fostering science education and research on the African continent. We are active in the Maker-Movement where we aim to promote the use of open source software and hardware approaches in research and education.
We recently published a [community page](http://journals.plos.org/plosbiology/article?id=10.1371/journal.pbio.1002086) in PLOS Biology on the use of consumer oriented 3-D printing and microcontrollers for the building of sophisticated yet low-cost laboratory equipment, or Open Labware. We argue that today it is possible to establish a fully operational home-factory for well below 1,000 USD. This is opening up new grounds for scientists, educators as well as hobbyists outside the traditional scientific establishment to make real contributions to the advancement of science tools and science in general, while at the same time allowing grant money to be used more effectively also at the financially more established institutions. We actively promote these ideas and tools at training courses at universities across Africa, while our co-authors and colleagues from the US-based [Backyard Brains](https://www.backyardbrains.com/) are running similar activities across Latin America.

**We will be answering your questions at 1pm EDT (10 am PDT, 6 pm UTC). Ask us anything!**


Dont forget to follow us (TReND) on [facebook](https://www.facebook.com/TReNDinAfrica) and [twitter](https://twitter.com/TReNDinAfrica?lang=en)! ([Andres twitter here](https://twitter.com/Chagas_AM?lang=en))
Further reading: [Open Source lab](http://www.appropedia.org/Open-source_Lab)  by Joshua M Pearce </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
