<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject4427</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-08 17:25:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thank you for the response! So is she supposed to record an introduction video or just send a message? Much appreciated. 
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Question About Skype Handshake </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-08 16:56:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hello. My girlfriend has a postdoc interview over skype. The email she received instructed her to "handshake" the interviewer a few days before the actual interview. Any idea what this means? There is a handshake emoticon but she does not think that is what they are looking for. Has anyone heard of this before? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-16 05:20:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What you are saying is that by paying off the highest interest loan, even tough the balance is not the largest, will help pay off the loans more quickly? She has been doing the opposite, paying more to the larger balance, lower interest loans because she thought they would cost more over the life of the loan due to compounding interest. Thanks!   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-16 03:39:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thanks for responding! She pays about 40% of her monthly income to the loans (PhD stipend does not pay well...) leaving her with about $11,000 to live on for the year. Do you have any recommendations for programs or for a smarter way to pay it down, because what she is doing now is clearly not working for her.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> 4 years of payments and the balance remains the same! </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-16 03:09:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hello I was hoping that you could help me with my girlfriends student loans. She pays over $700 a month on these loans but the balance remains the same! 

She has loans with:

Navient (Public)- $55,000 total over 6 loans.  
3 subsidized at 6.8% interest ($17,000) and 3 which are unsubsidized: 
(1.) $14,500 @ 6.8% 
(2.) $20,000 @ 6.8% 
(3.) $18,000 @ 5.625% 

NJ Class Managed by HESAA (Private)- $69,000 Total over 6 loans.
2 loans currently in repayment totaling $13,200 @ 7.2%.
1 loan currently in repayment totaling $3,600 @ 6.74%.
2 loans currently in deferment totaling $28,400@ 6.5%.
1 loan currently in deferment totaling $23,700 @ 6.7%.

All of the Navient loans are currently being differed because she is still in school.

She always pays $365 a month on her NJCLASS loans currently in repayment, and another $335 a month on the NJCLASS loans currently in deferment. Regarding the NJCLASS loans, the balance never seems to go down. She has tried to consolidate both public and private loans with NJ Class and SoFI but was told that she can not refinance while in school. The private loans are all undergraduate and the public loans are from undergrad and masters. She expects to graduate in September of this year. 

We would appreciate any advice you may be able to give us. Thank you so much for any recommendations you may have!

And sorry for the formatting I am not very good at this!
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-10-14 05:42:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thanks for the reply! I only gave them copies. I definitely don't trust them.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Rebuild transmission fails after multiple returns to shop. Warrantee expires this week! </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-10-14 00:25:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hello I could use your legal advice. 

I am from the state of New Jersey

On November 20, 2014 I paid a transmission shop to rebuild the automatic transmission in my 2000 Subaru Impreza with 100,000 miles. The car had a manufacturer defect, which causes the car not to go into drive. It is problem on virtually every Subaru from that era and the fix is well known. It is called delayed forward engagement.

The shop said that the rest of the transmission was in bad shape too and it needed to be rebuilt. They said that they worked on these all the time and I paid $1400 for the rebuild and an additional $400 for the timing belt, since it was due and I planned on keeping the car.  I am the type of person who does all scheduled maintenance. This included a 12-month, 12000 mile warrantee. 

Less then 24 hours after I had the transmission rebuilt, it would not go into gear and I nearly got hit after backing into traffic. I took it back and they claimed that it was fixed properly but the computer was remembering that there was a problem and was replicating it. They claimed to then replace the transmission computer. 

Less then a month later it was back. In fact I brought it back at least 2 more times (I have to look at my paperwork). Each time they said they made adjustments. They did not want to give me paperwork for each visit but I insisted. 

Eventually the car seemed to work for about 3 months. That was until this past week. The car stopped shifting and I had to abandon it. I brought the car to the shop with 10 days left on the warrantee (4 days ago).

Today I called and they said that they needed my original paperwork. I brought it over and they said that it was going to take them a while. They couldnt tell me what is wrong with the transmission but they needed my paperwork to send to their warrantee company to get money back on the parts that failed but they need an inspector to come and see if I abused the transmission (I went less then 8000 miles). They said they lost their paperwork on my car. 

A few things: I dont think they actually rebuilt the transmission in the first place. Each time I drop the car off it takes them over a week. They dont call me when its done. I have to keep calling them. Each time they have the car, they have it for a week and I do not have another vehicle. I have to get rides to work and to the shop. 
I have not paid more then the original $1800. Each fix has been under the warrantee.  What work I can see, was done poorly. This includes fluids spilled over the hood and sides of the car/engine compartment, missing bolts for the weather cover which was left to dangle and was dragging on the road, and the windshield washer tubing was removed and never put back. 

I really dont know what to do. Should I demand my money back? Can I? Should I take them to small claims court? Am I SOL? Please help!

TLDR: Paid $1800 for Rebuilt transmission and scheduled maintenance. Transmission never worked correctly after rebuild failed again this week after several returns to the shop. Warrantee is expiring this week. Shop says they need to hold on to the car to get it inspected from parts insurance adjuster. What should I do?
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-20 20:42:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Someone who stocks the shelves with things  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-20 15:58:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Story time: Several years ago I worked at a hardware store and there was a stock kid that was always bothering one of the cashiers. The stock kid was very obnoxious, he was the son of a local politician and ever sentence he spoke started with "my dad said". One of those people you just immediately want to punch in the face upon meeting them. Well one day the cashier had enough and she decided to pull a prank on him. Every 20 minutes or so this kid would go up to the front of the store, pull his mountain dew out of the mini fridge, drink it, and go talk to the cashier. She decided it would be a harmless prank to super glue the stock kids mountain dew lid so that he couldn't open it. So she superglued the lid and put it back in the mini fridge. Well we all learned that day that super glue doesn't cure when it's cold, at least not quickly. The stock kid went up and took his drink out of the fridge, opened it, and took a drink. The bottle immediately stuck to his lips, causing him to give a muffled yell as he run around the store, waving his arms in the air, with a mountain dew bottle attached to his mouth. After he pulled it off he claimed that he ended up with minor chemical burns and demand that the store fire the cashier. Even got his dad to complain but the store never did anything other than making the cashier write an apology letter. He didn't bother her again after that. It was glorious.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Travel to Berchtesgaden National Park from Salzburg </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-28 21:04:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hello r/travel I will be spending several days Salzburg in May and wanted to spend a day or 2 hiking in Berchtesgaden National Park. I was looking for the best way to get to the park. I have seen that there is a train or bus to the town of Berchtesgaden, but I wasn't sure if you could actually get into the park from there. I was considering renting a car but would prefer to stick to public transportation. Any suggestions would be helpful! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-16 04:54:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thanks for responding. I was hoping I had overlooked something rather than just picking the wrong shop. Glad to hear your fix lasted so long. It gives me hope that it can be fixed right!  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Help with the dreaded delayed forward engagement! </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-16 00:43:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hello r/Subaru I was hoping some of you could help me with my 2000 Impreza OBS (automatic) with about 105k. Here is my brief story:

About a year ago I noticed my car was taking a long time to shift into drive (initially 5-15sec). All other gears were fine and once it was in gear it was fine. Over time it got worse. I then researched the problem and saw that it was a common issue and I found the fixed site which recommended that you add Trans-X.
Trans-X fixed the problem for about 4 months before it came back with a vengeance. I was experiencing delays of 10+ minutes! So I took it to a local transmission shop and they recommended a full rebuild for $1400. This included a 1yr warranty and I was hopeful that this would fix the issue (even though at that price I was doubtful that they would fully rebuild the whole thing) so I had it done in November. Unfortunately thats where it gets frustrating.
After the initial rebuild I had to bring it back 3 times:
1.	After the rebuild the issue was worse than ever. Sometimes there was over a 30min delay into drive. I brought it back and they claimed they made some adjustments and that it was fixed.
2.	Of course it wasn't fixed. Same exact issue so I brought it back again. This time they claimed that the transmission was fixed but the transmission computer was "remembering that there was an issue and was replicating it so they replaced the transmission computer.
3.	Again not fixed so I brought it back and after a week of adjustments I got it back and it seemed to work! 
Well it worked for about 3 months (2k miles) and it is now starting to come back. Experiencing 3-10sec delays into drive (intermittent). I have brought the ATRA service bulletin to them and they claim to have seen it and stated that they see the Subaru 4-AT transmission all the time and know how to fix it.
Any suggestions on how I can get this fixed would be really helpful. Basically, what can I tell the shop to do since it is still under warranty (other than where to shove it)? I love my Subaru and other than this problem the car seems perfect. 
Thanks! 
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> I am looking for advice on an upcoming trip through Europe. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-08-28 17:30:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
