<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject4049</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-01-09 23:19:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Your imagination.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-01-09 23:18:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Well if I told you then we would have a situation similar to Facebook. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-01-09 23:15:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Eye candy. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-01-09 05:03:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Np </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-01-08 12:54:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The cold water on your skin causes the cold shock response. The first reaction is a deep gasp, followed by several minutes of hyperventilation. Generally this response is uncontrollable and unstoppable. Sudden immersion in cold water results in an involuntary gasp, followed by 1  3 minutes of involuntary hyperventilation. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-01-08 12:37:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> According to my parents, I am addicted to my xbox. Oh but it's ok to beat each other's scores on fucking candy crush! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-01-08 12:28:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Government agencies going against the constitution. 

 Edit: And really any document exercising human rights. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-01-08 12:23:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I believe there is a planet like ours that is smaller, has less hour days, but has more days in a year. I forgot the name. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-01-08 12:14:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Humans are 99% identical with 1% being different because of traits being passed down from generations of people.  I think cloning can wait. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-01-08 12:09:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Everytime we have sex, we dont always have the intention to have kids. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-01-08 12:00:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What will happen if pinocchio says: "My nose will grow" </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-01-08 11:55:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> There are many desirable women, but I love the girl im with right now. I love her looks but cant get over how her personality is. I asked her what she thinks cheating is and we both agreed that if you're going out with another woman/man expecting sex then you're already cheating. Thinking about another women or man isnt cheating because you cant always put a leash on desires even if you've fallen in love. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-01-08 07:12:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's nice to have nature's spidey-sense. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-01-08 07:07:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This honestly makes me feel like Reddit is the most reliable social network now. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-01-08 01:01:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Better sex. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-01-08 00:58:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> CA, if I had to be specific, I think Pasadena, CA </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-01-07 23:09:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Stories are real. Just 90% of each story is fabricated.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-01-07 23:03:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The picture is gray! What a jackass...right guys? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-01-07 22:59:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Fucker </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-01-07 22:57:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> When are you going to watch "The Lake house" again? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-01-07 22:16:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Well the majority of scientists arent rich unless they discovered a new theory got government funding and made a company that runs tests based of their theory. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-01-07 22:11:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> They dont live in NY... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-01-07 19:26:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Being a nerd and still able to have sex with beautiful women. *The Big Bang Theory* </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-01-07 19:23:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I always wondered, "Why the hell is cody bringing his noodle to school?" </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-01-06 23:54:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> 5th dentist here, I recommend to the 4th dentist to lay off the weed for a little bit before you start wearing aluminum.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-01-02 23:16:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-01-02 22:47:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thats great, I just wish some people were more forgiving. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-01-02 22:43:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Oh they werent, I wasnt allowed to date a great girl because she said she was atheist to my parents when they met her. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-01-02 22:41:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Well I didnt exactly know there is such a thing as an agnostic atheist.  Wouldnt that be contradicting then? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-01-02 22:40:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I guess I am then. Thank you. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-01-02 22:38:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thats what I believe. But those are also agnostic views too. I cant prove any "higher power" but I cant just say that it isnt true unless I get proof. How exactly can you tell me there isnt an afterlife when you cant prove it yourself? This is what makes me agnostic. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-01-02 22:34:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I completely agree with you about atheism. I myself was an atheist and I was shunned for it. Every thing you said happened to me also. I studied mythology, went through hard times in my family, started to realize my increased intelligence in Hs. (mostly in science and math). I always thought when I was younger, "if god created the earth, who created him/her/it?" So as I got older I started to think this god was just an alien from anothet planet because logically how would a person just form out of nothing and have commen sense and the intelligence to create an earth so complex? So I decided to be athiest but since religion is traditional I decided to be agnostic in the sense of taking the side of science and saying to myself, "how am I so sure that there isnt something waiting for me after I die besides a hole in the ground? We don't know everything" And thats when I made religon 2nd. I have athiest views but stick to agnostic because I wonder a lot. And so my brother and some friends stop calling me a Satanist. (these people are fucking ridiculously stupid)
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-01-02 20:32:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Why are you atheist exactly? See the only reason why most atheist are who they are is because the bible makes no sense. And it was created by man and not god. If god and heaven is real then whoever made the bible really fucked up and made god seem like a old Republican in a government building. Ill stick to being agnostic for now. How do you know for sure there isn't a "higher power". </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-01-02 20:23:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I would be thrown out immediately. I just told my mother im agnostic instead. Im basically hanging by a thin thread. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-01-02 20:17:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I usually suffer from this every night. I dont necessary know if its a real demon or my mind is accessing my worst fears. Every night a piece of my clothing comes alive and turns into a rabbid animal (my face is in the direction of clothes basket) last night my boxers turned into a very small Wolf. It's actually quite funny just thinking about it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-01-02 20:10:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I wish Pope Francis could pardon him. He is the most trustworthy person in the world at least. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-01-02 20:06:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Get rid of "Double Standards". Except if a girl sleeps with too many men. I think ill keep that double standard. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-01-02 19:56:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I would simply like to walk on rich people's lawns without the cops being called on me. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-12-31 23:35:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I think thats the best thing you can do for now. She can't keep her away forever. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-12-31 23:25:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This guy is a complete asshole. This world (especially the U.S) is going to shit and gay marriage crosses the line with him? I feel a meme brewing up. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-12-31 23:22:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Im sorry, I can't imagine how that feels. You'll get to see her again someday. Hopefully you stay in touch with her. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Hey Reddit, what has someone done so bad that you hate them for it? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-12-31 21:50:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-12-31 20:57:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Please...send me on one of your adventures again. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-12-31 20:54:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Does bitch work or do I have to look in the dictionary for better words? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-12-31 20:49:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Women who tan excessively or put on pounds of make-up. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-12-31 07:33:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Must of been Mind Quad!!!! *cue 80's action music followed by brief story and action montage* </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-12-31 07:29:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So it's a no im guessing. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-12-31 07:26:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Im pretty sure there was a scene from paranormal activity that fits to this comment. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-12-30 04:42:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I think "rare" is being used way too much, but then again it is rare that the last three comments contained the word "rare". </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-11-18 05:37:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> At least your brain makes you do that instead of me being told to do things by my parents. They make me clean when I'm tired, dehydrated, working on college work, studying, coding websites, or being sick. And they still think I'm a slacker, when really I'm an introvert individual that keeps to himself so they pile more shit on me. I should just make a meme and stop bitching. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
