<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject2258</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-07-28 19:13:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I do. It was the day of the wedding and all the friends and family of the bride were called and the family asked for us all to still come to the church and once we all got there the brides parents got up and spoke and they just told us that there was not going to be a wedding and they were very sad for their daughter but still invited everyone to go to the reception hall and enjoy the food and everything. The brides friends had taken her out of town as soon as the groom canceled the wedding.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-07-25 17:08:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> At one time we had an extention cord ran from our neighbors house to ours because our electricity had been shut off.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-07-24 18:01:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I deleted it- </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-06-25 22:21:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> My husband and I were standing in line at Qdoba (sp) and a young man was paying for his food with a gift card and was told there wasnt any money on it-he turned to his buddy and asked if he had any extra money and he didnt and I saw him reach into his pockets and pulled out some change but nothing close to what he needed. I turned to my husband and told him to pay for the kids food. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-06-23 19:41:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Leaving on a 7 day western carribean cruise in 6 days!! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-06-20 19:17:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I consider that a fun fact!  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-06-18 19:21:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> To quit smoking cigarettes-21 years ago. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-06-11 19:28:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I have watched it!! One of the funniest things I have ever seen!  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-06-11 18:54:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> In a search history when my son was a pre-teen he had did a search for "teenagers wearing diapers" WTH!!  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-06-02 18:23:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Oh my yes! I was an adult when I saw this and the daughter has the same name as my daughter..could barely stay in the theatre during that scene.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-06-02 17:39:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> A bulging disk in my back pressing on a nerve. Was worse pain than giving birth with no anesthesia. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-05-22 19:33:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Try roasting,  drizzle olive oil and a little kosher salt in a 400 degree oven until browned--about 20 min, tossing occasionally!!  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-05-21 22:08:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Fear the brow </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-05-21 21:43:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Dont completely agree with this one- I had a bulging disk on a nerve and have never been in so much pain! After a few visits to a Chiropractor I could stand and walk like a normal person. Now the "you have to continue to come back" I didnt go for. But he sure helped me. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-05-20 18:41:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I read that babies of smokers have a 50% increase in SID's and I was pregnant with our second at the time, so my husband and I picked a day that we were quitting and quit cold turkey. The hard candy jolly ranchers were my go to. We have been quit for 21+ years!  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Reddit readers, anyone that has had an experience with a medium or psychic? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-05-20 15:31:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Were they right on, or did you feel duped?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-05-16 22:40:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I am excited to do this! I got number 627 and thats Kate Bush-The Sensual World (MMMM) will come back and comment after I have a listen! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-05-09 20:35:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Wow </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-05-09 19:55:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Its called amish strawberries! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-05-09 19:44:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Had to create an account just for this thread-cream cheese on nacho cheese doritos!! Delish!! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
