<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject4639</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Redditors who CHOOSE to go by the first name, "Dick."  WHY?!?! </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-10-08 18:42:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Like, seriously.  Why not Richard, or Rich, or Rick?  Why Dick?  Is it that you enjoy making baristas uncomfortable when they finish your drink and have to yell "DICK!" in a crowded cafe?  Or what? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [MIXOFF] Reminder: Upload samples by the end of today for participation!  </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-10-04 14:22:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Entry thread with info [can be found here](http://www.reddit.com/r/hiphopheads/comments/10qpmm/mixoff_official_entry_thread_details_inside/) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [MIXOFF] "Official" entry thread. Details inside.  [x-post from r/hiphopheads] </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-10-01 13:11:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This thread is to provide information on what the mixoff is, how it works, and how you can join.  

The simple explanation - everyone who wants to participate contributes three samples.  Out of the collected sample pool, users create songs.  At the end we vote on favorite songs.

Detailed explanation - 

**To participate you must first upload three samples.**

1) These must be instruments, synths, breaks, or beatboxing.  Or basically, anything except pure vocal samples.  *It is recommended, but not necessary* that everyone submits two instrument samples and one drum sample.

2) Samples can be a solo instrument, a combo of instruments, or whatever except for voice.  You can upload a precut loop, or upload a raw sample.

3) Samples can be any length, but try to keep them under one minute long.  

4) **Most importantly** - Also upload a txt file explaning where your samples came from.  This isn't necessary, but highly encouraged.  If you can't remember where the break is from, ah well.

5) **Also important** - name your samples as "YourUserName - sample name" for easy recognition of who has uploaded what.  WAV or lossless format is preferred, but again not necessary.

6) **You upload/download samples from here** - FTP info - host address dny.webformix.com.  Login information can be found [here](http://dny.webformix.com/)  If you have problem logging in, send me a message.  Find the "hiphopheads MIXOFF" folder in the main entry.  If you need an FTP program, I recommend CuteFTP for Windows, which you can download  [here](http://download.cnet.com/3055-2160_4-10000625.html? tag=pdl-redir_)

**Everyone then makes a song out of the collected sample pool.**

**DUE DATE FOR SAMPLES BEING UPLOADED IS THE END OF THURSDAY OCTOBER FOURTH.**  If your samples are uploaded on Friday the fifth (Pacific), you won't be considered for voting.

_______________________


**Make your song.** 

Your song can only use music/break samples from the collective sample pool.  

**Exception** You can use any voice samples you want; singing, acapella raps, your own rapping, scratching.

___________________

**Upload your final track**  

**Due Date: The end of Saturday, October 20**

You have a little over two weeks to make a track.

1) There is a folder already created for placing your tracks.  You can upload your track any time before the due date.

2) Please name your file, "YourUserName - Song Name"

3) **Also**, include a txt file explaining which samples you used, including whatever voice samples  Also nice to include is what software/hardware you used.  

________

**Voting** 

Due date is October 27, one week after tracks are due.  Create a text file, and name your first, second, and third favorite tracks. First favorites get 5 points in voting, second gets 3, third gets 1.  Add the points up, that's the winner.  

_____________

If this is your first time making music, I recommend Sound Forge and Fruity Loops, which may or may not be able to be found on torrenting sites.  Sound Forge is good for cutting samples to make loops/etc, Fruity Loops is a fairly easy to use sequencer.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [MIXOFF] "Official" entry thread.  Details inside.   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-10-01 04:36:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This thread is to provide information on what the mixoff is, how it works, and how you can join.  

The simple explanation - everyone who wants to participate contributes three samples.  Out of the collected sample pool, users create songs.  At the end we vote on favorite songs.

Detailed explanation - 

**To participate you must first upload three samples.**

1) These must be instruments, synths, breaks, or beatboxing.  Or basically, anything except pure vocal samples.  *It is recommended, but not necessary* that everyone submits two instrument samples and one drum sample.

2) Samples can be a solo instrument, a combo of instruments, or whatever except for voice.  You can upload a precut loop, or upload a raw sample.

3) Samples can be any length, but try to keep them under one minute long.  

4) **Most importantly** - Also upload a txt file explaning where your samples came from.  This isn't necessary, but highly encouraged.  If you can't remember where the break is from, ah well.

5) **Also important** - name your samples as "YourUserName - sample name" for easy recognition of who has uploaded what.  WAV or lossless format is preferred, but again not necessary.

6) **You upload/download samples from here** - FTP info - host address dny.webformix.com.  Login information can be found [here](http://dny.webformix.com/)  If you have problem logging in, send me a message.  Find the "hiphopheads MIXOFF" folder in the main entry.  If you need an FTP program, I recommend CuteFTP for Windows, which you can download  [here](http://download.cnet.com/3055-2160_4-10000625.html? tag=pdl-redir_)

**Everyone then makes a song out of the collected sample pool.**

**DUE DATE FOR SAMPLES BEING UPLOADED IS THE END OF THURSDAY OCTOBER FOURTH.**  If your samples are uploaded on Friday the fifth (Pacific), you won't be considered for voting.

_______________________


**Make your song.** 

Your song can only use music/break samples from the collective sample pool.  

**Exception** You can use any voice samples you want; singing, acapella raps, your own rapping, scratching.

___________________

**Upload your final track**  

**Due Date: The end of Saturday, October 20**

You have a little over two weeks to make a track.

1) There is a folder already created for placing your tracks.  You can upload your track any time before the due date.

2) Please name your file, "YourUserName - Song Name"

3) **Also**, include a txt file explaining which samples you used, including whatever voice samples  Also nice to include is what software/hardware you used.  

________

**Voting** 

Due date is October 27, one week after tracks are due.  Create a text file, and name your first, second, and third favorite tracks. First favorites get 5 points in voting, second gets 3, third gets 1.  Add the points up, that's the winner.  

_____________

If this is your first time making music, I recommend Sound Forge and Fruity Loops, which may or may not be able to be found on torrenting sites.  Sound Forge is good for cutting samples to make loops/etc, Fruity Loops is a fairly easy to use sequencer.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Anyone here still interested in instrumental, sample-based hiphop?  If so, I have a proposal... </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-09-30 04:07:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> On a mailing list long long ago, we came up with an idea that was a blast.  You're probably familiar with Diplo?  The first song he ever made came out of this idea.  It's called a mixoff, and here are the rules we ran by - 

1) Everyone who wants to participate submits three samples.  No voice samples, only music or breaks.  We set a date on when samples must be contributed by in order to be a valid "contestant". 

2) Everyone makes a song out of the collected sample pool, and using **only** those samples.  

3) The one exception is you can use any voice samples that are not in the pool.  This includes scratching.

4) A given date, something like 2-4 weeks after the samples are submitted, is the day everyone has to have their final song submitted by.  Edit: When you submit your track you must also include a txt file saying which samples you used, and any other relevant notes.

5) We then have a vote on each song, and determine the "winner" of the mixoff.

So...what are your thoughts?  You guys down to do something like this?  

**Update** - working on securing some FTP space that I can make public for this.  An "official" post will soon follow here, and probably on /r/makinghiphop as well.  Glad to see the reaction!

Edit 2: [OFFICIAL THREAD HERE](http://www.reddit.com/r/hiphopheads/comments/10qpmm/mixoff_official_entry_thread_details_inside/) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Something about me makes people just not pay attention/care about me. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-09-29 05:42:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I don't know what it is, but there's some aspect to my personality, or something, that makes even my closest friends "forget" about me.  They throw a party, and I'm the last one invited, and only then because I just happened to call to see what's going on.  I'm attractive, I don't smell, I'm fairly articulate and intelligent and funny; it's not like I'm a 300 pound pimple faced basement dweller.  

And they're always quick to hate on me.  The instance that just occurred which caused this post - I made this mix many years ago.  I love it.  I have a friend who loves mixing music himself.  Twice I've given him copies, and he sends me messages basically saying it's crap.  Tonight we're hanging out, and I put this mix on.  He says "Wow, whatever this is, it's awesome."  Basically, he just confirmed that he didn't actually listen to my mix previously, but wasted no time laying into me about how bad it was, even though he (now obviously) hadn't actually listened to it. 

Shit like this happens all the time with me.  I don't know why.  When I do anything, I invite my friends.  When my friends do something, they don't invite me.  They criticize everything I do to the nth degree, even if they don't actually pay the slightest attention to it.  

Part of me tries to use this to better myself.  I try to tell myself, "They hate on you so much because they expect better from you."  But it's hard to do better when it seems like no matter what, they just don't give the slightest shit about me.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> A mashup mix I made a decade ago.  Early 90s hiphop/triphop. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-09-29 05:27:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Of all the announcers, the one that can most fuck off is Bob Costas.  Fuck his boring as shit, personal interest, whiney soapbox bullshit. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-09-10 04:04:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Sorry a bit late - Stuck watching on First Row Sports?  Here's how to make your viewing experience much better. (Also it will make your Internet use everywhere else much better.) </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-09-10 00:53:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I use a combination of Google Chrome, with the extensions AdBlock and FlashBlock, combined with a custom hosts file (works with any browser, not just Chrome).  

AdBlock - Most of y'all are probably familiar with this already, so I won't explain further.

FlashBlock - any flash element on a website, you have to click that element before it will load/play.  So any Flash-based ads just plain won't run.  And the feeds themselves don't use flash, so you don't have to worry about the feeds not working.

Hosts file - this is the most important part.  I've had a few beers but I'll do my best to explain how to create and install the file, and after I'll explain how it works.  (TL;DR - magic.)  This is going to be a lot of text, but it's a lot easier/faster than it looks.

**Note - These are Windows Vista/Windows 7 installation instructions.  If you're using a different Windows system, the instructions will be similar but slightly different.**

First you want to visit [this site](http://someonewhocares.org/hosts/).  This is a bigass webpage with tons of weird websites, all prefixed by 127.0.0.1.  (Near the top of the page explains the different locations for different Windows versions.)

**User Tunococh pointed out - Instead of these next few steps, you can just download the hosts file directly by clicking the "text file" link on the right side of the webpage.  Then all you have to do is put it in the right spot.**, then you can skip a few steps below to "Copy that file.  In windows Explorer go to C:\windows\system32\drivers\etc\"

Copy all the text on that page, every single bit.  Open Windows Notepad.  **NOT** wordpad.  **NOT** Microsoft word.  Not OpenOffice or anything else.  Notepad.  Start/Programs/Accessories/Notepad.

Paste all that text in there.  File-Save As- hosts  
Save it to your desktop to easily find it.  Go look at your desktop now.  Does the file say "hosts" or does it say "hosts.txt"?  If it says hosts.txt you can skip this next step.  If not, follow this next step.

Open Windows Explorer (hold the Windows key on your keyboard and hit E).  Hit ALT on your keyboard - this will bring up a few menus at the top - File / Edit / View / Tools / Help.  Click Tools, and in the menu that drops down, hit Folder Options.  Click the View tab in the new window that opens. You'll see an option called "Hide extensions for known file types".  Uncheck this box.  Apply or OK it.  

Now look at that hosts file on your desktop again.  You should see hosts.txt.  Right click the file, and rename it.  Delete the .txt part.  You'll get a warning from windows saying blah blah blah are you sure?  Yes, you're sure.  Now, the file should just be "hosts" and nothing else.  

Copy that file.  In Windows Explorer, go to C:\windows\system32\drivers\etc\

In that folder you'll notice there's already a "hosts" file.  Rename that to "hosts.bak" - this is creating a backup version of your original file.  After you've done that, paste the "hosts" file from your desktop.

Now you're done, for realz.

The explanation for what the hosts file is, how it works, why it's neat, etc. - 

When you visit a website, you're not actually visiting reddit.com, you're visitng their server, 68.254.153.18 for instance.  So the popup ads, they come from (for a made up example) StupidAdWebsite.com at 208.5.132.7.  

What the hosts file does, it is tells your computer that StupidAdWebsite.com is *actually* located at 127.0.0.1, which is a null/void IP.  It's kinda tricking your computer into going somewhere else, but in a good way.  

This is also useful on many other websites that may be suspicious.  The hosts file contains a number of other known malware/virus websites that will try to hijack your computer, and it blocks those.  Best of all, it does so without using any extra resources from your computer, like AdBlock or whatever do.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> I've seen this notion mentioned twice in two articles, curious about your thoughts; is College football going to seriously harm the NFL in the next few years? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-09-05 17:38:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Places keep mentioning how the rise of the Spread Formation in college is hurting future pros.  It was mentioned yesterday in a Grantland article where they talked about Brandon Weeden, then again today in the article on the Patriots' tight ends.

The first mentioned Weeden might have trouble acclimating to the NFL because of the Spread; the second mentioned the difficulties in finding quality TE's because of the Spread.  

Are Tebow/Newton the first trickles of a flood?  Are run first, throw second QBs going to be the norm soon?  Will superstar TE's fall off the map?  Running backs will become more valuable again? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Am I the only Oregonian who's sick to fucking death of things costing $5.99 or such when there's no sales tax?  Can we just ban pennies and round everything to the nearest 5 cents already? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-08-29 09:17:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Damn you, Zyclin!  I still can't unsee this when I view the Panthers logo. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-08-27 18:40:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> We've had one or two dozen bees flying around this area of our deck for a few years.  Today some beekeepers came to remove them and...well...this is what they found... </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-08-22 03:51:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Found a first-gen xbox at Goodwill for $10, all the cables and works fine.  How can I upgrade it for media-server purposes? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-08-22 03:41:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I've never had one of these, and all the links on google are either dead from being too old, or related to the 360 (even with -360 in the search terms).  

I want to throw a 1 or 2 terabyte drive into it and run XBMC.  Is this possible?  If so, does anyone have links to guides on how to do so? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> You have a button that lets you reset your life to ten years in the past.  Do you use it?  Why or why not? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-08-19 06:20:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I would, certainly.  Ten years ago I was living in Australia (instead of the US), in two bands, and I would have made every effort to marry a friend so I could stay.  

It would have meant I wouldn't have a college degree (and the associated student loans) and I would have given up a (failed) five-year relationship/engagement.  

To me, worth it.  

Edit: Why are people downvoting responses?  I don't get it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> On PED's - or, why I think they should be allowed (to some degree).   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-08-17 07:08:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'll begin with some of (what I believe) are the weaker arguments, and proceed to the stronger.  

It seems the reason for the ban of PED's is that they give an "unfair" advantage to a player/team that others might not have.  Secondarily, that the use of PED's harms the "purity" of the sport and, I suppose, gives the impression to younger-folk that if they aren't good enough they can "cheat" to win.  

First, let's consider Performance Enhancing Technology.  A recent article posted here talks about Detroit's use of iPads for playbooks, and the many advantages because of this.  I won't bother Patriots' fans with more than a mention of Spygate, but even going back to 2005, when Brian Billick was in charge of the Ravens, [Wired Magazine ran an article](http://www.wired.com/wired/archive/13.09/posts.html?pg=5) about their vast archive of digital video footage, which they used to analyze the likeliness of play-calling by opponents.  Was this an "unfair" advantage?  (Their record says no, and any team could have done this; but many losing teams have players using PED's, and if they were legal, any player could use them just as any team could have had a video archive.)

Second, many types of drugs are allowed already.  From simple pain-killers like Tylenol after a game, to receiving direct injections in the middle of a game.  The player is going from playing poorly/injured, to playing somewhat-better/more normal.  This is an allowed use of PED's.  So why is the line drawn at R, rather than S or T or U or V?  Or even A or B, for that matter?

Finally, there are Performance Enhancing Surgeries.  The most recent and notable of which is Peyton Manning.  Undergoing a series of operations, he's (mostly?) recovered from a condition that as little as ten years ago would have meant instant retirement.  Knees are "reconstructed" on a routine basis, and many surgeries that would have previously meant losing a season or two are down to missing just the off-season (Adrian Peterson).  Granted, these surgeries aren't shortening tendons to make people jump higher or throw further, but that they're Performance Enhancing there can be little argument.  

One might argue that the allowance of PED's sends a signal to younger children that it's okay to use potentially harmful drugs in order to increase their chances of success.  But even just the act of playing football exposes youth to the chance of harm (concussions or worse) for the chance at bettering their life.  

Is it really so different telling someone "it's okay to cause permanent brain damage by playing your hardest" from "it's okay to cause permanent kidney/liver damage by using a drug to help you play your hardest"?  If they understand the risks and are willing to accept them, in either form, should we really be allowed to say "sure" to one and "no way" to another?  

Edit: **TL;DR** - Performance enhancing Tech, Surgeries, and some Drugs are allowed. Why not testosterone or HGH? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Were there recent changes to the compass? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-08-15 08:19:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Look, I'm a pretty casual player.  In the last world I built, the compass pointed in the direction of the last bed I slept in.

I had an awesome town built in this new world.  Went exploring to replenish my stock, found a huge cavern, spent a ton of time down there.  Had to go to work.

I loaded the game, found my way out of the cavern.  Got lost.  Built a compass, followed the direction, and it led me to a random point in the jungle, apparently(?) vertically above the point I loaded my saved game from?  

Why is it not pointing to the last bed?  I slept in several beds in the town I built, I figured it would point to at least one of them.  

For a casual player, this is very frustrating. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Beating a dead horse - I finally saw TDKR and Prometheus back to back in the last two nights.  Prometheus was the superior movie.  [Spoilers] </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-08-09 08:44:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> 1) Prometheus has far more replay value.  This is partially due to it being more "superficial" and stereotypical and etc.  Bottom line is I don't want to sit through 2 hours of TDKR bullcrap to get to 1 hour of interesting bits interspersed.  I already know I can put on Prometheus a number of times without worrying about boring b.s.  

2) People talk about "plot holes" in Prometheus.  Sorry, but to me, TDKR contains two GIGANTIC "plot holes" that utterly ruin the movie.  First, Batman is **THE DARK KNIGHT**, and his big fight takes place during the day?  This is just so horribly breaking with Batman's ethos.  Second, as noted in a meme the other day, "Hates guns/puts guns on every mode of transport he uses."  These are just slaps in the face to the Batman background.  

3) So a highly trained martial artist can't make an eight foot jump, but an eight year old girl can?  BULL.  SHIT.  Apparently Bruce Wayne was able to finally make the leap from the HUGE amount of suspension of disbelief from the audience.  At least the "plot holes" in Prometheus required far less suspension.  "A geologist gets lost in a cave?"  He was panicked.  People act stupid when panicked.  That's far easier to swallow than an eight year old girl out-leaping Batman.  

4) I hated Spiderman 3 because it seemed like every fucking person cried.  First Peter cries, then Mary Jane cries, then May cries, then Peter cries again, then the Sandman cries, then Peter cries again...jesus christ, I'm here to watch a superhero movie, not a chick-flick.  TDKR was much the same.

5) People can argue Prometheus was more "mindless".  I'd say TDKR was the same, it just did a better job of pretending to be deep.  Prometheus was at least honest.  "We're here to make a visual spectacle, sci-fi action flick.  Done."  TDKR was some bullshit "let's explore human nature blah blah" that came off as pretentious as a college freshman after their first Philosophy class. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> My local airport ignored a customer suffering advanced Parkinson's, blamed him for being too slow, so he missed his flight, while offering no assistance.  (They later "amended" their mistake, while continuing to blame him on Facebook.) </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-08-05 05:04:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> A Mondrian-inspired coffee table I designed/built a few years ago. (I understand it's not for everyone.) </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-08-04 00:27:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> A Mondrian-inspired coffee table I built a few years ago.  Padouk, Pine, Yellowheart, Rosewood.   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-08-03 23:21:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> A disturbing trend on a lot of subreddits lately. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-08-03 22:42:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> If Mitt Romney hasn't been paying taxes, then why would he support tax cuts for the rich?  C'mon people, try thinking.   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-08-03 22:29:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Still feeling the soccer love from April Fool's?  LA Galaxy are taking on one of the top European teams right now.  3 goals in first 22 minutes.   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-08-03 05:04:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Nothing but purple links, but bored and have time to kill...?  Boardgamearena.com </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-08-03 04:54:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> After going through a few board game threads that have shown up here, it seems almost no one knows about this site.  It's freaking genius.  And I always have to wait a long time for a game to start because so few people use it.  

So join up fools!  Get your Dominion, Puerto Rico, and more on. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> About what percentage of total surface area in a given city would streets and roads comprise?  And does this contribute to Local Warming and/or weather fluctuations? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-08-03 00:40:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I suppose what I'm trying to ask is in a city like Los Angeles, which has so many miles of roads/freeways, is the amount of revealed asphalt a "significant" percentage of total surface area?  And, if so, does all of this hot black asphalt produce a measurable rise in temperature?  

Also, I understand (I think?) that Los Angeles has a lot of smog, which leads to a rise in temperature.  I'm asking you to set aside that info for this question.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What was your "reddit" before reddit? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-08-02 06:15:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> For me, an email list.  Well technically two.  Influx, then Hindsight.  First Influx, which was a DJ Shadow fanlist.  To start.  It was a tight group, but eventually was so flooded with "noobs" that we formed Hindsight; an invite-only "elite" group of around 60 members.  The most popular of us was the musician Diplo (his stories from his travels in India are hard to forget).  

It started as a DJ Shadow fanlist, but we became a lot more than that.  I learned how to shave properly from them, among the other LPT's and whatnot that sprang up.  We had mixoffs, which lead to my short but wonderful musical "career".  

I did a road trip around the US in 1999, mostly crashing at houses of people I met off this list.  And I moved to Australia a few months later because I was debating what to do with my life, and one person said semi-jokingly, "Hey, move to Australia."  So I got a student visa and I did.  Best time of my life.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> SQUAREPUSHER!  Visiting from Bend for a job interview tomorrow and just found out about this.  Anyone else coming? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-08-01 06:03:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> should be sweeeeeeeeeeeeet

edit : i'll be the guy in the blue bathing ape shirt.  flash me the reddit gang sign to say waddup.

edit 2 : um, i don't understand the downvotes?  did i piss off the hipsters?  is suggesting an impromptu mini-meetup off limits for this subreddit?   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What really little moment in a terrible movie will you never forget for being awesome? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-07-31 05:00:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Mine was the remake of "Planet of the Apes".  Spoilers follow, but really this movie is pretty spoiled as it is, so you shouldn't worry too much.  

In the final scene, where Mark Whalberg faces off against the main Damn Dirty Ape, and the original tiny chimpanzee shows up.  

And the gorilla just smacks the living shit out of the tiny chimp.  This backhand that sends the chimp flying 50 feet through the air.  

I lost my shit.  Laughing so fucking hard.  Primarily because this is the closest Hollywood would come to hitting a child.  Children are so sacrosanct in movies, this was like watching an 8 year old get smacked the hell out of.  

Have you had similar? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Do you have a #2 team you're cheering for this season?  Who and why? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-07-31 00:28:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> When the Saints signed Brees, it was them.  After they won the Super Bowl, I decided to start picking a new team every year.  Last season was the Buccaneers, whoops!  (Though I think they'll bounce back this year.)

This year I'm still debating.  Redskins or Cardinals.  Redskins because RG3, and I'd like to see them beat Eli and Romo.  Or Cardinals because I think they're a "fringe" team that could do better than most people expect. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Are there any alternate announcer teams you can listen to online?  (Preferably comedians) </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-07-29 21:17:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> When I was living in Australia during the Olympics there, a group of local comedians would radio broadcast their own commentary.  It was fuckin hilarious muting the TV and listening to them instead.

Tried googling but couldn't get any good results.  

Does such a thing exist?  If not, any redditors feel like starting one? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> I thought I was doing well.  Last night, I had a very literal dream where she was the main star.  Back to square 1. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-07-29 02:01:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Me 31, her 27.  Dated 4.5 years or so, engaged for the final 8 months, broken up for a year and a month now.  

We kept in contact the first 6 months or so.  Somewhat.  Sometimes lovey emails, sometimes hate emails, sometimes sad emails.  I finally said "no more" and broke off all contact.  But shortly after the one year "anniversary" of our split, she emailed me, and we talked a bit.  

And while exchanging emails, I thought I was finally over it.  I felt good.  I met a new lady shortly after.  I thought, "Yes, finally, I've moved on."

Today I woke up at 4 AM, after a dream in which she was the main star.  And it was the least-abstract dream I've had in some time.  No abrupt transitions, no weird gorillas that could talk, nothing like that.  My dream was basically "a day in the life of", where I was trying to convince her we should get back together, and she said no; which is, basically, what happened those many months ago.  

And now I feel like I'm back at the same spot I was a year ago.  Even the cheesiest love song that played on the radio at work made me think of her.  Nearly broke down a few times.  

How do you move on when your own subconscious is working against you? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Dear r/NFL'ers - this started as a joke on nflcirclejerk, but I'm actually curious - why do so many of you contribute to a good discussion, but refuse to vote on the thread? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-07-28 07:02:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's a bit of a trend that's been on the upswing over the months.  I kinda figured in the offseason the opposite would happen, but no.

Also, please note, I'm not speaking in 100% absolutes.  There are exceptions to the above statement, I agree.  **Generally,** this has been my observation.  Similarly, I understand discussions don't always need to be from self. posts but can take place in imgur.com links about Rex Ryan's weight loss.  Finally, I also understand that 500 comments does not = 500 unique commenters, and many people add many comments to a single thread.

When people talk about why r/NFL is great, it's generally agreed the discussions are why.  But you guys are damn freaking stingy with upvoting the threads that inspire the discussions.  

A few examples - 

[What's your "Holy shit, they do know what they're doing" moment?](http://www.reddit.com/r/nfl/comments/x9kxa/whats_your_holy_shit_they_do_know_what_theyre/) - 106 comments, 16 total votes, 13 upvotes.  0.15 votes per coment.

[What was the worst Super Bowl of all time?](http://www.reddit.com/r/nfl/comments/x8b4u/what_was_the_worst_super_bowl_of_all_time/) 155 comments, 32 total votes, 30 upvotes.  0.2 votes per comment.

[Will Tom Brady's two Super Bowl loses affect his place in history?](http://www.reddit.com/r/nfl/comments/x7zso/will_tom_bradys_two_super_bowl_loses_affect_his/) 160 comments, 49 total votes, 36 upvotes.  0.3 votes per comment.

[What is the biggest "If" for your team this year?](http://www.reddit.com/r/nfl/comments/x769t/what_is_the_biggest_if_for_your_team_this_year/) 397 comments(!), 62 total votes(?!?!), 56 upvotes.  0.15 votes per comment.  

/r/NFL - Y U SO STINGY about something you like so much, namely, discussions?  They're buried under twitters and imgur links because they don't get any upvote love. 

If you really love discussions, help get them to the front page of /r/nfl, eh?

Edit: Now you've just upvoting this thread and not commenting to fuck with me.  Damn you ironic bastards!

Edit 2: Also I throw off my own statistics since I comment on my own posts a lot.  Cause I'm vain like that. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Dear London, if announcers are required to explain why your opening ceremony is neat, you're doing it wrong.  Signed, China, Norway, and everyone else. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-07-28 05:43:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah the announcers are annoying, but seriously, without them this would just be a lot of "uhhhh....hmmm.....uhhhhhhmmmmm..." </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> THERE AREN'T ENOUGH GOOD DISCUSSIONS.  OH THERE'S ONE, LET'S LEAVE 500 COMMENTS BUT NOT UPVOTE SO IT'S HIDDEN UNDER TWITTER NEWS. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-07-28 02:06:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Has anyone built a media-center system where I can queue all ~10,000 of my video files in a single playlist, hit play, and watch? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-07-25 07:21:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I've used a second computer with VLC, but VLC seems to have a limit on playlist sizes (I think around ~2,000?).  Tried a few other PC-based media players, and they all seem to have similar issues, or codec problems.  

A friend had an X-Box with XBMC, but IIRC that also had a limit to playlist size.

All I'm looking for is to basically create my own "TV channel", where everything I have plays randomly non-stop.  Turn on the screen and something's on, without having to switch between a number of playlists or things like that.  

Does such a thing exist?

Edit Update: So I've got a few great answers regarding PC software, and I'll end up using one or the other.  

Is there a stand-alone device (like an X-Box running XBMC) that can do something like this, that doesn't require a PC?  Like that Boxxee thing or whatever? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> I've seen so much amateur porn, but I've never seen anyone I know. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-07-25 06:30:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Regarding "movie etiquette" - the only interruptions I've experienced lately haven't been from patrons, they've been from the employees. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-07-24 19:31:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Last night I saw two/three movies.  I caught the screenings of the two episodes from The Next Generation that were being shown in theaters, and the friends I went with hadn't seen the Avengers yet and wanted to, so fuck it, I went to that too.  

There wasn't a single cell phone that went off during any of the three screenings.  

However, twice per screening (a total of six times), about 10 minutes into the start and 10 minutes before the end of each, some staff member came in with a clipboard, stood at one end of the aisle and used a small flashlight to look at his board.  He then preceded to walk along the front of the theater, in front of the whole length of the screen, to check to make sure the exit door was properly closed, I guess to make sure people couldn't sneak in.  

Thinking back on past movie-going experiences, I don't think this is a rare occurrence at all.  And it's really fucking annoying.  

If the manager who posted about etiquette the other day reads this - please don't have your staff do this.  Is the threat of someone sneaking in really so great that you'll purposely interrupt my immersion?  I thought you didn't really make much money from the tickets anyway, most of your money came from concessions.

/rant </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> MY HOUSE  YOUR HOUSE TRASH TALK THREAD [SEASON 2 SPOILERS] </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-07-24 17:50:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This is something that takes place at places like /r/NFL, /r/soccer, and /r/olympics, and it's a lot of fun.  Thought it was worth a shot here.

RULES!

1) **Do not make things personal.**  It's meant to be good-spirited teasing, not actual insults.

2) If you're going to mention a future event that hasn't been in the show yet, spoiler tags still apply.  You do not have to use spoiler tags for anything that has been shown in the series so far.

3) TRASH TALKING ONLY WORKS IN ALL CAPS!

LET'S GET IT ON!

HEY HOUSE GREYJOY, YOUR GOD WAS SO SICK OF DEALING WITH YOU HE DROWNED HIMSELF.

**EDIT:  Some spoilers are sneaking in without tags.  They're mostly pretty minor, but as a warning, if you're the slightest bit worried about events past Season 2, you might not want to read this thread.**

Edit 2: Well this certainly exceeded my expectations by a large margin. Group hug thread next! ...or not. But thanks for contributing! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Any Star Trek geeks heading to the screening of the Next Generation at Old Mill tonight? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-07-24 02:22:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Debating whether I should wear my uniform...

Seeya there!

Edit: For those who were there, I was the one who yelled "Wooooooooooo!" at the start of the first episode, and at the end of the second episode yelled, "This is bullshit, no Darth Vader?!" </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> A problem with assuming a second identity </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-07-23 08:40:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> LPTea: Stop making tea like a chump.  3 different tea making methods. (Single cup, iced, many cups.) </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-07-21 02:09:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Best games for mediocre computers? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-07-20 18:46:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> My computer is a bit crap and I want to be a part of the Steam Sale. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What was the most amazing game you saw...wait for it...that your team lost? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-07-18 10:16:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> For me, the [2007 Vikings v Chargers](http://www.nfl.com/videos/nfl-game-highlights/09000d5d803e86e1/NFL-GameDay-Chargers-vs-Vikings-highlights) game.  Final score: Vikings 35 - 17 Chargers.  

LT breaks one of Jim Brown's records, Antonio Cromartie makes a record-breaking insane return on a field goal, Adrian Peterson sets a record for most yards in a single game with 315 yards from scrimmage.  

The game was played on my birthday no less.  

Just an all around insanely fun game to watch, even if it ended in defeat for my Chargers.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Our hero realizes obesity really is a problem in America </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-07-18 08:55:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Hey r/music, what apps/websites do you use to find good concerts to go to? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-07-18 02:56:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I live in a small town, so I have to drive to either Portland or San Fran to find a good show.  I tried just googling to find a website, but the ones I've found so far are awful.  There aren't any ways to browse by genre, for instance.  It's pretty much just every show they can find thrown together by date.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What's the closest encounter you've had with a deadly animal of some sort? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-07-17 07:39:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> For me, it was being within a few inches of an Australian [funnel web spider](http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Sydney_funnel-web_spider)

I'm an American who lived in Australia from 2000 to 2003.  At one point I was living in a house that had only one toilet, which was basically a glorified outhouse.  A separate room, completely detached from the house itself.  The "window" was just a rectangular hole cut out of the wall.  

So I wander outside a bit drunk, and I unzip and start going pee, and that's when I see it.  About arms-length away, at the edge of the window.  The second I see it, it starts raising its front legs much like the picture in that link.  

All I can think is "oh please god don't be able to jump, please just don't be able to jump" as I manage to squeeze off my stream.  

There was an empty beer bottle left in the bathroom.  I *very very* slowly reach down for said bottle, grab it, and with every inch of courage I can muster, reach over and smash the living fuck out of the spider.  I just smash and smash and smash until the fear of breaking the bottle out-weighs the fear of the spider, which was huge.  

So how close have you come to facing your mortality in the form of another living creature? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> If a beer doesn't have enough foam for you, add just a tiny sprinkle of salt. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-07-17 06:56:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Picked this up from a character in a Dortmunder novel, many years before I even drank beer.  But it always stuck with me.

I dislike when my beer is too flat, I like a good bit of foam on top.  Just a teeny sprinkle of salt will give you that.

Edit: I didn't realize there were so many people who don't understand the necessity of foam on beer.  Drinking a beer without foam is right up there with drinking warm beer.  Heathens, all of you. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Turning things around - in the last 12 hours, I got a girl's phone number, and got hired for my first job in over a year. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-07-16 17:55:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The [kinda lengthy, *very* Socially Awkward Penguin story of the girl I posted here](http://www.reddit.com/r/self/comments/wmo6j/you_want_a_sap_i_can_give_you_a_sap/), but there's a good bit of the story I left out.

In June of last year I was laid off.  A few weeks later, my fiance and I split up.  We'd been together almost 5 years.  The thing is, I initiated the split; she really wanted children, I really didn't.  I'd been able to trick myself into thinking I wanted kids, but my last job was working with kids which brought the issue to a head.  

And the thing is, I didn't really stop loving her after the breakup.  It was really only in the last week that I'd finally started to feel some sort of closure.  I don't know how or why, but something started to click, and I felt I was finally ready to move on.  

On to the job - I'd only seriously applied for one other job in the past year.  About 5 months ago Verizon was hiring.  I applied; got a phone call the next day, "We need to fill this slot very quickly, can you come in right away?"  I interviewed two days later ("right away" in corporate time).  The manager **loved** me.  

I didn't get the job.  I was kinda crushed.  I'd had a lot of these sorts of cock-tease job offers in the past and this one coming in a time I was already emotionally weakened...well I basically gave up.

This was the first resume I'd turned in since then.  And really, this was my first attempt at talking to a girl since around then, also.  

I'm trying not to get too excited for either; maybe I'll break the espresso machine or maybe she just gave me her number to be nice.  

But I'm at least realizing that if I try, I can do it.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> You want a SAP?  I can give you a SAP.   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-07-16 07:11:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> As a bit of background - I live in a semi-small town that has a lot of great qualities, but I've often felt I hate it here.  In part because I think there's only a very small number of women who are "my type."  

A few days ago I think, "well, I haven't met everyone in this town."  Today's the first day I go out for anything other than a trip to the store or whatever.  Lo and behold, a friend's sister and her friend (call her Casandra, the one I like) are joining my friends for an activity.  There's a bit of chatting getting to know one another, all innocent.  

Later in the night, I'm hoping there's some chance to get Casandra alone to ask for her number.  Success!  One friend stays out to finish his cigarette, her friend and my other friend both go to use bathrooms; just me and her.  She'd mentioned a place that makes beer ice-cream earlier in the night, I asked if she'd like to go sometime soon.  She says yes!  I get her number, we go back to chatting a bit, friends trickle in.

About 5 minutes later...

Casandra had mentioned a few times before how she was "probably ready to go home soon, order some food," but she was reliant on her friend for a ride.  

Without asking Casandra, I instead just turn to her friend and pretty much randomly say, "So I could give Casandra a ride home, if you still wanted to hang out."

What.  The.  Fuck.  DidIJustSayomyfuckinggodI'msofuckingstupidjesuschrist you didn't even ask her first?!

Her friend replies, "Oh no it's okay, my brother won't miss me anyway," and she turns around and tickles him and teases him and they're arguing and distracted.

I turn to Casandra.  "I'm sorry, I just meant it sounded like you wanted to get home and order some dinner is all."

Her reply: "Oh it's okay.  You could come in and have some dinner with me."

HOLY SHIT.  MIND SO FUCKING BLWON.

Her friend then intrudes, "So really I'm okay leaving anyway, I'll give her a ride home."  

Still, I got her number, and the most epic response to me totally stuffing my foot so far into my mouth.  

A few days, then I'll call, right? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Have we reached a point where we can stop using spoiler tags through Season 2? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-07-15 10:04:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> My opinion on one of the bigger problems with America. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-07-15 08:30:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Something I've felt for some time now, is one of the biggest issues America faces is that the vast majority of Americans have become entirely too infatuated with the phrase, "Suckerrrrrrrrr."  

We've become a nation largely composed of scammers, slackers, spammers, and generally lazy people.  We love the idea of being able to pull a fast one over someone else.  

Yes, there are still a great many people out there who value hard work and honesty.  But year by year, that percentage drops.  

We really just want to do the least work for the most reward possible, from the minimum wagers to the One Percenters.  We love getting away with reading reddit while at work, saving a few hundred dollars on piping when constructing a $200k house by building shower heads 5 1/2 feet tall, bidding for a government contract to repave a road and figuring out how to do it as cheaply as possible to pocket as much as possible, creating a dating website and populating it with employee-created accounts to keep users from unsubscribing.  

There's no longer such a thing as doing a good job, just doing the best job for the least effort.  

/rant </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [Meta?] Now presenting - awards for the best posts!   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-07-14 09:50:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thanks to user (and new moderator) bobbieluvsya, we now have [awards](http://imgur.com/Bmgoj) to give out to outstanding posts.  I can't say with what regularity these will be passed out, but I've wanted to thank a number of you with more than just words for some time now. 

And the awards may even be personally customized in the future!

Thank you all for helping this shitty sub grow!  And a gatorade-and-wine toast to you all!  
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> As a subscriber to r/Soccer and r/NFL, I'm here to say - I apologize for the animosity many fans of the NFL have for soccer. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-07-13 00:13:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> At /r/NFL a bit of a problem has arisen.  Someone has been trolling almost every submission and downvoting every single comment.  Every. single. one.  

After a day of posting comments at /r/NFL pretty frequently for 24 hours, plus a bit of insomnia that kept me up til 5 AM (PST), I noticed most of the auto-downvoting occurs at a time roughly analogous with Europe.  (Or it's an American with really bad sleeping habits.)  Which is to say, most of the troll downvotes occur roughly starting at 10-11 AM, Western/Central European time, and end around 5-6 PM.  

I pointed this out, and someone made a joke about "we should storm the gates of r/soccer and /r/rugby just in case."  

That's when I thought the troll might be a soccer fan.  

But it's very easy to see why a soccer fan might end up doing such a thing.  Here, and at r/sports, fans of the NFL are typically very rude, asshole-ish, and downright hateful about soccer.  

Regardless of whether or not it's someone from r/Soccer, I would still like to apologize for the comments and attitudes from fans of the NFL.  Football and football are my two favorite sports, and I hate seeing fans from one side attack fans of the other.  And, for the most part, it's NFL fans attacking soccer fans.  

Here's to hoping for football peace.

Edit: for some clarity, this isn't a personal troll just downvoting me.  It's someone downvoting practically *every* comment in *every* thread, regardless of which fan makes the comment.  The mods have noticed it happening for awhile now.  And yes I have too much time on my hands, so I reviewed my recent comments and saw they were right.  

Also, I'm not saying this just to (hopefully) get the troll to back off.  On the rare occasions an r/sports thread shows up on my front page, and soccer is mentioned, NFL fans tend to become irrationally hateful.  That's what I'm mainly apologizing for.  Y'all are lovely, despite the many downvotes this thread has. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [Brainstorming] To help the small subs, what about a "Best small shitty submission of the week" or something like that?   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-07-12 22:24:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> From /r/ShittySeduction here.

I started the sub mostly as a joke.  Someone in ShittyAskReddit asked if there was a ShittySeduction, and there wasn't, so I made it.  And for the longest time I didn't really know what a "good" ShittySeduction post should look like.  

It took a few months, but I started to see them.  

[I just met you, and this is crazy, but I have a gun. Get in the van.](http://www.reddit.com/r/ShittySeduction/comments/tpclh/i_just_met_you_and_this_is_crazy_but_i_have_a_gun/)

[I've heard about 'karma whores' on Reddit. How much karma do I need to buy one?](http://www.reddit.com/r/ShittySeduction/comments/u08x2/ive_heard_about_karma_whores_on_reddit_how_much/)

A few others.  I messaged the submitters personally, thanking them for finally showing me what a good ShittySeduction post should look like, and telling them I wish I had some sort of custom flair or other "prize" or something to give them.  

So I thought of this idea, as a way to hopefully get those posts to the front page.  Not just because it would help my shitty sub, but as a reward for a good post.  I feel if they posted in plain old ShittyAskReddit or something, they probably would have made it to the front page.  Instead they posted it in mine, where they had almost zero chance of that. 

Thoughts?  (Also I do see there's /r/shittypostoftheday but once a day seems too often to gain any traction, and a shitty post that makes the front page will obviously win that award, so it's not exactly helping to "spread the wealth," so to speak.) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What really little things always bothered you about any of the shows/movies? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-07-12 07:01:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> In TNG/Voyager, how frequently they were flying around without the viewscreen turned on.  

Like, everyone's just looking at this 14'x10' blank wall, rather than watching stars?  C'mon! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Why do so many people teaching abroad act so secretive about the recruiting agencies they use?  Maybe we could set up a thread linked in the sidebar for the well recommended agencies? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-07-12 06:39:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm exploring teaching English in Korea, so I did a search on reddit and opened up all the AMA's I found.  Almost every single one uses a phrase like this : 

"As for the HOW: It's very simple. Find a recruiter. "

And they don't mention which recruiter/agency they use.  

In the comments some people throw out certain names, but I can't figure out if - 

1) those comments are upvoted just for providing ANY name, or,  
2) an unscrupulous recruiter is using multiple reddit accounts to upvote themselves.

When people have dealt with bad agents they tend to post those names.  But it's much more rare that someone with a good experience mentions which agency/recruiter they used.  

I'm already a bit fearful about moving to Korea, I don't want to end up using a bad agent and getting screwed.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> You mean upside-down pistons don't push themselves up? My dreams of building a car are crushed :( </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-07-10 08:56:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Only started playing 2-3 weeks ago, and I've only done survival mode with randomly generated maps.  After successfully building my first redstone circuits (very very crude ones at that) I began to fantasize about pistons.  

I had this idea for building a car, primarily using pistons/sticky pistons as the "Wheels"...if you've read Snowcrash by Neal Stephenson, something along the lines of the spoked wheels on the skateboards.  

So for the first time I decided to launch a creative mode world and see if I could build it.  

I get why...should a single piston move an entire city placed on top of it upwards a block?  That would be silly.  Or should it just move a small range of blocks?  That'd be tricky to figure out.  

Ah well, back to survival mode! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Advice on dealing with "raw" wood?  (I have a giant cross-section of a tree I'm wondering what to do with.) </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-07-09 06:30:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> For background info, I'm not an entire noob when it comes to woodworking, my degree is in furniture design after all.  However, that was dealing with processed wood - planks and whatnot.  

The other day I found a neighbor had cut down one of their trees and had a whole ton of logs there for the taking, so I grabbed two.  [Here's a picture of one, with my slipper on it for better sense of scale](http://imgur.com/siXBD)

My plan was to use an angle grinder and create...something.  This something is somewhat in the air because I'm not as certain of "Raw" wood properties as I am of "processed" wood properties, such as expansion/contraction, how the wood will age over the years, etc.

One idea I had with this piece in particular was to grind away about 40-60% of the material, attach a few metal posts going upright to support a glass surface.  Kinda an inversion of the typical "wood=tabletop" mentality, and use it as a semi-natural base.  Another idea for a second log (which is about 10" diameter, 10" height) was to drill out some "holes" and use it as a log flower pot.  

So the things I'm wondering about - 

Regarding the table, if I just, say, use some screws to connect the metal supports for the glass surface, is this wood so much more likely to deform (since it still has a higher moisture content) that it will eventually pop out the screws?  

Am I able to just grind/sand to a nice surface and apply a good varnish, and it will mostly look the same from then on?  Or will there be a significant water/color loss over time, since it's higher moisture content than properly treated wood?  

For the log flower pot idea, similarly, can I apply a thick enough varnish/lacquer/whatever on the surfaces that house the plant (drilling holes to provide drainage), that the water from watering the plants won't harm the wood?  Or after some amount of time, will watering the plants cause the wood to rot from being too moist? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Can we try to institute a reddit-wide ban of pictures of wikipedia edits? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-07-09 05:52:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> STNG - S05E02 - The reason I believe Picard is the best damn captain ever. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-07-04 06:42:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This is the episode that introduces Ro Laren. 

The way Picard deals with Ro, Admiral Kennelly, is so god damn awesome.  And why is it so awesome?  Because it's so understated, subtle...bottom line is it was damn well played.  To me, Sisko, Janeway, they would have been entirely overstated, yelling and demanding and being antagonistic...

In poker it's called the "slow play", where you keep making the minimum bet in order to "stay in the game" when you actually have a great hand.  That's what Picard does, that the other captains would only pull off occasionally.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [Suggestion] New material - Silver.  Suggested uses included. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-07-04 06:25:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Base info: Roughly as rare as gold, more common in caves under tundra regions.  

Creates (alone) :

Silver ingot.

Silver Sheet - 3 silver ingots in a row.  Solid light-grey with glass-like highlights, 1/4-height block, can be placed on any surface (ground, wall, ceiling). On ceiling - if block above is removed, silver drops as well.  Persists on walls/ground.

Silver Coins - Does not require multiple-slots for creation, however, only able to be created through multiples of 4 ingots.  4 ingots = 1 coin.  i.e. The only possible creations are 4 ingots for 1 coin, 8/2, 12/3, 16/4, 20/5, etc... (i.e. pressing 'e' all of your ingots will be in one slot, for creation on the fly, but requires the specific numbers still.)

Created (combined with other materials) : 

Mirror - 3 wood planks left column, 3 wood planks right column,  2 glass panes middle column (top and bottom slots), 1 silver sheet center = 1x1 mirror.  Can be combined to create larger mirrors like chests/art.  Only reflects a five-block distance.

Quicksilver - Single column, coal on top, water in a bucket in the middle (bucket persists, water removed), silver ingot on the bottom.  Quicksilver combines with iron to create steel.  (Say, 3 quicksilvers to 1 iron = 1 steel.)  ((Steel, for now, only to be used for armor/tools.  Steel helmet, steel axe, steel sword...))

Silver-tipped Arrows - 4 arrows + 1 silver ingot = 2 silver-tipped arrows.  50% chance to one-hit kill undead mobs.  

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Back again with more probably noob questions/observations about NPC villages/villagers. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-07-04 05:32:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Heyo!  So.  Found a village.  Started rocking it. More questions have arisen.

1) Can you create a specific type of villager (eventually) by creating their specific buildings?  My village didn't have a blacksmith, so I build a forge following the blueprints from the minecraft wiki, hoping that would create one.  Technically, I'm 3 stone bricks short from completing the roof, but everything else is there.  Will a blacksmith eventually spawn from breeding and take up occupation there?  

2) Does there need to be an equivalent of a "local economy" in order to encourage a population increase?  i.e. Aside from just doors, do I need to build more wheat farms/churches/forges?  

2b) Similarly, does the environment need to be population-friendly to encourage population growth?  The village I found was smack dab in the middle of the desert.  I've imported a ton of grass/dirt and trees, and I notice during the day that a large proportion of villagers enjoy spending time in the grass.  It makes me wonder if I should attempt grassing-over my entire village.

3) Is there ever a way to make a village completely safe from hostile mobs?  I've got a giant wall surrounding everything, but does the village need to be 100% enclosed (as in create a roof over everything) to keep hostile mobs out?  Or will littering the ground with torches eventually keep them away?

4) Can someone tell me what's wrong with my [apartment building](http://imgur.com/DO4QR)?  It doesn't seem to be spawning anything, and no one stays there at night.  Is it because I got greedy and built all three levels at once?  Should I have built one level, waited for all the rooms to be taken up, then the second level, then the third?  It's only just across "the street" from a regularly inhabited, naturally created building.  Would replacing the wool carpets with glass blocks cause them to be inhabitable?  (The reason for confusion is I occasionally, but very rarely, see an NPC spend the night in one of the rooms, but it's typically one maximum.)

5) Oh man I love this game.  Two weeks in, five different maps, a dozen (or two) deaths that make me rip my hair out.  And I haven't even gotten into redstone circuitry yet. 

Some other random observations - sandstone works as a building material, even though the discussion on the minecraft wiki says it doesn't.  My sandstone buildings are thriving, while my cobblestone apartments are failing.  

Iron Golems are idiots.  3 out of my 5 routinely get stuck in a 1-block deep pond and just sit there confused until I push them out using stairs.  A day or two later and they end up right back in the same spot.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> I can't find the answer I'm looking for in google/forums, so I bring my (probably really noob) questions to you - NPC VILLAGES?!?!?! </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-06-29 00:36:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So I pretty much just clicked "Create a new world" and started doing stuff.  I reached a point where I could start making serious maps, so I decided to go out in search of an NPC village.  After searching 6 maps worth of area I've yet to find one.  So my questions -

1) Do they *only* spawn in flat-land worlds?  Comments in forums made me believe they're more common in flat-lands, but they should still exist in other types.  (My world is a big mix of everything, some flat, some desert, some plains, some giant hills...)

2) Do they appear on a map before you find them?  I've basically been cruising coastlines, figuring at some point I'll see some weird geometric pattern that suggest humans.  Now I'm wondering if I have to actually find the village up close before it will appear on a map.  

3) Are borders of plains/deserts the best place to find them?  On my 6 maps, I've found literally zero places where big deserts border big plains.  Either desert islands or deserts next to swamps or plains surrounded by jungle/tundra.  

4) Do they only appear in multiplayer games?  This game is single player.

I'd prefer not starting a new map just to get villages, but I also don't want to feel like I'm "missing out" by not having villages on this map.  (Also I don't want to do mods/hacks or things of that nature.)

Thanks!

Edit: PS - I'm quite certain I had "generate buildings" turned on when the map was created.  I found an abandoned mine, so that means there should be villages too, yes? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> In the first Iron Man, he tried to beat the SR-71's maximum altitude record.  What altitude did he achieve before his system crashed? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-06-19 01:41:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Surely one of you can work it out based on the visuals provided. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Something I've come to appreciate in movies, thanks to downloading - In primarily English-speaking movies, not having subtitles for foreign speech. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-06-19 01:11:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm re-watching Iron Man 1, and there are many scenes during his capture where his Afghan/Arab wardens speak a foreign language, and originally there are subtitles so I knew what they were saying.  

In the downloaded version, no subtitles, so I have no idea what they're saying.  And I love it.  I just have to guess based on the acting/direction.  And it's more immersive, in that I don't understand these languages, so I shouldn't be able to know what they're saying. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> This was a study based on soccer, but I wonder what the results from the NFL would be - Enthusiastically celebrating a score increases your team's chance at winning.   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-06-16 09:15:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [The study](http://www.alphagalileo.org/ViewItem.aspx?ItemId=79505 CultureCode=en)

Again, this is only related to soccer, and only related to penalty-kick shootouts at the ends of draws. 

I'd be curious if a similar study was conducted in the NFL.  People oft complain about the NFL being the "No Fun League."  Are the crackdowns on celebrations really helping, or harming?   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Are you a good cook, but always fail at some very simple thing? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-06-16 05:55:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> For me it's baking a potato.  I make awesome curries, pasta sauces, lasagnas, soups...

But I cannot bake a decent potato to same my freaking life.  Maybe 1 out of 5 is successful.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Sound waves interfere with other sound waves. So do light waves interfere with one another? If light is composed of particles, particles still interfere with one another. Is light really some third other thing we don't understand yet? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-06-15 11:07:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> TIL - During penalty shoot-outs, if a player excitedly celebrates a successful goal, their team is more likely to win.  (Being "classy" hurts your teams chances.) </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-06-14 02:17:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Marketing Futurology. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-06-14 02:02:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This started as a comment in another thread that I thought I should expand upon here.

Futurology could use something like a Marketing/PR Department.  

Off the top of my head - convincing Intel/IBM to set up manufacturing facilities on the moon.  

CPU's require silica, found in abundance in lunar regolith.

The manufacturing facilities require some of the cleanest/purest air on Earth.  On the moon that's not a worry; put workers in a spacesuit and they can work in a sealed (and automatically sterilized) vacuum. 

They also require intense heating, 1500-2000 degrees Celsius.  A solar reflector removes the majority of energy costs needed for that.   

And they already spend billions to set up these facilities here.  

Living in Oregon, I see plenty of towns that were created for a specific industry (logging).  Some industries may be able to be convinced to do the same with the Moon. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> You keep using that word. I do not think it means what you think it means. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-06-13 07:19:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> I believe I know what the "problem" with Futurology/the Singularity is, in terms of general acceptance of the notion. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-06-11 07:01:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The claims that often spring from such notions are that we (the majority of carbon-based sentient bipedal life) will some day, whether in 20 years or 80 or 200, achieve "immortality", most often through downloadable replications of our personality.

The problem that I see with this is a notion that I've seen repeated several times in several places, so I will just do a rough paraphrasing of the general sentiment -

"When you tell someone they're a million times more likely to get cancer from standing near paint fumes, the number is so large they find it laughable.  Tell someone they're 10 times more likely to get cancer from standing near paint fumes and they believe you."

This seems to me the fundamental "flaw" in Futurology - it will be hard to gain true acceptance as an idea because it promises **too** much.  

This thought sprang from thinking how many posts here I should try to post in the general reddit subs, and how none of them would be believed/upvoted.  

If we told people about just the first 10 years of Russia2045 (or whatever), they might understand/accept enough to begin seriously considering it, even if sporadically.  When we tell people the *entire* Russia2045 concept, it becomes an idea they find laughable.  

[Note: I was able to convince a writer from Cracked.com about all the Singularity had to offer...kinda...](http://www.cracked.com/blog/5-plausible-ways-humans-could-become-obsolete/) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Ladies, how frequently do you enjoy sex? (Not necessarily orgasm.) </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-06-11 06:39:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> A few notes/further questions/etc. -

First, I don't mean how often do you orgasm.  This seems to vary wildly.  But even if you don't orgasm, are you still enjoying the act?

Second, was there a time you went from not enjoying to enjoying?  Was it a specific person, but other people after continued the enjoyment?  Was the enjoyment confined to the lone person?  

Third, this all sprang from a lady friend who had been in one very long relationship, and only two people in her life.  When she said she never enjoyed it, I immediately thought "I have to show her what she's missing."  It was after that, I realized how often I'd had that thought because of how often I'd heard the previous statement.  

As a guy, I know I've had plenty of "just okay" sex and plenty of "holy lord thank you for these gifts" sex, but even the "just okay" I orgasm so it's "enjoyable."  

If you had to put percents on enjoy vs. meh, what would it be? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Some beers were drunk, some BB guns were fired, a fence was decorated. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-06-11 05:06:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Now that the second season is over - what wsa your favorite line?  Not necessarily the line itself, but maybe how it was delivered? [Spoilers through Season 2!] </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-06-11 04:25:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> As I re-watched the second season in the buildup to the final episode, I think I found my favorite.

S2E8 - Cersei and Tyrion talking before the war.  Just before Cersei brings in a beaten-up Roz.  

Cersei - "This one you like.  You like her very much.  Could it be love?" 

Her mannerisms and expressions and cadence, the shoulder shrug as she asks...I just *love* the delivery.

Edit: ps. I couldn't find a gif of her asking "Could it be love?"  Well it would be love if someone could gif this for me.  I love how she nailed this line. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Any thread on r/nfl </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-06-07 08:42:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Circlejerks are all we do nowadays.

The Browns are sad amirite?!

The Saints were the only team with bounties amirite?!

Manning and Tebow, boy I'm tired of hearing about them, here's 5 more articles about them amirite?!

Pat Tillman is the greatest American hero, what's the Vietnam War amirite?!

Top 3 QB's are X, Y, and Z amirite?! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> (Spoiler ALL) The deaths of characters - an honest discussion, without resorting to cliches ("he kills everyone you care about") </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-06-05 06:27:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So I'd like to have a proper discussion on this subject.  I'm curious about how my interpretations of the books may be skewed based on personal feelings, or if I'm being too cynical when one of my "favorite" characters dies.

________________________

Eddard - This part is still shocking to me, in a wonderful way.  I still find myself thinking "Goddamn" and "If only...or maybe if..."  I think his death was necessary; both for setting the tone of the books, and also because he's almost too perfect not to kill.  Ned was almost like this perfect human, he kinda plain didn't "fit" in the GoT universe.

Catelyn (kinda) - Okay, she was brought back.  Before I knew that, I was somewhat heartbroken, though not as much as Robb (who died at the same time).  I'm not sure if this is simply because I cared somewhat less for Cat.  I've stated elsewhere that I have trouble sympathizing with Cat because she often makes bad situations worse.  But while I thought "She didn't deserve that", I also thought it was also a somewhat "necessary" death, for reasons I can't explain as well as Ned's.  I *loved* that she was brought back.

Robb - For awhile I held hope he'd share a "fate" like Cat's; they sewed the wolf head to his body, maybe he'd come back as a wolfman?  Okay, that would just be silly.  This one hurt more than any other death, I think.  Not because of the character necessarily, but because of my belief in his "righteous" cause.  I still don't know if it was his death, or the death of his cause, that hurts most.  But overall a death I don't think is uncalled for or done just because I like him.

Jon (possibly?) -  This death is what made me feel most cynical about the series, and question whether I'd keep reading.  This death felt the most forced, and taking myself out of the GoT universe, it felt like it made the hundreds of pages of reading about Jon's unification attempts of Crows/Wildlings completely irrelevant.  "Surely" their alliance will break now, so why did I read ~300 pages building this alliance?  But, hey, other characters have survived worse, so maybe he'll be back?  (He has made friends with some magical people lately.)

Daenyrs (possibly?) - Sorry for the disordered list, but Jon reminded me of Daenyrs because, again taking myself out of the GoT universe, it felt very forced and made many hundreds of pages of reading seem irrelevant.  Again, she's not necessarily dead, she certainly has it easier than Jon in that Drogon might be able to scare the Dothraki and save her.  If that isn't the case, it feels like all these threads were carefully and intricately woven together into a rope that was then severed and split for lulz.  

There are other characters I could get into, but that feels like a good start. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Been re-watching the show with my dad, who's going very deaf.  It's made me realize how important practically *every* line is.  If you have questions; re-watch previous episodes and pay *careful* attention. [TV Spoilers, both seasons] </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-06-04 18:27:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> For instance, lots of people are asking about Qorin Halfhand.  Why did he and Jon fight, why did Jon kill him.  If you re-watch the episode in which they're captured, or even just the "Previously on Game of Thrones intro" for S2E10, it's kinda obvious.  

That's just the most obvious question I can think of since it's most recent.  But I know I've seen dozens of other questions that can **easily be answered by paying careful attention to previous episodes.**  

Another frequent one - Why was Mellisandre left behind when Stannis sailed on King's Landing?  Answered in an earlier episode.

Another - How did Theon capture Winterfell?  Weren't there a bunch of troops there?  Again, the reason Winterfell was undefended was clearly spoken in a previous episode.  

What's wrong with an excuse to re-watch the show?  If you have a question, before coming here, try watching the previous episode or two.  Or even just the "Previously on..." is likely to answer it.  

But I'm starting to think a lot of you people with tons of questions are distracted by reddit when watching and you're just missing key bits of dialogue.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> A delightful discovery - when making guacamole, mix 1-2 tablespoons of cream cheese per avocado. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-06-03 02:37:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I heat up the cream cheese in the microwave, ~15 seconds, so it's easier to mix in.

It keeps the guac a nice light shade of green for a longer amount of time, thickens the consistency, enriches the flavor. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Le Goog is failing me, so I turn to you.  Is it okay to prune yellowing leaves off a broccoli plant? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-06-01 01:26:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The only answers I can find online relate to prune leaves so large they're blocking light.  I'm still kinda new to gardening, and I know that with some plants it's encouraged to prune dead/dying leaves.

I'm still unsure if I should wait til the leaves actually wither, or if them turning yellow/drooping is a sign they should be removed?  Or with a broccoli plant is it best to just let it be? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Don't ask why, because I couldn't tell you.  Half an avocado, 1 egg, beaten together and fried.  I had green eggs (sadly, no ham).   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-06-01 00:06:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> No, no, no.  THIS actor would be perfect in season 3. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-05-31 17:29:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Just started watching Green Lantern: The Animated Series.  First 10 minutes I thought how tacky it was.  Next six episodes made me wish a show like this was on when I was a kid. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-05-31 08:51:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I've just been sucked in.  Red Lanterns, "Now shake hands", characters dying...

The graphics can seem weak at first, but then I think of Reboot, which was on when I was a kid.  The graphics were lacking for the time, compared to movies; but considering it's a half hour weekly show, they're really pretty impressive.  And there's a bit more maturity/depth than typical cartoon comic book shows.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Went into a head shop to buy coals for a friend's hookah.  Saw this and had to impulse buy.  (Then impulse use.) </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-05-31 07:55:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> People!  Stop asking questions about future events if you don't want spoilers!   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-05-31 07:03:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Chief among the dozen+ posts asking questions about the future:

Does Tyrion live?  

Why did the member of the King's Guard attack him?

Did you ever stop and think, *maybe these things will be explained?*

Furthermore, how the @#$@# are the questions meant to be answered without spoilers, when you're asking **specifically** about future events?

Calm down.  Take a deep breath.  Wait a week (or until next season), and your questions will (most likely) be answered.  

Sorry to rant, but one of my biggest pet peeves is watching a movie with someone who constantly asks, "Why'd he do that?  What's going to happen to him?" etc.  Just.  Freaking.  WAIT. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> For folk who love engineering questions, regarding Tyrion's ploy on the Blackwater [ACoK - Current Episode Spoiler] </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-05-30 00:56:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So, a bit of a big stink has been made in this sub lately, regarding the different strategy employed by Tyrion in ACoK vs. the show.  **If you're planning on reading ACoK and don't want to know, stop reading now please.**

__________________


Okay, so in the book, Tyrion uses a great big chain to catch a bunch of ships in his wildfire trap.  This idea never felt comfortable to me.  There were a bunch of ships, being pushed downstream, against the chain, while on fire...

The basic question is - how big does that chain have to be in order to not break?

In order to make your job a little easier, I've tried coming up with the numbers for you.  (We'll also ignore the wildfire for the time being).  But of course, these numbers weren't so easy to find.  SO -

1) There's no map with a scale for King's Landing, but it *seems* from descriptions to be roughly analogous to the river Thames in London.  London Bridge is **265 meters**, so we'll say that's the length of the chain from tower to tower.

2) It is crazy difficult to find a simple KPH/MPH for a river since they're all measured in gallons discharged.  One of the best answers I could find is "a brisk walking pace," so I guess around **4 MPH.**  Then again that doesn't include the mass of the water adding to the pressure exerted, so if you want discharge, **5,696 million litres/day** is average near London.  

3) It's also confusing just how many ships are caught up against the chain, but it seems to be around 8-12 main vessels, and maybe a few smaller ones.  [13th Century Cogs had three classes](http://www.abc.se/~m10354/mar/cog.htm); under 10 tons, 10-24 tons, and the lovingly vague "more than 24 tons".  I'm going to say there are 5 Cogs at 35 tons each, 3 cogs at 18 tons, and 4 more vessels at 8 tons.  175t + 54t + 32t, or **261 tons** worth of ship pressing against the chain.  

So we have a 265 meter chain, supporting 261 tons of ship, being pushed at 4 MPH by the river.

If you don't actually want to do the maths, but have a pretty good idea of an estimate - is it even remotely possible that an iron chain big enough could have been constructed that would hold up?  (Also, anchoring the chains in the towers without one end or the other ripping loose?)  Or are we talking about a chain that would have had to have been like 10 feet thick? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Is a One World Government (or political party spanning multiple nations) necessary to help bring about the Singularity?  Or at least speed up the process? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-05-27 00:44:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It seems to me that only a highly unified Earth would be able to put forth the necessary effort/focus required to bring about the Singularity.  Or, at least, it could help bring it about ~20-40 years sooner than it otherwise would.  

(I still feel that Vinge's original estimate is far too optimistic, and the Singularity wouldn't happen until 2060 or so, at the soonest.) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Am I the only one who finds this superfluous, since ALL debates on reddit are shitty?  Also don't bother responding because you're wrong and you'll make a typo that proves you're wrong. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-05-26 05:00:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Snow?  Snow?!  There is one week until June, Bend.  Cut this shit out. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-05-24 23:16:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> TV spoilers galore (and Book spoilers too) - What prophecies/foreshadowing have you noticed, from early episodes to the current one, that weren't necessarily explained? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-05-24 08:36:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Note: I am **NOT** going to use spoiler tags in my post, maybe comments will.  But you were well warned in the title. **PLEASE STOP READING IF YOU DON'T WANT SPOILERS UP TO THE CURRENT EPISODE.  Book spoilers only go through the current TV episode, so through the early parts of Book Three or so.**  I will use spoiler tags for anything past the end of Book Two/the current episode, and encourage others to do the same.

**Also,** I don't mean foreshadowing that was later easily explained, like, say, [TV Spoiler S2E6?](/s "the House of Undying stealing the dragons, since that was thoroughly spelled out.")  

I finally got my parents to start watching the show (which they now love), so I've been re-watching from the start for the third or fourth time.  I'm only through the third episode with them, but already I've noticed so many.  I'm sure others of you have noticed many I've missed.  Without further adieu...

_______________________

What first started this was Catelyn telling Bran, "You always look at your feet before you lie."  So I rewatched the episode where Theon takes Winterfell.  When Theon asks Bran where Hodor is, Bran looks at his feet. He seems to be looking at his feet again when he says "I've yielded Winterfell to Theon."  

In S1EP1, Daenyrs gets into a bath.  Her servant tells her, "It's too hot!"  At the time I thought she was just desensitized from what was about to happen to her.  

When Jorah finds out Daenyrs is pregnant, he suddenly has to leave, and says he'll rejoin the Dothraki horde later.  I didn't pay much attention to this and I had no idea why, until book four or five.  This also explains [Book 4 spoiler, TV Spoiler](/b "Why Jorah suspected the wine merchant wasn't totally honest")

Tyrion says he's visiting the wall and wants to piss off the edge of the world.  He later pisses off the wall.  (Minor one, I know.)

In S1E1, [TV Spoiler, future episode, book three or four spoiler](/s "Jaime says he would rather die than live as a cripple.")

Finally, and this one is kinda weak, but in S1E1, Jaime mentions Robert "fucks boars and hunts whores," and is later completely fucked over by a boar.  

I'm sure there are more that I'm forgetting, and when I finish the re-watching the rest of the first season I'll find even more.

It just amazes me how well thought out the book/show is, that they have so many little references like this, that can often seem like just witty dialogue at the time, but in fact foreshadow future events. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> I have a hunch it's one of you blokes who's hosted the Bargearse torrent for six years, even without a single download in all that time.  THANK YOU! </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-05-24 04:58:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Lived in Australia from 2000 to 2003, and friends introduced me to this gem while there.  After I left I looked for it a few times, but the net wasn't quite the force in Australia it is now.  

Inspired by today's Micallef post, I started looking up other Aussie comedy from my time there.  When I typed in "Bargearse" I thought no way would someone have taken the time to copy it from VHS, and no way would it be popular enough to still be seeded.

Whomever you are, kind soul, you have my thanks. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> god I hate to prattle on, but I still can't get over how great this last episode was.  [Uhhh...minor/subtle spoilers?] </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-05-22 08:57:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> To be honest, the previous two or three episodes I found somewhat lacking.  They were good, still far better than typical TV sludge, but it was more-so a few awesome moments mixed into the generally-good stew.  I also understand most people think every latest episode is the best, since it's the newest.

But this last episode, just...every single goddamn nuance was amazing.  A single eyebrow-twitch was so perfectly performed, the slight smirk from Cersei, the awesome return of Varys, how they brought together the "loose ends" from the slight deviations from the books...

This show being one of my all-time favorites is not in question.  But this latest episode in particular will forever be iconic of the show, a la Seinfeld's "The Bet", the Simpsons visiting Itchy and Scratchy land, or Sealab 2021's "I, Robot".  It was just the greatest distillation of what the whole show is about.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> I'm OCD about continuity in shows.  Little things like this are why I love this show so much. [Not a spoiler] </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-05-21 20:11:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [This little bit](http://imgur.com/blquD) in the latest episode.  So many things about the latest episode were amazing, but I really cherished this bit.  

I'm the kinda guy who notices "his wristwatch was on his left wrist in one shot, but in the next shot it's on the right" and things like that.  The way the movement in this scene is seamless from one shot to the next just floors me.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> So, immortality.  How do we deal with it responsibly? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-05-21 07:59:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Theory: Immortality "pill" (whatever form it takes, let's assume a one-time vaccination) is available.

Suggested law: Anyone who currently has children cannot receive the "pill".  Those who chose to receive the "pill" will be permanently sterilized.  

Problems: There will still be groups of people smart/resourceful enough to circumvent such a law.  (See: TOR system.) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> I think my neighbor's dog is turning my dog gay.  How do I stop it? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-05-20 18:52:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Regarding team loyalty - everyone says "football is a business," so why is deciding to take your business elsewhere so frowned upon? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-05-19 21:41:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I mean if we, the fans, treat football as "just another business," then how is it any different than me saying "Blockbuster Video was the first video store in my town, fuck Netflix, Blockbuster forever!"  That's loyalty, apparently.  

Fuck you Enron haters, just because they were caught cheating, they were still the best ever.  My veins bleed Nike.  Ford for life.

Edit: The point of this isn't to question loyalty to a team.  The point is to question the "football is a business" mentality. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> So...DAE think Diablo3 isn't that great?  Not even particularly good? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-05-19 19:38:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Reached nightmare mode, and all I can think is Titan's Quest, a very old game, is superior in every way except graphics.

1) If there's a difference between "pro" and "noob" players, I can't tell.  The only difference I see is who gets distracted from the main quests or not.

2) Follow-the-path leveling.  You reach level 30, you get the level 30 skill.  Simple as that.  In TQ reaching a certain level would cause me to reconsider my entire build, skills and items and all.  I'd pay assloads of gold to un-level one ability to put those points in a different ability.  

2b) Leveling cont. Dual character types in TQ.  You could be a warrior-mage, or a wizard-thief, or a spell-casting archer.  In D3 you are your one character, no more no less.  

3) Ridiculously simplistic "gameplay."  TQ made me feel strategy was involved in some way.  D3 is kite and click and nothing else.

Late edit 4) The graphics.  The "fog" in the first act just makes my eyes hurt.  

Sorry, but after 12 years and billions of dollars from WoW, I expected far more.  

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The best damn vegetarian lasagna I've had.  But a damn long process to create.  [Album, description in comments] </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-05-15 19:44:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> So what movie, for you, was made special by the secondary actors, not the main stars? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-05-15 10:18:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Watching Galaxy Quest brought this up.  Tim Allen, Sigourney Weaver, Alan Rickman, they all do a good job.  But really it's Tony Shalhoub, Sam Rockwell, and Justin Long who make the movie.  

Just wondering what other movies are around where the secondary cast shines? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Does my voice sound somewhat different to every listener who hears it? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-05-14 21:40:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Is there a way to create a crunchy/crispy bottom to a lasagna? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-05-14 21:13:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If I spray the baking dish with cooking spray, and put down a thin layer of breadcrumbs, will they crisp and turn golden brown?  Or will all the moisture from the rest of the lasagna just turn them mushy?   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> He did this when we were in elementary school together.  He still does it at the age of 32. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-05-14 00:13:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Only 104 r/Bend'ers, so it's a longshot.  Found some soccer practice cones in a park, looking for the owner. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-05-12 18:28:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Maybe they're used for laying out ultimate frisbee fields?  I dunno.  

But if you can name the park they were left in and give a brief description of how they were stored, I'm happy to return them.

Edit: A downvote?  Really?   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> One day is sunny and cloud-free and 60 degrees.  The next day is sunny and cloud-free and 80 degrees.  Why? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-05-12 09:36:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I have a semi-vague understanding of meteorology in general, pressure fronts and whatnot.  It just seems downright confusing though, that two back-to-back days can visually appear so similar, but have a 30% swing in temperature. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> A friend just posted her first world problem on Facebook, had to meme it here. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-05-12 05:59:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Why are most breakfast foods so hard to keep as leftovers?   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-05-06 17:13:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I haven't been a breakfast guy most of my life, preferring a small nibble until lunch.  This past week I started making breakfast every day, and it was some combination of eggs, bacon, potatoes, toast...

And I was thinking "Boy it sure would be nice if I could just make a big batch of eggs and potatoes."  But it seemed like leftover eggs/potatoes would be...disgusting.  

Are there breakfasts I can make more amenable towards creating in one huge batch and dividing out during the week? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Closing on a year since the breakup.  She's still the last thought as I go to bed and the first thought in the morning.   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-05-01 17:27:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Me 30, her 27, together about 5 years.  

For about 6 months after the break we kept in contact.  One week being friendly and reminiscing, the next week depressed, the week following anger; repeat.  For awhile I even held hope of reconciliation.  But at some point she made it clear there was zero possibility of us being one again, and at that point I told her I had to cut off all contact then.  The thought of being her friend, hearing about her dating a guy...it still makes my blood boil.  

I thought being in a new relationship would help my mindstate.  But no new relationship has been found, and women are just this...weird abstract idea to me now.  I just see them all as her.  This one shares her stature, but blonde and with a horrible laugh.  That one looks nothing like her, but she's wearing light gray jeans that are identical to her favorite pair.  That other girl, she's so awesome, so much more creative...but utterly lacking any sort of critical-thinking and mostly speaks in generic platitudes.  She was just so...well rounded.

I miss her. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Recently celebrated her fourth birthday.  She still wants to cuddle every night and use my arm for a pillow. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-05-01 02:58:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The funniest fuck to reach broadcast.  Cheers to you, Mr. Micallleff. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-04-25 09:14:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Holy shit, 1,000 subscribers?  This sub was like masturbating into a sock, and somehow it fertilized? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-04-25 07:09:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What I think of when people point out typos during an argument. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-04-24 17:41:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Bill Belichik, not wanting to be out-done, has started videotaping the opposing teams IN THEIR OWN HOMES. #forrealnotjoking </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-04-24 05:57:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What are some slow cooker no-no's? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-04-24 05:13:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I just started getting into using a slow cooker, made an awesome chicken tortilla soup the other week.  In the comments for the recipe, I saw someone's turned out horribly, they were asked what they put in the soup, and the answer was Cayenne Pepper.

Apparently, cayenne will make your dish horribly bitter and/or inedible if put in a slow cooker?  

So now I'm a little paranoid about other spices I might be tempted to use.  And other foodstuffs in general.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Number of games I've purchased in the last 3 months : 3.  Number of games I've purchased in the previous 15 years : 3.  Steam, thank you for a consumer-friendly business model.   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-04-24 04:02:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm a "hardcore gamer" in that I play games a lot, but I'm not a "hardcore gamer" in that I've never played a large variety of games.  Hell, I'm still happy loading up Civ2 or X-Com on DosBox and playing for a few hours.  

The idea of paying $40 for the latest greatest game, which I'd probably have to play with all the graphic settings on "low", just never sat right with me.  

Now here I am downloading Warhammer 4000 because I saw a friend play it for a few minutes and I was curious, and it's only $10.  

Thanks, Steam. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> An attempt at quantifying "What is the toughest division in the NFL?"  Finished!  And more stats! </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-04-21 20:40:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [The Google Doc](https://docs.google.com/spreadsheet/ccc?key=0AqvV7vId7_QJdGpmVkZfZFByLVc2ZW5lV3l0NUJhNVE)

**What's included** 

Sheets 1-3) The Strength of Schedule analysis.  Sheet 1 the numbers in no particular order.  Sheet 2 each division in order of how frequently they play future playoff teams.  Sheet 3 each division in order of win percent against future playoff teams.

Sheet 4) Averaging each division's ranking in terms of total points per game allowed.  

Sheet 5) The division's W-L record, combined.

**Faults, explanations, "logic"**

1) I only looked at the last 5 years.  Going back 10 years would probably normalize some numbers.

2) Points per game was looked at because NFL.com doesn't have a "total defense" ranking.  Also if a team can put up 400 yards passing but only earn 10 points, I'd say that D they're against is pretty tough in terms of bend-don't-break.  YPA and YPC could probably be added.  (You're welcome to work it out and message me the results.)

3) I was about to throw in stats for W-L against common opponents, but that's probably the hardest to sort through, and certain trends were becoming pretty apparent anyway.  Seemed like a lot of work for (probably) not very compelling evidence.  

4) Again, this all ends up semi-arbitrary.  Which stats you feel are stronger/etc.  

**Conclusions, interesting numbers**

The division that has played the most games against future playoff teams : The AFC North. (41.25%)

The division that has played the least games against future playoff teams : The NFC West. (32.19%)

The division that has won the most games against future playoff teams : AFC South. (37.5%)

The division that has won the least games against future playoff teams : NFC West. (17.48%)

The division with the best average PPG over 5 years : AFC North, average ranking of 10.45.

The division with the worst average PPG over 5 years : AFC West, average ranking of 20.25.

Best combined W-L ratio over 5 years : ~~AFC South, 174-146.~~ NFC East, 174-145-1.  [A tie counts for half a win.] (http://www.reddit.com/r/nfl/comments/slk04/an_attempt_at_quantifying_what_is_the_toughest/c4eztov) 

Worst combined W-L ratio over 5 years : NFC West, 127-193.

The **AFC South** was the only division where every team won at least one game against a future playoff team every single season.  

The **AFC North** has the second worst record against future playoff teams.  Mostly because the Browns and Bengals, out of 10 combined seasons, have 5 seasons where they did not win a single game against a future playoff team.

The **NFC East** is 1/2 a game ~~out of tied~~ ahead for first at best W-L ratio.  The Eagles tie with the ~~Browns~~ Bengals has them at 174-145-1, technically a half game better than the AFC South.

The **AFC South** has two seasons with the best W-L record.  The **NFC South** is second with one season the best, and one season tied for the best.  The **AFC North** is third with one season the best.  The **AFC East** is fourth with one season tied for the best.  However, the **AFC South** also has one season with the worst W-L record.  The **NFC West** has four seasons with the worst.

There have only been three instances of a division whose average PPG rankings are in the single digits.  The **NFC East** once (2008), and the **AFC North** twice (2011, 2008, and very close in 2010 and 2009 also).

The **AFC North** and **NFC East** are the only two divisions to win 30 or more games per season every year.  

**Conclusion(?)** 

The AFC North is arguably the toughest, however the AFC South gives them a very strong run for their money and in some ways was the tougher division.  And the NFC North, South and East are all very close as well.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> I heard people are an inch taller when they wake up in the morning.  How often do I have to take a nap before I can begin my career in the NBA?   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-04-17 05:52:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What major changes are you hoping/expecting with the new series/movie? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-04-16 03:20:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> First, there will be a new forgotten sister.  Not Nelly.  In one episode, George says something along the lines of, "What? You've never heard someone called Polly before?  Or is it Nelly...I get those confused..."  So I think there will be a new sister named Polly.

Second, Ann will come back and be drop-dead gorgeous (her?).  She'll have grown out of her awkward teenager phase.  

I also think Buster will get a hand transplant.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Minimap on the right side.  I've come to love it. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-04-13 21:00:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It seems no one ever does this.  I tried it out for two games to see what it was like, and it was confusing as hell when shopping for the first game, but by the end of the second game I found it to be far more useful in the lower right.  

Since the primary actions travel from South West to North East, there's far less chance of accidentally clicking the minimap.

I also find that it makes me analyze more of the screen, leading to better map awareness.  Most of the important things are on the left -ally icons, minimap, attributes.  By switching the map to the right, instead of doing a quick scrolling glance along the left, I more routinely seem to do whole-screen glances instead.  

I haven't found a disadvantage to it being on the right, other than taking two games to get used to it.  The advantages might be small on the right, but even small advantages are useful.

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> 32 of 32: Week 8.  Only 24 more weeks of me stating the obvious to go! </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-04-12 23:33:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Did you know the Patriots are going to be pass-heavy next year?

Also Tebow is going to cause a stir in the media in New York.

Boy, the Saints sure are in quandary since they don't have a head coach!

Stay tuned for more keen analysis, as I visit r/Falcons, ask them about their team, then repost what they say here!
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> DJed a party last night and this track got some good action </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-04-08 18:59:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> So I was going through Sound Cloud when I ran across this song... </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-04-07 22:48:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> My fleshlight friend-zoned me.  How do I make it want me? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-04-05 19:51:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I've tried to make a move a few times but it's totally uninterested. One of my friends even took it home last weekend and he's way lamer than me.  What gives? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Does the NFL have the ability to take over a team they think is being run into the ground, a la the Dodgers? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-04-05 17:54:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Or similarly, when an owner dies and passes the team on to their kids as an inheritance, does the NFL have the right to tell the new owner they *have* to sell the team?  Do inheritances have to be approved the way other new owners (Khan) need league approval?

I'm thinking of the Chargers and Rams.  

The Chargers aren't being run into the ground.  But only five owners have owned an NFL team longer than Spanos, at 28 years.  For how long he has been an owner, his name never once came up in the CBA's, his name never comes up in the competition committees, he's almost never available for comment in the San Diego Union Tribune.  To me these are signs of an owner who just does not care about the game, only about the money.

And with the Rams, they seem to be squatting at the bottom of the division for better leverage when it comes to moving the team.  Like  they're purposely being bad to upset the fanbase enough that they'll want the team to leave.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Soccer: If you're a fan of the Green Bay Packers, you might like the All Svenskan (All Swedish) League.  Most teams are owned by their communities! </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-04-03 01:59:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I thought I'd follow a Swedish team.  I've always been fascinated by Sweden, plus the starting times of matches correspond pretty nicely with US viewing times.  (I'd have to wake up very early to watch the EPL).  

I went to [/r/Sweden](/r/Sweden) to get help picking a team, and that's when I was told no individual can own more than 49% of a team, and most teams are owned primarily by the communities.  

There's also pretty good parity, though a handful of teams show up in the top 8 fairly regularly.  
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> For any Packers fans thinking of following a soccer team now, might I suggest the Allsvenskan (Swedish) League? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-04-02 22:31:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Firstly because I'm trying to find a rival.

Second, the League has a rule that no individual can own more than 49% of a team, with many/most teams owned primarily by the communities they play in.  I immediately thought of Green Bay when I was told this.  

Second B, the League also seems to have a lot of parity, compared to other Leagues constantly dominated by one or two teams.  

Third, their games start around 12 noon in Wisconsin.  

Malmo FF ftw!

[Allsvenskan](http://www.allsvenskan.se/)

Also the folks at [/r/Sweden](/r/Sweden) have been [helping me](http://www.reddit.com/r/sweden/comments/rptjq/swedish_soccer_can_you_help_me_pick_a_team_to/) pick a team.
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> So what could the NFL learn from soccer, and vice versa? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-04-02 21:52:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm a huge fan of both sports, though more-so the NFL.  

What the NFL could learn from soccer: 

If it meant 30% fewer ads on TV and somewhat shorter games, I think I would support sponsors on jerseys.  I'm finding three hour games harder to get through in the regular season.

The chanting.  Oh yes, the chanting.

What soccer could learn from the NFL: 

Instant Replay.  Here me out.  Only on penalties which draw a card, penalties in the box, or questionable goals.  The clock/play is *never* stopped.  There is a ref in a booth and he has only thirty seconds to review video and signal the ref on the field.  If play has continued in the meantime, the ref whistles the ball dead (on a successful reversal) and the play is re-set at the spot of the review.  

Also cheerleaders.  

Edit: Also oh my god I would love to see a World Cup All Star game.  (Or is that the same as watching a Manchester United match?) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Thanks to April Fool's Day, soccer is finally accepted in America.  Should overtake the NFL in a year or two.  - Adam Shefter   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-04-02 20:48:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Swedish soccer.  Can you help me pick a team to cheer for? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-04-02 20:07:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> For April Fool's, [/r/NFL](/r/NFL) and [/r/soccer](/r/soccer) recently played a joke and "switched places" and it's revived my interest in soccer.  I've always been very involved in the World Cups (last Cup I went to my local bar at 7 AM every day to watch the matches, good times).  

So I thought it was time to pick a foreign team to follow.  I've always been fascinated by Sweden, and my timezone works out so I can watch Swedish matches live.  (Watching Malmo v Gefle now)

And now I don't know what team to pick.  

I like teams that normally do just okay, but occasionally have the chance to be champions.  Teams that win all the time bore me.  

I had a friend who lived in Gothenburg.  I've seen the name Malmo a lot from following design.  Hmmm....

Edit: The largest factor is what teams I can watch from here in the US.  After a few weeks, the answer is few to none.  So someone in Sweden will have to marry me so I can move there and see the games. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> So guys, should we storm the gates of r/soccer again in September, to remind them the season has started again? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-04-02 16:33:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The 7th of September is Brazil's independence day, two days after the first game but just before the Sunday games.  We could get our HUEHUE's on...

The 8th of September is Turkmenistan's "Day of the Workers in the Oil, Gas, Power, and Geological Industry"...

Not many good September holidays in Europe.  Maybe just start a "Football Riot!" thread??

Edit: I didn't *actually* mean "storm the gates" and I don't want anything other than the good spirit of the last few days.  C'mon guys.  

Also Blackburn 0 - 0 Manchester United, 25 minutes in.  [Match thread](http://www.reddit.com/r/soccer/comments/rpwdi/match_thread_blackburn_rovers_vs_manchester_united/) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The episode in which Dwight Schulz becomes interfaced with a computer, gains confidence (especially with women), and eventually threatens to harm those he loves.   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-04-02 05:00:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Why do they call it football?  More like handoval, amirite guys? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-04-01 03:00:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Edit: Here in Britain, we call eggs "ovalspazwangers," or ovals for short.  You Yanks and your eggs can fuck off! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Felt like crunching some numbers today.  An attempt at quantifying "What is the toughest division in the NFL?"   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-03-29 20:52:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I've never been sure exactly how this was determined.  The AFC North routinely has 2 or more teams in the top 5 on defense.  Is that the only thing people are using to determine toughness?  **Edit** - The original title should have read -

"Felt like crunching some numbers today.  An attempt at quantifying **an aspect** of "What is the thoughest division in the NFL?"  I still think things like Total Defense rankings and intra-division records play a part as well, for instance.  

My idea: Find out how often each Division has played against eventual playoff appearing teams, and what their win percentages against those teams were.  Strength of schedule analysis, basically.  I analyzed the last 5 seasons.  

I've only done two Divisions so far -AFC North (generally considered tougher/toughest) and AFC West (generally considered weaker/weakest).  More Divisions coming soon.  (maybe)

[My spreadsheet](https://docs.google.com/spreadsheet/ccc?key=0AqvV7vId7_QJdGpmVkZfZFByLVc2ZW5lV3l0NUJhNVE)

**If you don't want to open the link or read all the numbers, here's a basic summation** - 

The AFC North has played 41.25% of their games against teams that would eventually reach the playoffs.  

The AFC North has won 25.76% of games against opponents that would eventually reach the playoffs.

The AFC West has played 34.69% of their games against playoff teams.

The AFC West has won 27.03% of games against playoff teams. 

Edit: Added the NFC North also, which'll probably be it for now.  I'll finish the rest through the week and update.

The NFC North played  40% on the dot against future playoff teams.  

The NFC North won 30.47% of games against future playoff teams.  

**Some other interesting numbers that came out of this**

Cincinnati is the reason for the near-parity in numbers.  They've reached the playoffs twice in the last five years (increasing the total number of games against eventual playoff teams), but in three out of five seasons failed to win a single game against an eventual playoff team. (With a fourth season only having one win.)

The AFC West only had one season where they played more teams that would go on to the playoffs, in 2007, with 37.5% of their games against playoff teams (versus 26.6%).  However, they had a worse record against those teams.  (20.8% wins versus 23.5% wins.)

The AFC North had a better win % three out of five seasons. 

San Diego has played the least amount of games against eventual playoff teams.  Second is KC (26), and the rest are all 30+.

**TL;DR - Over the last five seasons, the AFCN has had tougher schedules compared to the AFCW, in terms of how often they play against teams eventually reaching the playoffs.  However, the AFCW has won 1.27% more games, basically tied.**

Edit: I was an idiot and did some math wrong on win%.  Updated.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> My biggest issue with VLC: limited number of files allowed in playlist?   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-03-29 06:51:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I have ~5,200 video files between movies, TV, and music video.  I try to add them all to a single playlist, so it's a Seinfeld followed by 300 followed by a Chris Cunningham video etc...

I was hoping this issue would be resolved in 2.0.  Would an SSD help, or is this an issue within the program?  I use WMP (shudder) for the lone reason that I can add all the files to a single playlist and it works, which leads me to think it's an issue with the program...

If anyone knows of any optimization tweaks I can do in the preferences and could pass them along, I really would prefer to use VLC.     </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> LPT: Never plug in your USB the wrong way again.   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-03-28 19:22:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Halfway through the final season of DS9 for the first time.  A long rambling affair of my thoughts on the show. [Sure to be spoilers.  I'm trying to be subtle but they'll show up.] </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-03-26 11:21:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> **First** It's thanks to you guys I watched this.  And, really, thank you.  A friend had downloaded it (he runs an ISP so I get my downloads through him...) and I was only a few episodes through the first season when his hard drive crashed.  "Oh well."  But because of your recommendations, I got them all again. (And to add to the preface, I'd seen TNG all the way through who knows how many times, and had just gone through VOY/ENT for the third/second time.)

**Ships** This comes to mind first.  There was talk the other day about the variety of Starfleet ships.  While I guess DS9 still uses mostly the same handful of models, this was the first series that gave any sense of scale within the show itself.  In TNG, within the individual races, it seemed all the ships were of the same size, even though I'd seen charts that said differently.  Seeing a Bird of Prey backdropped with a Battle Cruiser(?)...it made me appreciate the ships all the more.

**Next** I think part of the reason I didn't like the show originally was the semi-heavy religious aspect, what with the wormhole and prophets and all that.  It still rubs me a bit the wrong way...though maybe the final few episodes will change that...

**Something else** The Klingon episodes were...more tolerable...than other series.  Maybe after seeing the episodes 7-25 times (like with TNG) I'll grow as weary.  Even when that *one* Klingon came back, I thought I'd hate the episode, but it turned out allright. 

**On a critical note** I found the intrigue of the subtle manipulations of the races (the shapeshifters infiltrating various governments etc) in some ways much more interesting.  I freaking loved the battle scenes, don't get me wrong.  But it seems like Season 5 (I think?) peaked with the intrigue, and after that it became more or less typical war scenarios.  (The hour-long "Captain's Log" episode involving the Romulans was amazing though.)

**Holy shit, I end up liking Ferengi?!**  It's true.  I was so certain I'd hate Nog the most, but grew to love him.  Though apparently the explanation is because it wasn't a child actor, but a growth-stunted adult.  (TIL)

**The new Dax...** She's been in Cube, Kids in the Hall: Brain Candy, and now DS9?!  How does this woman not get more geek-love?  (Not saying I didn't love Jadzia, but de Boer beats the pants off Deschanel foer instance, whom I still can't figure out what the fascination is about.)  

**Oh sure, the usual "inconsistencies"** The shields are at 13% after a single shot, but manage to last another 15 shots and whatnot.  But we all know that's gonna happen.

**The genetically enhanced** Both the Dominion and those in Starfleet.  I'm glad to see a "hard sci-fi" topic tackled like this.  I always felt the lack of recognition of nano- and bio-tech hurt the other shows.  (Yeah Voyager had nanoprobes but...they never sat quite right with me either...also, granted, topics like this weren't quite so seriously considered at the time.)

**Love to Hate** The only semi-regular character I disliked was Jake, and even he had a good redeeming episode.  Alexander or Roxanna from TNG didn't, Neelix didn't and Kess was borderline, and the main characters in Enterprise were barely memorable enough as it is I can't recall the secondaries.

Okay, those are my 2,000 cents. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> My dinner.  A roasted bell pepper stuffed with hash browns and cheese, topped with grilled onions and ham, a fried egg, and of course avocado. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-03-24 05:41:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Okay so I'm slow.  I only just realized.  In the future, they cosplay as us! </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-03-23 11:54:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I almost turned it into an "In Soviet Russia" joke but thought I'd refrain.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> A grandfather of glitch.  Snog - The Ballad (Atom Heart   The Systematic Error Mix).  First time I heard it I thought the CD player was broken. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-03-18 04:06:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Were Davis, Kroenke, and Hunt the start of big changes?  A list of 15+ year owners who are getting pretty old.   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-03-16 19:46:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Looks like over the next decade we might see a new generation of owners come in?  The league is already about 1/4 or 1/5 newer younger owners, but that might increase to half or two-thirds soon?

Bills - 94 (owner for 52 years)  
Patriots - 71 (18y)   
Bengals - 75 (21y)  
Steelers - 80 (24y)   
Titans - 89 (52y)   
Broncos - 68 (28y)   
Chargers - 89 (28y)   
Cowboys - 70 (23y)  
Eagles - 61 (18y)   
Bears - 89 (29y)  
Lions - 87 (48y)   
Panthers - 76 (19y)  
Saints - 85 (27y)   
Bucs - 84 (17y)   
Cardinals - 81 (40y)  

Ages of other "newer" owners:  
Dolphins - 72  
Jets - 65  
Ravens - 52  
Browns - 50    
Texans - 75  
Colts - 53  
Jaguars - 62  
Chiefs - 47  
Raiders - 57  
Giants - 58 (Mara) / 63 (Tisch)  
Redskins - 47  
Packers - (President, 56)  
Vikings - 62  
Falcons - 70  
49ers - 31  
Seahawks - 59  
Rams - 65   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What totally wrong "lessons" did Star Trek teach you? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-03-13 17:24:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> For me, any time a friend from my past shows up whom I haven't seen for years, they're up to no good and there's an 80% chance I'll have to arrest them.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> System sounds coming through music player.  What do? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-03-10 02:13:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Before next season starts, can we agree to not call every late/"dirty" shot a bounty? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-03-05 08:14:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It'll be like the 2012 version of the Tebow phenomenon otherwise... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The American version of "The Office," "Parks and Rec," and others, are all really fucking stupid.  The mockumentary format is 10 years too old.  Just...stop.   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-03-02 07:08:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Supposedly "great" shows.  But, apparently no one understands the basic premise of a sitcom: the opposite of what you expect is what will happen.

As soon as you know that, these shows lack any sort of humor at all.  They can elicit a chuckle, maybe, at their best moments.

Please hollywood, stop making shows like this.  I get it, one worked, so make a half-dozen copies and see if any of them work.  But it's such a tired format. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> LPT-ish: Yes, your microwave and cordless (non-mobile) phone can interfere with your wifi.  Buy a better microwave with better shielding, or the trashy version... </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-02-29 22:19:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Off-Season Review: The comments from the Week 1 Trash Talk thread that came true.   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-02-29 06:38:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I did this after week 1.  Seems only right to do it after the season.  

[runningblack](http://www.reddit.com/r/nfl/comments/k7y3p/official_trash_talk_thread_week_1_go/c2i6a5j) makes a fairly accurate assessment of the 49'ers.

[taybme](http://www.reddit.com/r/nfl/comments/k7y3p/official_trash_talk_thread_week_1_go/c2i77hd) had a similarly prescient view of the Cardinals' season.

and while we're on the division, [rabidoctopus](http://www.reddit.com/r/nfl/comments/k7y3p/official_trash_talk_thread_week_1_go/c2idhem) sums up the NFC West.

[preludeoflight, bluefoot55, hot_soup, friendlyaussie, plink_plink, and trollyg-yo](http://www.reddit.com/r/nfl/comments/k7y3p/official_trash_talk_thread_week_1_go/c2i6vse) make some good observations on quarterbacks.  

[rockon4life45 and lystrodom](http://www.reddit.com/r/nfl/comments/k7y3p/official_trash_talk_thread_week_1_go/c2i61g5) show some faith in a rookie qb...in a way.

[keepswinging's](http://www.reddit.com/r/nfl/comments/k7y3p/official_trash_talk_thread_week_1_go/c2i6tj1) comment still makes me laugh my ass off, and i'm pretty confident it came true.

[monkeysmarts](http://www.reddit.com/r/nfl/comments/k7y3p/official_trash_talk_thread_week_1_go/c2i6rci) is right, they didn't *start* slow for once...

and finally, [arbysguy's](http://www.reddit.com/r/nfl/comments/k7y3p/official_trash_talk_thread_week_1_go/c2i625n) comment is always true twice per season.

Also, a good excuse to go through the Week 1 trash talk thread again.  You guys made me laugh my ass off.

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> AMA Requests: Steve Jobs's daughter, Lisa; or, a non-celebrity pranked by Sacha Baron Cohen. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-02-29 06:05:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The first I believe the questions are obvious.  For the second, my (at least) five questions I'd personally have - 

1) How did the show/movie get clearance to use your face un-blurred? Were you told it was actually a Kazakhstani show?  Did they let you in on the joke after getting their bit?

2) How strong was your suspicion you were having the piss taken?

3) How long did he speak to you versus how much was shown?  Or put differently, did it seem like he was continually asking questions until he got a good joke, or was it one-and-done?

4) Did friends/family find out before you?  What was their reaction?  If you found out first, did you hope no one would see or show off to everyone?

5) And what was your segment (naturally)?   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Who are the little known, probably late round draft picks that you think have the most potential? [Bracket: Round 2] </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-02-29 03:19:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Howdy folks.

I decided to auto-resolve what was previously declared "round 2."  

If there were 4 or more nominations for a group, I took the winner of #1v#2 and the winner of #3v#4.  Now #1 is against #3.  No new nominations!  Upboat whom you like, downboat whom you don't, state your case for your pick if you want to sway the "audience."

If there were fewer than four nominations, I just picked #1 (who gets a "bye" this round), unless there was a tie.

The positions/players who are automatically advancing to the next round - 

DB - Brandon Boykin (Georgia)

RB - Robert Turbin (Utah State)

LB - Brian Hendricks (Wyoming)

TE - Michael Williams (Alabama)

Edit: **No New Nominations!** </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The "Uniform Number" article on wikipedia is actually more interesting than it sounds.  TIL Brian Bosworth sued the NFL for the right to wear #44, for instance.  (He lost) </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-02-29 02:36:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [El Linko](http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Uniform_number_(American_football) )

What started this was seeing somewhere that QB's, place-kickers, and punters are all #1-19, and receivers are #80-89, unless those numbers are all taken, in which case they can be anything open in #10-19.  RB's and DB's share numbers?  wtf yo?

I still haven't gotten any closer to finding out why the numbering system seems downright silly.  

Still, some interesting trivia in there.  

Edit: Oh yeah, what really started this was trying to find rules on colors/helmet decorations.  Still browsing, but here's a [funny line (pg. 27)](http://static.nfl.com/static/content/public/image/rulebook/pdfs/2011_Rule_Book.pdf) - "All pants must carry a small NFL Equipment logo on the front left groin area of the pants, midway between the fly opening and side seam" </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Why don't people exploring arctic regions wear something like a spacesuit? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-02-27 19:29:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Little drunk and on a roll.  Consensus is it's 4th of 5, maybe.  But here's to Voyager.  Chip in! [Also, there'll probably be spoilers] </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-02-26 10:31:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The main reason I liked Voyager?  They seemed to really follow through the implications for certain technologies, at least much more so than other series.  

I'd have to go through the series again to come up with a proper list to back it up, and I'm sure there are a good number of examples in other series.

But what comes to mind is the very thorough exploration of holographic technology.  It was just a toy on TNG  (sans the occasional Moriarty episode or whatnot), hardly mentioned on DS9, did it even exist in Enterprise?  

A hologram trying to become "human" was formulaic at first, but quickly became similarly intriguing to an android becoming human.  Holograms physically (not just "computationally") taking over a ship, EMH taking over command...

Voyager seemed to have the best exploration of technologies, not people.  Probably part of why many find it very cardboard-acting and whatnot.  But part of why I enjoyed it quite fine.  

Here's to you, Voyager! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Could we assume that, despite no particular evidence, combadges contained some sort of neural circuitry? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-02-26 10:01:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The moment sparking this idea was a Personal Log in S02E17.  Sisko walkin around (like a pimp) and the "recording" overdubbed.  Got to thinking, maybe he's recording that log at that time just by thinking it.  

Other things that I thought about that made me think the idea has some merit : 

Picard is in the middle of some tense negotiations between two very hostile neighbors, the slightest mis-step could result in war. Suddenly, **SQWAK** RIKER TO PI---D HEAVY FIRE ......... *ATA DEAD* **SQWAK** 

That would be inconvenient eh?  Not to mention getting paged while trying to reroute a lady's tachyon pulse emitors would be muy frustrante.  Or when you're hanging out with friends and suddenly "Troi to Anotheranotherother, I need to sex u up long time," how could I explain that to my twelve other girlfriends?

So when Riker taps his manly chest and says "Riker to Picard," Picard hears the call internally (not that way pervert), not out loud.  It's not until Picard caresses his similarly masculine pectoral  that audio communication takes over.  (Two-way "telepathy" not possible, just a one-way signal only?)

Maybe there's some secret way to tap the combadge that's never been shown, that activates the Personal Log mental-recording.  Like long-press press.  

** *NEED MOAR?! * ** - Why would a neural connection go through the chest, rather than...the skull?  *fuck you buddy, thasswhy*.  Or, this also allows for remote monitoring of the entire body for medical purposes.  Combadges connect at the chest and establishe (French for "establish") nanofiber links to the heart/spinal column/funny bone/brain.

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> A case of mistaken identity leads to an email spat, which results in my receiving a David Thorne-style "win" </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-02-24 21:42:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The once-a-month (maybe?) r/NFL Bracket - Who are the little known, probably late round draft picks that you think have the most potential? [Bracket: Round 1] </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-02-24 05:44:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Inspired by the [snake-bitten](http://www.reddit.com/r/nfl/comments/q321l/rnfl_i_would_love_to_know_your_opinion_on_this/) thread, had the idea of a bracket system we could do for "big questions" once in awhile.  

So here's how I see this working.  I'm going to pre-populate comments with the eight main position groups - Wide Receiver, Defensive Back, Running Back, Quaterback, Linebacker, Tight End, O-Line, D-Line.  You place your nominations under the comment for that position.  **Only** under the position-comment.  

The four "nominations" with the most upvotes proceed to the next round in a day or two.  

Round 2 - #1 v #2   #3 v #4 in each position group.  

Round 3 - Winner of #1v#2 v Winner of #3v#4

Round 4 - The "winner" of each group then faces the group following.  Winner of WR goes against winner of DB.  QB v RB.  LB v TE.  O-Line v D-Line.  

Round 5 - Winner of WRvDB v Winner of QBvRB.  LBvTE v OLvDL.  

Round 6 - The "winner" - for this particular question, who [/r/NFL](/r/NFL) seems to think has the most potential as a (probable) late-round pick.  

Yeah I know it probably sounds a bit confusing right now, and if I knew how to code I'd set something up.  Really though, it's just creating a thread every two days and seeing the top 4 comments per group.  

And with nominations, people can also state their cases, which would help spread football knowledge around.  So hey all you guys really gotta do is upvote and nominate someone if you feel like it. 

Future threads won't involve all this explanation. 

Without further adieu, let's start a bracket?

Edit: So I said a day or two, but nominations are still trickling in.  So I'm going to wait til the end of tonight.  Thanks for the contributions so far! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Like a grampa handing down his sweet leather jacket, I give you internet youngins the "reddit" of my day. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-02-24 03:15:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Is it possible to determine and/or achieve precisely zero velocity, though out the universe? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-02-24 00:00:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Hey guys! I caught a double rainbow!  Does that mean I have the powers of a God now? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-02-23 20:16:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> I only just realized what a great, pre-built, post-apocalyptic fortress this would make, for around 50 people. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-02-23 18:15:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Buster chose his furniture based on a mysterious William H. Macy's lawn decorations.   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-02-23 08:37:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Why has no one thought of this before?  The ultimate post-apocalyptic fortresses.   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-02-23 06:22:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> My biggest hope: Since the "rebooting" due to the last movie, there will be a rebooted, alternate-universe TNG.   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-02-23 04:03:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I've put a lot of thought into what I'd like to see/what the galaxy would look like in such a thing.  

Either way, I just want to see it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> I can never find the video on YouTube that I'm looking for.  DAE wish Google would buy them out and fix their search? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-02-23 02:13:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Guide to choosing an NFL team to cheer for (Contributions plenty welcome) </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-02-21 23:17:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's a topic that comes up with some frequency, so let's set up a guide. (Primarily for foreign fans.)

**The r/NFL Guide to Picking a Team**

**1)** There's choosing whether you want to root for an annual contender, a middle-of-the-road team with potential, or one of the underdogs.  Based on the last ~10 years or so, and predicting the next few seasons. More details on each team provided at the very bottom.

*Annual Contenders - "sure" to reach the playoffs* - Baltimore Ravens, Pittsburgh Steelers, Green Bay Packers, New Orleans Saints, New England Patriots, New York Giants.

*So-So - could reach the playoffs, "guaranteed" 7-9 or better* - Chicago Bears, Indianapolis Colts, Detroit Lions, Cincinnati Bengals, Houston Texans, Atlanta Falcons, Carolina Panthers, Tennessee Titans, Miami Dolphins, New York Jets, Dallas Cowboys, Philadelphia Eagles, Kansas City Chiefs, San Diego Chargers, Denver Broncos, San Francisco 49ers, Seattle Seahawks.

*Definite Underdogs* - Cleveland Browns, Minnesota Vikings, Jacksonville Jaguars, Tampa Bay Buccaneers, Buffalo Bills, Washington Redskins, Arizona Cardinals, St Louis Rams, Oakland Raiders.

**2)** Choose based on colors!  Or better for international folk, timezones.  [Kludgey started a timezone map, add your region!](http://www.reddit.com/r/nfl/comments/pzxyb/guide_to_choosing_an_nfl_team_to_cheer_for/c3tmebz)

**3)** Based on rivalries.  Maybe you don't have a favorite team yet, but you do have a team you hate already?  

**4)** Big score teams.  You like seeing teams that put up a bunch of points?  NE, NO, GB, DET, HOU, SD are all pretty routine high-scorers.  Others that can often put up high scores include CAR, NYG, PHI, DAL, BUF, and ATL.

**5)** Find a divisional opponent of the team you don't like.  If you dislike the Steelers, cheer for the Ravens or Bengals.  Hate the Tebow phenomenon?  Cheer for the Dolphins or Bills.  

**6)** Follow a specific player you already know and like - When Drew Brees left the Chargers for the Saints, the Saints became my #2 team.  They're not in the same conference as the Chargers so there's no rivalry.  Or read up on some college prospects, see if there's one you like, follow the team that drafts him.

**7)** Follow a Division for a season, then pick a team from that Div.  AFC North is the "toughest" division.  Both West's are wacky, and who knows which team will make the playoffs from them.  Follow the NFC South next season, then choose one of the four teams you liked most.  

**8)** Location - You visited the States and really enjoyed Miami.  Cheer for the Dolphins why not?  Enjoy the NBA and cheer for the Celtics?  Cheer for another New England team then.


--

A very brief summary of teams and their potential next year (granted, the draft and free agency could change this in the next few months).  Also mentioning why I placed them in the contender/so-so/underdog status earlier.  

Also adding an extra note about team's "personality" or perception around the league.  (Bonus World Cup comparison!)

**Villain (V)** - Generally disliked by most of the league.  (Argentina, Netherlands, Italy)  
**Them (T)** - Hate playing against them, but respect them.  (Germany, Spain)  
**SeeSaw (SS)** - Up one game, down the next; Up one season, down the next.  (England, France)  
**Poor Bastards (PB)** - Teams that receive sympathy from other teams.  (Fiji, US)  
**Not Quites (NQ)** - They aren't as successful as people think they should be.  (US, Czech)   
**Under the Radars (UR)** - Generally not talked about much.    (Sweden, any African team)  
**Jokers (J)** - Generally entertaining for the wrong reasons.  (Italy, Brazil)  

* Arizona Cardinals (UR) - Underdog - Though they made the Super Bowl in the last decade, since losing the Hall of Fame QB that got them there, they've struggled.  This is likely to continue, but due to a weak division, always a chance they reach the playoffs.  

* Atlanta Falcons (T) - So-So - They've had some pretty good regular season success lately, and have a pretty talented team.  They can't seem to get it together in the playoffs, and their division is fairly tough.

* Baltimore Ravens (T) - Contender - Consistently reach the playoffs, great defense, an offense that can be frustratingly inconsistent.  

* Buffalo Bills (PB) - So-So - Mostly basement-dwellers, the Bills seem to finally be turning things around.  Injuries hurt the second half of last season. They could be threatening next season, they could also return to the bottom. 

* Carolina Panthers (UR/T after Cam) - So-So - Really, they're an Underdog team, playing in a division that has two teams (NO, ATL) that routinely makes the playoffs, making it more difficult for Carolina.  But after the showing last season, with a few key pickups this offseason, they could contend.

* Chicago Bears (T) - So-So - I'm sure I'll get plenty of flak for not naming them a Contender, which based on the past they are.  Based on the future, playing with GB, DET, and a new offensive scheme, it'll be challenging for the next few seasons.

* Cincinnati Bengals (SS) - So-So - If they played in another Division they'd have the potential to be Annual Contenders.  Almost always a very good defense.  Things look good for the future.

* Cleveland Browns (PB) - Underdog - Possibly the NFL's longest tenured underdog.  The future isn't terribly comforting.  

* Dallas Cowboys (NQ/J/V) - So-So - Usually have plenty of talent, but a meddling owner and a QB who seems to wilt at the worst times, despite otherwise putting up good numbers.

* Denver Broncos (NQ/SS) - So-So - They play in the AFC West.  Could go 3-13, could go 10-6.  With Manning now on the team the latter seems more likely.

* Detroit Lions (PB, until last year, but they went 0-16 so they'll always be PB really) - So-So - On the ascension, shoring up some Defense this offseason could get them in the Playoffs.

* Green Bay Packers (T) - Contender - They should be in the playoffs for most of the next decade, barring key injuries.  

* Houston Texans (NQ) - So-So - They've often had decent seasons, but it was only last year they finally got over the hump and made the playoffs.  Could frequently appear in the playoffs for the next few seasons.

* Indianapolis Colts (T/PB last year) - So-So - Contender, until a certain QB received a major injury.  While they're likely to get the "next Peyton Manning," last season showed a number of deficiencies and they've gone through a complete overhaul of their coaches/GMs.  

* Jacksonville Jaguars (PB/UR) - Underdog - QB questions.  Bad receivers.  But almost undoubtedly the best rushing team in the league.  Probably won't make the playoffs next season, but should do better than this last one.

* Kansas City Chiefs (SS) - So-So - Again, the AFC West, who knows?  But they could have a very scary defense for the next few years.

* Miami Dolphins (SS) - So-So - The start of last season made them appear to be Underdogs.  But a solid second half of the season shows promise for next.

* Minnesota Vikings (T) - Underdogs - Not exactly pushovers despite what their record last season says, they still look #4 in their Division.

* New England Patriots (V) - Contenders - Earned the ire of most of the league by winning 3 rings and falling one crazy stupid catch short of a perfect season.  While they haven't won another since, Patriots reaching the playoffs is one of the safest bets you can make.  

* New Orleans Saints (T) - Contenders - No denying they're an offensive juggernaut.  No question Brees will captain this ship for the next five years or so, and they should reach the playoffs each of those years.

* New York Giants (T/SS) - Contenders - True, they've had some disappointing seasons between their Bowl wins, but can't deny a team that's won two rings with the same QB/Coach.  

* New York Jets (J/V) - So-So - Even with the loudest coach in the league, they were one game from the Super Bowl two years out of the last three.  But the honeymoon with their QB seems over and without a solid showing next season, big changes could be on the way. (And in comes Tebow.)

* Oakland Raiders (V) - So-So - Again, AFC West.  And proud holders of the "Most Penalties in a Season" award.  

* Philadelphia Eagles (SS/J) - So-So - It's always a circus in Philly and you really can't know what to expect from them.

* Pittsburgh Steelers (T/V) - Contenders - Winning so much can lead to a lot of resentful fanbases.  But this offseason has some interesting question marks for next year.

* San Diego Chargers (NQ/SS) - So-So - Perennially disappointing.  Bonehead plays and missed field goals have ended many-a-promising season.

* San Francisco 49ers (PB, now T) - So-So - They finally found an answer to a decade of coaching problems.  Could easily be Contenders now.

* Seattle Seahawks (UR/SS) - So-So - Coach Carrol seems to have silently built a very solid foundation.  A few key acquisitions could result in a scary team.

* St. Louis Rams (PB) - Underdogs - I'm pretty sure the Rams are the poster boys for Poor Bastards.  They have a promising QB...maybe.  Still hard to see them better than fourth in their division.

* Tampa Bay Buccaneers (UR) - Underdogs - Two seasons ago looked great with a rookie QB.  Last season showed a definite regression.  With some coaching changes, could be So-So next year, could be Poor Bastards.

* Tennessee Titans (UR/SS) - So-So - The Titans probably won't do much with Hasselbeck at QB, but that should only last for another season or two while they continue to build up other positions.  But a pretty solid organization, it seems.

* Washington Redskins (PB/J) - Underdogs - When you change coaches and QBs on a near-annual basis, you can't expect too much success.  

--

These aren't my laws and my opinions aren't always right.  If you have other ideas for how to pick a team, if people think I really whiffed on an opinion or categorization, I'll update.  

Edit: Added addendum below. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> People shouldn't play for at least 10 days after receiving a concussion.  Your thoughts on a 32 week regular season, with teams playing every other week? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-02-20 22:27:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Do you think it would lessen the game, that players would be too lazy with two weeks between games?  

Maybe it could improve things.  Pretend the Chargers have a week 9 game against the Panthers, followed by a Thursday game at KC.  They probably wouldn't game plan for the Panthers as much as they normally would, since they'd need to focus more on the divisional opponent on the short week.  With two weeks for every team, every game should have a good plan?

Would a 32 week season, but games only every other week, be more intolerable than a long offseason?

If it provided enough safety benefits that no new rules need to be created, what would your thoughts be then?  

Edit: Some points that have come up -

1) This would leave the postseason in the same format.  For teams that don't make the postseason, they have 17 weeks off (including 3 preseason games).  Teams reaching the Super Bowl have only 12 weeks off. 

2) A variation by ThaCarter - 18 game season, but with 6 bye weeks (I'm assuming spread evenly?).
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Why aren't cures or antibodies communicable/sexually transmitted?   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-02-19 01:05:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I was on my way to Shitty Ask Science, something like, "If I get the flu, and a few weeks later you get the same flu, can I spit in your drink to cure you?"

Then I got to wondering.  I know in the womb there are antibody transfers.  But otherwise...?

Why have all the bad things figured out we really enjoy sex and it's a great way to get around, but good things haven't seemed to figure that out yet?  

Even if there was just some Vitamin C in my ejaculate, it'd be something.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Does deleting old comments/posts I've made hurt my standing with the spam filter? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-02-18 23:46:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Just what organs are used in organic products? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-02-18 19:00:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> I don't get it.  Girls say rain is romantic.  So why do they get so mad when I pee on them? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-02-18 01:20:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Started rewatching the classic Space: Above and Beyond.  You should watch it if you haven't, but if you have, I had a question... </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-02-17 01:50:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> There will be **spoilers**, so if you haven't watched the show but are thinking about it, you might not want to read further.












In the episode Choice or Chance, a shadowy government-ish figure gets his hands on a strange "briefcase" at the end, that when he opens and looks glows red but you can't see what's inside, a la Pulp Fiction.  I guess I missed if anything happened with this?  Any follow up as to what was in it?  Or was this going to be something revealed in season 2 if it made it? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Watching a show created in 1995, set in 2063. An episode mentions 1995 is the last year the 49ers win a Super Bowl.  Last time the 49ers won the SB?  1995. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-02-17 01:29:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Angry Niners fans who believe they've been hexed can track down the writers for the show Space Above and Beyond.  But don't, because it was a good show.  

Edit: Also - 1/3 of the way there guys!  We can do it!

Edit2: Also - Hey guys I can get you great deals on viagra just ask me how! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> So if girls don't like pickup lines, does that mean they like putdown lines? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-02-16 07:51:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Not ST, but another 90s scifi show I just started rewatching. If only it lasted longer than a single season.   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-02-15 22:26:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> You knew it was coming - r/ShittySeduction - because sometimes the worst advice is the best advice. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-02-15 22:16:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Every study I read involves a lead scientist.  I thought we understood lead pretty well by now, what's so great about this metal that it's in every experiment? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-02-15 21:41:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> From quantum mechanics to oceanography to plastic engineering, there's always someone studying lead.  They could at least study gold.  

Edit: Also, if you read the title a second time, did you change the pronunciation of "read"? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> There's 66 of us apparently but no one talks.  So let's introduce ourselves? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-02-15 17:25:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Peter King is still ragging on Wes Welker's drop.  Sorry, but doesn't it sound like the talk of a person who never tried to run a route and catch a pass? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-02-14 01:20:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The quote : "The fact is, that ball contacted the palms of both of Welker's hands cleanly, and he was not touched by a Giant defender. Call it a drop. Don't call it a drop. I don't care. But Wes Welker has to make that catch. Has to."

I know this is something of a dead horse, and it was already discussed shortly after the Super Bowl.  But King brings it up again, and so I will too.  

Ask NASA to design a robot that spins 270 degrees to catch an object travelling between 40-60 MPH(?) and they'll hand you a $600 million bill.  

If the ball was thrown to the correct spot, it's a catch Welker makes 100 out of 100 times, as Colinsworth said.  The sort of catch Welker is asked to make there?  More like one out of twenty, at best.

It's not that Welker should have made that catch.  Brady should have made the throw.  I agree there were other drops that fell on the receivers/TE's shoulders, but this is not one of them.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> If The Day After Tomorrow taught me one thing, it's that Arctic Wolves can travel 600 miles to lower Manhattan in less than an hour.  What awesome facts have you learned from movies? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-02-13 23:06:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> If a bit of food is stuck in your teeth overnight, does it turn rotten by the time you floss it out the next day? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-02-12 20:56:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> I smoke pot.  Does that bias me to the point that it's unreasonable for me to consider this a really shitty "study"? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-02-12 20:38:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> AMA Request : A non-celebrity who was played for a fool by Ali G/Borat/Bruno </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-02-12 20:26:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
