<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject4083</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-16 17:51:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  look at how manly and tough

Which is their primary demographic.

I know lots of oil field workers who have jacked up F250s.  The trucks sit at home 25 weeks out of the year, the other 25 they're on grocery duty.  

100% over compensation.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-16 17:49:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> When I ordered mine I was able to part out specific things without having to get the full package.  I was ready with check in hand and they were able to pull some strings or whatever.

My wife's C300 has the larger screen but no NAV, dimming and folding mirrors, backup camera.  Thats it.  
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-16 17:46:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> They have a physical volume control on the steering wheel. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Who forgot to bring her in? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-16 17:06:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-16 16:52:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> TY.

I'm a net admin, need to really start looking into Python to make my life easier.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-16 06:17:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Woah need more pics!  Interior!  Lemme get a roof shot!  I hate that they call these Targas but they're still sexy.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-15 23:05:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Ah, the new event.  Gotcha.  Totally slipped my mind.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-15 22:55:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Havent been able to play lately.  Did they buff Mei/change her Right Click?   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-15 22:50:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> S65 Cabrio.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-15 19:38:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If you're a Ford person, think the sedans are ugly as sin (they are) but want to stick with the company, paying the premium for a good looking car like the MKZ is fine.  It's OPs money.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-15 19:36:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  $7500 off. Negotiations took literally 5 minutes and started with $6500 off. My original salesguy left me a voicemail later that day saying okay come back I'll give you the original deal. I didn't bother ever returning his call.

Should have driven by, asked him to step outside, showed him the car, and then drove off.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-15 19:32:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  2017 Lincoln MKZ 2.0T AWD Reserve

These are the brand new models, right?  Good looking cars.  Maybe check back in with us and let us know how good a car it's been? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-15 18:53:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thinking back on all the cars I've owned since Ive been paying for them myself, the monthlies all seem to line up at 15% of my post savings/401k/rent-mortgage net.  Be it when I was a relatively broke teenager to now.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-15 17:59:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  To me it was just a spoiled brat who lacks any self-awareness complaining about phonies and the movies for 270 pages. 

It's a book written for 1950s tweens.  If you're  15 in this day and age there is nothing relevant in this book for you.

It, like other American classics, isn't that great.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-15 17:47:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  Should I save some money and get a lightly used MY 2016 instead of a new MY2017?

The answer to "Should I buy CPO?" is always Yes.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-15 17:35:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> They bought a 981, not a Miata.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-15 17:30:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  Unpopular opinion: I think the Cayman is their best looking car.

Not particularly unpopular.  When discussing a 911 versus a 718, it seems to be 50/50 between my friends on looks, with practically 100% of my gear head friends behind the 718.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-15 17:26:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm putting money away and plan on getting a 991.2 when I hit 35 in a few years.  A 1500 lease/finance would be around 15% of my income post mortage/401k if I were to lease one today.  But I want to recast my home and pay off the baby-mobile (Prius :( ) first.

Depending on end of 2017 I may just get a 718 if there's a good CPO out there.

Or just trade the baby-mobile in and get a Cayenne GTS.

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-15 17:24:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Not particularly.  If after all of your expenses and savings a month, a car is 40% or less of the remaining funds, then you're good IMO.  

After taxes/401k you bring home 6k?  1500 goes to rent/mortgage, 1000 goes to utilities/cell/etc.  Another 1500 goes into savings, that gives you 2k left for fun expenditures.  

A 70k car depending on down payment can run around 650 a month.  

If you're the type that really cares about the car you drive and aren't a bar hopper/foodie/gamer/etc, that's a perfectly reasonable financial situation. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-14 16:25:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  Of course you won't get arrested for it though.

Not arrested, just scrutinized and have your life threatened daily by scriptkiddies. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-14 16:16:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If the MBP was enough for you to consider buying it, so is the SB.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-14 16:10:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  with the glass roof.

Yeah but not really a Targa. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-14 16:09:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> On top of that, now that the Panamera line all have Turbos (or is it like Macan where just the entry does?) what's the difference between the base Panamera with Turbos and the Panamera Tubro?  More Turbos?  Larger engine block?

I assume the same for the 991.2? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-14 16:07:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Some of us just have geriatric souls. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-14 04:13:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  But not a deal breaker by any means

Speak for yourself.  ;)   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-14 04:12:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  but the RS3 is supposed to start around $50k, CLA45 is north of that as base IIRC?

That's Mercedes for you.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-13 21:52:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Surface Book still super ugly.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-13 21:51:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  The RS3

CLA45?

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-13 20:24:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> CLS is a CLE and last I heard they were going to change to that proper naming convention.  

I never understood the point of the K designation.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-13 20:23:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I like how just M class was thrown in there haphazardly.  Everything was G except for that one.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-13 20:22:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  And you can tell they don't put the same heart and soul into the SUV line as they do the sedan/coupe/roadster lines.

The GLA got alot of attention.  They took the negative feedback from the CLA45 when building the GLA45. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-13 20:21:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>   The C and E class now are identical looking cars, with a different wheelbase being one of the few things different about them.

Front grill is slightly different looking but yeah.

 Another 50 would have put it in competition with the Golf R.

And would have made it more powerful than the C300, which has an engine based on the CLA250.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-13 20:20:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> There is no 1 in the USA.  3, 3 Wagon, 3GT which looks like the X4, the 4 GC which looks like a small 3GT even though it's a step up in product, etc etc.  5 series GT which looks like the X4 and may be slightly larger... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-13 20:16:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You know what dilutes a brand worse than some added entry level options?

Insolvency and bankruptcy and leaving the industry all together.

My only problem with the MB lineup is how everything now is just a version of the other.  C class was very very similar to S class in and out.  Now so is the E.  They need some level of cosmetic differentiation  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-13 20:15:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yup, great engine all around.  Definitely beats out BMW's in the *28/*30 competition. 

Too bad it's bogged down with a sloppy transmission.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-13 19:31:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If you think Porsche is difficult to navigate then just have a gander at BMW's different designations.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-13 17:56:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> My guest bathroom toilet, if you don't use it for a while, the tank drains but it doesn't trigger the refill mechanism.  So you go to flush and nothing.  Then you have to wait on the tank to refill after that flush and it works fine.  No leaks.  Thoughts? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-12 21:56:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Anything like this for Python? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-12 19:09:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Electors: "Since Trump doesn't want his intelligence briefings, can we have them?"  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-12 16:21:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  I didn't even mention Vermintide.

To be fair, neither did they.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-12 16:11:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What happened to the plans to reroute the train tracks and use that land to expand Mopac further?

Sucks that even if that started today we wouldn't see it completed for another 5 years.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-12 16:08:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> And the last couple of times I've gone south on Mopac the south bound wasn't even open, so.... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-12 06:38:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Ill probably go for BS!   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-10 22:56:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Are there two BS now or did they just move?  I never went to BS simply because when they first opened it was tasting menu only.  Is that no longer the case?   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-10 20:30:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm older so I'll tak ea look!   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-10 20:29:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Qui was on the list but everything I've heard is that it has significantly gone down hill due to Qui's personal issues.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-09 22:37:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  compared to the likes of Audi

A3/A4 is in line with a 230/330i.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-09 21:21:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Only been once since they upgraded from the truck, sadly.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-09 21:20:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  Lenoir

On my list but I didn't want to bring a party to a fixed menu restaurant.  

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-09 18:35:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Take the pic with your phone, go to imgur.com, it will let you upload (ignore the request to dl the app) and it will give you a url to copy and paste.

Or if you want to post a new thread, click on "submit new link" when in the sub forum and it will let you upload directly from your phone. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-09 17:45:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  I've actually unwillingly tested this when I let my dad drive my car for the first time - 7500 rpm and he kept trying to downshift. :S

Porsche's may be better about it, but I've gotten a C300 to hit the red line before when trying to force it to do so. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-09 17:44:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Keep us updated, post some pics!   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-09 17:02:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  Seems like the software would prevent that.

Should but is never guaranteed.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-09 03:20:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yup.  More or less, depending on options.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-09 00:35:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Can be.  Get a PPI done and ask them to inspect.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-08 23:10:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Mind if I ask how much?   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-08 22:18:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That's right at 15000 miles a year, which is the sweet spot.  If he's hit all of his maintenance in reasonable time, I'd bite.  Especially if you take it to a mechanic to get a good inspection.  If there are no over revs and the CarFax looks good, then buy with confidence.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-08 22:15:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Ebay and Ali Express have everything for your bootleg needs. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-08 18:45:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  Porsche's classic program

What does this entail?  What's the benefit?   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-08 18:43:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This was not a scientific number, I just pulled it out of my ass to get my point across.  :)   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-08 04:28:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> lol, sure, kid.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-08 03:21:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Tearing up paper isn't against the law. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-08 02:39:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  That's so weird.

Not really.  It's also to allow you to comfortably pass someone.  If the speed limit is 70 and some knucklehead is dancing between 68 and 70, it's perfectly reasonable for you to hit 75 to get around them.

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-08 02:37:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  It should be legal to rip up a ticket in front of the cop's face and casually drive away if they actually ding you for doing 1-2 mph over.

It is perfectly legal to do  that.

You'll legally also get the shit kicked out of you for it though.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-07 20:37:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> From what I recall, they took the feedback on the CLA45 and tried to address them with the GLA45.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-07 19:18:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  DON'T BE "That Guy"

Most of them became "That Guy" the moment they lifted their truck. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-07 17:58:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I just think BMW's interior is getting dated.  So was MB until they refreshed it recently. 

MB and Porsche is where it's at, honestly.  But there's a premium for that interior.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-07 17:43:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If you're over 65 then hood ornament and silver paint job is for you.
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-07 17:40:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Is it ever possible to to get them to readjust the residuals higher?

Wouldn't that lead to leasing a CPO being a good thing?  Residuals on a CPO would be a much smaller % difference between sticker price and, say, three years out than residuals on a new car off the lot.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-06 19:51:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That interior.  Looks like a Fischer Price toy.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-06 19:49:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> There's a red cabrio I see around here from time to time. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-06 19:48:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> 2014 model and 35k,  so this would be an E class, right? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-06 19:47:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Cars that old with mileage high enough, it's to be expected.

I was sinking 1500 into my 06 Dodge Hemi every other month due to constant issues.  It was 10 years old and had 200k miles, but still.

I was hoping to get one more year out of it before she was hit and killed by a drunk driver. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-06 19:40:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> How much did you pay?  2014 with reasonable mileage are going for 30k around here.  That seems pretty solid price.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-06 19:39:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Are the residual values on leases something you can haggle over at all?  Would a higher or lower residual result in better lease terms/monthlies?  
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-05 19:07:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Demand far outstripped supply and they're yanking them from dealerships to fulfill preorders.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-02 21:50:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Needs it.  Interior is super dated, and they need to stop trying to pair it with the S class since it is an E class vehicle. 

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-02 02:03:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> And the Macan S is even better and more car like. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-02 01:59:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If you can afford a new CLA you can afford a CPO C300 and should go that route.

Otherwise, it's not a bad vehicle for a first car.


 People say the car feels stiff, what does that mean?


Stiff suspension, definitely compared to a Prius (my wife has one and I have a C300).  Run flats make it a more bumpy ride.  But it isn't unbearable.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-02 01:55:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Not in the slightest. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-01 04:38:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I am curious as to the expected MSRP.

And I know that if I have to ask that I probably can't afford it.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-30 23:45:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yup.  Biker split the lane and drove up aggressively to the car?  I'd have probably flipped him off too. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-30 23:17:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If they'll hurry the hell up and release it I'll be first in line. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-30 23:13:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> S'ok.  We just know where you made your sacrifice for the Cayenne God.  ;) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-30 23:13:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Which is what will be put in the Cayenne and Macan in a year or two.  :( </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-30 23:12:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Still too bright for my tastes.

So is the new Chalk interior.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-30 22:03:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'll take "Things you say on your way out of office but never while holding office" for $1000.
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-30 21:34:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If it's CPO then no, this stuff isn't covered under CPO.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-30 19:34:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  It's a mostly rubber interior which needs a lot of money to make it feel like a luxury car

It's the exact same interior as everything else.  You can pay extra for leather/etc if you want it but this isn't a Macan only situation.    </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-30 17:30:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  base Macan isn't all that nice.

Only difference between the Macan and the S is the motor.  pretty much everything else is the same.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-30 15:30:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Good luck! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-30 15:29:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Lease?   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-30 15:28:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Seconded.  Also looked at a Q5 and GLC and the Porsche ended up being similarly priced/spec'd and performed better than both by leagues.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-30 15:27:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> 2016/2017 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-30 00:54:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Spoiler:  There won't be any new SAAB's on the road.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-30 00:41:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Vented seats.  Larger screen.  Reasonable backseat space.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-30 00:39:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What are the differences?   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-30 00:36:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You can't "order it online".  Whatever you order, you'll have to go to the dealership to actually put the order in.

You can still haggle with custom orders. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-30 00:34:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> And in NYC of all places.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-30 00:12:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Macans are great, great driving, the base has a bit too much Audi in it for some people but I like em enough.  All are turbo'd.

Macan is more a hatch than an SUV and the back seat is super cramped.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-30 00:09:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah, I'm only interested in the Macan because I fucking hate SUVs and it's kinda not but it satisfies the wife's ingrained womanly lust for an SUV.

Had hoped that Panamera Wagon would be out by now.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-30 00:00:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I actually overshot it.  2016 328i is going for  350 at the moment.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-29 22:26:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  The back seats are like the 911 (useless except for toddlers).

Little hyperbolic here, but I have measured.  The back seats of a Macan have the exact same space as my Mercedes C Class.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-29 22:19:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Your problem OP is that you probably could have bought the car, paid a little more down, paid on it a little more time, and come out owning it and at least have that going forward.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-29 22:17:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yup.  320i and you get 12,000 miles and free maint. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> 2002 Boxster w/ 85k Miles, Tiptronic. 9500 bucks. Thoughts? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-24 16:09:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> My brother lives out in the boonies and his one single neighbor has this for sale sitting at the end of their drive way.  Price seems to be just right gauging by Porsche's car locator and AutoTrader.

Anything I should look out for on these 986s?  I've asked him some mechanical questions and he doesn't seem to be a car guy at all (Lawyer).

This would be a fantastic xmas present to myself.  :D </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Rumor: Honda to Celebrate Its 70th Anniversary with New S2000 Roadster </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-21 17:03:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> 991.1 to 991.2 owners, how has the change been? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-21 16:07:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm still biding my time before making the jump into a 911.  I was originally looking at a CPO 2014 4 Cabrio.  But now I'm not so sure, and am thinking of waiting a few years to catch the 991.2 when it starts hitting the CPO market.

Why?

I've almost exclusively driven turbo'd cars and have gotten spoiled by the instant torque availability and the light touch/sensitive throttle mapping.  The last natural intake car I had was a 6.1 liter Hemi.  I loved that car and it was a beast to drive but you had to work for it, constantly.  

That's how I feel when I've driven any non Turbo Porsche, and probably can expect the same for the 991.1.  

Granted, my Hemi had something like 900 pounds on a 911 so its not a 1:1 comparison.

For those that drove, or daily'd, a 991.1 and then swapped to a .2, how different is it?  Is it such a change that you couldn't imagine going back to a 991.1?  Does the 991.2 just feel quicker than the 991.1? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Are you using your pinky? I mean really using it? GET. UP. IN. THERE. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-19 23:01:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Interview with Filmmaker Debbie Lum | Seeking Asian Female | Independent Lens | PBS </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-19 20:08:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
