<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject8546</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-06 02:04:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Also good: Radiolab and 99 Percent Invisible. There are a ton of episodes of each, and they're all super interesting.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Researchers say urban racoons are smarter than rural ones. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-05 15:36:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Overview of emerging Zika virus research </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-05 15:20:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> In Charlottenburg. Love the difference in tone between the English and German. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-05 15:10:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What Research Says about Defeating Terrorism - Seven Enlightening Studies from Social Psychology </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-30 15:28:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-30 15:09:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I have to say, these results really surprise me given Sanders' success with young voters and his rhetorical focus on economic inequality. Always seemed to me a lot of support for him grew out of the Occupy movement (or at least the mindset/worldview that spurred it). </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-30 14:42:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Here's an [explanation in German from FairWertung](http://www.fairwertung.de/blog.3/index.html). They also certify legit donation charities. 

Edit: here's more [information in English](http://www.exberliner.com/features/second-hand-scam/).  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-30 14:37:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You can box them and mail them to Deutsche Kleiderstiftung. They pay the postage. You just print a label from their website and drop at your nearest package shop. http://www.kleiderstiftung.de/kleiderspenden-im-paket/ </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-15 20:09:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Oh wow. Bruce Duncan gets around. Sorry for the more-or-less repost. Am new to the subreddit and missed the first article.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-15 20:05:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> True, this kind of piece gets posted to some online publication or another approximately every five minutes, but I like this one better than most. Particularly the distinction between compound word that aren't that different from English phrases and more nuanced, interesting combinations. Which is a nice way to frame my frustration with non-German speakers' obsessions with relatively boring, albeit long, compound German words.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-15 15:16:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> "By about 1860, New York began to require means of egress in tenement buildings. Landlords, of course, often went with the least expensive egress option: rope. There were ropes and ropes with baskets, with which people were supposed to lower themselves to the ground. There were even advertisements for fake cabinets, hollow refrigerators, and empty washing machines in which to stow away a rope baskets." </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> TIL in the late 1800s, many New York apartments were equipped with ropes and baskets with which to lower yourself to the ground in case of fire. You could buy a fake refrigerator or washing machine to store them in. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-15 15:14:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Why German has so many great words </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-15 15:00:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Why stories that invoke fear spread more quickly online. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-14 12:00:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> "I think we have to be mindful of the fact that most of the work actually gets done by PhD students and postdocs." - Senior LIGO researcher gets real with physics grad student. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-12 00:35:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-10 18:19:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thanks for the link. I like this one too. They hit a really good balance of setting up the gender parity issue as a framework, but writing profiles that focus on the women's work and research, not their gender.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-09 23:22:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This is actually an art project. It's in the stairwell of the main building of Humboldt University under a Karl Marx quote put there before the Wall fell. 

Edit: [Details here](https://www.hu-berlin.de/de/pr/medien/publikationen/pdf/feuerbach_en) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-09 23:19:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Humboldt University in Berlin. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Science made me a better parent </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-09 17:58:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Science article on applicants ghost-writing letters of recommendation. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-09 17:45:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-09 13:32:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You can also just take your contract in person to the insurance provider's office. My experience with TK is that they enrolled me and gave me proof of insurance on the spot (pretty sure--if not the mailed it to me a few days later). It stated that my insurance started on my first day of employment. 

If you're from a country allowing you to be in Germany as a tourist up to 90 days, the Auslnderbehrde won't care that you don't have insurance effective immediately. They'll either give you a residence permit that's valid the day you start work, or one that's valid immediately. 

On your first day of work, your employer will ask you which of the public providers you're insured with. You tell them, and part of your paycheck automatically goes to that insurance provider. Easy peasy.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What was your favorite "women in science" International Women's Day article? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-09 11:05:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So, yesterday was International Women's Day, meaning tons of media outlets posted articles celebrating women in science and/or highlighting the difficulties we face, leaky pipeline, under-representation etc. That [New York Times](http://www.nytimes.com/2016/03/06/opinion/sunday/she-wanted-to-do-her-research-he-wanted-to-talk-feelings.html) piece and [ResearchGate](https://www.researchgate.net/blog/post/celebrating-womens-contributions-to-science) blog post have already been discussed here. Did you see any others you thought were exceptionally good? Or exceptionally bad?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-05 15:51:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Their reputation is (in my circles at least) not the best. I think the global primary is a great idea, but am put off by the venue to be honest. Might be worth considering a different one next time around. 

Unsolicited advice aside, thanks for volunteering and hope tomorrow's event is great for you guys!  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Gang of goats roaming the streets causing havoc </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-04 18:33:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-04 15:27:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hey, I'm curious about how the polling place was selected and how involved ICD is. Any insights?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What true statement did you think was a lie when you first heard it? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-02 21:29:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-02 18:17:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The Butter Battle Book. As a kid, the [animated version](https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=_MNNl-oOI7I) was my absolute favorite. I grew up to go to grad school for international relations, so it all comes full circle.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Successful female researchers in male-dominated fields offer advice for young women pursuing STEM careers. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-02 18:00:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-02 08:50:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I got a student visa, the application for which was stapled to the back page.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The visa guy at the Japanese embassy picked an interesting spot on my passport to staple my documents to. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-02 00:27:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> TIL Swiss apartment dwellers can get stickers to put on their mail boxes to indicate which household items they can lend to their neighbors. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-01 23:56:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> 40 percent of Germans believe the media are not credible, especially in reporting on refugees. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-25 11:22:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-24 20:54:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> OS: [Rob MacInnis](http://www.robmacinnis.com/farm-series/) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Squad goals. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-24 20:53:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-23 18:29:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I don't know. I always used to think of her and Olympia Snowe as double agents. They'd lose that advantage if they formally left the Republican party.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-23 18:21:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Would be a great resource. Now that you mention it, [they actually have that in Germany.](https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/German_Institute_for_International_and_Security_Affairs).   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-23 18:11:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thanks for this response. Any ideas about how to get policymakers to rely more on research? Is a perceived need to act quickly part of the problem?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-23 17:59:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What kind of research would you like to see done (scientific or qualitative) that could improve US foreign policy by making it better informed?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-23 13:30:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's always baffled me how the same state that boasts such moderate Republican senators could also produce LePage.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Susan Collins breaks ranks with Republican leaders over Supreme Court nominee </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-23 12:31:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-22 16:10:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The summer language school is probably at the language center though, which is in Mitte.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-22 11:12:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> When I'm feeling fancy, I mix lemon juice in with the avocado and crumble goat cheese on top. So good.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-22 10:44:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I really enjoyed all my MA classes at FU (more so than HU, but I have friends who say the opposite). The neighborhood is a fairly affluent suburb that's a nice escape from the city. Not much in the way of student housing there--its' mostly single-family homes. 

Most of the students live more centrally and take public transport out there. If you want a short commute and don't mind living in a quiet area, consider Steglitz. Schneberg and Tempelhof are also quiet, but more central. And all the trendier student neighborhoods are also perfectly well connected with public transport, just longer commutes (60 minutes for me in Friedrichshain).  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-22 10:33:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Having taken MA classes at both, I'd also recommend HU. FU is in a beautiful, green area, but it's rather on the outskirts. If you're coming to experience the city, the very central HU will be more convenient.

I have some more outdated experience (2010) at the HU language center, which I thought was pretty good. No language course experience at FU though, so I can't compare.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Italys coffee pot king Renato Bialetti was buried in the appliance that made him famous </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-18 12:52:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-18 00:32:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Have fun with the people you meet during orientation, but stay open to meeting even more new people as the semester progresses. It's likely you'll find those most comparable as friends after a little trial and error.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-18 00:17:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> A printer. I'm a student and have to print stuff all the time. Can't imagine how I got anything done six months ago when I had to go to the library or a copyshop to do it.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-17 23:59:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah, in Germany houses are made of brick or cinder block and covered with stucco. Like this [random example](http://imgur.com/6CEDA2S) I pulled from a real estate website.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Scientists solve mystery of where puffins go in the winter </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-17 22:34:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-17 21:28:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Am I the only one who saw this at home and thought, "That reminds me: I need to check my work account to see if I got that one email"? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-17 08:27:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You can renovate and modernize a station without stripping it of its character. Or at least in a way that gives it new character. See Baumschulenweg for an example. Obviously they couldn't leave it as it was. I just find the new station kind of soulless.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-16 16:55:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I don't know for sure, but if that's who you used to register, I imagine it'll be fine.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-16 15:06:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> According to the [Berlin city website](https://service.berlin.de/dienstleistung/120335/), you need to submit the "Abmeldung bei der Meldebehrde" form (1st link under "Formulare") along with proof from your landlord that you moved out. If you don't have proof, you can have your landlord fill out the form in the second link under "Formulare." It's basically an example of the kind of proof you need.  

De-registration is required only if you leave the country. You can send the documents by post to any of the city offices listed at the bottom of the above website.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-16 14:52:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What can European countries do to make it easier for refugees to find jobs and otherwise successfully integrate and build lives in Europe?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-16 14:38:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [this one](http://lostkreuz.de/2011/06/sommers-nach-grunau/) really captures the good old days for me.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Life as a female refugee: 'You don't know who to trust' </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-16 14:33:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-16 12:53:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> My high school AP history teacher pronounced the word "hegemony" wrong (like "hedge-a-moany"). I went on to get a BA in international relations and an MA in political science. I write and talk a lot about hegemonic theory. I still say it wrong like 40% of the time and have to pause and think a fraction of a second in order to say it right. Very embarrassing to say the least.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> If you'll excuse me, I've got to go call my mom. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-16 12:41:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> When you're operating heavy machinery and are also so sick of your job. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-16 12:27:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> "Lostkreuz": photos of Ostkreuz from back in the good old days before they stripped most of the S-Bahn stations of their character. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-16 11:48:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
