<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject9914</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-04 09:01:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You must have never seen avilo post </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-04 08:59:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You mean like the way you need a ground army to support tempests so they don't go mowed down by marines and hydras? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-04 08:57:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thor or collosus costing 4 supply would be way more broken than tempest.  Those units do far more DPS, are tankier, have splash attack.  Tempests only have long range, that's all that's going for them </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-04 01:13:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The DNC publishing a public apology to Bernie admitting that they acted unethically is pretty strong evidence </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-03 23:37:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Was the DNC public apology to Bernie not enough of a confession for you?  Or that 3 high ranking DNC officers have resigned after the leak?   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-03 03:37:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You can't choose something that doesn't really exist </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-03 03:35:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If you could be strapped into a virtual reality machine through which you could spend the rest of your days living a perfect simulation of your identified gender, that would be a pretty effective treatment.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-03 02:09:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah try walking with people who do nothing but talk about one topic that you don't particularly care about, and ignore you when you attempt to talk about anything else.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Thank you Niantic for giving my friends back </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-03 01:58:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Pokemon go, eat, sleep, pokemon go, eat, pokemon go.  That's all my friends had been doing nonstop for the past few weeks.  But then the new update happened and it's like I actually have friends again.  THANK YOU NIANTIC.  No more sitting quietly to myself at McDonalds while my peers bury their faces in their phones.  No more lonely walks at the park while my friends ditch me to chase Squirtle.    I'm through being constantly singled out as the only person who isn't addicted to this game. I implore you, please don't reinstate the footprint system, or let services like Pokevision come back. This game had become too big for its own good, it's time to let it deflate a little bit.         </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-01 22:47:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Getting impaled by a lurker spike out of nowhere would be pretty bad </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> How much Trump supporters respect women </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-01 05:59:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-31 17:44:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> im so stoked about this.  can't wait to have my friends back from this horrible game </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-31 03:55:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> beautiful.  surgical </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-30 01:38:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Just when we all thought tankivac complaints were dead... jfc </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-19 18:59:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's a good joke because Chitinous plating reduces damage to the extent that it takes an inordinate amount of time to deplete its health bar.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-19 02:09:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The game would overall be more pleasing to look at if everything had a visual indicator.  Adrenal glands, resonating glaives, advanced ballistics, chitinous plating.... would add a lot more visual immersion.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-18 18:41:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Scatology? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-17 23:16:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> sorry i meant yellowjackets </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-17 20:57:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If wasps are violent, then hornets are fucking genocidal </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-17 09:06:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What if you are lazy because of genetics? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-15 01:37:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Do you guys think this is a direct result of the spore + queen buff?  Or do you think this would have eventually happened regardless? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-13 18:58:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> A puppet for the dominion?? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> I think that self replier is just rolling with it now </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-12 02:35:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-11 23:26:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> i'm sure zealots could deal with phoenix void ray </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Crank's dank proxy carriers </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-11 08:13:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-11 06:36:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Is the sight of a normal deep dish such a novelty to everyone outside of Chicago?  Why is this front page material?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-11 06:30:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Maybe air blockers should be renamed "Tempest Forts" </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-11 06:28:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Agreed.  Sometimes you just want to play games without talking to anyone.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-09 03:41:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> that's some serious APM </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-08 11:31:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> yeah you were don't lie lol </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-08 11:20:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> what's it like to be fooled by a bait post? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-08 11:16:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> hook line and sinker </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-08 10:41:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If the victims had been armed with guns, then none of this would have happened.

Oh wait... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-08 10:41:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If the victims had been armed with guns, then none of this would have happened.

Oh wait... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-08 10:40:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If the victims had been armed with guns, then none of this would have happened.

Oh wait...

Edit: successful bait is successful : ) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-08 02:29:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Retard magnet </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-07 22:44:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Well technically all of humanity originated from Africa... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-07 18:04:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Blizzard should have at least informed the players that they were making changes to the map they voted for.  This is straight up bait-and-switch </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-07 05:41:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> okay I hate Avilo but this deserves props </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-07 05:40:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I just imagine Life being allowed 1 game of starcraft while in jail and then this happens to him </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-07 00:55:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Topped with the dollop of creme fraiche~ </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-07 00:54:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> For your own good really </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-06 22:51:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It sounds severe when you say it like that, but queens already outranged them by nearly that much.  It's just a 14% increase now.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-06 22:48:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Increasing Liberator transformation time was the better way to go.  It's stupid how quickly liberators can reposition themselves.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-06 22:39:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Don't queens already outrange banshees though?     </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-06 19:08:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Removal of hype abilities like the Vortex negatively impacted viewership.  Archon toilets were just so cool.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> All the reasons the Rio Olympics are fucked </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-06 18:55:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-05 07:31:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Why did they have to kill the vortex... they could have nerfed it and still made it entertaining... i miss moments like these </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-01 00:59:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The technology just isn't there yet </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-01 00:42:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Now we just need the Spear of Adun auto-gas ability in ladder and Protoss will be set </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-01 00:37:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Reduce BC tactical jump energy cost to 100.  Make BCs interesting without being overpowerd.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-29 23:48:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> pretty sure he's happier without your patronage </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-29 23:42:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Does your career ever detract from the enjoyment of food?  Is it possible for you to walk into a restaurant and just eat, without thinking about the technical details of creating that meal?  Are there some days when nothing tastes good?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-29 08:42:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> They shouldn't be able to dodge corrosive bile at all.  That's the whole point of being stationary.  You see ravagers coming?  Transform and get the hell out of there!   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-29 01:06:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The liberator transformation time should be increased.  This would help with the AA as well.  A small group of liberators that are deployed in ground attack mode would then be countered by mutalisks, because of the long transformation time.  The terran would have to keep a cadre of liberators in AA mode, consuming more resources and reducing the liberators overall versatility </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-28 18:12:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Koreans don't actually exist, it's all been fabricated by blizzard to assert their control over the meta.  Wake up sheeple </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-28 18:04:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> In your opinion, do you think zerg is as weak as the Korean scene says? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-27 19:05:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm growing increasingly in favor of Texit.  The union would be better off without this ass backwards state </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-26 01:54:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's like the exaggerated look you make to seem disgusted when you actually find something quite appealing </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-26 00:26:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Woman* 

sorry for the typo </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-26 00:25:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> "It would be horribly tragic if my ability to protect myself or my family were to be taken away, but thats exactly what Democrats are determined to do by banning semi-automatic handguns." </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Women who claimed to need guns to protect her family fatally shoots her two daughters, is then killed by police in armed standoff </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-26 00:25:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-26 00:09:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Someone should devise an experiment.  Have dolphins pass bubble rings for 15 minutes, the one that passes the most gets a huge fish buffet.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-25 23:58:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Nah this is all meta.  SouL wanted his opponent to think he would cancel the nuke when he sent in his marines.  He sacrificed some marines and liberators to kill like 10 lurkers!   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-25 10:40:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Why isn't this done more often?  It doesn't appear overly difficult.  No diss to the OP, i'm just wondering  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-25 10:15:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> destroy the warp prism with corrosive bile.  pull queens to heal </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-25 09:26:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> that was a really interesting read, i had no idea </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-24 22:06:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The morality argument of growing meat in petri dishes makes no sense.  Those cells have to be cultured using vast quantities of plasma serum, which provides nutrients for the cells.  Guess where that serum usually comes from?  COW blood.  We're killing cows to save cows.    </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-24 21:01:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> ULTRALISK ARMOR NERF THE IMPOSSIBLE MIGHT HAPPEN </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Best way to clip in-ear monitors for vigorous stage use? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-24 19:16:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I've just started using wireless in-ear monitors for touring with my band.  I have Shure IEMS that loop over the ear.  I'm having some difficulty managing the cable that connects to my belt receiver.  I tried running it inside my shirt, but it would snag and bunch up behind my neck, especially when headbanging or otherwise moving a lot.  Does anyone have advice for the best way to keep the wires under control, even while moving a lot?   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-24 18:24:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> why does kerrigan have high heels? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The only terran unit more OP than liberators </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-23 10:48:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-23 00:01:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> he should have target fired the disruptor instead of running. polt always does this  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-22 23:55:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> they start recruiting pretty early in korea dont they </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-22 23:54:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> pure mech should never be viable.  no other race makes this sort of demand.  imagine protoss with no gateway units.  the desire to have pure mech terran an antiquated idea carried over from brood war.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-22 23:51:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> congrats motherfather </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-22 02:31:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Koreans are genetically superior </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-20 20:50:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Unforgivable.  Who let this shit pass QC </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-20 19:40:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That's like saying we shouldn't let people register as organ donors because it encourages car accidents.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-20 19:25:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I would have thought Libra but this works too </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-20 11:30:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The day I stopped seeing the therapist and stopped taking anti-depressants cold turkey was the day my life turned around for the better.  It was then I realized that no one can fix you but yourself   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-20 10:01:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> literally cutting corners </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> /Starcraft Balance Map Organization Suggestions </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-20 00:13:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm really looking forward to the balance testing from the Reddit community: https://www.reddit.com/r/starcraft/comments/4o73w4/rstarcraft_balance_test_map_balance_change/  

I do have one small suggestion for organizing feedback to make it easier for people to participate.  Right now, all the responses are put into the same thread, making it difficult to sort through duplicate suggestions and to determine what people care the most about. You can try searching, but it is often difficult to formulate a search term that accurately reflects what you are suggesting.  

Instead, I would like to suggest that a moderator organizes the suggestions thread like this:  

1.  Under the main posts are 3 master responses, titled Terran, Protoss, Zerg. These will be used as the 3 race subthreads.  
   
2.  Under each race subthread are several additional response subthreads, one for each unit in that race.  So under the Terran subthread, would be Marine, Marauder, Reaper, Hellbat, etc.  

3.  Also under each race subthread is an additional response called "Other."  This is for all suggestions that don't directly pertain to units.  


People would then put in their suggestions by responding to the individual unit subthreads or to the "other" subthread for each race.  This way, it will be easy to tell if your idea has already been suggested--simply go to the appropriate subthread and see what has been written.  This also helps the map creators easily see what are the most requested changes, since they can see how many responses there are under each category, how many upvotes under each category, etc.  
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-19 23:52:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> that's not a nerf.  Downvoted for not being related to the OP </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-19 23:50:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Basically all of Avilo's complaints are pretty funny:

-Tempests are OP even though they do pathetic damage

-Invincible nydus is OP even though nobody struggles with this anymore

-Pure mech is too weak even though nobody should expect to win like this. It's like Protoss players expecting to win with no gateway units.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-19 20:33:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So if you have enough phoenix, you could theoretically kite the opponent indefinitely? Then again, if you had that many phoenix you'd probably be better off lifting your opponent instead.. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-18 03:05:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> "teen stops masturbating long enough to save couple from fire" </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-18 02:57:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> People being stupid under stress is not hard to understand at all.  Doesn't make it any less moronic or more deserving of sympathy </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-18 02:43:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> a running black? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-18 02:39:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Can someone clarify why he was pulled over in first place?  The article was very ambiguous about this.  Something about the cops not wanting him to be driving around there?  I'm confused.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-18 00:10:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I think currently it is unthinkable to uproot spores in response to Banshees precisely because it is so slow and you lose detection during that time.  If it were significantly faster, it may not be that way.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-17 23:48:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Banshee harassment is the first thing that comes to mind, especially cloaked Banshee.  Being able to quickly reposition your AA detectors would have a very pronounced affect on this interaction.  More generally, I think it could impact all forms of air harassment.    </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Fixing the liberator in TvZ </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-17 23:40:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> From its inception, the liberator has been a tricky unit to balance.  Due to their versatility against both air and ground, they have become a mainstay of most terran compositions.  According to David Kims most recent community feedback, many Korean pros specifically point out that Zerg has a hard time dealing with liberator harassment: http://us.battle.net/sc2/en/forum/topic/20745116041  

David Kim's proposed changes include decreasing spore crawler root time or increasing Queen AA range, but both of these changes can have far reaching consequences outside of the ZvT liberator dynamic.  The spore crawler change would impact all forms of air harassment, and Queen's already have 7 AA range.  Thus, I am personally against both of the proposed changes.   
 
As an alternative, I would like to propose an increase in the transformation time of the liberator when switching attack modes.
 
Benefits:

-Allows the defending opponent to react to liberator harassment with a bit more lenience

-Forces the Terran player to commit when transforming, rather than doing so willy-nilly. It becomes a more meaningful risk-reward decision.  

-Would minimally affect the defensive role of the liberator

If this change is in the right direction, we can perhaps even un-nerf the ground attack radius.  The goal is to keep the liberator as a potent unit, but make its usage a more conscious choice, rather than something always used by default.  Would like to hear your thoughts on this. 

Edit: edited for clarity.

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-17 23:08:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Increase the liberator transformation time. It will still be strong defensively, but weaker for harassment </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-17 10:33:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Polt isn't a big fish in a small pond.  He's a fucking whale </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-16 01:09:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> 60 supply of marines in 1 second oh yeesssss </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-16 01:07:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> We have awesome plays like seeker missiles being used to make kamikaze hellions, and then we have this... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-15 01:07:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> the only meaningful response on this thread so far.  thanks </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-15 00:55:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> League of Legends has been out for more than 15 years and is updated more frequently than SC2 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-15 00:42:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> To play devil's advocate, could the pro scene be stifling innovation in game design?  Seems like Blizzard is too afraid to make bold changes when people's livelihoods hang in the balance </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Overwatch first balance patch in just 3 weeks; LOTV took almost 3 months </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-14 23:21:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm not necessarily saying Blizzard is neglecting LOTV, it's just an observation. Do you think this just reflects the nature of two very different genres? Or is it just because Starcraft is a more matured game than Overwatch?  Or do you think it reflects where Blizzard is putting its resources?   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-14 05:10:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> MERGING IS COMPLETE </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-14 05:09:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Is this the cooldown bug or the supply bug or both?   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Mirror's Edge and motion sickness </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-06 23:31:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Saw this article today about one reviewer who basically couldn't complete his review due to the intense motion sickness he experienced playing Mirror's Edge catalyst.  
http://www.polygon.com/2016/6/6/11871262/mirrors-edge-catalyst-made-me-hella-motion-sick

The author states that he is an avid FPS fan, and that no other game gives him motion sickness like Mirror's edge.  Are other players experiencing similar sickness from playing Catalyst?  

P.S. 

In the article, he summarizes a theory of motion sickness from the Guardian: 

"The TL;DR is that the brain is often convinced by the motion in a game, but the inner ear is like, Nah bro, youre just sitting on your couch. This disagreement convinces the brain that you must be hallucinating, perhaps due to a poison you ingested. Therefore the brain sends alarm bells to your stomach to puke up the non-existent poison. Poof: motion sickness."

I've suffered from motion sickness for many years.  I basically cannot play any FPS for more than 30 minutes without puking.  But I'm pretty skeptical about this theory about the mind thinking you have been poisoned.  I mean, I can actually take hallucinogenic mushrooms and get crazy visual hallucinations, and yet feel no need to puke.  So it seems like this theory doesn't apply to me?  Hmm... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Why are LOTV new units mostly low tech? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-05 18:19:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Specifically the ravager, the liberator, and the adept.  These units have unique active abilities and are extremely powerful, to the point that all of them have been nerfed since release.  My question is this: why did blizzard decide to make these units so low tech, when their effectiveness, appearance, and lore make them seem more like high tech units?  Why is ravager the only zerg morph that doesn't require a prerequisite building?  Why don't liberators require tech labs, when they definitely look and operate like high tech units? And shouldn't the adept, with its fancy psionic transfer ability, be unlocked by cybernetics core or templar archives? 

Forcing these units to be low tech severely limits how strong/cool they can be, since early all-ins and timing attacks would be overpowered. Initially these units were way too good for the early game; consequently, they all were gimped in weird ways in the name of balance. Ravagers are unarmored and have less health than roaches, despite appearing more beefy and tough.  Adepts were nerfed by 1 damage against light units to prevent early game abuse--a pretty contrived adjustment that some people claim is still not enough.  Liberators had their AA attack nerfed recently, yet some are clamoring for a nerf to their ground attack as well. 

Wouldn't it make more sense for these strong units to appear mid or late game? Wouldn't a lot of these issues be solved if these units were high-cost, high-power tech units that require a significant time and financial commitment?  Am I alone in feeling this way? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> I wanna play Overwatch so much but FPS games give me terrible motion sickness : ( </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-24 07:43:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> LOTV Mothership unit info page still shows vortex </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-21 21:54:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Avilo's rant about getting beaten by Vibe </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-21 00:11:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> April 21 Balance Map: how do the changes feel? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-23 21:04:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I've been out of town and not had a chance to play with it yet.  But I'm curious to hear other peoples' impressions.  Are the cannons helping deal with mutas?  Are banshees even better harassers now?  How does the new thor AA feel?  How bout the liberator AA nerf?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Buff Photon Cannon Against Air : the Answer to PvZ </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-15 22:30:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Edit: Looks like a version of this suggestion will be in the next test map!  Thanks DK!  Thanks for all the feedback guys!

There seems to be a general consensus that Protoss struggles against Zerg early-mid game.  Particularly, Protoss has a hard time dealing with Overlord drops and Mutalisk harass, forcing them to always go PICA, resulting in a dearth of viable Protoss builds against Zerg. Unfortunately, the proposed nerfs to Zerg have not been widely embraced, as many players were hoping for a Protoss buff instead. David Kim has expressed that he wants simple changes that affect the least number of variables, so complete redesigns are off the table.  

I propose a simple change that may address all these issues:

-Buff photon cannon damage against air

This can be coded by making the Photon Cannon have separate ground and air attacks, both with the same animation, and then independently buffing the air damage.  

Potential benefits

-Help defend against Mutalisks

-Help defend against Overlord drops

-Provide a stronger role for the currently underused photon cannon

-Does not affect photon cannon cheese, since it is only buffed against air

-Barely affects PvT (Vikings cant shoot down; Liberators already cant attack buildings; would only affect banshee harass)


I believe this will greatly benefit Protoss defense in PvZ, providing some much needed breathing room without the potential side effect of being abusable offensively.  I would love to hear Reddits thoughts on this proposal.    





EDIT 1:  Got some great feedback.  Some people are suggesting to make this more specific by buffing damage only against light air or biological air.  I think these are both great ideas, especially if we don't want it to affect medivacs.

EDIT 2: I want to clarify that the idea is not to make Protoss impregnable from muta harass. I would only want to marginally buff the damage to the extent that it is slightly easier to defend multiple bases, buying time for stalkers and other anti-air units if you don't already have a cohort of Phoenixes on standby. Furthermore, with the right adjustment, I don't think this will encourage too much turtle style play, as Protoss remains just as vulnerable to ground-based harassment (zergling run-bys, roach/ravager timing attacks, lurkers)




 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Polt wins base trade after his main army gets wrecked </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-13 08:24:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Polt vs Scarlett incredible macro play </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-07 10:46:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Huawei product quality and customer service </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-28 21:04:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hi everyone!  Recently I saw Huawei unveil their new matebook tablet.  I've been looking for a windows tablet that's lighter than the surface pro, and this seems perfect!  But I've never owned Huawei products before.  I was hoping people here could help fill me in.

1. Do they make high quality products?  
2. Are their products durable/long-lasting?
3. Is their software generally robust and bug-free? 
4. When bugs are present, do they do a good job fixing them down the line?     
4. If I have any issues with my product, is their customer support good?  

Any feedback would be greatly appreciated! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Suggestion: air units can block corrosive bile from hitting ground units under them </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-23 08:34:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I thought of this after reading about the proposed removal of tankivac.  A lot of people were concerned that this would make tanks far too vulnerable to corrosive bile, and that this would remove a degree of micro that made games more exciting.  While I am personally against tankivac, I do agree that it allows for micro and helps tank survival.  

I instead propose another way to utilize micro to help tanks survive against corrosive bile. What if corrosive bile, upon hitting an air unit, didn't continue passing to the ground?  The bile effectively stops after hitting the first unit in a vertical line.  This way, you could "shield" tanks with air units.  With proper micro, you can even swap between multiple air units hovering over the ground unit, in order to spread out the damage so that no individual unit is destroyed (think blink stalker micro). This way, tanks are no longer completely at the mercy of corrosive bile, without becoming a flying harassment tool. It also allows for a new defensive micro mechanic that is less inane than flying tanks.   

This change could have positive impacts on other aspects of the game as well.  For example, in ZvZ, corruptors, which are often useless when there are no air units, can protect lurkers by soaking up corrosive shots.  

I think this is an aesthetically intuitive behavior to implement. You would naturally expect that a projectile would stop if a physical object is in the way.  This change "feels" right.  And I hope others agree : )  
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Blizzard Staff to Korean Pros: "Think SC2 isn't fun? Play something else!" </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-05 20:54:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's making big news in Naver games section. Here is the original link:
http://sports.news.naver.com/esports/news/read.nhn?oid=347 aid=0000082270

SKT coach claims that the Blizz Korea staff told pro players "You don't think SC2 is fun?  Go play something else."

So far, no official comment from Blizzard regarding these statements yet.  Personally, I think stuff like this is unacceptable, and it will further damage the already deteriorating SC2 community.  

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
