<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject9647</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-20 15:08:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yes!! I almost forgot I've lifted here. Had to get a bag of dog food. Lol. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> My Lifting Experiences/Advice </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-20 05:53:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This is a list of all the stores I've lifted from and MY PERSONAL EXPERIENCE in case it can be of use to anyone. I'm not claiming these circumstances are the same at every single store, so if you take my advice, proceed with caution.


Target - first store I started lifting at. Started stealing small things, then did several push-outs. They have reusable bags now which makes it easy. My best trick was to start heading toward the exit through the dollar spot and look at items there, then when employees and customers are gone, confidently head to the exit.

Walmart - SO MANY BLIND SPOTS. Customers are nosy though. Not many items are tagged and some of the "sensors" on their jewelry are decoys.

CVS - fairly easy to lift from. Employees don't care. Plenty of blind spots. But sometimes they hide the sensors on their products really well (especially cosmetics) and you have to be careful. Best bet is to head to the bathroom and remove packaging, then stash it in a ceiling tile. Use the hand dryer to mask any noises the packaging makes. Be careful because checkout lines are near the exit, so employees hang out there...not many blind spots.

Publix - back when I was practically homeless, I used to go to their deli and order sandwiches, make myself a drink, and walk out. Good, easy way to get a healthy and substantial meal. They don't ring you up at the deli so you can just walk out.

Ulta - several blind spots (i.e. drugstore makeup and hair care or skincare) come late in the day, when the manager is gone, and when there are few employees and they all want to go home. They won't address you. Be careful of sneaky RFID tags. Some of their products are tagged with these weird, light-sensing things that SUCK. easy to conceal small items. Best tactic for me is to go to an aisle with few cameras and no customers and to crouch down to "look at items on the bottom shelf" and then stuff items in my purse. Park away from the store because they WILL get your license plate number.

Sephora - BEWARE. This is the one store I've ever been busted in, and I've been lifting for over a year. Employees are very condescending and they will watch you like a hawk if you don't have a certain "look". They follow you around the store and every employee has a walkie/headset. Nothing is tagged, so if you're really good, go right ahead, especially if they're busy. I've gotten away once with a pretty decent haul. Sephora inside of JC Penney is a fucking cake walk. Items are tagged but the towers are at the exits to the entire store. There's normally only one or two employees. Stupidly enough, popular items (at the store in my area) are stocked around the perimeter which makes it sooo easy to just grab them under your arm and walk away. Head to a fitting room (which are totally unattended by the way) and peel off the RFID tags. I stick them to the back of the mirror so no one will see.

Barnes and Noble - fairly easy, but employees are somewhat hard to spot. My number one tactic is to grab some books I like, wander around the store "shopping" and then casually head over to the Starbucks. I chill at a table near the exit (yes, there is an exit in the caf and it makes things gloriously easy) and read, then leave.

Sally Beauty Supply - this one is moderately difficult. There's like one camera in the store and it's a small store with very hands-on employees, but you're golden if you come in when they're super busy or late at night when no one wants to help any customers. Nothing is tagged and the shelves are super tall!

Victoria's Secret - this one can be difficult if a lot of people are working because they will customer service the shit out of you. Try to go late at night. Make sure you can spot all of the employees. The VS I go to has a bathroom and multiple exits, which is a life saver. The little panty drawers make your job easier because you can crouch down to "look in the bottom drawer" while concealing goodies. (I actually visited there today)

Forever 21 - most jewelry is not tagged. Occasionally a random item will not be tagged. If they have those mesh shopping bags, look for one that doesn't have a sensor on it (this doesn't take long). Casually fill it up with items to "purchase" and then stroll the fuck out while the cashiers are busy with other customers.

Old Navy - at the store near me, I have seen an employee actually on the floor ONCE. Fitting rooms are usually NOT monitored (especially early in the morning) and a good bit of their items are not tagged. Just take a few items to the dressing room (some you want and some you don't want. They won't count them), stuff the ones you want in your bag, and leave the ones you don't. The stores are usually super busy with very little staff. Have fun!

Famous footwear - easy if you're experienced. Clearance shelves are super high up and easy to conceal in. Staff do not help you much unless you approach them first. Little to no cameras.

Ross - easy to pocket small items (journals, makeup, trinkets, etc.)  but most of their shit is tagged. They count items going into fitting rooms. Cash wrap "blocks" the exit.

JoAnn - SUPER EASY. I've done a few push-outs here. A friend of mine just stuck a $300 sewing machine in a cart and walked out, no questions asked. Very few employees, little to no cameras, and tall shelves. Just be cautious around the sewing department/fabrics.

DSW - fairly easy. Not many employees but lots of customers. NO CAMERAS in the clearance section. Only purses/glasses are tagged. Just act confident.

Torrid - I used to work here and it's so easy. They don't chase or apprehend (don't want to "offend" the customer). There are usually 1-3 employees working at a time. No cameras, no LP. They don't count items going into fitting rooms, but almost all items are tagged.

Best Buy - VERY RISKY. Stick to small items and act like you're just browsing. Act like you're not doing anything wrong, and head to the bathroom as long as no employees are nearby (they're allowed to follow you), then remove the packaging because their sensors are sneaky and stash it in a ceiling tile.

Staples - super easy. Outdated cameras, few employees. Shelves are extremely high and can conceal you easily.
Toys R Us - a fucking cake walk. It's easy to get away from employees because the store is so huge. Quite a few cameras, though. But if you go later at night there's very few employees at the cash wrap so you can just walk out.

Victoria's Secret Pink - employees are somewhat pushy, put it's pretty simple when they're busy. All clothing is tagged but perfumes, lotions etc. are a buffet.

Urban Outfitters - somewhat difficult because the store layout is fairly open, but employees generally don't give a shit and lounge around at the cash wrap talking. They aren't consistent with tagging items and most of the time won't approach you at all. 

MAC Cosmetics - be VERY careful. I wouldn't recommend going here just because you won't get much out of it. I stole a sample once but that was all I could get away with. Employees are similar to the ones at Sephora, very rude and judgmental and will single customers out. Their products are stored in drawers that they flip out if you touch AT ALL. Boo.

Disney Store - easy but I stole there once and felt like a terrible person. They aren't allowed to chase or apprehend and very little is tagged.

JC Penney - easy late at night. There are almost no employees in sight and very little is tagged. I grabbed two dresses and walked out without seeing anyone.

Books a Million - nothing is tagged. Few if any employees on the floor. 

Nordstrom ****I've never lifted here but I work here and wanted to give you guys a warning. VERY IMPORTANT. I wouldn't recommend lifting here...we are all trained in basic LP, we have the same cameras as casinos (PTZ and "can go so far as to read your phone screen" per my LPM) and our registers have buttons to page LP. There is a code name for LP (not sure if I should mention it) and we have plainclothes LP too. They don't fuck around. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-20 05:46:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Whoops...let me fix it and repost. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-20 05:13:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I have a shirt that looks like a cheesy postcard and says "Jonestown" with the Kool-Aid Man on it, also a "Jurassic Parks and Rec" shirt with Chris Pratt on it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-19 14:14:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> There's so many blind spots in the Ulta where I visit, and the workers are normally too apathetic to even address people when they're in the store.

Also, there's a Sephora inside of JC Penney and it's like a fucking buffet. You just grab shit and conceal it, then head to one of the dressing rooms (which are never monitored, btw) and stash the trash in the ceiling. Easy as pie. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-19 05:09:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I've done several push-outs at Target for over a year and have never been caught. I was apprehended once but I was let go immediately. Ulta is somewhat easy if you know what to take. They have these new weird sensors now with a light sensor, so that if you palm them or stick them in a bag they beep. It's pretty easy to find blind spots at Ulta and I've never even been approached by staff. I know what hours are the best to lift based on who's working. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-19 00:06:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I just joined the group. Haven't done much looking around. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> a quick question </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-18 23:08:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Where do you buy detachers? And what is an S3/how do I get one? I've been shoplifting a little over a year and have limited myself to items with no tags. Gets tricky because I really need nice clothes for my job but I don't have much luck when all I can get is stuff someone forgot to stick a tag on...

Also, what are your best tips for lifting clothes/makeup? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-18 22:47:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I definitely know that's true! I've never been charged/arrested etc. but anytime I feel like something's off I'll just ditch the stuff in an empty aisle and head out. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-18 22:45:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah, I need to use different techniques...I've been apprehended by an LP agent before but I got out of it. Needless to say I don't go there anymore. Lol </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> i thought i was the only one! </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-18 22:29:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Glad to see such an awesome community of people. I've hidden my lifting from my boyfriend and friends and family...although I did get a close friend to start. Lol.

I'm not exactly a rookie. I've been lifting for a little over a year now, but my techniques aren't great.

They work, so I guess that's alright, but I've been somewhat sloppy and I worry that I could get caught. I came to this community to meet my fellow lifters and learn some tricks of the trade!

My favorite places to lift from are Target, Walmart, Ulta, and Old Navy. Comment your favorite stores below! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
