<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject5554</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Saw this on tumblr. Anyone know the source or the artist? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-05-14 21:39:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Is it normal to have occasional days of complete inactivity? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-04-12 06:20:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yesterday I was quite productive, working on a project until 4 AM. However today I did nothing. I woke up late, laid around, surfed the web, and didn't leave the house. I have days like this AT LEAST once a week. Maybe it's because I'm self-employed, and rather lazy about it, or because I still live with my mom so I don't have to do much around the house, but even when I'm older and self-sufficient, I can't imagine not having days like this on a regular basis. Then I see people on TV like Michelle Obama on the Colbert Report tonight, and wonder if she ever has days like this where she does absolutely nothing productive, or if that's just something loser manchildren do and real adults are busy every day. Perhaps reddit isn't the best slice of the global population to survey, but did you reach a point where you stopped having regular days of doing nothing? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> How are these photos processed to get these effects?  </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-03-20 17:03:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> If my parmesan cheese now tastes like bleu cheese, is it still safe to eat? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-03-15 22:30:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Do I now simply have grated bleu cheese? Or is it harmful? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> So you're alone, it's late, you're horny, what do you do? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-03-13 06:53:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If sex is not an option, how do YOU deal with that late night horniness? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> ELI5 What is loneliness? Why does it happen? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-03-07 05:18:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What is loneliness physically in the brain? Why can someone have plenty of friends and family, but still feel lonely? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What if you're NOT an addict? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-03-02 22:55:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I just recently discovered NoFap, but I'm getting kind of mixed messages about who it's actually for. It seems a lot of people engage in the NoFap 90 day challenge because they have a problem with porn addiction and want to reclaim some control over their habits. That's fine, but what if you're not an addict? Are there other benefits to not masturbating for long periods of time? Does it affect your brain in a positive way?

Speaking personally, I've found in the past that not having any kind of "release" for a long time really messes up my judgement and leads me to go to extraordinary lengths and wastes of time, money and energy in hopes of getting laid. However some things I've read here claim that feeling goes away eventually, and once you get over the hump you are actually MORE clearheaded and more focussed than ever.

Can anyone who has abstained for a long time please explain how it has positively affected your life, aside from beating an addiction? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> One of the best debuts in the WWE </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-02-20 19:16:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> 22, thinking of moving to the west coast this year </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-01-16 19:26:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I live in New Jersey. It's been good to me, but last summer I spent a month travelling through the northwest and found several beautiful areas I loved. Specifically, I'm hoping to move to Arcata, CA.

Some concerns....I don't know anyone out there. I have a little bit of money saved up (less than $10,000) and I don't know how easy it is to find a job out there. I've never lived on my own before, but have a pretty low standards. 

Ideally I'd like to build up an email relationship with someone that lives there that would let me live with them for a few weeks until I got settled and found a job. Maybe I'm going about this all wrong. Is there a subreddit for moving far away?

Any advice would be appreciated.

Note: I don't smoke weed, and weed has nothing to do with why I want to move to Humboldt County. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> I hated this place. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2011-12-11 19:48:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Louis CK offers his new special on his website downloadable to anyone in the world for $5. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2011-12-10 20:06:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Fans of old school Mortal Kombat will dig this </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2011-11-19 18:50:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Why do girls go for older guys? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2011-11-07 05:06:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Maybe it's just something camgirls say to make more tips, but apparently a lot of girls my age (22) prefer guys over 26 or older. What's up with that? Is it just that they want an independent guy with his own place and whatnot? I admit I'm not at that point yet, so should I be hitting on 19 year olds or something? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Why do people break up fist fights? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2011-10-24 17:45:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> TIL a woman can donate her kidney through her vagina </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2011-09-14 15:40:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Is there any way we can get Comedy Central to play good movies again? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2011-09-12 06:27:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Seriously all they air is Employee of the Month, Waiting, or a shitty Broken Lizard movie. When I was a kid growing up watching it they would play comedy classics like Raising Arizona, The Big Lebowski, Clue and Coneheads along with lesser-known cult movies like Pecker, Tank Girl, The Road to Wellville, Hairspray, and Rushmore. They also played great stand up specials from the 80s like Gallagher and Sinbad that were clean for daytime audiences. Why do they now rely on the same handful of terrible movies that nobody wants to see again? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> CAE make their toes curl by pressing their Achilles tendon? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2011-09-09 03:45:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> I was bored at home so I made a little 3 minute experimental cliche film </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2011-09-09 03:40:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Is it possible to think of a melody that's impossible to play on a piano/guitar? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2011-09-08 06:22:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Did Michael Jackson molest those boys or not? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2011-09-05 20:33:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I've heard that both boys admitted to lying after Jackson's death. I also heard that is a load of bullshit. Can anyone here who followed the cases tell me what you think, and why? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Just got told I'm not aggressive enough in bed </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2011-09-05 06:58:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> A friend I hooked up with once claimed last time she was on top of me and I "didnt do anything." For a guy, this is a major ego killer. However I'm not one to throw a girl around like a rapey caveman. How can I improve? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> IWTL how to choose a flattering haircut (I'm a man) </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2011-09-03 20:47:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I figure there must be some kind of facial-structure guidelines for choosing a haircut on a man. I have strong eyebrows and dark hair. Sometimes I grow a beard and it's just a whole lot of hair on my head. I also tend to choose something that's longer on top than the sides to make my head less round, but I don't know if that's the right approach. Thoughts? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Do you like to be called "pretty?" </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2011-09-01 00:32:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I know "beautiful" is probably the best compliment, but sometimes that's a little over the top, especially when first meeting. So if a guy says you're really pretty is that a nice compliment or do you wish he used a different word? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> DAE think they could be a perfectly good psychotherapist without any formal training? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2011-08-29 20:15:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What's up with mosquito bites? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2011-08-21 21:12:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Louis C.K. on Conan last night </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2011-08-19 21:26:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Alright, can we stop with these dumb Old Spice copy-cat commercials? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2011-08-07 02:27:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> You know, if silverware was made top-heavy, they'd never fall off the plate and stain all my shit </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2011-08-03 03:24:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I can't count the number of times I pick up my plate to carry it back to the kitchen, and a knife or fork -- being handle-heavy by design -- falls off the plate, flinging scraps of food or sauce onto my clothes, carpet and furniture. If all silverware were designed to be heavier at their business ends than at the handles, this shit wouldn't happen. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> A Letter To the Young and Suicidal (a work in progress) </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2011-08-01 06:53:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> hey reddit, here's some old people. they did some cool shit in the 40's or something. take me to the front page please. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2011-08-01 06:09:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> I give up. Critique please? (21/m) </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2011-07-27 02:48:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Welp, that's the most depressing Cracked list I ever read. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2011-07-25 05:17:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Fry's self-diagnosis </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2011-07-23 21:23:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> IWTL how to make a killer first impression with an OKCupid message </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2011-07-23 04:38:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I find the usual "hey whats up?" or "I like your profile" sometimes leads to a brief conversation but quickly dies off. Whats the best way to make a lasting positive impression with a complete stranger on a dating site? And how do you keep the conversation going without constantly asking pointless personal questions like "how long have you lived in Portland?" </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> DAE have an intolerance or lack of patience for fiction? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2011-07-23 00:32:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Can anyone help me find a decent entry level job in north jersey? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2011-07-17 05:29:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm a recent college grad. I've been pretty much self employed since I was 18 as a wedding photographer, but with the economy's downturn that's pretty much dried up. I'm skilled in photoshop and html, as well as video editing and some animation. But I'm not really looking for that kind of work to be honest. I actually just recently applied to Trader Joes, and even though I said I was available 7 days a week from 4am to midnight, and that I'd take all the hours they could give me, they still didn't hire me. Does any north jersey redditor work for someone who's hiring? I'm located in the Paramus area. Thanks! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What are some good comedy screenplays to read? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2011-07-11 00:58:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It seems writing comedy is especially tricky. I was watching The Pineapple Express last night and noticed that a lot of the funny lines aren't actually funny on paper. The joke is completely in the delivery and comedic timing, which can't really be written. So if you're trying to pitch a spec comedy script, how do you explain "This is funny only if it's delivered a certain way. If he just says it it won't work." What are some good examples of modern comedy scripts that have a lot of written jokes? I found an old draft of 40 Year Old virgin and it's fucking terrible. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Why do colossal monsters in movies always move in slow motion? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2011-07-09 17:52:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> A site that connects people who need to talk with people who are willing to listen -- all via videochat </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2011-07-03 02:07:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Imagine a site where you can go when you are stressed out, or depressed, or just lonely that will connect you with another person who is willing to hear you out and help you get through tough times. 

You make an account and whenever you're on the website you select whether you are currently a TALKER or a LISTENER. 

If you are a talker, the site will present you with a list of available listeners currently online, along with a little paragraph they wrote about themselves. You pick the one you want to talk with. When you're done with the conversation, you can rate the Listener with a Thumbs Up/Down depending on if they helped you. 

Listeners work on a karma system based on these ratings, so abuse of the system will lead to negative karma and eventually banishment from the community. 

I think this is a great idea for people who are hesitant or can't afford a real therapist, and just need a friend or some advice. Then when they're feeling better, they can pay it forward by helping other people who need some support.

What do you think? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> I think it's ridiculous that driving while talking on the phone is against the law </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2011-06-28 23:49:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I got a $130 ticket yesterday for something that I see at least 5 people doing on any random drive to the store. I don't think it's right to be suddenly "busted" for something that cops let slide ALL THE TIME. Either enforce it all the time, or don't criminalize it at all. And to suggest that holding the phone in my hand is any less safe than a hands-free set is preposterous. A distracting conversation is a distracting conversation whether it's on the phone, coming over your car speakers or with the person riding shotgun.

And by the way, I wasn't having a casual conversation with a friend. I had just received the call from a potential employer that I'd been anxiously awaiting for for days. I even told the cop this, but of course he didn't care. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Is it a waste of time to go to the gym once a month? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2011-06-20 19:41:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Obviously going a few times a week is ideal, but that's not always possible for whatever reasons. However I still keep my membership because it's very cheap, and once every few weeks I have nothing to do and consider going for an hour or two for some moderate lifting and cardio. Is going so infrequently basically the same as not going at all? Would I be better off at home doing something more productive?

Note: I'm not overweight or terribly out of shape. Just average. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> I feel like I'm incapable of loving anyone </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2011-06-14 05:57:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I was in a good relationship and in love in high school, but since then every relationship I've had has been mostly shallow and based on lust or boredom. Now I've been seeing a girl on and off for a few months and although I feel like I love her when we're together and hanging out, when we're apart I kind of don't care. I meet girls I think are beautiful and I think I fall for them but then the next day I forget about them and go back to not caring. I feel like I've just lost interest completely in love and romance and I don't understand why. Has this happened to anyone else?

EDIT: I've had prior problems with depression and took Paxil/Paroxetine for over a year, but weened off it early last month. However I felt the same while I was on paxil. I'm afraid I could have anhedonia, but I feel pretty normal otherwise. Does anyone know more about this? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Why is all this Anthony Weiner stuff okay? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2011-06-14 05:17:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Why can't I even play this today? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2011-06-03 07:35:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Today I did something that scared me </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2011-05-27 23:54:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I was searching through craigslist's job postings a few days ago and came across an ad stating that Leo Dicaprio's next film is looking to cast people for speaking and non-speaking roles. No experience necessary, and the auditions were in New York City just two days away. Knowing I had nothing planned for that day, and recently had a friend take a very nice photo of me, I went to CVS and had a headshot printed. I memorized two 30 second monologues and on the day of, sucked up the courage and went for it.

And it really wasn't that bad. I doubt I'll get a call back, but I felt really good just for going for it. A lot of my friends have these dreams in the back of their minds of getting into acting, or standup, or improv and they just won't because of fear. **FUCK FEAR.** You gotta make your opportunities and you gotta take your opportunities before you croak and everyone forgets who the fuck you were anyway. Figure out what you want to do and **GO DO IT** </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Outtakes from Bridesmaids - Funny or Die </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2011-05-26 15:49:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> I really need help landing a job </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2011-05-24 18:24:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I feel like I have a lot of skills to offer, but my submitted applications have all been dead ends so far. I was a professional photographer for 5 years. I've dealt with people. Ran my own business out of my bedroom. Now that the economy sucks, I barely book any jobs anymore (and I fell out of love with it anyway) so I'm looking for video gigs. I can direct, gaff (light scenes), edit, color correct, do graphic design and web design. I've been applying to gigs on mandy but no luck. I'm right outside of NYC too, so you would think there's an ocean of jobs there, and there are but they're not interested in me.

Also, another problem I have is that I'll be away for a week in June to help a friend film a documentary. How do I explain to an employer that I really need the job, but also need a week off just a couple of weeks after they hire me?

It's getting to the point where I'm considering just applying for Blockbuster or AMC theaters or something like that and taking minimum wage. It's just a shame to take an unskilled-labor position when I actually have a good amount of skills. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> IAMA Request: Someone who had sex with Michael Jackson </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2011-05-19 00:52:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Why the fuck do college textbook writers insist on writing like this? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2011-05-11 02:12:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> My short drama. Requiem meets Saw. [14 mins] </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2011-05-06 02:28:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> DAE else think P. Diddy is the most overrated rapper of all time? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2011-04-15 07:15:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Should a film festival submission be Interlaced or Progressive? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2011-04-15 00:42:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I shot a documentary in standard definition, 60i. I've been doing a lot of reading on how best to export it, and I know that interlaced video does serve a purpose when viewing on a television. However, it won't look good viewed on a computer monitor. By deinterlacing my video, I'll ensure that it looks good on computers, but I'm essentially deleting half of my resolution and letting the computer interpolate the in-betweens. I've been doing some furious googling but am really at a loss for where to go here. Any tips? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Guaranteed to be Reddit's favorite movie of all time </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2011-04-03 21:43:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Tips for my first animation? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2011-03-25 00:52:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I have an idea for my first animation. I'd like to it with pen+ink, but I'm afraid I won't have the time to make 24 frames a second (deadline is in a week or two). So I thought I'd draw the keyframes and perhaps use the aid of software to do some of the tweening. I have no experience with cel animation software or working with acetate. Could anyone provide some tips or reading material that could help me before I get started? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> I just had an interaction with an Indian tech support associate. It was completely normal and he solved my issue quickly. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2011-03-20 01:38:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I find that this is almost always the situation. Can we all agree to stop complaining about this?

EDIT: For the record, it was an online chatroom type of support with Amazon. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Why can't we just cut the defense budget? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2011-03-11 19:03:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I mean whenever there's a discussion on budget cuts, nobody even brings up the enormous defense budget, instead opting to shoot our country in the foot by cutting healthcare and education. I'm not saying we should disband the military, but couldn't we possibly cut a few hundred billion? Why is that taboo to even propose? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> HAE stopped caring about getting laid because internet porn is so much easier? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2011-03-03 06:20:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Now, just to clarify, I'm a relatively attractive dude. If I really put effort into going out, getting girls drunk, or relying on charm, I could probably get laid the old fashioned way. But I realized I have other shit to do, and don't really care that much about sex. So when I get horny, I crank one out and continue my day clear-headed. Anybody else stop caring about sex? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The making of Taxi Driver </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2011-02-21 04:46:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> I have a couple of articles I'd like to sell...but to whom? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2011-02-19 16:46:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I have a few blog posts that I spent a lot of time on. One on depression, another on photography for beginners, another on writing, etc. I think these could be useful to many people and I'd like to get them "out there" somehow. I don't really care about money, but I'm wary of using content mills like suite101 and demandstudios. Does anyone know any reputable publications that may be interested in these? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The Our Lips Are Sealed website is up for the documentary about Matty   Bobby - new trailer too! </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2011-02-16 15:19:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Nice to see my site's SEO is working well. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2011-02-15 07:11:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> How can we put a stop to these new ad-banners that are basically TV commercials with audio? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2011-01-29 06:27:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Lately I've been encountering a lot of these new ads on the internet that are basically full-on TV commercials playing automatically next to the web content. Whether they're for Lysol or a car company, they are the most obnoxious thing since pop-ups. What can we do as a community to put a stop to this practice?

edit: [here](http://tv.blinkx.com/show/inside-the-actors-studio/c7GwpIDV4_2uwPhk) is an example </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> I think the majority of people on this earth have probably licked an asshole in their lives. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2011-01-22 19:08:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Discuss. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Neil Young - Harvest Moon </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2011-01-19 14:28:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What is the usual cut for an indie producer? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2011-01-18 04:40:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm in kind of a unique situation. I'm a film student that put together a one-hour documentary completely on my own, including filming and editing it. It cost me nothing to make other than time, so there were no funds raised or anything like that. However, the film is quite good and has a strong chance of being selected into some major film festivals and likely being bought by a TV network (hopefully HBO). My professor saw a rough cut of the film that I gave to her to get some feedback and she got really excited about it. She wants to be my "producer" in the sense that she has navigated the film festival market and cutting deals with distributers before and she wants to help me with those things for my film. In the case that the film rights sold for X amount of money (lets say $10,000 to make it simple), what percentage would normally go to a "producer" like this? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> My new writing method - treatments and index cards aren't the devil </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2011-01-11 20:00:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Can any redditor describe in detail what its like to withdraw from heroin? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2011-01-11 06:38:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I am writing a story about a heroin addict who is chained to a radiator by his wife in order to force him to detox and get over the habit. What kind of experience would this be for a junkie? Obviously there'd be fever, chills, vomiting, nausea, I'm guessing mood swings? Any details you could provide would be really helpful. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Does my idea here already exist, or would anyone like to create it? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2011-01-08 07:52:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> DAE hate beer pong? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2011-01-03 17:47:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I enjoy parties and don't mind drinking, but there's always gotta be a gaggle of frat boys stacking tables and arranging cups in one of the rooms. DAE find no enjoyment in beer pong? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Reddit, let's end Wikipedia's fundraiser today. Surely you have $5. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2010-12-29 10:04:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What's the easiest way to subtitle a film? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2010-12-27 08:25:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm editing in final cut. I figure there must be an easier way to subtitle the entire film than adding a Text clip to every single scene. I'm bilingual so I'd like to make a spanish version to submit to international festivals. The film is an hour long so I'm looking for the most streamlined method possible. Any tips? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Who does this pic Jack Black look most like? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2010-12-24 22:07:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> This taught me a lot about AfterEffects in just 20 mins </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2010-12-24 07:37:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> I'm looking for musicians to score my documentary film before it goes to festivals. Interested? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2010-12-24 03:40:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> IWTL how to be a better shoplifter </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2010-12-19 01:23:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's a new hobby. I've only stolen small items so far usually by just putting them in a pocket. Today I managed to steal a book from B N by simply hiding it under my arm beneath my jacket. Books don't typically have sensors that can go off, but after getting caught stealing a hat with a hidden sensor in the lining, I know to check thoroughly now. Any of you thieves have good tips? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Reddit, how can I teach my brain to be more musical? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2010-12-17 02:30:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm normally more of a visual person, but I'm trying to get into some basic music production as a hobby and to help score some of my films. I even bought myself a little 25 key midi keyboard and I've taught myself some chords on guitar, but I'm still musically retarded. I have a lot of trouble distinguishing if a note is higher or lower than the one that precedes it. I mostly make tracks by trail and error, having no idea what progressions sound good until I try dozens out. Is there any exercises or something that I can do to help my brain 'learn' music a bit better? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Reddit, I wrote a really good analysis of Eraserhead. How can I get it published somewhere? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2010-12-13 05:51:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> This DID NOT happen did it??! </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2010-12-13 05:27:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> "We are a greater generation" </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2010-12-12 22:20:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> I'm worried this guy at my school may be dangerous. Is there anything I can do? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2010-12-11 23:57:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I've had a few classes with him. He's dark, antisocial, uncommunicative, and seems very very intelligent. He sometimes makes a violent or gross comment laughs maniacally when the class is shocked or disturbed by what he said.

That's really all I know. Do I think he's gonna shoot up the school? Probably not. Do I think he's serial killer material? Yup. Is there anything that can be done or do we as a society just have to wait for this guy to snap and hurt somebody? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What would you tell your college-aged self? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2010-12-04 09:07:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Our new opening sequence for The Walking Dead </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2010-11-30 04:14:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Please let me know what you think. This was shot as a class project for an undergrad TV production class. The professor really enjoyed it and called it better than the sequence on TV now (which I think is shot better than ours, but much more boring).

EDIT: not sure if the link attached properly. It's [here](http://vimeo.com/17275877) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What do Princes William and Harry call the Queen? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2010-11-29 06:14:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> TIL that there is a term for throwing someone out of a window </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2010-11-27 21:45:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> CAE just "feel" when they have something copied to their clipboard? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2010-11-18 23:11:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Often I'll highlight some text and copy it, then get distracted with somethign else and come back to the computer later and I can just "feel" that I have something "charged up" to paste somewhere. Anyone else feel that? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> DAE hate strict password requirements? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2010-11-12 06:10:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I think if I want to have a weak password for something as stupid as an AMC account, it's my prerogative. Fuck that "one capital letter, one number, no spaces' bullshit. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Who's this cute black girl? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2010-11-09 14:07:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> I don't think I'm the marriage type </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2010-11-08 00:05:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> TIL Mitch McConnell is an asshole </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2010-11-05 00:06:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> DAE hate condoms and love cake? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2010-11-04 04:50:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Teaser trailer for doc about Matty   Bobby's record breaking kiss!! </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2010-11-03 07:44:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Is there any legitimate way to enter or exit North Korea? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2010-10-29 19:48:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I mean obviously the elite ruling class can do whatever they want, but what about ordinary folks? Is there any country that North Korea is on good terms with and will allow tourists from? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> I Just Wanna Fuck </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2010-10-27 18:38:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Reddit, whats the most fucked up disturbing movie you've ever seen? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2010-10-26 05:21:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm not talking about the Nick Berg beheading or other sick real shit like that, but actual films that I could maybe find on Netflix. What sticks out in your mind as shocking and disturbing you like nothing else ever has? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> DAE start beating off to porn, but finish thinking about an ex-gf or hookup every time? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2010-10-22 19:09:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> IAE flabbergasted when grown adults still confuse 'left' and 'right'? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2010-10-20 06:53:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I've had that shit down since I was 6 years old, but as a photographer and someone who works on tv and film sets, I often tell people "Move just a little bit to your left" and stand dumbfounded as they move the opposite way. I can't believe people still mix up the most simple dichotomy possible. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> And here's hoping this helps you too - my recent struggle with depression </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2010-10-19 07:33:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> And here's hoping this helps you too - my recent struggle with depression </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2010-10-19 07:20:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> IWTL How To Get My Blog More Exposure </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2010-10-19 05:17:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm not trying to spam, so I won't mention the blog name or URL, but I would like to learn more about the blogosphere because I'm pretty new to it. I've found that I really like blogging and writing daily about things that interest me, and I always try to write my blogs in a way that will be interesting and insightful to others, and have some kind of cohesion and specific topic for each post. Though the blog itself is mostly about creativity and motivation and ambition and success.

How does one find other blogs similar to ones own? What simple things can I do to make my blog posts more search engine friendly? I would love to get some more eyes on the page and build up a little fanbase of loyal readers, but how does one get to that point from square one? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> This is just so...so wonderful. Emo lesbians on webcam </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2010-10-15 06:34:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Seriously, reddit? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2010-09-25 07:54:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Tell me this doesn't make you want to kill yourself </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2010-09-24 04:27:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Reddit, if you believe in LGBT activism, please help me out </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2010-09-21 04:48:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This story has been tremendously underreported IMO, judging by how much it meant to the thousands of people that tuned in to watch and tell us how inspired they were by the event. We tweeted major gay figures like Lady Gaga and Ellen Degeneres among others during the event but they have yet to acknowledge it. Ideally we'd like the story to get picked up by the Assosciated Press so it can go national. I ask that you please tell your local news, or call your local radio stations, or email your friends, or tweet your favorite celebs, or do anything you can to make sure the mainstream media does not ignore this story!

EDIT: Forgot the link! D'oh! http://stfproductions.wordpress.com/2010/09/20/they-did-it-matty-and-bobby-break-the-record-in-the-name-of-lgbt-rights/ </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> I filmed live while Matty and Bobby broke the longest kiss record - AMA </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2010-09-20 05:01:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This is John or 'Red Shoes Guy' who most of you probably saw on the uStream. I'd be glad to answer any questions you have about the event, but please check the official site first at mattyandbobbykiss.tripod.com to see answers to the most common questions.

Before you ask: They couldn't pee. The only option that was valid according to the Guinness rules was a catheter, which they opted against. Matty couldn't hold it anymore and pissed himself about 4 hours prior to the end.

I'm going to sleep now and will have class much of tomorrow but I will check back and answer as many questions as I can! In the meantime please keep bringing attention to this event as we failed to get much attention from the mainstream media. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Matty and Bobby try and break world record for longest kiss today - Watch live on Ustream at 10AM </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2010-09-18 13:34:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> DAE repeat a word over and over in their head when their mind is idle? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2010-09-14 02:31:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Sometimes when I have nothing else to think about, my inner monologue is just "Boner boner boner boner boner boner boner..."

It's not that I have a boner, or am thinking about boners, but I just like the sound of the word and it loops well, so it's kind of a silly mental mantra. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Can anyone suggests books to improve my storytelling? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2010-09-11 02:34:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm not talking about screenplay books. I know all about Mckee and Syd Field and whatnot, but books about storytelling in general. I find that when telling a story out loud to friends, I'm terrible at building it up in a way that keeps their interest and finishes in a satisfying conclusion, especially when I'm recounting something. What books have helped you with your storytelling skills? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> DAE anticipate a new relationship crashing and burning before it even starts? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2010-09-02 00:51:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I met a great girl a few days ago and we're going to the movies on friday, and I've been texting her occasionally since then and everything is going great. She's cute, she's smart, etc. But at the same time I have this terrible anxiety that I'll find something I won't like about her, or the distance will be too much of a hassle, or our age difference (I'm a senior in college, she's a senior in high school), or her parents won't like me or I won't like them or something. Basically picturing all the ways this could go wrong instead of focusing on how great it is. I'm normally not like this about anything else, but always with new relationships. I'm just waiting to screw it up or it to fizzle out on it's own. Anyone else like this? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> People whine and cry about the lack of asian actors in Last Airbender movie </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2010-07-12 16:21:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Can I have a video camera out in an airport? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2010-07-09 03:06:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm shooting a documentary about an extended trip I'm going on with 20 people, and I'd like to do some interviews and B-Roll of planes taking off and all while we're waiting to board the flight next week. Do you think I'll be harassed or questioned for having a video camera out and filming in an airport? Do I have any rights to do so? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Reddit, is there even any money in making porn anymore? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2010-07-07 07:14:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I mean I want to be a legitimate filmmaker, but I'm not above directing some porn to pay the bills. I think it'd be a lot more interesting than music videos or car commercials. However I just don't see the point of making new porn when there are GALAXIES of porn available for free on the internet. Do people still rent and buy DVDs or actually subscribe to porn paysites? And if so, do you think they still will in 5-10 years?

Edit: some rewording to clarify. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> I feel like I've lost a friend to the cult of Christianity </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2010-07-06 07:02:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> A few years ago she was a normal girl and a good friend, now she constantly refers to her being a Christian and being saved and whatnot. She's going on a missionary trip to cambodia this summer and posted a note on facebook asking for people's prayers and financial support.

Quote from the note:
"Seems crazy that I've only been a Christian for 3 years, but God has been doing amazing things and I'm really excited to see what He's been doing in Cambodia. Maybe you're not Christian and you don't care about missions and God-related things. I still ask that you take the time to pray for me. God has been so amazing in my life and it's a big deal for me to take this step of faith for Him. After meeting Jesus three years ago, He has continued to show me how broken my life is, but how i can be alive in Him. I thought Christianity was a set of rules, but its definitely not. Having a relationship with God has opened up my eyes to the person He wants me to be."

I mean this stuff freaks me out. I'm glad that she's happy and I'm all for people believing what they want to believe, but the way she talks about religion now is both sad and scary to me. I feel like I've lost a friend to a cult. I'm not mad at her by any means, but instead at the people who've brainwashed her with this shit. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Reddit, what's a good software for a non-musician to make some simple music?  </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2010-07-04 03:17:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm a PC user, so no GarageBand for me. I've heard a lot about FL Studio and Reason but I fear that it may be above my head. I'm not looking to make masterpieces, just layer a few instruments together and make some jingles. Any tips?

EDIT: Thanks for the suggestions. So how does FL Studio compare to Ableton? What are their strengths and weaknesses that would lead me to stick with one over the other? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> How to stop shooting your camera in Auto mode </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2010-07-02 10:04:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> DAE fake a yawn to check if someone is staring at them? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2010-07-02 03:00:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Often in a classroom when I feel someone is eying me, I'll force a yawn, wait a few seconds, then check to see if they're yawning too. Works very well most of the time. Anyone else do this? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Louis C.K. talks about Father's Day </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2010-06-20 21:38:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> TIL There's an extended version of Take On Me </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2010-06-16 08:20:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> DAE pronounce Warez as 'war-ehz' just because? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2010-05-28 19:55:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> I have an idea, and I want to know if its already been done </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2010-05-24 08:07:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> As a very visual person, I often wish that there was a website or a software I could download that would give me something to watch while I listened to my music. Sort of a channel that would just constantly display a slideshow of random images, whether taken from deviantart or flickr or the New York Times or anything. Just a never-ending deluge of imagery to chill out to and watch while I listen to music. Maybe if it was a software, you could customize what kind of images you like. Perhaps a Like or Dislike option for each one, and if you wanted to know more about an image, you could just click it and get the photographer/artist/story behind the image.

So reddit, does anything like this exist? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> TIL that some people prefer to sleep without pillows </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2010-05-20 06:05:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That's really strange to me. I occasionally nap without a pillow, but I can't imagine sleeping every night without them. I'm a stomach sleeper. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Well this is disconcerting, considering I never linked my facebook to CNN. They seem to have done it anyway. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2010-05-16 15:46:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> I made another crappy webcomic </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2010-05-13 06:11:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> I need an LA consultant for a story I'm writing! </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2010-05-02 19:08:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I tried craigslist, but then realized my fellow redditors are way more reliable.

Basically I'm an east coaster and have never been to LA, but I am currently writing a screenplay which takes place largely in LA and I want to bring the LA spirit into it.

In the first act our two protagonists realize they are fed up with their lives in New Jersey and decide to move to LA to live with one of their cousins, Chino, a Chicano ex-gang banger and East LA native. Much of the story will deal with the dissonance between their visions of Hollywood and the ugly realities of East LA and surrounding areas.

This is more the B story than what the plot is about, but I definitely need some questions answered periodically while I'm writing and hit dead ends. I'm looking for an LA native that I can email or text with questions on the fly about the area, and any knowledge of the chicano culture and gang life is a definite plus.

And yes, I'd love to fly out there and see it myself, but I can't afford it just yet! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Even Celebrities Think the War on Drugs is a Joke - Celebrities - Gawker.TV </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2010-04-11 18:13:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Do cops really read Miranda Rights when arresting someone? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2010-03-25 03:43:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Super cute russian girl </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2010-03-17 20:40:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Have you ever worked at a pet store? I'm researching for my screenplay.... </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2010-03-14 20:13:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> My protagonist works at a pet store for the first act of my screenplay, but I need a little insight into the daily or weekly routines that pet store employees go through. What kind of maintenance has to be done daily, weekly, monthly, and annually at a pet store? What type of activities might two employees do together because it's hard or impossible to do alone? My character is going to fall in love with his coworker at the store and I need some things for them to do other than sit around and chat while waiting for customers. Any insight would be appreciated. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> I made my first webcomic... </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2010-03-07 22:10:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Pythagoras also came up with a theorem for all beauty in the universe.... </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2010-03-06 05:38:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> All of the smartest and most creative people that I most admire just happen to be atheists </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2010-02-25 18:34:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This includes Carl Sagan, Ira Glass, Richard Dawkins, Penn Jillette, Adam Savage, Howard Stern, Steven Soderbergh, Gene Wilder, John Malkovich, Seth MacFarlane, Bruce Lee, Dave Foley, Patton Oswalt, Doug Stanhope, Stephen Fry, Ricky Gervais, Paul Giamatti, Adam Carolla, Douglas Adams, Woody Allen, Andy Richter, Ian Mackellan, Robert Altman, Bjork, Wayne Coyne, Roger Waters, Kurt Vonnegut, AJ Jacobs, Stanley Kubrick, Roger Ebert, Matt Stone, and many more. I find it interesting that the members of society that I find to be most intelligent and open minded have all landed on the same conclusion of atheism. And yet despite that, atheists are still in a tiny minority of the world population. Makes me a sad panda. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
