<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject1779</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Wizard Harry Dresden has fought many monsters and dark wizards. But babysitting the Archive may be his greatest challenge yet. [EU] </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-22 13:16:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [EU] Years after the War, Harry Potter receives a message from his cousin Dudley, requesting a meeting. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-12 16:40:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> In a world of superheroes, supervillains, and spies of all kinds, you are a traveling salesman. You sell death traps for a living. [WP] </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-07 12:54:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [TT] A superhero begins to take things into his own hands, in the name of the Greater Good. Many join his cause. A few heroes and villains stand against him. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-07 03:52:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> You are a medic in an army; two wounded soldiers, one on your side, one on the other limp in together. You ask them which side won. They have no idea. [TT] </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-26 00:03:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Dr. Cox, why does everybody, except me, cry when they play "The Last of Us"? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-25 12:35:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Dr. Cox, Elliott agreed to marry me! Wanna be a groomsman? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-19 02:04:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm getting married! I'm getting married! I'm getting married!

La la la la la la!

Married! Married! Married!

Elliot and I are getting married, Coxy! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Dr. Cox, is there something wrong with my taste buds? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-17 02:58:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Specifically, I like to put chocolate syrup on my macaroni and cheese. 

And marshmallow fluff on my steak sirloin. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Dr. Cox, what would you like me to get you for your birthday? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-16 12:52:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The Garden [IP] </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-10 13:04:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> http://azot2016.deviantart.com/art/Garden-with-Round-Trees-441674720 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [IP] Dangling in the sky </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-09 19:46:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> http://embrisionarts.deviantart.com/art/Monkey-bar-to-freedom-295633503 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [CW] Write the start of a story. A commenter will write the next part, another the next. The catch - each part has a completely different genre from the previous. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-09 01:29:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What was the best gift anybody has ever given you? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-07 17:00:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> While in the middle of a great feast in Vahalla, Thor and several others leave when the battle horn blows. Ted from Accounting realizes that Thor has left behind Mjolnir. [TT] </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-05 12:19:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Having finished "Cursed Child" and becoming interested in Peggy Sue fanfics again, let me direct your attention to "Harry Potter and the Nightmares of Future Past." </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-01 13:02:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This is one of my all-time favorite fanfictions.

https://www.fanfiction.net/s/2636963/1/Harry-Potter-and-the-Nightmares-of-Futures-Past </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> People of Reddit, how did your older siblings tease you? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-31 14:57:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> You're a elementary school teacher. All of your students have animal sidekicks that follow them to school. [TT] </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-29 03:29:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Evangelist, Tim LaHaye, author of the "Left Behind" novels, has passed away at 90. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-26 13:26:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Your sister is a superhero. Your brother is a supervillain. And you, you're a cop. [WP] </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-25 12:41:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What is the best Hey Arnold! quote? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-18 12:33:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> "Cinemawins" provides a light-hearted take on reviewing movies that is thoroughly enjoyable, and finds things to enjoy in even the most poorly received of films. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-17 03:40:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> "I don't want to be a villain anymore. Help me change." [TT] </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-17 02:58:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> "Kids, I've been telling you the story of How I Met Your Mother for a while now. This part is actually really important--a lot of things changed, really quickly." [EU] </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-16 00:33:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This Prompt will be Legend, wait for it... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Write the story of a secondary character in an existing work, that we only see sporadically. [EU] </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-14 01:08:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> To clarify, there are lots of stories where we only see one character a few times. So what happens in the in-between. I used Established Universe instead of Writing Prompt because I was curious to see what people would develop for characters that are already...well, established and wondered about. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> "THE FLOOR IS LAVA!" [WP] </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-12 12:36:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Nobody knew they existed. When the aliens invaded, they rose up to protect us. [TT] </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-01 13:06:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> You discover that when you make your kid sister laugh, she can see visions of the future. The harder you make her laugh, the clearer the visions become. [WP] </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-28 12:30:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> They were not lovers; their PLATONIC love was far greater. [TT] </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-17 03:30:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> You are a super-villain. Your nemesis, the hero, was just killed in a fight with another villain. How will you respond. [TT] </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-13 22:59:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The most disproportionate vengeance for the most trivial wrong-doing imaginable. [TT] </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-10 01:32:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Usually it seems that when revenge gets out of hand, it tends to be collateral damage. So what if the revenge is deliberately extreme, but the fault was exceptionally minor?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> You live in a world where everybody has a visible shoulder angel and a shoulder demon. [WP] </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-06 13:28:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The war was fought and it was brutal, but nobody died. [WP] </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-01 02:28:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> You discover that when you make your kid sister laugh, she can see visions of the future. The harder you make her laugh, the clearer her visions become. [WP] </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-28 23:36:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Will you use this to your advantage? Maybe win the lottery? 

Why does it only work when *you* make your sister laugh? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> On a beach trip with your family, your kid sister asks you to help her build a sandcastle. [TT] </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-25 12:49:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Is there a sandcastle contest going on?

Is the tide coming in?

Will you bury your sister in the sand and build the castle on top of her? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> You're playing Hide-And-Go-Seek with your cousins. [TT] </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-21 00:00:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Have you continuously lost the game and are determined to win?

Is there cheating involved?

Is the Master Bedroom off-limits?

What happens when you get stuck in your hiding spot and can't get out? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Your younger sibling claims that the cardboard box they play in is a time machine. They're right. [WP] </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-18 13:27:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Redditors with siblings, how did your brothers or sisters use to tease or torture you? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-18 13:17:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Children's logic dictates the way the world works. [WP] </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-17 12:07:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The way young children see the world--their concepts of fairness, their overt cause-and-effect worldview, their unorthodox views on nutrition, etc.--is the dominant force on Earth. What happens now? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The Disney Villains meet up for Poker Night. [WP] </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-16 12:34:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> A private investigator is hired to assist the police in finding a billionaire's kidnapped daughter. [TT] </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-15 04:04:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> You live in a world where warriors can not only communicate with their weapons, but also their armor and shields as well. Unfortunately, your sentient equipment won't stop arguing with each other. [WP] </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-14 13:09:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> You are a private investigator; this is your very first case. [TT] </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-13 03:20:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> You are riding a train and get out at your stop. When you get out, you do not recognize the station. When you turn around, you do not recognize your train. [WP] </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-12 14:02:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What is your least favorite thing about your most favorite character? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-11 13:00:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> One of the nice things about Harry Potter is how so many of the characters are well-rounded, having traits that are likeable and traits that are more negative.

So, what's your least favorite thing about your favorite character? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Your two favorite franchises (Harry Potter, James Bond, Harry Dresden, Marvel Cinematic Universe, etc.) find themselves intertwined with each other's plots. [EU] </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-09 03:24:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Will Dumbledore's Army join the Avengers?

Will the Guardians of the Galaxy take on the Death Star?

Unleash your imagination! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> It's Mother's Day, Reddit--what is your favorite memory with your mother? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-08 17:29:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> "This isn't what I signed up for when I told Mom I would babysit!" [WP] </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-07 15:06:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Which fictional character have you ever felt an absurdly large amount of sympathy for? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-04 14:31:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [WP] "Why did they do it, then? They all died." "They did it because it was the right thing to do. Because they were heroes." </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-03 02:14:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> "Why did they do it then? They all died." "They did it because it was the right thing to do. Because they were heroes." </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-03 02:03:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [Serious] Following backlash, Will Ferrell has pulled out of portraying an Alzheimer's-stricken President Reagan in potential film. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-30 01:11:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> A billionaire approaches you and offers you a chance to go into business with him. He wants to branch out a bit--he wants to become a Zoo Tycoon. [WP] </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-27 12:06:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What animals would you adopt?

Multi-species exhibits?

What would you prioritize? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Even now, Pixar's *The Incredibles* succeeds in being both an excellent superhero film and surprisingly prompt social commentary. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-24 03:27:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Whether it's the draconian laws of Superhero Relocation Act, the unsatisfying atmosphere of living in a world that praises mediocrity and discourages actual drive and success--a world that feels entirely too familiar at times, or the dynamics of family, I find that *The Incredibles* is one of the more overlooked animated feature films.

What are /r/movies thoughts?

Edit: Clarification </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Marvel's "Inhumans" film has been pulled from the line-up. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-23 13:01:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> You're playing a game of your favorite sport, when you realize everyone else on BOTH teams is trying to lose. [TT] </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-22 02:58:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What is one MAJOR thing you would change about a show you watched that would have a significant effect on the plot? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-21 03:39:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> She's only ever cried in front of you. [WP] </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-21 01:11:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> You're a new teacher. Your kid sister is in your class. [WP] </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-20 13:19:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> You're the only one who can make her laugh. [WP] </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-20 01:36:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Which mysterious animal or cryptid do you think has the best chance of having its existence confirmed by science? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-17 12:52:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [WP] You discover that when you make your kid sister laugh, she can see visions from the future. The harder you make her laugh, the clearer her visions become. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-17 02:09:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What is something that, while apparently well-intentioned, you firmly disagree with? [Serious] </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-13 02:02:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Redditors with siblings, how did you and your brother/s and/or sister/s tease or torment each other? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-10 13:22:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Two rival gangs interfere with the other's attempts to kidnap the daughter of a billionaire. [WP] </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-08 00:28:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [Serious] Redditors, have you ever witnessed a miracle? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-26 12:43:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Redditors who have siblings, what is your favorite memory concerning your sibling? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-19 16:20:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Your kid sister is a teen superhero and you are her arch-nemesis. One day, during a battle in your lair, you reveal you know her *fatal flaw.* It's the same weakness you used to exploit when you were kids. [TT] </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-12 02:30:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [EU] Severus Snape challenges Harry Dresden to a duel over who will get to be the new DADA professor at Hogwarts School of Witchcraft   Wizardry. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-11 03:05:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Hogwarts gets its newest professor to teach DADA. This year, it is a foreigner. He goes by the name Harry Dresden. [EU] </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-10 03:15:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Who is the least likable hero in film or television? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-06 19:40:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> A fan-film based on *Harry Potter* focusing on Severus Snape and James Potter has been released. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-02 00:14:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Which television character's self-sacrifice is most moving? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-29 03:12:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What piece of fanon is something you cannot stand? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-24 01:54:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Headcanons and fanon are a huge part of this fandom, and it's often a lot of fun to speculate, but are there any popular theories that you do not like?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Redditors with siblings, how did your brothers and sisters used to tease or torment you? How did you tease them? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-21 02:26:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What is something you find hilariously ironic? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-18 02:10:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [Request] Platonic Ginny/Luna </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-15 16:05:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Ginny Weasley and Luna Lovegood have one of the more interesting friendships in the series, but the vast majority of fics I've found ship them. I'm looking for fics that explore their platonic friendship.

One of my favorite fics, that has since been taken down, was *Faith and Understanding.* </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Redditors, what was the most off-topic story your teacher told your class? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-13 04:49:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Missing and Disappeared Fanfics </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-10 02:29:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It has come to my attention that my very favorite fanfic from *Harry Potter,* *Faith and Understanding* has been taken down for some reason or another. Not really sure why, all it says at Fanfiction.net is "Unable to locate story. Code 1." Not sure what that means, but moving on to the topic at hand:

Have there ever been fanfics that you were fond of that were taken down? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Redditors with siblings, how did you use to tease or annoy your brothers and sisters? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-09 00:58:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What is something you learned in a classroom, that you thought you would never need, but wound up being useful later in life? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-07 16:23:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What was a secret you kept, that when it was found out, turned out not to be a very big deal? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-07 02:15:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What scene in a movie is totally unnecessary for advancing the plot, but is still your favorite scene? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-06 23:18:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> A lot of popular scenes in films are...well, for want of a better word, filler. But that doesn't mean, necessarily, that they're bad. So, this leads into the question--what unnecessary scenes are your favorites? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What is a television show from your childhood, or else is currently marketed to children, did you not enjoy? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-06 23:04:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What was the most interesting conversation you ever had with a stranger? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-06 01:14:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [Serious] Redditors who are adamant about ***NOT*** supporting Bernie Sanders for President, what are your justifications? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-03 13:47:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What is your favorite overlooked scene from an animated Disney film? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-31 05:43:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What would you like to see them do in the new "Marvel's Spider-Man" film? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-23 00:59:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Recently confirmed for July 7, 2017, I was wondering what specifically people wanted to see in the upcoming Spider-Man film? How should they explore the Peter-Harry dynamic? Supervillains or average thugs? Etc. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What is the most rage-inducing moment in film? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-21 03:07:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What's an tourist attraction that a lot of people don't know about, but it's actually a gem? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-07 00:46:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What was a food you hated until you tried it homemade? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-06 19:48:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [WP] Far in the future, gladiatorial combat has seen a resurgence in popularity. To liven up the competition, genetic modifications are made on the fighters, combining their DNA with that of animals. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-06 01:06:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [WP] War is upon us; you are the champion of your army. Your opponent--your twin sister; the battleground--the house. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-04 17:56:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Basically, this is sibling rivalry with a war/espionage twist. Stealing your sister's diary? A mission for a spy. Nerf guns and Super Soakers. That sort of thing. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [WP] You discover that when you make your kid sister laugh, she can see visions from the future. The harder you make her laugh, the clearer her visions become. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-04 14:04:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What is an episode of your favorite show that even you have to admit is bad? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-02 17:51:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [Serious] Texans who support the new Open-Carry Law, what are your reasons? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-02 00:39:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> History buffs and historians and movie buffs of Reddit, what is your favorite film that is "Based on a true story"? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-28 20:54:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [WP] You discover that when you make your kid sister laugh, she can see visions from the future. The harder you make her laugh, the clearer her visions become. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-28 06:16:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [EU] Instead of killing *just* her mother, the wayward spell kills both of Luna Lovegood's parents. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-27 02:34:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Can be pretty much anything--the accident itself. Or maybe the aftermath--what happens to Luna? Or a few years later, how does losing both her parents affect her connection to Harry Potter? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [EU] Mace Windu kills Darth Sidious despite Anakin Skywalker's pleas. What happens next? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-24 03:01:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [WP] You discover that your kid sister can see the future when she laughs. The harder she laughs, the clearer the visions are. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-23 21:59:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [EU] While eating a meal of assorted meats with Thor, Ted asks him where Phil Coulson, who died in battle shortly before the Battle of New York, is. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-23 03:31:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [WP] Your thirteen-year-old younger sister is a secret agent. You discover this. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-23 00:35:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Your thirteen-year-old younger sister is a secret agent. You discover this. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-23 00:05:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [WP] Santa Claus and the Sandman confront the Boogie Man over his creating nightmares and scaring children. Boogie says his work is justified. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-22 02:48:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What is the plot of a story that you've always wanted to read, but you don't know whether or not it's ever been written? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-21 18:33:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What is the plot of a story you've always wanted to read but never knew whether or not it'd actually been written? Other redditors, has that story been written? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-21 18:17:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Non-Americans of Reddit, what is your favorite food that is unique to America? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-21 01:23:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Superhero fans of Reddit, what is your favorite scene in a superhero television show? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-20 00:25:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Whose last words do you find particularly meaningful and why? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-18 18:50:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Santa Claus appears to you, and says that as a reward for your good behavior, he is giving you a one-day-free pass for the Naughty and Nice List; your behavior today will not affect your spot on the list. [TT] </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-17 20:22:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Fresh out of the academy, you are assigned to interrogate a member of the opposing faction in a war of espionage. The person you are to interrogate is your kid sister. [WP] </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-15 17:26:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The same methods you would use to find out her secrets when you were younger are now to be used for a political purpose. You must learn everything possible that your sister knows and she is not going to just tell you the information. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Fresh out of the academy, you are assigned to interrogate a member of the opposing faction in a war of espionage. The person you are to interrogate is your kid sister. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-15 16:58:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What unpopular Christmas song do you actually enjoy? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-11-30 13:51:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What death scene, in any form of media, did not have the impact you were expecting it to have? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-11-29 22:51:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What is your favorite, overlooked Christmas movie? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-11-28 15:40:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Christmas movies are awesome, but it seems like the channels play the same ones over and over--Home Alone, Wonderful Life, etc. So, what's your favorite overlooked Christmas movie that doesn't usually play during the holiday season, simply because it's overshadowed by the classics? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Who would you consider is the best Young Adult fiction writer? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-11-27 21:55:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Who would you consider is the best Young Adult fiction writer? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-11-27 21:39:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [Serious]Reddit, has there ever been an instance when you completely switched your position on something? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-11-25 21:49:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What is your favorite nature documentary? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-11-23 02:56:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> A lot of people seem to really like watching documentaries about various sub-cultures in the Western World, or documentaries about hot-button issues.

I'm curious to find out what are your favorite nature documentaries. I always loved "Wolves at Our Door," by Jim and Jamie Dutcher. I also liked "Meet the Coywolf" that aired on PBS last year. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Can somebody please explain why there doesn't appear to be verification of melanism in mountain lions? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-11-22 20:36:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I am aware that many species exhibit a phenomenon called melanism, which is essentially the opposite effect of albinism, and then this can be an explanation for assorted "mysterious creatures." I also know that in the world of the Big Cats, "black panthers" are melanistic leopards and jaguars. There have been many sightings of so-called "black panthers" in the United States and Canada, but to my knowledge, there has never been a verified melanistic mountain lion.
Is there some genetic reason for this? Are some creatures just pre-disposed not to exhibit melanism or albinism? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Why hasn't there been any verification of melanistic mountain lions? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-11-22 20:25:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Is there any plot point that you would change, and if it wound up having a larger snowball effect on the series as a whole, what do you think would happen? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-11-22 14:26:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hey guys. A while back, I was reading a thread that theorized what would have happened had Cassius Warrington been drawn as the Hogwarts Champion in lieu of Cedric Diggory. The thread elaborated potential side effects of this one change and I found it compelling.

And I also read a thread once that theorized a storyline in which Aunt Petunia takes Harry under her wing from the very beginning, and I found it equally compelling.

So, to clarify my question, what plot element would you change that could sway the tide of events in the series and what would those effects be? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Reddit, who is somebody you consider to be a hero, and why? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-11-10 03:18:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Reddit, what is your favorite schism in fiction and why? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-11-07 23:36:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
