<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject5054</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-26 01:57:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Study (open access): [Climate Change and Future Pollen Allergy in Europe](http://ehp.niehs.nih.gov/EHP173/)
___

**Abstract**:

**Background**: Globally pollen allergy is a major public health problem, but a fundamental unknown is the likely impact of climate change. To our knowledge, this is the first study to quantify the consequences of climate change upon pollen allergy in humans.

**Objectives**: To produce quantitative estimates of the potential impact of climate change upon pollen allergy in humans, focusing upon common ragweed (Ambrosia artemisiifolia) in Europe.

**Methods**: A process-based model estimated the change in ragweeds range under climate change. A second model simulated current and future ragweed pollen levels. These were translated into health burdens using a dose-response curve generated from a systematic review and current and future population data. Models considered two different suites of regional climate/pollen models, two greenhouse gas emissions scenarios (RCP4.5 and 8.5), and three different plant invasion scenarios.

**Results**: Our primary estimates indicate that sensitization to ragweed will more than double in Europe, from 33 to 77 million people, by 2041-2060. According to our projections, while sensitization will increase in countries with an existing ragweed problem (e.g. Hungary, the Balkans), the greatest proportional increases will occur where sensitization is uncommon (e.g. Germany, Poland, France). Higher pollen concentrations and a longer pollen season may also increase the severity of symptoms. Our model projections are driven predominantly by changes in climate (66%), but also are influenced by current trends in the spread of this invasive plant species. Assumptions about the rate at which ragweed spreads throughout Europe have a large influence upon the results.

**Conclusions**: Our quantitative estimates indicate that ragweed pollen allergy will become a common health problem across Europe, expanding into areas where it is currently uncommon. Control of ragweed spread may be an important adaptation strategy in response to climate change.
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-26 00:23:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> During the early formation of the solar system Jupiter in no way protected the inner planets. The migration of the gas planets (see: [Nice Model](https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Nice_model)) is what lead to the [Late Heavy Bombardment](https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Late_Heavy_Bombardment). Water, is largely attributed to asteroids (not comets) and the Earth itself (ie. [it was always here](http://science.sciencemag.org/content/346/6209/623) since the formation of the planet and was not delivered later on). These are the most strongly supported arguments currently accepted by the majority of the scientific community.

Basic celestial mechanics tells us that the early solar system, *any* early solar system, will be chaotic - by definition then Jupiter like planets cannot 'protect' terrestrial planets, or any others for that matter. Any migration of planetesimals and planets will perturb the orbits of surrounding bodies until new orbital resonances are configured and stabilized.

I would also add that ... the possibility that a moon heated by tidal forces orbiting around a gas giant beyond the ice line might also be an additional habitat for potential life.

I think that's about the only thing I you've said that I would agree with. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-25 20:41:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> We have a sample size of one when it comes to solar systems with life. 

Physics and chemistry don't suddenly start operating differently once you step off of planet Earth. I understand what you're getting at but I'm solely focusing on correcting your improper statement with regard to Jupiter acting as a 'protector.'

Of course having a Jupiter has pros and cons. Even the article you cite comes to that conclusion.

That doesn't change the fact that Jupiter sends *more* material towards Earth. Pros, it stops the occasional comet from reaching the inner planets. Cons, it continuously perturbs the orbit of the asteroids and sends a shit ton of debris towards the inner planets. Stating that there are pros and cons without weighing the pros and cons is dismissive of the net effect. The article clearly states:

"It definitely sends asteroids and comets our way and, in any given year, more than 90 percent of all objects crossing Earths orbit are asteroids, so the protection Jupiter provides us from long period comets, or by eventually removing short period comets, is of lesser importance. Hence Jupiter is not the friend that it has been perceived to be" </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-25 10:10:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> "[So I've run some calculations re surface temp of new planet around Proxima Centauri...](https://pbs.twimg.com/media/CqrKWJAUMAgeRKZ.jpg)" - Chris Colose (twitter)
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-25 10:08:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Jupiter protecting the inner planets is a common myth. It actually send far more material in towards the inner planets than it does from preventing material from reaching the inner planets. It is, as they say, a "[villain in disguise](http://www.astrobio.net/news-exclusive/villain-in-disguise-jupiters-role-in-impacts-on-earth/)." </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-24 21:44:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Study: [Early onset of industrial-era warming across the oceans and continents](http://www.nature.com/nature/journal/v536/n7617/full/nature19082.html)
___

**Abstract**:

*The evolution of industrial-era warming across the continents and oceans provides a context for future climate change and is important for determining climate sensitivity and the processes that control regional warming. Here we use post-ad 1500 palaeoclimate records to show that sustained industrial-era warming of the tropical oceans first developed during the mid-nineteenth century and was nearly synchronous with Northern Hemisphere continental warming. The early onset of sustained, significant warming in palaeoclimate records and model simulations suggests that greenhouse forcing of industrial-era warming commenced as early as the mid-nineteenth century and included an enhanced equatorial ocean response mechanism. The development of Southern Hemisphere warming is delayed in reconstructions, but this apparent delay is not reproduced in climate simulations. Our findings imply that instrumental records are too short to comprehensively assess anthropogenic climate change and that, in some regions, about 180 years of industrial-era warming has already caused surface temperatures to emerge above pre-industrial values, even when taking natural variability into account.* </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-24 21:44:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Study: [Early onset of industrial-era warming across the oceans and continents](http://www.nature.com/nature/journal/v536/n7617/full/nature19082.html)
___

**Abstract**:

The evolution of industrial-era warming across the continents and oceans provides a context for future climate change and is important for determining climate sensitivity and the processes that control regional warming. Here we use post-ad 1500 palaeoclimate records to show that sustained industrial-era warming of the tropical oceans first developed during the mid-nineteenth century and was nearly synchronous with Northern Hemisphere continental warming. The early onset of sustained, significant warming in palaeoclimate records and model simulations suggests that greenhouse forcing of industrial-era warming commenced as early as the mid-nineteenth century and included an enhanced equatorial ocean response mechanism. The development of Southern Hemisphere warming is delayed in reconstructions, but this apparent delay is not reproduced in climate simulations. Our findings imply that instrumental records are too short to comprehensively assess anthropogenic climate change and that, in some regions, about 180 years of industrial-era warming has already caused surface temperatures to emerge above pre-industrial values, even when taking natural variability into account. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-24 21:36:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Study: [Early onset of industrial-era warming across the oceans and continents](http://www.nature.com/nature/journal/v536/n7617/full/nature19082.html)
___

**Abstract**:

The evolution of industrial-era warming across the continents and oceans provides a context for future climate change and is important for determining climate sensitivity and the processes that control regional warming. Here we use post-ad 1500 palaeoclimate records to show that sustained industrial-era warming of the tropical oceans first developed during the mid-nineteenth century and was nearly synchronous with Northern Hemisphere continental warming. The early onset of sustained, significant warming in palaeoclimate records and model simulations suggests that greenhouse forcing of industrial-era warming commenced as early as the mid-nineteenth century and included an enhanced equatorial ocean response mechanism. The development of Southern Hemisphere warming is delayed in reconstructions, but this apparent delay is not reproduced in climate simulations. Our findings imply that instrumental records are too short to comprehensively assess anthropogenic climate change and that, in some regions, about 180 years of industrial-era warming has already caused surface temperatures to emerge above pre-industrial values, even when taking natural variability into account. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-24 21:14:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Seriously, dude, thanks for your good work. It's good to have information like this available.

Don't forget to thank the good people at [the USGS](http://earthquake.usgs.gov/earthquakes/eventpage/us10006gbf#executive) then that *actually* do the all the work and make the information available. He simply copies and pastes the information without giving credit where credit is due.

If I were him, amongst his post I would be directing people to the USGS site and telling people to be proactive on how they can easily obtain information for themselves rather than teaching people to be reliant on him. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-23 22:07:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The article's underlying assumption (the crux of any argument) is for a large investment and rapid expansion of renewables or near-zero carbon technologies (NZCT) if attempts to reduce global emissions are to be adopted. On the other hand, should little be done to reduce emissions then emissions are likely to see a continued increase even when switching from coal to natural gas as you've pointed out, but is also pointed out in Hausfather's paper from which his article is based on: [Bounding the climate viability of natural gas as a bridge fuel to displace coal](http://www.sciencedirect.com/science/article/pii/S0301421515300239), which is illustrated in [here](https://i.imgur.com/VTwS5DA.png). 

...that means cheap natural gas is not just replacing coal, but solar and wind, too...

Hausfather briefly touches on this in the article stating, "*But if we end up locking in gas infrastructure that sticks around and delays renewables, we might be better off eschewing a gas bridge even if it means sticking around with coal a bit longer.*"

I have yet to read the paper you've linked in full, but it would be interesting to see how well the models account for climate policy, for example COP21 (taking place over a year after the papers publishing). </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-23 11:23:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Study (open access): [Decadal variability of tropical tropopause temperature and its relationship to the Pacific Decadal Oscillation](http://www.nature.com/articles/srep29537)
___

**Abstract**:

*Tropopause temperatures (TPTs) control the amount of stratospheric water vapour, which influences chemistry, radiation and circulation in the stratosphere, and is also an important driver of surface climate. Decadal variability and long-term trends in tropical TPTs as well as stratospheric water vapour are largely unknown. Here, we present for the first time evidence, from reanalysis and state-of-the-art climate model simulations, of a link between decadal variability in tropical TPTs and the Pacific Decadal Oscillation (PDO). The negative phase of the PDO is associated with anomalously cold sea surface temperatures (SSTs) in the tropical east and central Pacific, which enhance the zonal SST gradient across the equatorial Pacific. The latter drives a stronger Walker Circulation and a weaker Hadley Circulation, which leads to less convection and subsequently a warmer tropopause over the central equatorial Pacific. Over the North Pacific, positive sea level pressure anomalies occur, which damp vertical wave propagation into the stratosphere. This in turn slows the Brewer-Dobson circulation, and hence warms the tropical tropopause, enabling more water vapour to enter the stratosphere. The reverse chain of events holds for the positive phase of the PDO. Such ocean-troposphere-stratosphere interactions may provide an important feedback on the Earths global surface temperature.* </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-23 01:40:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Study (open access): [Nuclear energy and path dependence in Europes Energy union: coherence or continued divergence?](http://www.tandfonline.com/doi/full/10.1080/14693062.2016.1179616)
___

**Policy relevance**:

*This article highlights the significance of non-market forces in shaping the EUs energy markets. It finds that intensities of national commitment to nuclear power tend to be inversely related to degrees of success in achieving EU climate policy goals. While the nuclear sector is increasingly economically uncompetitive and appears to be in decline for the EU as a whole, an abiding political challenge remains one of increasing interests and incentives in popular participation and interest in energy systems management.*

**Abstract**:

*Since its initial adoption, the EUs 2020 Strategy  to reduce its greenhouse gas emissions by 20%, increase the share of renewable energy to at least 20% of consumption, and achieve energy savings of 20% or more by 2020  has witnessed substantial albeit uneven progress. This article addresses the question of what role nuclear power generation has played, and can or should play in future, towards attaining the EU 2020 Strategy, particularly with reference to decreasing emissions and increasing renewables. It also explores the persistent diversity in energy strategies among member states. To do so, it first surveys the current landscape of nuclear energy use and then presents the interrelated concepts of path dependency, momentum, and lock-in. The article proceeds to examine five factors that help explain national nuclear divergence: technological capacity and consumption; economic cost; security and materiality; national perceptions; and political, ideological and institutional factors. This divergence reveals a more general weakness in the 2020 Strategys underlying assumptions. Although energy security  defined as energy availability, reliability, affordability, and sustainability  remains a vital concern for all member states, the 2020 Strategy does not explicitly address questions of political participation, control, and power. The inverse relationship identified here  between intensity of nuclear commitments, and emissions mitigation and uptake of renewable sources  underscores the importance of increasing citizens' levels of energy policy awareness and participation in policy design.* </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-23 00:31:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Study (open access): [Nuclear energy and path dependence in Europes Energy union: coherence or continued divergence?](http://www.tandfonline.com/doi/full/10.1080/14693062.2016.1179616)
___

**Policy relevance**:

This article highlights the significance of non-market forces in shaping the EUs energy markets. It finds that intensities of national commitment to nuclear power tend to be inversely related to degrees of success in achieving EU climate policy goals. While the nuclear sector is increasingly economically uncompetitive and appears to be in decline for the EU as a whole, an abiding political challenge remains one of increasing interests and incentives in popular participation and interest in energy systems management.

**Abstract**:

Since its initial adoption, the EUs 2020 Strategy  to reduce its greenhouse gas emissions by 20%, increase the share of renewable energy to at least 20% of consumption, and achieve energy savings of 20% or more by 2020  has witnessed substantial albeit uneven progress. This article addresses the question of what role nuclear power generation has played, and can or should play in future, towards attaining the EU 2020 Strategy, particularly with reference to decreasing emissions and increasing renewables. It also explores the persistent diversity in energy strategies among member states. To do so, it first surveys the current landscape of nuclear energy use and then presents the interrelated concepts of path dependency, momentum, and lock-in. The article proceeds to examine five factors that help explain national nuclear divergence: technological capacity and consumption; economic cost; security and materiality; national perceptions; and political, ideological and institutional factors. This divergence reveals a more general weakness in the 2020 Strategys underlying assumptions. Although energy security  defined as energy availability, reliability, affordability, and sustainability  remains a vital concern for all member states, the 2020 Strategy does not explicitly address questions of political participation, control, and power. The inverse relationship identified here  between intensity of nuclear commitments, and emissions mitigation and uptake of renewable sources  underscores the importance of increasing citizens' levels of energy policy awareness and participation in policy design. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-21 23:38:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Study: [Human influence on tropical cyclone intensity](http://science.sciencemag.org/content/353/6296/242)
___

**Abstract**:

Recent assessments agree that tropical cyclone intensity should increase as the climate warms. Less agreement exists on the detection of recent historical trends in tropical cyclone intensity. We interpret future and recent historical trends by using the theory of potential intensity, which predicts the maximum intensity achievable by a tropical cyclone in a given local environment. Although greenhouse gasdriven warming increases potential intensity, climate model simulations suggest that aerosol cooling has largely canceled that effect over the historical record. Large natural variability complicates analysis of trends, as do poleward shifts in the latitude of maximum intensity. In the absence of strong reductions in greenhouse gas emissions, future greenhouse gas forcing of potential intensity will increasingly dominate over aerosol forcing, leading to substantially larger increases in tropical cyclone intensities. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-21 23:26:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Study: [Human influence on tropical cyclone intensity](http://science.sciencemag.org/content/353/6296/242)
___

**Abstract**:

*Recent assessments agree that tropical cyclone intensity should increase as the climate warms. Less agreement exists on the detection of recent historical trends in tropical cyclone intensity. We interpret future and recent historical trends by using the theory of potential intensity, which predicts the maximum intensity achievable by a tropical cyclone in a given local environment. Although greenhouse gasdriven warming increases potential intensity, climate model simulations suggest that aerosol cooling has largely canceled that effect over the historical record. Large natural variability complicates analysis of trends, as do poleward shifts in the latitude of maximum intensity. In the absence of strong reductions in greenhouse gas emissions, future greenhouse gas forcing of potential intensity will increasingly dominate over aerosol forcing, leading to substantially larger increases in tropical cyclone intensities.* </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-20 22:45:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> They certainly do. They also contribute to the widening, and creation of fractures in the ice as well as potentially increasing the velocity at which the glacier moves. If the supraglacial lakes drain, they commonly do so through [moulins](http://www.global-greenhouse-warming.com/images/iceflowMoulin.jpg?e8ab49) which [channel](http://www.venachu.com/uploads/2/2/6/1/22616488/8754639.jpg?956) the melt water into (en) and below (sub) the glacier, which promotes an increase in the velocity of glacial flow through basal sliding. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-20 12:02:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The [Transantarctic Mountains](http://blogs.ei.columbia.edu/wp-content/uploads/2015/11/antarctica-NASA-lima-map-1200.jpg) divide Antarctica into East and West. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-20 11:42:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Study: [Seasonal Evolution of Supraglacial Lakes on an East Antarctic Outlet Glacier](http://onlinelibrary.wiley.com/doi/10.1002/2016GL069511/full)
___

**Abstract**:

Supraglacial lakes are known to influence ice melt and ice flow on the Greenland ice sheet and potentially cause ice shelf disintegration on the Antarctic Peninsula. In East Antarctica, however, our understanding of their behaviour and impact is more limited. Using 150 optical satellite images and meteorological records from 2000-2013, we provide the first multi-year analysis of lake evolution on Langhovde Glacier, Dronning Maud Land (6911'S, 3932'E). We observe 7,990 lakes and 855 surface channels up to 18.1 km inland (~ 670 m a.s.l.) from the grounding line, and document three pathways of lake demise: (i) refreezing, (ii) drainage to the en-/sub-glacial environment (on the floating ice), and (iii) overflow into surface channels (on both the floating and grounded ice). The parallels between these mechanisms, and those observed on Greenland/the Antarctic Peninsula, suggest that lakes may similarly affect rates and patterns of ice melt, ice flow and ice shelf disintegration in East Antarctica. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-20 11:39:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Study (open access): [Spatially governed climate factors dominate management in determining the quantity and distribution of soil organic carbon in dryland agricultural systems](http://www.nature.com/articles/srep31468)
___

**Abstract**:

Few studies describe the primary drivers influencing soil organic carbon (SOC) stocks and the distribution of carbon (C) fractions in agricultural systems from semi-arid regions; yet these soils comprise one fifth of the global land area. Here we identified the primary drivers for changes in total SOC and associated particulate (POC), humus (HOC) and resistant (ROC) organic C fractions for 1347 sample points in the semi-arid agricultural region of Western Australia. Total SOC stock (00.3m) varied from 4 to 209t C ha^1 with 79% of variation explained by measured variables. The proportion of C in POC, HOC and ROC fractions averaged 28%, 45% and 27% respectively. Climate (43%) and land management practices (32%) had the largest relative influence on variation in total SOC. Carbon accumulation was constrained where average daily temperature was above 17.2C and annual rainfall below 450mm, representing approximately 42% of the 197,300km2 agricultural region. As such large proportions of this region are not suited to C sequestration strategies. For the remainder of the region a strong influence of management practices on SOC indicate opportunities for C sequestration strategies associated with incorporation of longer pasture phases and adequate fertilisation. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-20 11:36:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Study: [Ensemble projections of wildfire activity and carbonaceous aerosol concentrations over the western United States in the mid-21st century](http://www.sciencedirect.com/science/article/pii/S1352231013004573)
___

Highlights

 We apply ensemble projection for future wildfire using output from 15 GCMs.

 We develop and evaluate both regressions and a parameterization for fire predictions.

 We investigate the impacts of climate change on fuel load by the midcentury.

 We examine fire-induced changes in OC/BC by the midcentury.

**Abstract**:

We estimate future wildfire activity over the western United States during the mid-21st century (20462065), based on results from 15 climate models following the A1B scenario. We develop fire prediction models by regressing meteorological variables from the current and previous years together with fire indexes onto observed regional area burned. The regressions explain 0.250.60 of the variance in observed annual area burned during 19802004, depending on the ecoregion. We also parameterize daily area burned with temperature, precipitation, and relative humidity. This approach explains 0.5 of the variance in observed area burned over forest ecoregions but shows no predictive capability in the semi-arid regions of Nevada and California. By applying the meteorological fields from 15 climate models to our fire prediction models, we quantify the robustness of our wildfire projections at midcentury. We calculate increases of 24124% in area burned using regressions and 63169% with the parameterization. Our projections are most robust in the southwestern desert, where all GCMs predict significant (p  0.05) meteorological changes. For forested ecoregions, more GCMs predict significant increases in future area burned with the parameterization than with the regressions, because the latter approach is sensitive to hydrological variables that show large inter-model variability in the climate projections. The parameterization predicts that the fire season lengthens by 23 days in the warmer and drier climate at midcentury. Using a chemical transport model, we find that wildfire emissions will increase summertime surface organic carbon aerosol over the western United States by 4670% and black carbon by 2027% at midcentury, relative to the present day. The pollution is most enhanced during extreme episodes: above the 84th percentile of concentrations, OC increases by 90% and BC by 50%, while visibility decreases from 130 km to 100 km in 32 Federal Class 1 areas in Rocky Mountains Forest.
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-20 11:31:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Study: [Seasonal Evolution of Supraglacial Lakes on an East Antarctic Outlet Glacier](http://onlinelibrary.wiley.com/doi/10.1002/2016GL069511/full)
___

**Abstract**:

Supraglacial lakes are known to influence ice melt and ice flow on the Greenland ice sheet and potentially cause ice shelf disintegration on the Antarctic Peninsula. In East Antarctica, however, our understanding of their behaviour and impact is more limited. Using 150 optical satellite images and meteorological records from 2000-2013, we provide the first multi-year analysis of lake evolution on Langhovde Glacier, Dronning Maud Land (6911'S, 3932'E). We observe 7,990 lakes and 855 surface channels up to 18.1km inland (~ 670ma.s.l.) from the grounding line, and document three pathways of lake demise: (i) refreezing, (ii) drainage to the en-/sub-glacial environment (on the floating ice), and (iii) overflow into surface channels (on both the floating and grounded ice). The parallels between these mechanisms, and those observed on Greenland/the Antarctic Peninsula, suggest that lakes may similarly affect rates and patterns of ice melt, ice flow and ice shelf disintegration in East Antarctica. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-20 11:21:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Study: [Pacific sea level rise patterns and global surface temperature variability](http://onlinelibrary.wiley.com/doi/10.1002/2016GL069401/abstract)
___

**Abstract**:

During 19982012, climate change and sea level rise (SLR) exhibit two notable features: a slowdown of global surface warming (hiatus) and a rapid SLR in the tropical western Pacific. To quantify their relationship, we analyze the long-term control simulations of 38 climate models. We find a significant and robust correlation between the east-west contrast of dynamic sea level (DSL) in the Pacific and global mean surface temperature (GST) variability on both interannual and decadal time scales. Based on linear regression of the multimodel ensemble mean, the anomalously fast SLR in the western tropical Pacific observed during 19982012 indicates suppression of a potential global surface warming of 0.16  0.06C. In contrast, the Pacific contributed 0.29  0.10C to the significant interannual GST increase in 1997/1998. The Pacific DSL anomalies observed in 2015 suggest that the strong El Nio in 2015/2016 could lead to a 0.21  0.07C GST jump. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-20 11:19:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Study: [Pacific sea level rise patterns and global surface temperature variability](http://onlinelibrary.wiley.com/doi/10.1002/2016GL069401/abstract)
___

**Abstract**:

During 19982012, climate change and sea level rise (SLR) exhibit two notable features: a slowdown of global surface warming (hiatus) and a rapid SLR in the tropical western Pacific. To quantify their relationship, we analyze the long-term control simulations of 38 climate models. We find a significant and robust correlation between the east-west contrast of dynamic sea level (DSL) in the Pacific and global mean surface temperature (GST) variability on both interannual and decadal time scales. Based on linear regression of the multimodel ensemble mean, the anomalously fast SLR in the western tropical Pacific observed during 19982012 indicates suppression of a potential global surface warming of 0.160.06C. In contrast, the Pacific contributed 0.290.10C to the significant interannual GST increase in 1997/1998. The Pacific DSL anomalies observed in 2015 suggest that the strong El Nio in 2015/2016 could lead to a 0.210.07C GST jump. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-20 03:57:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Misleading title to say the least. No one is expecting an 'intense' La Nia. Current predictions are for a relatively weak La Nia to develop, if at all. 

La Nia is slightly favored to develop during August - October 2016, with about a 55-60% chance of La Nia during the fall and winter 2016-17. 

http://www.cpc.ncep.noaa.gov/products/analysis_monitoring/enso_advisory/ensodisc.html </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-18 22:31:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Study (open access): [Ubiquity and impact of thin mid-level clouds in the tropics](http://www.nature.com/ncomms/2016/160817/ncomms12432/full/ncomms12432.html)
___

**Abstract**:

*Clouds are crucial for Earths climate and radiation budget. Great attention has been paid to low, high and vertically thick tropospheric clouds such as stratus, cirrus and deep convective clouds. However, much less is known about tropospheric mid-level clouds as these clouds are challenging to observe in situ and difficult to detect by remote sensing techniques. Here we use Cloud-Aerosol Lidar with Orthogonal Polarization (CALIOP) satellite observations to show that thin mid-level clouds (TMLCs) are ubiquitous in the tropics. Supported by high-resolution regional model simulations, we find that TMLCs are formed by detrainment from convective clouds near the zero-degree isotherm. Calculations using a radiative transfer model indicate that tropical TMLCs have a cooling effect on climate that could be as large in magnitude as the warming effect of cirrus. We conclude that more effort has to be made to understand TMLCs, as their influence on cloud feedbacks, heat and moisture transport, and climate sensitivity could be substantial.* </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-18 22:20:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Clouds are complex, especially to model. They have both a cooling effect, and a warming effect (though the net effect is to cool the planet). Note the confidence level in relation to radiative forcings for clouds is "[Low](http://www.realclimate.org/images/ipcc_rad_forc_ar5.jpg)." </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-18 22:12:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Comment by /u/nimbuscile ([source](https://www.reddit.com/r/science/comments/4ybp2t/thin_clouds_at_about_5_km_altitude_are_more/d6mmdpq)) 

I'm going to jump in here before the comment section gets too busy.

**This does not mean climate models are projecting too much global warming.**

This research used observations of clouds from a relatively-new satellite instrument that allows us to observe clouds that are very thin. Very thin clouds aren't represented in global climate models because they divide the atmosphere into boxes that are typically 100 km across and about 600 m deep at the relevant altitudes.

The study then uses a regional model with much higher resolution model (1 km in the horizontal, 325 m in the vertical) to simulate the formation of these clouds. This allows us to resolve the small-scale processes required. Although this model was informative in understanding how such clouds can form, the authors found discrepancies between the high-resolution simulation and the observations. This suggests the process generating these clouds is too weak in the model.

The authors then calculated the effect of the these clouds on the Earth, based on the satellite observations. They showed the effect is rather larger than expected, giving a cooling effect of -0.9 to -0.3 Wm-2 in the tropics. To put this into perspective, we know that clouds as a whole have a cooling effect of -20 Wm-2 in the same region, so these thin clouds represent 1.5 to 4.5 % of the entire effect.

My summary of the research would be as follows:

- Our observational capabilities are increasing and allowing us to probe the Earth's atmosphere in more detail.

- These observations allow us to test our understanding of the processes behind cloud formation.

- Thin cloud layers appear to be more common than we expected. Their overall effect on Earth's temperature is to cool it slightly.

We need to think harder to understand exactly how these thin cloud layers form because numerical simulations of them typically generate too few of them.

**What does this mean for climate models?**

There are many effects climate models are unable to capture. By definition global climate models cannot simulate small-scale processes as we lack the computational resources. We run climate models because they allows us to understand the limits of our knowledge, not because we think they perform identically to the real world. They are useful tools and not the be-all and end-all of climate science. Any professional climate scientist knows this.

**What does this mean for global warming projections?**

It's difficult to say. Clouds in general have a cooling effect on climate (though there are exceptions). If they become less common under global warming this means warming will be enhanced (a positive feedback) since the cooling effect will be weakened. If they become more common warming will be weaker (a negative feedback).

From the conclusions of the study:

In a context of a global warming of 2 K, a perturbed high-resolution model simulation indicates that the morphological properties of TMLCs [thin mid-level clouds], as well as their cloud water content, and thus their OD, remain similar. However, it is difficult to say how TMLCs would change in a changing climate as not even the high-resolution model is able to accurately represent them. The cloud feedback and cloud adjustment to increasing CO2 would likely change the physical and optical properties of clouds at different levels, affecting the properties and radiative effect of TMLCs. Fewer, higher and thicker clouds are simulated to form in a warmer climate. Moreover, their albedo may decrease in the tropics due to the cloud adjustment to increasing CO2. On the one hand, thicker TMLCs and a decrease of low-level cloud albedo will likely induce a more negative radiative effect. On the other hand, fewer clouds and an increase in surface albedo, for example, due to deforestation, will lead to a less negative radiative effect. Changes in the intensity and distribution of deep convection in a warmer climate may also directly affect the TMLC formation process and spatial distribution. All in all, a proper representation of TMLC formation in global climate models is needed to draw more firm conclusions on how the radiative effect of TMLCs would be affected in a warming climate. Our results suggest that further studies on TMLCs are needed to better understand their life cycle and physical properties, to represent them accurately in models, and to fully explore their radiative effects and overall impact on climate.

I'm happy to help with interpretation of this paragraph if people would find it useful.
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-18 21:56:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Study: [The last Summer Olympics? Climate change, health, and work outdoors](http://www.thelancet.com/journals/lancet/article/PIIS0140-6736(16\)31335-6/abstract)
___

**Abstract**:

*Climate change threatens human health in many ways, through heat waves, extreme weather events, and shifts in disease vectors, as well as economic and social stresses on populations living in or trying to escape areas affected by seawater intrusion, drought, lower agricultural productivity, and floods. In the short term, most of these impacts could be substantially ameliorated by actions to reduce background disease risks and other known causes of vulnerability. The world beyond 2050 poses increasingly difficult challenges, not only because of the inherent uncertainties in long-term predictions, but because the extent and speed of change might exceed society's ability to adapt.* </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-18 21:51:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Study: [The last Summer Olympics? Climate change, health, and work outdoors](http://www.thelancet.com/journals/lancet/article/PIIS0140-6736(16\)31335-6/abstract)
___

**Abstract**:

Climate change threatens human health in many ways, through heat waves, extreme weather events, and shifts in disease vectors, as well as economic and social stresses on populations living in or trying to escape areas affected by seawater intrusion, drought, lower agricultural productivity, and floods. In the short term, most of these impacts could be substantially ameliorated by actions to reduce background disease risks and other known causes of vulnerability. The world beyond 2050 poses increasingly difficult challenges, not only because of the inherent uncertainties in long-term predictions, but because the extent and speed of change might exceed society's ability to adapt. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-17 22:37:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Source: https://twitter.com/simondonner/status/765572148970659844 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-17 20:35:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Given the abstract of the study I shared, I'm not certain if the authors are suggesting that their results can be applied to wild bees, although it does appear that way given their wording by stating "bee behavior" and not honey bee behavior specifically. In other words they may be using honey bees as a proxy for wild bees. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-17 17:56:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Another recent study concludes that there is a low potential for negative effects on bee behavior or colony health from neonicotinoid pesticides. 

Study: [Survey and Risk Assessment of Apis mellifera (Hymenoptera: Apidae) Exposure to Neonicotinoid Pesticides in Urban, Rural, and Agricultural Settings](http://jee.oxfordjournals.org/content/early/2016/01/19/jee.tov397)
___

**Abstract**:

A comparative assessment of apiaries in urban, rural, and agricultural areas was undertaken in 2013 and 2014 to examine potential honey bee colony exposure to neonicotinoid insecticides from pollen foraging. Apiaries ranged in size from one to hundreds of honey bee colonies, and included those operated by commercial, sideline (semicommercial), and hobbyist beekeepers. Residues in and on wax and beebread (stored pollen in the hive) were evaluated for the nitro-substituted neonicotinoid insecticides imidacloprid and its olefin metabolite and the active ingredients clothianidin, thiamethoxam, and dinotefuran. Beebread and comb wax collected from hives in agricultural landscapes were more likely to have detectable residues of thiamethoxam and clothianidin than that collected from hives in rural or urban areas (50% of samples vs. 10%). The maximum neonicotinoid residue detected in either wax or beebread was 3.9 ppb imidacloprid. A probabilistic risk assessment was conducted on the residues recovered from beebread in apiaries located in commercial, urban, and rural landscapes. The calculated risk quotient based on a dietary no observable adverse effect concentration (NOAEC) suggested low potential for negative effects on bee behavior or colony health. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-17 17:51:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This is a different study with a different conclusion. The removal is in error. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-17 17:40:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Study: [Survey and Risk Assessment of Apis mellifera (Hymenoptera: Apidae) Exposure to Neonicotinoid Pesticides in Urban, Rural, and Agricultural Settings](http://jee.oxfordjournals.org/content/early/2016/01/19/jee.tov397)
___

**Abstract**:

A comparative assessment of apiaries in urban, rural, and agricultural areas was undertaken in 2013 and 2014 to examine potential honey bee colony exposure to neonicotinoid insecticides from pollen foraging. Apiaries ranged in size from one to hundreds of honey bee colonies, and included those operated by commercial, sideline (semicommercial), and hobbyist beekeepers. Residues in and on wax and beebread (stored pollen in the hive) were evaluated for the nitro-substituted neonicotinoid insecticides imidacloprid and its olefin metabolite and the active ingredients clothianidin, thiamethoxam, and dinotefuran. Beebread and comb wax collected from hives in agricultural landscapes were more likely to have detectable residues of thiamethoxam and clothianidin than that collected from hives in rural or urban areas (50% of samples vs. 10%). The maximum neonicotinoid residue detected in either wax or beebread was 3.9ppb imidacloprid. A probabilistic risk assessment was conducted on the residues recovered from beebread in apiaries located in commercial, urban, and rural landscapes. The calculated risk quotient based on a dietary no observable adverse effect concentration (NOAEC) suggested low potential for negative effects on bee behavior or colony health. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-17 17:25:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Study (open access): [Impacts of neonicotinoid use on long-term population changes in wild bees in England](http://www.nature.com/ncomms/2016/160816/ncomms12459/full/ncomms12459.html)
___

**Abstract**:

Wild bee declines have been ascribed in part to neonicotinoid insecticides. While short-term laboratory studies on commercially bred species (principally honeybees and bumblebees) have identified sub-lethal effects, there is no strong evidence linking these insecticides to losses of the majority of wild bee species. We relate 18 years of UK national wild bee distribution data for 62 species to amounts of neonicotinoid use in oilseed rape. Using a multi-species dynamic Bayesian occupancy analysis, we find evidence of increased population extinction rates in response to neonicotinoid seed treatment use on oilseed rape. Species foraging on oilseed rape benefit from the cover of this crop, but were on average three times more negatively affected by exposure to neonicotinoids than non-crop foragers. Our results suggest that sub-lethal effects of neonicotinoids could scale up to cause losses of bee biodiversity. Restrictions on neonicotinoid use may reduce population declines. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-17 08:04:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Source: https://twitter.com/hausfath/status/765572586520584193 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-17 08:01:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> National Trust for Scotland: [Case study: Ben Lawers National Nature Reserve](http://www.nts.org.uk/Learn/adult_benlawers.php)

Related Material(s):
___

- [On the trail of Scotland's rare mountain plants - in pictures](https://www.theguardian.com/environment/gallery/2016/aug/17/on-the-trail-of-scotlands-rare-mountain-plants-in-pictures) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-17 05:30:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hi Dr. Laken, 

Firstly, thank you for time - it's greatly appreciated, and secondly I apologize for the low user activity (it's a small subreddit, but growing). Hopefully others will chime in with their questions in time.

The paper was certainly interesting, and it did raise a number of questions. I apologize for any degree of ignorance as a good portion of the paper is outside the scope of my degree. 
___

Questions:

(1) What lead to exclusion of other climatic phenomena such as the Arctic Oscillation (AO), and the Pacific Decadal Oscillation (PDO) in your analysis?

(2) I didn't see where the AOD data was coming from. I was interested in the specifics of this data set as it relates to, assumingly, volcanic injection of stratospheric aerosols (is this data set cross referenced with known ash layers for major eruptions, etc.?)

(3) For the sake of clarity, is there a table summarizing the effectiveness of WSDs as influenced by ENSO, NAO, SC, and AOD depending on the boreal winter / summer? If not, do you think this could be a beneficial tool for visualizing the results of the paper by color coding their relative strength?

(4) Discussion in paper suggests no significant affects from SC to the NAO... and although you discuss possible causes for the discrepancy between your findings and other published studies, there appears to be a good degree of uncertainty for the discrepancy. In the future, what analytical methods do you see helping to clear up this discrepancy?

(5) In particular one of the statements made in the study peaked my interest:

"*...it is highly problematic to disambiguate the forcing effects of internal variations in the climate system, such as volcanic eruptions or ENSO, which operate over timescales comparable to solar variability*..." 

I am not aware of timescale comparisons between volcanic activity and solar variability and the references provided
16   18 are not related to volcanic activity. Perhaps I am misinterpreting the statement, but it seems to be implying some sort of cyclic timescale on which volcanic activity may increase and decrease that is comparable to solar variability. If my interpretation is correct, do you feel such a statement is warranted given - what I believe to be - a lack of evidence for such timescales relating to volcanic activity?

(6) Could your methodology be applied/adapted to a recent paper suggesting that Mt. Pinatubo suppressed an  acceleration signal of SLR? (See: [Is the detection of accelerated sea level rise imminent?](http://www.nature.com/articles/srep31245)) Have you looked at applying/adapting your studies method to other earth system phenomena?

(7) Is it possible to extend this studies methods further back without the use the HBGWL?

Thanks again for your time. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-17 02:58:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Study (open access): [Antarctic last interglacial isotope peak in response to sea ice retreat not ice-sheet collapse](http://www.nature.com/ncomms/2016/160816/ncomms12293/full/ncomms12293.html)
___

**Abstract**:

Several studies have suggested that sea-level rise during the last interglacial implies retreat of the West Antarctic Ice Sheet (WAIS). The prevalent hypothesis is that the retreat coincided with the peak Antarctic temperature and stable water isotope values from 128,000 years ago (128ka); very early in the last interglacial. Here, by analysing climate model simulations of last interglacial WAIS loss featuring water isotopes, we show instead that the isotopic response to WAIS loss is in opposition to the isotopic evidence at 128ka. Instead, a reduction in winter sea ice area of 657% fully explains the 128ka ice core evidence. Our finding of a marked retreat of the sea ice at 128ka demonstrates the sensitivity of Antarctic sea ice extent to climate warming. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-17 00:39:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Study: [Earliest land plants created modern levels of atmospheric oxygen](http://www.pnas.org/content/early/2016/08/10/1604787113)
___

**Significance**:

*The rise of atmospheric oxygen over Earths history has received much recent interdisciplinary attention. However, the puzzle of when and how atmospheric oxygen reached modern levels remains unresolved. Many recent studies have argued for a major oxygenation eventof uncertain causein the Neoproterozoic Era 541 Ma, enabling the rise of animals. Previous modelling work has predicted a late Paleozoic oxygen rise (380 Ma) due to the rise of forests. Here we show that neither scenario is correct. Instead, the earliest plants, which colonized the land from 470 Ma onward, first increased atmospheric oxygen to present levels by 400 Ma, and this instigated fire-mediated feedbacks that have stabilized high oxygen levels ever since, shaping subsequent evolution.*

**Abstract**:

*The progressive oxygenation of the Earths atmosphere was pivotal to the evolution of life, but the puzzle of when and how atmospheric oxygen (O2) first approached modern levels (21%) remains unresolved. Redox proxy data indicate the deep oceans were oxygenated during 435392 Ma, and the appearance of fossil charcoal indicates O2 1517% by 420400 Ma. However, existing models have failed to predict oxygenation at this time. Here we show that the earliest plants, which colonized the land surface from 470 Ma onward, were responsible for this mid-Paleozoic oxygenation event, through greatly increasing global organic carbon burialthe net long-term source of O2. We use a trait-based ecophysiological model to predict that cryptogamic vegetation cover could have achieved 30% of todays global terrestrial net primary productivity by 445 Ma. Data from modern bryophytes suggests this plentiful early plant material had a much higher molar C:P ratio (2,000) than marine biomass (100), such that a given weathering flux of phosphorus could support more organic carbon burial. Furthermore, recent experiments suggest that early plants selectively increased the flux of phosphorus (relative to alkalinity) weathered from rocks. Combining these effects in a model of long-term biogeochemical cycling, we reproduce a sustained +2 increase in the carbonate carbon isotope (13C) record by 445 Ma, and predict a corresponding rise in O2 to present levels by 420400 Ma, consistent with geochemical data. This oxygen rise represents a permanent shift in regulatory regime to one where fire-mediated negative feedbacks stabilize high O2 levels.* </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-17 00:35:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Study: [Earliest land plants created modern levels of atmospheric oxygen](http://www.pnas.org/content/early/2016/08/10/1604787113)
___

**Significance**:

The rise of atmospheric oxygen over Earths history has received much recent interdisciplinary attention. However, the puzzle of when and how atmospheric oxygen reached modern levels remains unresolved. Many recent studies have argued for a major oxygenation eventof uncertain causein the Neoproterozoic Era 541 Ma, enabling the rise of animals. Previous modelling work has predicted a late Paleozoic oxygen rise (380 Ma) due to the rise of forests. Here we show that neither scenario is correct. Instead, the earliest plants, which colonized the land from 470 Ma onward, first increased atmospheric oxygen to present levels by 400 Ma, and this instigated fire-mediated feedbacks that have stabilized high oxygen levels ever since, shaping subsequent evolution.

**Abstract**:

The progressive oxygenation of the Earths atmosphere was pivotal to the evolution of life, but the puzzle of when and how atmospheric oxygen (O2) first approached modern levels (21%) remains unresolved. Redox proxy data indicate the deep oceans were oxygenated during 435392 Ma, and the appearance of fossil charcoal indicates O2 1517% by 420400 Ma. However, existing models have failed to predict oxygenation at this time. Here we show that the earliest plants, which colonized the land surface from 470 Ma onward, were responsible for this mid-Paleozoic oxygenation event, through greatly increasing global organic carbon burialthe net long-term source of O2. We use a trait-based ecophysiological model to predict that cryptogamic vegetation cover could have achieved 30% of todays global terrestrial net primary productivity by 445 Ma. Data from modern bryophytes suggests this plentiful early plant material had a much higher molar C:P ratio (2,000) than marine biomass (100), such that a given weathering flux of phosphorus could support more organic carbon burial. Furthermore, recent experiments suggest that early plants selectively increased the flux of phosphorus (relative to alkalinity) weathered from rocks. Combining these effects in a model of long-term biogeochemical cycling, we reproduce a sustained +2 increase in the carbonate carbon isotope (13C) record by 445 Ma, and predict a corresponding rise in O2 to present levels by 420400 Ma, consistent with geochemical data. This oxygen rise represents a permanent shift in regulatory regime to one where fire-mediated negative feedbacks stabilize high O2 levels.
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-16 23:09:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Study: [Airborne methane remote measurements reveal heavy-tail flux distribution in Four Corners region](http://www.pnas.org/content/early/2016/08/10/1605617113)
___

**Significance**:

Fugitive methane emissions are thought to often exhibit a heavy-tail distribution (more high-emission sources than expected in a normal distribution), and thus efficient mitigation is possible if we locate the strongest emitters. Here we demonstrate airborne remote measurements of methane plumes at 1- to 3-m ground resolution over the Four Corners region. We identified more than 250 point sources, whose emissions followed a lognormal distribution, a heavy-tail characteristic. The top 10% of emitters explain about half of the total observed point source contribution and 1/4 the total basin emissions. This work demonstrates the capability of real-time airborne imaging spectroscopy to perform detection and categorization of methane point sources in extended geographical areas with immediate input for emissions abatement.

**Abstract**:


Methane (CH4) impacts climate as the second strongest anthropogenic greenhouse gas and air quality by influencing tropospheric ozone levels. Space-based observations have identified the Four Corners region in the Southwest United States as an area of large CH4 enhancements. We conducted an airborne campaign in Four Corners during April 2015 with the next-generation Airborne Visible/Infrared Imaging Spectrometer (near-infrared) and Hyperspectral Thermal Emission Spectrometer (thermal infrared) imaging spectrometers to better understand the source of methane by measuring methane plumes at 1- to 3-m spatial resolution. Our analysis detected more than 250 individual methane plumes from fossil fuel harvesting, processing, and distributing infrastructures, spanning an emission range from the detection limit mml:mathmml:mo\/mml:mo\/mml:math 2 kg/h to 5 kg/h through mml:mathmml:mo\/mml:mo\/mml:math 5,000 kg/h. Observed sources include gas processing facilities, storage tanks, pipeline leaks, and well pads, as well as a coal mine venting shaft. Overall, plume enhancements and inferred fluxes follow a lognormal distribution, with the top 10% emitters contributing 49 to 66% to the inferred total point source flux of 0.23 Tg/y to 0.39 Tg/y. With the observed confirmation of a lognormal emission distribution, this airborne observing strategy and its ability to locate previously unknown point sources in real time provides an efficient and effective method to identify and mitigate major emissions contributors over a wide geographic area. With improved instrumentation, this capability scales to spaceborne applications [Thompson DR, et al. (2016) Geophys Res Lett 43(12):65716578]. Further illustration of this potential is demonstrated with two detected, confirmed, and repaired pipeline leaks during the campaign.
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-16 11:17:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Study: [Potential for widespread electrification of personal vehicle travel in the United States](http://www.nature.com/articles/nenergy2016112)
___

**Abstract**:

Electric vehicles can contribute to climate change mitigation if coupled with decarbonized electricity, but only if vehicle range matches travellers needs. Evaluating electric vehicle range against a populations needs is challenging because detailed driving behaviour must be taken into account. Here we develop a model to combine information from coarse-grained but expansive travel surveys with high-resolution GPS data to estimate the energy requirements of personal vehicle trips across the US. We find that the energy requirements of 87% of vehicle-days could be met by an existing, affordable electric vehicle. This percentage is markedly similar across diverse cities, even when per capita gasoline consumption differs significantly. We also find that for the highest-energy days, other vehicle technologies are likely to be needed even as batteries improve and charging infrastructure expands. Car sharing or other means to serve this small number of high-energy days could play an important role in the electrification and decarbonization of transportation. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-16 11:14:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Study: [Potential for widespread electrification of personal vehicle travel in the United States](http://www.nature.com/articles/nenergy2016112)
___

**Abstract**:

Electric vehicles can contribute to climate change mitigation if coupled with decarbonized electricity, but only if vehicle range matches travellers needs. Evaluating electric vehicle range against a populations needs is challenging because detailed driving behaviour must be taken into account. Here we develop a model to combine information from coarse-grained but expansive travel surveys with high-resolution GPS data to estimate the energy requirements of personal vehicle trips across the US. We find that the energy requirements of 87% of vehicle-days could be met by an existing, affordable electric vehicle. This percentage is markedly similar across diverse cities, even when per capita gasoline consumption differs significantly. We also find that for the highest-energy days, other vehicle technologies are likely to be needed even as batteries improve and charging infrastructure expands. Car sharing or other means to serve this small number of high-energy days could play an important role in the electrification and decarbonization of transportation. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-16 10:34:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Related Material(s):
___

- [We have almost certainly blown the 1.5-degree global warming target](https://theconversation.com/we-have-almost-certainly-blown-the-1-5-degree-global-warming-target-63720) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-16 00:11:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Study: [Amplification of RNA by an RNA polymerase ribozyme](http://www.pnas.org/content/early/2016/08/10/1610103113)
___

**Significance**:

Darwinian life requires the ability to replicate genotypes and express phenotypes. Although all extant life relies on protein enzymes to accomplish these tasks, life in the ancestral RNA world would have used only RNA enzymes. Here, we report the in vitro evolution of an improved RNA polymerase ribozyme that is able to synthesize structured functional RNAs, including aptamers and ribozymes, and replicate short RNA sequences in a protein-free form of the PCR. Thus, the replication of RNA and the expression of functional RNA can be accomplished with RNA alone. Combining and improving these activities may enable the self-sustained evolution of RNA and offers a potential route to a synthetic form of RNA life.

**Abstract**:

In all extant life, genetic information is stored in nucleic acids that are replicated by polymerase proteins. In the hypothesized RNA world, before the evolution of genetically encoded proteins, ancestral organisms contained RNA genes that were replicated by an RNA polymerase ribozyme. In an effort toward reconstructing RNA-based life in the laboratory, in vitro evolution was used to improve dramatically the activity and generality of an RNA polymerase ribozyme by selecting variants that can synthesize functional RNA molecules from an RNA template. The improved polymerase ribozyme is able to synthesize a variety of complex structured RNAs, including aptamers, ribozymes, and, in low yield, even tRNA. Furthermore, the polymerase can replicate nucleic acids, amplifying short RNA templates by more than 10,000-fold in an RNA-catalyzed form of the PCR. Thus, the two prerequisites of Darwinian lifethe replication of genetic information and its conversion into functional moleculescan now be accomplished with RNA in the complete absence of proteins.
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-14 07:39:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Are they all mistaken about that?

Yes, they are (under the context in which they imply) - and no they aren't (there are a number of reasons provided as to why contrails may be lasting longer). This was discussed in the paper. If you're interested in the discussion the article is open source and freely available to read in full. 

Furthermore, as contrails are essentially clouds they can evolve and be indistinguishable from cirrus, and cirrostratus clouds. For example: [Young   Old contrail](https://i.imgur.com/NzBp3Qe.jpg) and [cirrus clouds - former contrails](https://i.imgur.com/swnVU8f.jpg). </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-13 02:53:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Because there are similarities. Admittedly I'm not fully versed in how conspiracy theorists define 'chemtrails,' or perhaps what may constitute as a subcategory of 'chemtrail,' however, a number of unethical experiments have been conducted over US and Canadian cities which *may* contradict the findings of this study (depending on definitions, etc.). Excerpts from the wiki:

The experiments included a wide array of studies, involving things like ...  deliberately releasing radioactive chemicals over U.S. and Canadian cities... amongst other things.

... 

From 1950 through 1953, the U.S. Army sprayed chemicals over six cities in the United States and Canada, in order to test dispersal patterns of chemical weapons.

etc. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-13 00:41:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Study: [Was Venus the First Habitable World of our Solar System?](http://onlinelibrary.wiley.com/doi/10.1002/2016GL069790/abstract)
___


**Abstract**:

Present-day Venus is an inhospitable place with surface temperatures approaching 750 K and an atmosphere 90 times as thick as Earth's. Billions of years ago the picture may have been very different. We have created a suite of 3-D climate simulations using topographic data from the Magellan mission, solar spectral irradiance estimates for 2.9 and 0.715 Gya, present-day Venus orbital parameters, an ocean volume consistent with current theory, and an atmospheric composition estimated for early Venus. Using these parameters we find that such a world could have had moderate temperatures if Venus had a rotation period slower than ~16 Earth days, despite an incident solar flux 46  70% higher than Earth receives. At its current rotation period, Venus's climate could have remained habitable until at least 715 million years ago. These results demonstrate the role rotation and topography play in understanding the climatic history of Venus-like exoplanets discovered in the present epoch. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-13 00:36:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Study: [Was Venus the First Habitable World of our Solar System?](http://onlinelibrary.wiley.com/doi/10.1002/2016GL069790/abstract)
___


**Abstract**:

Present-day Venus is an inhospitable place with surface temperatures approaching 750K and an atmosphere 90 times as thick as Earth's. Billions of years ago the picture may have been very different. We have created a suite of 3-D climate simulations using topographic data from the Magellan mission, solar spectral irradiance estimates for 2.9 and 0.715 Gya, present-day Venus orbital parameters, an ocean volume consistent with current theory, and an atmospheric composition estimated for early Venus. Using these parameters we find that such a world could have had moderate temperatures if Venus had a rotation period slower than ~16 Earth days, despite an incident solar flux 4670% higher than Earth receives. At its current rotation period, Venus's climate could have remained habitable until at least 715 million years ago. These results demonstrate the role rotation and topography play in understanding the climatic history of Venus-like exoplanets discovered in the present epoch. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-13 00:27:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Study: [The challenge of climate-change neoskepticism](http://science.sciencemag.org/content/353/6300/653)
___

**Summary**:

Opponents of policies to limit anthropogenic climate change (ACC) have offered a changing set of argumentsdenying or questioning ACC's existence, magnitude, and rate of progress, the risks it presents, the integrity of climate scientists, and the value of mitigation efforts (1). Similar arguments have characterized environmental risk debates concerning arsenical insecticides in the late 1800s (2), phosphates in detergents in the 1960s (3), and the pesticide DDT in the 1960s and '70s (4). Typically, defenders of business as usual first question the scientific evidence that risks exist; then, they question the magnitude of the risks and assert that reducing them has more costs than benefits. A parallel rhetorical shift away from outright skepticism (57) led us to identify neoskepticism as a new incarnation of opposition to major efforts to limit ACC (8). This shift heightens the need for science to inform decision making under uncertainty and to improve communication and education. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-13 00:08:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Some may also find the history of [unethical human experiments in the United States](https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Unethical_human_experimentation_in_the_United_States) of interest. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-12 23:30:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Study (open access): [Quantifying expert consensus against the existence of a secret, large-scale atmospheric spraying program](http://iopscience.iop.org/article/10.1088/1748-9326/11/8/084011)
___

**Abstract**:

Nearly 17% of people in an international survey said they believed the existence of a secret large-scale atmospheric program (SLAP) to be true or partly true. SLAP is commonly referred to as 'chemtrails' or 'covert geoengineering', and has led to a number of websites purported to show evidence of widespread chemical spraying linked to negative impacts on human health and the environment. To address these claims, we surveyed two groups of expertsatmospheric chemists with expertize in condensation trails and geochemists working on atmospheric deposition of dust and pollutionto scientifically evaluate for the first time the claims of SLAP theorists. Results show that 76 of the 77 scientists (98.7%) that took part in this study said they had not encountered evidence of a SLAP, and that the data cited as evidence could be explained through other factors, including well-understood physics and chemistry associated with aircraft contrails and atmospheric aerosols. Our goal is not to sway those already convinced that there is a secret, large-scale spraying programwho often reject counter-evidence as further proof of their theoriesbut rather to establish a source of objective science that can inform public discourse. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-11 10:14:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Study (open access): [Retraining Investment for U.S. Transition from Coal to Solar Photovoltaic Employment](https://www.academia.edu/26372861/Retraining_Investment_for_U.S._Transition_from_Coal_to_Solar_Photovoltaic_Employment#_blank)
___

**Abstract**:

Although coal remains the largest source of electricity in the U.S., a combination of factors is driving a decrease in profitability and employment in the coal-sector. Meanwhile, the solar photovoltaic (PV) industry is growing rapidly in the U.S. and generating many jobs that represent employment opportunities for laid off coal workers. In order to determine the viability of a smooth transition from coal to PV-related employment, this paper provides an analysis of the cost to retrain current coal workers for solar photovoltaic industry employment in the U.S. The current coal industry positions are determined, the skill set evaluated and the salaries tabulated. For each type of coal position, the closest equivalent PV position is determined and then the re-training time and investment are quantified. These values are applied on a state-by-state basis for coal producing states employing the bulk of coal workers as a function of time using a reverse seniority retirement program for the current American fleet of coal-powered plants. The results show that a relatively minor investment in retraining would allow the vast majority of coal workers to switch to PV-related positions even in the event of the elimination of the coal industry. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-11 10:11:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Study (open access): [Retraining Investment for U.S. Transition from Coal to Solar Photovoltaic Employment](https://www.academia.edu/26372861/Retraining_Investment_for_U.S._Transition_from_Coal_to_Solar_Photovoltaic_Employment#_blank)
___

**Abstract**:

*Although coal remains the largest source of electricity in the U.S., a combination of factors is driving a decrease in profitability and employment in the coal-sector. Meanwhile, the solar photovoltaic (PV) industry is growing rapidly in the U.S. and generating many jobs that represent employment opportunities for laid off coal workers. In order to determine the viability of a smooth transition from coal to PV-related employment, this paper provides an analysis of the cost to retrain current coal workers for solar photovoltaic industry employment in the U.S. The current coal industry positions are determined, the skill set evaluated and the salaries tabulated. For each type of coal position, the closest equivalent PV position is determined and then the re-training time and investment are quantified. These values are applied on a state-by-state basis for coal producing states employing the bulk of coal workers as a function of time using a reverse seniority retirement program for the current American fleet of coal-powered plants. The results show that a relatively minor investment in retraining would allow the vast majority of coal workers to switch to PV-related positions even in the event of the elimination of the coal industry.* </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-11 09:03:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Study (open access): [Liquid-filled canyons on Titan](http://onlinelibrary.wiley.com/doi/10.1002/2016GL069679/full)
___

**Abstract**:

In May 2013 the Cassini RADAR altimeter observed channels in Vid Flumina, a drainage network connected to Titan's second largest hydrocarbon sea, Ligeia Mare. Analysis of these altimeter echoes shows that the channels are located in deep (up to ~570m), steep-sided, canyons and have strong specular surface reflections that indicate they are currently liquid filled. Elevations of the liquid in these channels are at the same level as Ligeia Mare to within a vertical precision of about 0.7m, consistent with the interpretation of drowned river valleys. Specular reflections are also observed in lower order tributaries elevated above the level of Ligeia Mare, consistent with drainage feeding into the main channel system. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-10 23:32:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> As far as the North Slope of Alaska, observations indicate [no significant increase in long-term CH4 emissions...despite significant increase in air temperature](http://onlinelibrary.wiley.com/doi/10.1002/2016GL069292/full) suggesting "*the observed short-term temperature sensitivity from the Arctic will have little impact on the global atmospheric CH4 budget in the long term*..."

Increasing CH4 emissions have been predominantly attributed to the boom in [hydraulic fracturing](http://www.climatecentral.org/news/us-60-percent-of-global-methane-growth-20037), as well as global [agricultural practices](http://phys.org/news/2016-03-scientists-attribute-methane-agriculture.html). </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-10 19:26:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> To be clear, this study does not say that oceans *aren't* rising - they are, that's indisputable - however, the authors have found no strong evidence for *acceleration* in sea level rise (SLR) since observations through satellites began in the 90s, though they suspect that the acceleration has been masked by internal variability.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-10 19:14:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Study (open access): [Is the detection of accelerated sea level rise imminent?](http://www.nature.com/articles/srep31245)
___


**Abstract**:

*Global mean sea level rise estimated from satellite altimetry provides a strong constraint on climate variability and change and is expected to accelerate as the rates of both ocean warming and cryospheric mass loss increase over time. In stark contrast to this expectation however, current altimeter products show the rate of sea level rise to have decreased from the first to second decades of the altimeter era. Here, a combined analysis of altimeter data and specially designed climate model simulations shows the 1991 eruption of Mt Pinatubo to likely have masked the acceleration that would have otherwise occurred. This masking arose largely from a recovery in ocean heat content through the mid to late 1990 s subsequent to major heat content reductions in the years following the eruption. A consequence of this finding is that barring another major volcanic eruption, a detectable acceleration is likely to emerge from the noise of internal climate variability in the coming decade.* </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-10 19:11:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Study (open access): [Is the detection of accelerated sea level rise imminent?](http://www.nature.com/articles/srep31245)
___


**Abstract**:

Global mean sea level rise estimated from satellite altimetry provides a strong constraint on climate variability and change and is expected to accelerate as the rates of both ocean warming and cryospheric mass loss increase over time. In stark contrast to this expectation however, current altimeter products show the rate of sea level rise to have decreased from the first to second decades of the altimeter era. Here, a combined analysis of altimeter data and specially designed climate model simulations shows the 1991 eruption of Mt Pinatubo to likely have masked the acceleration that would have otherwise occurred. This masking arose largely from a recovery in ocean heat content through the mid to late 1990s subsequent to major heat content reductions in the years following the eruption. A consequence of this finding is that barring another major volcanic eruption, a detectable acceleration is likely to emerge from the noise of internal climate variability in the coming decade. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-09 04:40:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Study: [Climate warming reduces fish production and benthic habitat in Lake Tanganyika, one of the most biodiverse freshwater ecosystems](http://www.pnas.org/content/early/2016/08/02/1603237113)
___

**Significance**:

*Understanding how climate change affects ecosystem productivity is critical for managing fisheries and sustaining biodiversity. African lakes are warming rapidly, potentially jeopardizing both their high endemic biodiversity and important fisheries. Using paleoecological records from Lake Tanganyika, we show that declines in commercially important fishes and endemic molluscs have accompanied lake warming. Ongoing declines in fishery species began well before the advent of commercial fishing in the mid-20th century. Warming has intensified the stratification of the water column, thereby trapping nutrients in deep water where they cannot fuel primary production and food webs. Simultaneously, warming has enlarged the low-oxygen zone, considerably narrowing the coastal habitat where most of Tanganyikas endemic species are found.*

**Abstract**:

*Warming climates are rapidly transforming lake ecosystems worldwide, but the breadth of changes in tropical lakes is poorly documented. Sustainable management of freshwater fisheries and biodiversity requires accounting for historical and ongoing stressors such as climate change and harvest intensity. This is problematic in tropical Africa, where records of ecosystem change are limited and local populations rely heavily on lakes for nutrition. Here, using a 1,500-y paleoecological record, we show that declines in fishery species and endemic molluscs began well before commercial fishing in Lake Tanganyika, Africas deepest and oldest lake. Paleoclimate and instrumental records demonstrate sustained warming in this lake during the last 150 y, which affects biota by strengthening and shallowing stratification of the water column. Reductions in lake mixing have depressed algal production and shrunk the oxygenated benthic habitat by 38% in our study areas, yielding fish and mollusc declines. Late-20th century fish fossil abundances at two of three sites were lower than at any other time in the last millennium and fell in concert with reduced diatom abundance and warming water. A negative correlation between lake temperature and fish and mollusc fossils over the last 500 y indicates that climate warming and intensifying stratification have almost certainly reduced potential fishery production, helping to explain ongoing declines in fish catches. Long-term declines of both benthic and pelagic species underscore the urgency of strategic efforts to sustain Lake Tanganyikas extraordinary biodiversity and ecosystem services.* </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-09 04:37:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Study: [Climate warming reduces fish production and benthic habitat in Lake Tanganyika, one of the most biodiverse freshwater ecosystems](http://www.pnas.org/content/early/2016/08/02/1603237113)
___

**Significance**:

Understanding how climate change affects ecosystem productivity is critical for managing fisheries and sustaining biodiversity. African lakes are warming rapidly, potentially jeopardizing both their high endemic biodiversity and important fisheries. Using paleoecological records from Lake Tanganyika, we show that declines in commercially important fishes and endemic molluscs have accompanied lake warming. Ongoing declines in fishery species began well before the advent of commercial fishing in the mid-20th century. Warming has intensified the stratification of the water column, thereby trapping nutrients in deep water where they cannot fuel primary production and food webs. Simultaneously, warming has enlarged the low-oxygen zone, considerably narrowing the coastal habitat where most of Tanganyikas endemic species are found.

**Abstract**:

Warming climates are rapidly transforming lake ecosystems worldwide, but the breadth of changes in tropical lakes is poorly documented. Sustainable management of freshwater fisheries and biodiversity requires accounting for historical and ongoing stressors such as climate change and harvest intensity. This is problematic in tropical Africa, where records of ecosystem change are limited and local populations rely heavily on lakes for nutrition. Here, using a 1,500-y paleoecological record, we show that declines in fishery species and endemic molluscs began well before commercial fishing in Lake Tanganyika, Africas deepest and oldest lake. Paleoclimate and instrumental records demonstrate sustained warming in this lake during the last 150 y, which affects biota by strengthening and shallowing stratification of the water column. Reductions in lake mixing have depressed algal production and shrunk the oxygenated benthic habitat by 38% in our study areas, yielding fish and mollusc declines. Late-20th century fish fossil abundances at two of three sites were lower than at any other time in the last millennium and fell in concert with reduced diatom abundance and warming water. A negative correlation between lake temperature and fish and mollusc fossils over the last 500 y indicates that climate warming and intensifying stratification have almost certainly reduced potential fishery production, helping to explain ongoing declines in fish catches. Long-term declines of both benthic and pelagic species underscore the urgency of strategic efforts to sustain Lake Tanganyikas extraordinary biodiversity and ecosystem services.
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-08 22:01:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's little surprise that your comment is nothing but logical fallacy after logical fallacy given your ideology so I won't go into those as it's a waste of time.

I will however direct you to look at timelines on major oil   gas projects across the globe. For example, I would *love* to see projections for Canada's oil sands whereby expansion is clearly, as you say, stopped, by 2035. 

Here's a start: [Canadas Energy Future 2016: Energy Supply and Demand Projections to 2040](https://www.neb-one.gc.ca/nrg/ntgrtd/ftr/2016/index-eng.html)  

If Kurzweil suggests, as you imply, that fossil fuels will no longer be in use in a mere ~19 years then his grip on reality is just as ignorant as your own. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-08 21:14:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Study: [Influence of oil and gas emissions on summertime ozone in the Colorado Northern Front Range](http://onlinelibrary.wiley.com/doi/10.1002/2016JD025265/abstract)
___

**Abstract**:

Tropospheric O3 has been decreasing across much of the eastern U.S. but has remained steady or even increased in some western regions. Recent increases in VOC and NOx emissions associated with the production of oil and natural gas (O NG) may contribute to this trend in some areas. The Northern Front Range of Colorado has regularly exceeded O3 air quality standards during summertime in recent years. This region has VOC emissions from a rapidly developing O NG basin and low concentrations of biogenic VOC in close proximity to urban-Denver NOx emissions. Here VOC OH reactivity (OHR), O3 production efficiency (OPE), and an observationally constrained box model are used to quantify the influence of O NG emissions on regional summertime O3 production. Analyses are based on measurements acquired over two summers at a central location within the Northern Front Range that lies between major regional O NG and urban emission sectors. Observational analyses suggest that mixing obscures any OPE differences in air primarily influenced by O NG or urban emission sector. The box model confirms relatively modest OPE differences that are within the uncertainties of the field observations. Box model results also indicate that maximum O3 at the measurement location is sensitive to changes in NOx mixing ratio but also responsive to O NG VOC reductions. Combined, these analyses show that O NG alkanes contribute over 80% to the observed carbon mixing ratio, roughly 50% to the regional VOC OHR, and approximately 20% to regional photochemical O3 production. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-08 20:44:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> /r/climateskeptics and /r/conspiracy are among the top subreddits you contribute discussion to. It's [no surprise](http://www.sciencealert.com/new-study-links-climate-change-denials-with-conspiracy-theories) then that your understanding of reality is distorted beyond reason.

By the year 2035... no one will be burning fossils.

I rest my case. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-08 20:36:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> In the long run (which isn't that long tbh) climate change will result in substantial economic losses that could be avoided, or at least mitigated, by rapidly transitioning away from fossil fuels.

A couple of peer reviewed studies are discussed and linked in the following article: [Climate change will wipe $2.5tn off global financial assets - Losses could soar to $24tn and wreck the global economy in worst case scenario](https://www.theguardian.com/environment/2016/apr/04/climate-change-will-blow-a-25tn-hole-in-global-financial-assets-study-warns)   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-05 18:13:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's like you made your own conclusion, entirely ignoring the discussion of not only the paper you linked, but also this study.

The following is according to the 2012 paper you have linked. The accumulation rate at Camp Century, while at ~0.32m/y, clearly shows a negative trend over the decades as the authors themselves state:

In Northern Greenland we only have few data... but the data that do exist show a drop in accumulation rate across the divide and also indicate a significant change in the 18O-accumulation relationship.

Three of the four records that contain recent data indicate an increase in temperature for the decade after 2000 AD.
For NEEM [ie. Camp Century] and B26, the decade 20002009 has the warmest 18O value of the records of 270 yr and 110 yr, respectively. In the 1820 yr long record from NGRIP only four decades have warmer 18O values than 20002009. At Camp Century no increase in accumulation rate or 18O can be seen, and the record from ACT10A is too short to draw any conclusions from. Thus, no conclusive statement can be made about the accumulation rate from these ice core data, but they indicate an increase in temperature after 2000 AD.

I'll leave you to *actually* read the open access study linked ITT that relates to the article.
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-05 17:49:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Because Trump poses a serious risk to climate policy that has been developed throughout the years both nationally and internationally. Under the banner of climate policy Hillary is absolutely better. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-05 05:46:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Study (open access): [The abandoned ice sheet base at Camp Century, Greenland, in a warming climate](http://onlinelibrary.wiley.com/doi/10.1002/2016GL069688/full)
___

**Abstract**:

*In 1959 the U.S. Army Corps of Engineers built Camp Century beneath the surface of the northwestern Greenland Ice Sheet. There they studied the feasibility of deploying ballistic missiles within the ice sheet. The base and its wastes were abandoned with minimal decommissioning in 1967, under the assumption they would be preserved for eternity by perpetually accumulating snowfall. Here we show that a transition in ice sheet surface mass balance at Camp Century from net accumulation to net ablation is plausible within the next 75 years, under a business-as-usual anthropogenic emissions scenario (Representative Concentration Pathway 8.5). Net ablation would guarantee the eventual remobilization of physical, chemical, biological, and radiological wastes abandoned at the site. While Camp Century and four other contemporaneous ice sheet bases were legally established under a Danish-U.S. treaty, the potential remobilization of their abandoned wastes, previously regarded as sequestered, represents an entirely new pathway of political dispute resulting from climate change.* </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-05 05:44:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Study (open access): [The abandoned ice sheet base at Camp Century, Greenland, in a warming climate](http://onlinelibrary.wiley.com/doi/10.1002/2016GL069688/full)
___

**Abstract**:

*In 1959 the U.S. Army Corps of Engineers built Camp Century beneath the surface of the northwestern Greenland Ice Sheet. There they studied the feasibility of deploying ballistic missiles within the ice sheet. The base and its wastes were abandoned with minimal decommissioning in 1967, under the assumption they would be preserved for eternity by perpetually accumulating snowfall. Here we show that a transition in ice sheet surface mass balance at Camp Century from net accumulation to net ablation is plausible within the next 75 years, under a business-as-usual anthropogenic emissions scenario (Representative Concentration Pathway 8.5). Net ablation would guarantee the eventual remobilization of physical, chemical, biological, and radiological wastes abandoned at the site. While Camp Century and four other contemporaneous ice sheet bases were legally established under a Danish-U.S. treaty, the potential remobilization of their abandoned wastes, previously regarded as sequestered, represents an entirely new pathway of political dispute resulting from climate change.* </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-05 05:41:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Study (open access): [The abandoned ice sheet base at Camp Century, Greenland, in a warming climate](http://onlinelibrary.wiley.com/doi/10.1002/2016GL069688/full)
___

**Abstract**:

In 1959 the U.S. Army Corps of Engineers built Camp Century beneath the surface of the northwestern Greenland Ice Sheet. There they studied the feasibility of deploying ballistic missiles within the ice sheet. The base and its wastes were abandoned with minimal decommissioning in 1967, under the assumption they would be preserved for eternity by perpetually accumulating snowfall. Here we show that a transition in ice sheet surface mass balance at Camp Century from net accumulation to net ablation is plausible within the next 75 years, under a business-as-usual anthropogenic emissions scenario (Representative Concentration Pathway 8.5). Net ablation would guarantee the eventual remobilization of physical, chemical, biological, and radiological wastes abandoned at the site. While Camp Century and four other contemporaneous ice sheet bases were legally established under a Danish-U.S. treaty, the potential remobilization of their abandoned wastes, previously regarded as sequestered, represents an entirely new pathway of political dispute resulting from climate change. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-04 22:34:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> While I generally agree with some of the concerns for increasing the likely hood with regard to pathogen mobility under increasingly warming conditions, it should be noted that anthrax outbreaks within the Arctic are not restricted to the more recent decades:

Study: [An Overview of Early Anthrax Outbreaks in Northern Canada: Field Reports of the Health of Animals Branch, Agriculture Canada, 1962-71](http://arctic.journalhosting.ucalgary.ca/arctic/index.php/arctic/article/view/761)
___

**Abstract**:

Between 1962 and 1971, six outbreaks of anthrax occurred in the bison herds of the Northwest Territories and northern Alberta. In response, the federal Health of Animals Branch dispatched staff veterinarians to oversee carcass disposal operations and later to take part in bison depopulation and vaccination programs. Recently, a collection of documents from that agency concerning the outbreaks was discovered in the federal archives. The collection includes field reports from the veterinarians that provide valuable, detailed, first-person accounts of the outbreaks and later programs, information which has generally been lacking in the published literature. The reports identify at least 1102 bison that died of anthrax during the six outbreaks, dozens more than reported previously. They also indicate that the disease spread into Wood Buffalo National Park in 1963, rather than in 1964, as reported previously. A minimum of 598 healthy bison were also killed in depopulation programs aimed at preventing the spread of anthrax into the Park, even though anthrax carcasses had already been discovered within the Park and the targeted regions would be repopulated within weeks. Coverage and revaccination rates were low throughout the vaccination program, and a further 828 bison died during the vaccine roundups. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-04 10:09:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Report: [Fewer Americans doubt global warming is occuring](http://closup.umich.edu/issues-in-energy-and-environmental-policy/29/fewer-americans-doubt-global-warming-is-occurring/) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-03 22:59:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Study: [A synthesis of the basal thermal state of the Greenland Ice Sheet](http://onlinelibrary.wiley.com/doi/10.1002/2015JF003803/full)
___

**Abstract**:

The basal thermal state of an ice sheet (frozen or thawed) is an important control upon its evolution, dynamics, and response to external forcings. However, this state can only be observed directly at sparse boreholes or inferred conclusively from the presence of subglacial lakes. Here we synthesize spatially extensive inferences of the basal thermal state of the Greenland Ice Sheet to better constrain this state. Existing inferences include outputs from the eight thermomechanical ice-flow models included in the Sea Level Response to Ice Sheet Evolution (SeaRISE) effort. New remote-sensing inferences of the basal thermal state are derived from Holocene radiostratigraphy, modern surface velocity, and Moderate Resolution Imaging Spectroradiometer (MODIS) imagery. Both thermomechanical modeling and remote inferences generally agree that the Northeast Greenland Ice Stream and large portions of the southwestern ice-drainage systems are thawed at the bed, whereas the bed beneath the central ice divides, particularly their west facing slopes, is frozen. Elsewhere, there is poorer agreement regarding the basal thermal state. Both models and remote inferences rarely represent the borehole-observed basal thermal state accurately near NorthGRIP and DYE-3. This synthesis identifies a large portion of the Greenland Ice Sheet (about one third by area), where additional observations would most improve knowledge of its overall basal thermal state. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-03 22:53:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Study: [A synthesis of the basal thermal state of the Greenland Ice Sheet](http://onlinelibrary.wiley.com/doi/10.1002/2015JF003803/full)
___

**Abstract**:

The basal thermal state of an ice sheet (frozen or thawed) is an important control upon its evolution, dynamics, and response to external forcings. However, this state can only be observed directly at sparse boreholes or inferred conclusively from the presence of subglacial lakes. Here we synthesize spatially extensive inferences of the basal thermal state of the Greenland Ice Sheet to better constrain this state. Existing inferences include outputs from the eight thermomechanical ice-flow models included in the Sea Level Response to Ice Sheet Evolution (SeaRISE) effort. New remote-sensing inferences of the basal thermal state are derived from Holocene radiostratigraphy, modern surface velocity, and Moderate Resolution Imaging Spectroradiometer (MODIS) imagery. Both thermomechanical modeling and remote inferences generally agree that the Northeast Greenland Ice Stream and large portions of the southwestern ice-drainage systems are thawed at the bed, whereas the bed beneath the central ice divides, particularly their west facing slopes, is frozen. Elsewhere, there is poorer agreement regarding the basal thermal state. Both models and remote inferences rarely represent the borehole-observed basal thermal state accurately near NorthGRIP and DYE-3. This synthesis identifies a large portion of the Greenland Ice Sheet (about one third by area), where additional observations would most improve knowledge of its overall basal thermal state. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-03 00:14:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Related Material(s):

Warm Regards Podcast: [Climate Forensics: How scientists reconstruct the past to understand change today](https://soundcloud.com/warmregardspodcast/climate-forensics-how-scientists-reconstruct-the-past-to-understand-todays-climate) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-03 00:12:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Related Material(s):
____

Warm Regards Podcast: [Climate Forensics: How scientists reconstruct the past to understand change today](https://soundcloud.com/warmregardspodcast/climate-forensics-how-scientists-reconstruct-the-past-to-understand-todays-climate) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-02 23:00:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Source: https://twitter.com/ericsteig/status/760577380385558529 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-02 22:27:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Study (open access): [The collapse of Io's primary atmosphere in Jupiter eclipse](http://onlinelibrary.wiley.com/doi/10.1002/2016JE005025/full)
___

**Abstract**:

Volcanic outgassing due to tidal heating is the ultimate source of a tenuous SO2 atmosphere around Jupiter's moon Io. The question of whether SO2 frost on the surface plays a part, and to what degree, in maintaining Io's atmosphere with the constant volcanic outgassing is still debated. It is believed that for a sublimation-supported atmosphere, the primary atmosphere should collapse during eclipses by Jupiter, as the SO2 vapor pressure is strongly coupled to the temperature of the ice on the surface. No direct observations of Io's atmosphere in eclipse have previously been possible, due to the simultaneous need for high spectral and time sensitivity, as well as a high signal-to-noise ratio. Here we present the first ever high-resolution spectra at 19m of Io's SO2 atmosphere in Jupiter eclipse from the Gemini telescope. The strongest atmospheric band depth is seen to dramatically decay from 2.5(0.08)% before the eclipse to 0.18(0.16)% after 40min in eclipse. Further modeling indicates that the atmosphere has collapsed shortly after eclipse ingress, implying that the atmosphere of Io has a strong sublimation-controlled component. The atmospheric column densityfrom pre-eclipse to in-eclipsedrops by a factor of 52. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-02 22:09:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> - Full Report: [State of the Climate in 2015](https://www.ametsoc.org/ams/index.cfm/publications/bulletin-of-the-american-meteorological-society-bams/state-of-the-climate/) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-02 08:25:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I would certainly hesitate when it comes to any remarks regarding clouds. Note the confidence factor (L for Low) and the margin of error from [the IPCC](http://www.realclimate.org/images/ipcc_rad_forc_ar5.jpg). Cloud dynamics are highly complex and it remains amongst the largest areas of uncertainty in climate modelling:

...existing methods of representing convection and clouds are crude, and, in some cases, can be shown even to be qualitatively incorrect. 

\- [MIT: Convection, Atmospheric Water Vapor, and Cloud Formation](http://cgcs.mit.edu/research/convection-atmospheric-water-vapor-and-cloud-formation) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-02 02:29:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Please don't. A number of its claims are not factually supported, and it clearly has a strong bias. If you're looking to educate yourself on climate change I would recommend actually reading the [IPCC's 5th assessment report](http://www.ipcc.ch/report/ar5/).  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-02 02:14:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yes, it's a major component of global sea level rise. A common misconception is that sea ice doesn't increase sea level. However trivial, it in fact does due to the differences in density between fresh water and sea water. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-02 01:46:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> See: [Saving the World's Terrestrial Megafauna](http://bioscience.oxfordjournals.org/content/early/2016/07/25/biosci.biw092.full) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-02 01:41:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> See: [Saving the World's Terrestrial Megafauna](http://bioscience.oxfordjournals.org/content/early/2016/07/25/biosci.biw092.full)

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-02 00:57:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Study: [Scale-dependent regional climate predictability over North America inferred from CMIP3 and CMIP5 ensemble simulations](https://link.springer.com/article/10.1007/s00376-016-6013-2)
___

**Abstract**:

Through the analysis of ensembles of coupled model simulations and projections collected from CMIP3 and CMIP5, we demonstrate that a fundamental spatial scale limit might exist below which useful additional refinement of climate model predictions and projections may not be possible. That limit varies among climate variables and from region to region. We show that the uncertainty (noise) in surface temperature predictions (represented by the spread among an ensemble of global climate model simulations) generally exceeds the ensemble mean (signal) at horizontal scales below 1000 km throughout North America, implying poor predictability at those scales. More limited skill is shown for the predictability of regional precipitation. The ensemble spread in this case tends to exceed or equal the ensemble mean for scales below 2000 km. These findings highlight the challenges in predicting regionally specific future climate anomalies, especially for hydroclimatic impacts such as drought and wetness. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-01 21:20:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Study: [Timing and causes of mid-Holocene mammoth extinction on St. Paul Island, Alaska](http://www.pnas.org/content/early/2016/07/27/1604903113)
___


**Significance**:

St. Paul Island, Alaska, is famous for its late-surviving population of woolly mammoth. The puzzle of mid-Holocene extinction is solved via multiple independent paleoenvironmental proxies that tightly constrain the timing of extinction to 5,600  100 y ago and strongly point to the effects of sea-level rise and drier climates on freshwater scarcity as the primary extinction driver. Likely ecosystem effects of the mega-herbivore extinction include reduced rates of watershed erosion by elimination of crowding around water holes and a vegetation shift toward increased abundances of herbaceous taxa. Freshwater availability may be an underappreciated driver of island extinction. This study reinforces 21st-century concerns about the vulnerability of island populations, including humans, to future warming, freshwater availability, and sea level rise.

**Abstract**:

Relict woolly mammoth (Mammuthus primigenius) populations survived on several small Beringian islands for thousands of years after mainland populations went extinct. Here we present multiproxy paleoenvironmental records to investigate the timing, causes, and consequences of mammoth disappearance from St. Paul Island, Alaska. Five independent indicators of extinction show that mammoths survived on St. Paul until 5,600  100 y ago. Vegetation composition remained stable during the extinction window, and there is no evidence of human presence on the island before 1787 CE, suggesting that these factors were not extinction drivers. Instead, the extinction coincided with declining freshwater resources and drier climates between 7,850 and 5,600 y ago, as inferred from sedimentary magnetic susceptibility, oxygen isotopes, and diatom and cladoceran assemblages in a sediment core from a freshwater lake on the island, and stable nitrogen isotopes from mammoth remains. Contrary to other extinction models for the St. Paul mammoth population, this evidence indicates that this mammoth population died out because of the synergistic effects of shrinking island area and freshwater scarcity caused by rising sea levels and regional climate change. Degradation of water quality by intensified mammoth activity around the lake likely exacerbated the situation. The St. Paul mammoth demise is now one of the best-dated prehistoric extinctions, highlighting freshwater limitation as an overlooked extinction driver and underscoring the vulnerability of small island populations to environmental change, even in the absence of human influence.
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-01 02:25:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Study: [More extreme precipitation in the worlds dry and wet regions](http://www.nature.com/nclimate/journal/v6/n5/full/nclimate2941.html)
___

**Abstract**:

*Intensification of the hydrological cycle is expected to accompany a warming climate. It has been suggested that changes in the spatial distribution of precipitation will amplify differences between dry and wet regions, but this has been disputed for changes over land. Furthermore, precipitation changes may differ not only between regions but also between different aspects of precipitation, such as totals and extremes. Here we investigate changes in these two aspects in the worlds dry and wet regions using observations and global climate models. Despite uncertainties in total precipitation changes, extreme daily precipitation averaged over both dry and wet regimes shows robust increases in both observations and climate models over the past six decades. Climate projections for the rest of the century show continued intensification of daily precipitation extremes. Increases in total and extreme precipitation in dry regions are linearly related to the model-specific global temperature change, so that the spread in projected global warming partly explains the spread in precipitation intensification in these regions by the late twenty-first century. This intensification has implications for the risk of flooding as the climate warms, particularly for the worlds dry regions.* </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-01 02:22:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Study: [More extreme precipitation in the worlds dry and wet regions](http://www.nature.com/nclimate/journal/v6/n5/full/nclimate2941.html)
___

**Abstract**:

Intensification of the hydrological cycle is expected to accompany a warming climate. It has been suggested that changes in the spatial distribution of precipitation will amplify differences between dry and wet regions, but this has been disputed for changes over land. Furthermore, precipitation changes may differ not only between regions but also between different aspects of precipitation, such as totals and extremes. Here we investigate changes in these two aspects in the worlds dry and wet regions using observations and global climate models. Despite uncertainties in total precipitation changes, extreme daily precipitation averaged over both dry and wet regimes shows robust increases in both observations and climate models over the past six decades. Climate projections for the rest of the century show continued intensification of daily precipitation extremes. Increases in total and extreme precipitation in dry regions are linearly related to the model-specific global temperature change, so that the spread in projected global warming partly explains the spread in precipitation intensification in these regions by the late twenty-first century. This intensification has implications for the risk of flooding as the climate warms, particularly for the worlds dry regions. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-31 03:59:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If humanity makes it to the next glacial period, what's going to happen really?

That's a good question, and one full of speculation  \\\_()_/. I can say that humanity won't see the next glacial period for a considerable length of time though. Given our current configuration - where the continents are located, ocean currents, etc. numerous studies have shown that CO2 emissions are required to fall below ~240-280ppm before the next glacial period would occur on natural cycles due to Milankovitch cycles. Currently atmospheric CO2 is sitting above [400ppm](https://scripps.ucsd.edu/programs/keelingcurve/) and expected to rise under [different RCP scenarios](http://i.imgur.com/2Hr4eQE.jpg). That being said, human emissions have therefore delayed the onset of the next glacial period for [~100,000 years](https://www.carbonbrief.org/human-emissions-will-delay-next-ice-age-by-50000-years-study-says). For the sake of clarity as to why it's speculative at best as to "what's going to happen" if humanity makes it to the next glacial period a simple thought experiment should suffice: Simply ask yourself how well predictions made a mere 100 years ago turned out... now extend that further back to 200 years... ok, now how about a few thousand years ago during such times as the Egyptians and Babylonians? Our species, *Homo Sapiens*, only arose ~195,000 years ago... clearly then, predicting what will happen in 100,000 years time is anybody's guess.  

It seems we would be more likely to be wiped out by a glacial periods than the size of the sun increasing...

It's not necessarily about whether or not the change is with regard to cooling or warming, but rather how abrupt the change is. In other words, can the terrestrial biosphere adapt rapidly enough? Most extinction events are preceded by abrupt warming as cooling typically occurs on far slower time scales (it takes time for massive ice sheets to grow, but they can collapse catastrophically when warmed).

Is there a connection between global warming and glacial periods?

Milankovitch cycles may be one component, though there are seemingly countless components that form a complex system of positive and negative feedbacks. Our current warming, however, can be entirely attributed to human activity.

Thanks for your time and knowledge!

You're welcome, and if you have any other questions feel free to ask, and hopefully I can answer them, and if not at least I could point you in the right direction. You may find some links in the following [sticky](https://www.reddit.com/r/GlobalClimateChange/comments/2b9wog/a_list_of_available_resources_for_climate/) useful.

EDIT: Added clarity on *why* it's nothing but pure speculation </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-30 20:31:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> He incorrectly used the term ice age, and should have used glacial periods (though the last glacial period is also confusingly known as "the Ice Age"). We are currently still in an ice age which began ~2.58Ma (million years ago) which marks the start of the Pliestocene. We are currently within an interglacial period which began ~11.7ka (thousand years ago) and marks the start of the Holocene - a period of relatively unusual stability within the climate system. Glacial periods are marked with even numbers, and interglacial periods are marked with odd numbers (known as Marine Isotope Stages): https://i.imgur.com/Rxim2EO.jpg </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-30 20:19:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Anyway, I think you missed the point of what I was saying in my very short comment...

I think you missed /u/orthag's point. You statement assumes that every glacial period (not ice age as you incorrectly state) had the same conditions as the previous glacial period. This couldn't be further from the truth. Each glacial / interglacial period had its own unique characteristics. However, a general trend can be observed such that the [more recent glacial periods were colder than previous episodes](https://i.imgur.com/Rxim2EO.jpg), not only did their durations differ but their ice extent became greater and ice sheets became thicker. While they may have experience previous glacial episodes, they had not experienced the likes of any that came after the previous glacial period. This is further observed whereby "Neandertals were processing faunal remains more heavily during glacial periods, suggesting a response to increased nutritional stress during colder time periods."^[1](http://www.sciencedirect.com/science/article/pii/S004724841630001X)       </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-30 15:36:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Citation: [Collard, M., Tarle, L., Sandgathe, D. and Allan, A. (in press) Faunal evidence for a difference in clothing use between Neanderthals and early modern humans in Europe. Journal of Anthropological Archaeology.](http://profmarkcollard.com/publications/) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-30 12:22:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Related Material(s):
___

- [How Parka jackets saved early humans from the chilly fate of the Neanderthals](http://www.telegraph.co.uk/science/2016/07/29/how-parka-jackets-saved-early-humans-from-the-chilly-fate-of-the/) --- Collard, M., Tarle, L., Sandgathe, D. and Allan, A. (in press) Faunal evidence for a difference in clothing use between Neanderthals and early modern humans in Europe. Journal of Anthropological Archaeology. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-30 11:50:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Study: [Climate-mediated shifts in Neandertal subsistence behaviors at Pech de l'Az IV and Roc de Marsal (Dordogne Valley, France)](http://www.sciencedirect.com/science/article/pii/S004724841630001X)
___

**Abstract**:

*Neandertals disappeared from Europe just after 40,000 years ago. Some hypotheses ascribe this to numerous population crashes associated with glacial cycles in the late Pleistocene. The goal of this paper is to test the hypothesis that glacial periods stressed Neandertal populations. If cold climates stressed Neandertals, their subsistence behaviors may have changedrequiring intensified use of prey through more extensive nutrient extraction from faunal carcasses. To test this, an analysis of Neandertal butchering was conducted on medium sized bovid/cervid remains composed of predominately red deer (Cervus elaphus), reindeer (Rangifer tarandus), and roe deer (Capreolus caprelous) deposited during global warm and cold phases from two French sites: Pech de l'Az IV (Pech IV, Bordes' excavation) and Roc de Marsal (RDM). Analysis of surface modification on high survival long bones and proximal and middle phalanges demonstrates that skeletal elements excavated from the cold levels (RDM Level 4, Pech IV Level I2) at each cave have more cut marks and percussion marks than elements from the warm levels (RDM Level 9, Pech IV Level Y-Z) after controlling for fragment size. At both sites, epiphyseal fragments are rare, and although this pattern can result from carnivore consumption, carnivore tooth marks are almost nonexistent (0.1%). Alternatively, processing epiphyseal ends for bone grease may have been a Neandertal survival strategy, and epiphyses were more intensively percussed in cold levels than in warm levels at both RDM and Pech IV. The exploitation of low marrow yield elements such as phalanges does not show a consistent pattern relating to climate, but may have been a general Neandertal behavioral characteristic, suggesting that these hominids were regularly on the edge of sufficient nutrient availability even during interglacials. Overall, the faunal assemblages from Roc de Marsal and Pech IV provide some support for the hypothesis that Neandertals were processing faunal remains more heavily during glacial periods, suggesting a response to increased nutritional stress during colder time periods.* </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-30 11:06:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Study (open access): [Observational evidence confirms modelling of the long-term integrity of CO2-reservoir caprocks](http://www.nature.com/ncomms/2016/160728/ncomms12268/full/ncomms12268.html)
___

**Abstract**:

Storage of anthropogenic CO2 in geological formations relies on a caprock as the primary seal preventing buoyant super-critical CO2 escaping. Although natural CO2 reservoirs demonstrate that CO2 may be stored safely for millions of years, uncertainty remains in predicting how caprocks will react with CO2-bearing brines. This uncertainty poses a significant challenge to the risk assessment of geological carbon storage. Here we describe mineral reaction fronts in a CO2 reservoir-caprock system exposed to CO2 over a timescale comparable with that needed for geological carbon storage. The propagation of the reaction front is retarded by redox-sensitive mineral dissolution reactions and carbonate precipitation, which reduces its penetration into the caprock to ~7 cm in ~10^5 years. This distance is an order-of-magnitude smaller than previous predictions. The results attest to the significance of transport-limited reactions to the long-term integrity of sealing behaviour in caprocks exposed to CO2. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-30 11:03:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> http://images.remss.com/msu/msu_time_series.html 

I still see an increase in temperature in TMT under 'recent' trend, although that's beside the point anyways. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-30 10:39:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Study: [A global assessment of the societal impacts of glacier outburst floods](http://www.sciencedirect.com/science/article/pii/S0921818116301023)
___

**Highlights**:

 1348 floods from 332 sites, and 36% of these sites have recorded societal impact.

 Over 12,000 deaths recorded globally due to glacier floods.

 Recurrence intervals calculated based on volume, discharge and damage.

 Damage type and index determined per event, per country and per major world region
___

**Abstract**:

*Glacier outburst floods are sudden releases of large amounts of water from a glacier. They are a pervasive natural hazard worldwide. They have an association with climate primarily via glacier mass balance and their impacts on society partly depend on population pressure and land use. Given the ongoing changes in climate and land use and population distributions there is therefore an urgent need to discriminate the spatio-temporal patterning of glacier outburst floods and their impacts. This study presents data compiled from 20 countries and comprising 1348 glacier floods spanning 10 centuries. Societal impacts were assessed using a relative damage index based on recorded deaths, evacuations, and property and infrastructure destruction and disruption. These floods originated from 332 sites; 70% were from ice-dammed lakes and 36% had recorded societal impact. The number of floods recorded has apparently reduced since the mid-1990s in all major world regions. Two thirds of sites that have produced  5 floods (n = 32) have floods occurring progressively earlier in the year. Glacier floods have directly caused at least: 7 deaths in Iceland, 393 deaths in the European Alps, 5745 deaths in South America and 6300 deaths in central Asia. Peru, Nepal and India have experienced fewer floods yet higher levels of damage. One in five sites in the European Alps has produced floods that have damaged farmland, destroyed homes and damaged bridges; 10% of sites in South America have produced glacier floods that have killed people and damaged infrastructure; 15% of sites in central Asia have produced floods that have inundated farmland, destroyed homes, damaged roads and damaged infrastructure. Overall, Bhutan and Nepal have the greatest national-level economic consequences of glacier flood impacts. We recommend that accurate, full and standardised monitoring, recording and reporting of glacier floods is essential if spatio-temporal patterns in glacier flood occurrence, magnitude and societal impact are to be better understood. We note that future modelling of the global impact of glacier floods cannot assume that the same trends will continue and will need to consider combining land-use change with probability distributions of geomorphological responses to climate change and to human activity.* </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-30 09:56:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Study (open access): [Observational evidence confirms modelling of the long-term integrity of CO2-reservoir caprocks](http://www.nature.com/ncomms/2016/160728/ncomms12268/full/ncomms12268.html)
___

**Abstract**:

*Storage of anthropogenic CO2 in geological formations relies on a caprock as the primary seal preventing buoyant super-critical CO2 escaping. Although natural CO2 reservoirs demonstrate that CO2 may be stored safely for millions of years, uncertainty remains in predicting how caprocks will react with CO2-bearing brines. This uncertainty poses a significant challenge to the risk assessment of geological carbon storage. Here we describe mineral reaction fronts in a CO2 reservoir-caprock system exposed to CO2 over a timescale comparable with that needed for geological carbon storage. The propagation of the reaction front is retarded by redox-sensitive mineral dissolution reactions and carbonate precipitation, which reduces its penetration into the caprock to ~7cm in ~10^5 years. This distance is an order-of-magnitude smaller than previous predictions. The results attest to the significance of transport-limited reactions to the long-term integrity of sealing behaviour in caprocks exposed to CO2.* </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-29 10:39:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Study: [Contribution of Antarctica to past and future sea-level rise](http://www.nature.com/nature/journal/v531/n7596/full/nature17145.html)
___

**Abstract**:

*Polar temperatures over the last several million years have, at times, been slightly warmer than today, yet global mean sea level has been 69metres higher as recently as the Last Interglacial (130,000 to 115,000 years ago) and possibly higher during the Pliocene epoch (about three million years ago). In both cases the Antarctic ice sheet has been implicated as the primary contributor, hinting at its future vulnerability. Here we use a model coupling ice sheet and climate dynamicsincluding previously underappreciated processes linking atmospheric warming with hydrofracturing of buttressing ice shelves and structural collapse of marine-terminating ice cliffsthat is calibrated against Pliocene and Last Interglacial sea-level estimates and applied to future greenhouse gas emission scenarios. Antarctica has the potential to contribute more than a metre of sea-level rise by 2100 and more than 15metres by 2500, if emissions continue unabated. In this case atmospheric warming will soon become the dominant driver of ice loss, but prolonged ocean warming will delay its recovery for thousands of years.* </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-29 10:24:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Study: [Low atmospheric CO2 levels during the Little Ice Age due to cooling-induced terrestrial uptake](http://www.nature.com/ngeo/journal/vaop/ncurrent/full/ngeo2769.html)
___

**Abstract**:

*Low atmospheric carbon dioxide (CO2) concentration during the Little Ice Age has been used to derive the global carbon cycle sensitivity to temperature. Recent evidence confirms earlier indications that the low CO2 was caused by increased terrestrial carbon storage. It remains unknown whether the terrestrial biosphere responded to temperature variations, or there was vegetation re-growth on abandoned farmland. Here we present a global numerical simulation of atmospheric carbonyl sulfide concentrations in the pre-industrial period. Carbonyl sulfide concentration is linked to changes in gross primary production and shows a positive anomaly during the Little Ice Age. We show that a decrease in gross primary production and a larger decrease in ecosystem respiration is the most likely explanation for the decrease in atmospheric CO2 and increase in atmospheric carbonyl sulfide concentrations. Therefore, temperature change, not vegetation re-growth, was the main cause of the increased terrestrial carbon storage. We address the inconsistency between ice-core CO2 records from different sites measuring CO2 and 13CO2 in ice from Dronning Maud Land (Antarctica). Our interpretation allows us to derive the temperature sensitivity of pre-industrial CO2 fluxes for the terrestrial biosphere (L = 10 to 90 Pg C K^1 ), implying a positive climate feedback and providing a benchmark to reduce model uncertainties.* </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-29 10:20:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Study: [Low atmospheric CO2 levels during the Little Ice Age due to cooling-induced terrestrial uptake](http://www.nature.com/ngeo/journal/vaop/ncurrent/full/ngeo2769.html)
___

**Abstract**:

Low atmospheric carbon dioxide (CO2) concentration during the Little Ice Age has been used to derive the global carbon cycle sensitivity to temperature. Recent evidence confirms earlier indications that the low CO2 was caused by increased terrestrial carbon storage. It remains unknown whether the terrestrial biosphere responded to temperature variations, or there was vegetation re-growth on abandoned farmland. Here we present a global numerical simulation of atmospheric carbonyl sulfide concentrations in the pre-industrial period. Carbonyl sulfide concentration is linked to changes in gross primary production and shows a positive anomaly during the Little Ice Age. We show that a decrease in gross primary production and a larger decrease in ecosystem respiration is the most likely explanation for the decrease in atmospheric CO2 and increase in atmospheric carbonyl sulfide concentrations. Therefore, temperature change, not vegetation re-growth, was the main cause of the increased terrestrial carbon storage. We address the inconsistency between ice-core CO2 records from different sites measuring CO2 and 13CO2 in ice from Dronning Maud Land (Antarctica). Our interpretation allows us to derive the temperature sensitivity of pre-industrial CO2 fluxes for the terrestrial biosphere (L = 10 to 90PgCK^1 ), implying a positive climate feedback and providing a benchmark to reduce model uncertainties. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-28 02:21:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Jason 2 displays time frames accurately and in easily understood format.

They all appeared to be displayed accurately and were easily understood though... are you referencing something other than the those available through the [time series](http://www.aviso.altimetry.fr/en/data/products/ocean-indicators-products/mean-sea-level/products-images.html)? 

Again, I'm curious as to why you have opted to select the Jason 2 time series as opposed to others available. I can understand why you would choose it for more recent times, but then why not Saral? Do you think Saral is currently too short of a time series? Do 'climate norms' exist for SLR?

...stop over at the ASIF, in the consequences folder...

Providing a direct link is the courteous thing to do if you know where it is, and others don't. You really expect me to sift through [13 pages](http://forum.arctic-sea-ice.net/index.php?topic=874.0) for a single post or two on Jason 2? I'm well aware of the consequences of SLR so if that's all you're directing me to I think I'll pass. That being said, the forum does present a number of interesting discussions worth exploring. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-28 01:53:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Study: [Genetic structure of the beaked whale genus Berardius in the North Pacific, with genetic evidence for a new species](http://onlinelibrary.wiley.com/doi/10.1111/mms.12345/abstract)
___

**Abstract**:

There are two recognized species in the genus Berardius, Baird's and Arnoux's beaked whales. In Japan, whalers have traditionally recognized two forms of Baird's beaked whales, the common slate-gray form and a smaller, rare black form. Previous comparison of mtDNA control region sequences from three black specimens to gray specimens around Japan indicated that the two forms comprise different stocks and potentially different species. We have expanded sampling to include control region haplotypes of 178 Baird's beaked whales from across their range in the North Pacific. We identified five additional specimens of the black form from the Aleutian Islands and Bering Sea, for a total of eight black specimens. The divergence between mtDNA haplotypes of the black and gray forms of Baird's beaked whale was greater than their divergence from the congeneric Arnoux's beaked whale found in the Southern Ocean, and similar to that observed among other congeneric beaked whale species. Taken together, genetic evidence from specimens in Japan and across the North Pacific, combined with evidence of smaller adult body size, indicate presence of an unnamed species of Berardius in the North Pacific. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-27 20:23:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Too often redditors get off on apocalyptic fantasies...

[Tell me about it](https://np.reddit.com/r/videos/comments/4u5m5k/weird_methane_bubbles_starting_to_pop_up_in_the/d5nej0b?context=3) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-27 20:13:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Oh trust me, I have, and [continue to do so](http://www.nature.com/ngeo/journal/v8/n1/abs/ngeo2316.html). It's an interesting theory, but one certainly not without its problems in its attempts at explaining the large observed carbon isotope excursion.

Its almost embarrassing that we haven't worked out a cause yet, says Wing. Its the first thing anyone wants to knowbut even 20 years after identifying the PETM were still arguing about the cause. - [article](http://www.smithsonianmag.com/science-nature/ancient-earth-warmed-dramatically-after-one-two-carbon-punch-180953610/?no-ist)

While there are parallels to draw on, I would certainly hesitate to jump to conclusions (ie. methane clathrates).
Also note that I mention the most recent glacial and interglacial periods, extending back ~2.6Ma to the start of the Pleistocene as they are most similar to todays' environment. The PETM occurred ~56Ma. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-27 19:39:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Why opt for Jason 2? Why not Saral then which shows [+6.87mm yr^-1](http://www.aviso.altimetry.fr/fileadmin/images/data/Products/indic/msl/MSL_Serie_AL_Global_IB_RWT_GIA_Adjust.png) if we're talking time frames? 

The multi-mission [+3.20mm yr^-1](http://www.aviso.altimetry.fr/fileadmin/images/data/Products/indic/msl/MSL_Serie_ALL_Global_IB_RWT_GIA_Adjust.png) seems less 'cherry picked' for a lack of better wording which is in good agreement with others such as those already pointed out above and displayed by the Colorado University Sea Level Research Group which shows a value of [+3.4  0.4mm yr^-1 ]  (http://sealevel.colorado.edu/).

Or do you feel that Jason 2 is the most applicable time series? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-27 19:22:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> But doesn't all this hope for survival go out the window once you factor in the methane being released from the artic?

No, methane release from permafrost and offshore hydrates - while a concern - is far too often hyped as some apocalyptic scenario (ie. [clathrate gun hypothesis](https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Clathrate_gun_hypothesis)) that there simply isn't evidence to support. 

One such example, from the craters being observed in Siberia:

[How much methane came out of that hole in Siberia?](http://www.realclimate.org/index.php/archives/2014/08/how-much-methane-came-out-of-that-hole-in-siberia/comment-page-2/)

...If the bubble was pure methane, it would have contained about  wait for it  0.000003 Gtons of methane. In other words, building a Shakhova event from these explosions would take approximately 20,000,000 explosions, all within a few years, or else the climate impact of the methane would be muted by the lifetime effect.

A recent study also found "[No significant increase in long-term CH4 emissions on North Slope of Alaska despite significant increase in air temperature](http://onlinelibrary.wiley.com/doi/10.1002/2016GL069292/full)":

Our results suggest that even the observed short-term temperature sensitivity from the Arctic will have little impact on the global atmospheric CH4 budget in the long term if future trajectories evolve with the same temperature sensitivity.

While current warming is certainly abrupt, the arctic has scene abrupt warming in its past throughout multiple glacial and interglacial periods - (~1C per year for 5 years in steps, and an unbelievable 5-10C warming per year or 100 and 1,000 times faster warming than current warming respectively) - why is there no record of catastrophic methane release then from those periods? Because it didn't happen. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-27 18:55:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Study (open access): [Observed and simulated full-depth ocean heat-content changes for 19702005](http://www.ocean-sci.net/12/925/2016/)
___

**Abstract**:

*Greenhouse-gas emissions have created a planetary energy imbalance that is primarily manifested by increasing ocean heat content (OHC). Updated observational estimates of full-depth OHC change since 1970 are presented that account for recent advancements in reducing observation errors and biases. The full-depth OHC has increased by 0.74 [0.68, 0.80]1022Jyr^1 (0.46Wm^2 ) and 1.22 [1.161.29]1022Jyr^1 (0.75Wm^2 ) for 19702005 and 19922005, respectively, with a 5 to 95% confidence interval of the median. The CMIP5 models show large spread in OHC changes, suggesting that some models are not state-of-the-art and require further improvements. However, the ensemble median has excellent agreement with our observational estimate: 0.68 [0.540.82]1022Jyr^1 (0.42Wm^2 ) from 1970 to 2005 and 1.25 [1.101.41]1022Jyr^1 (0.77Wm^2 ) from 1992 to 2005. These results increase confidence in both the observational and model estimates to quantify and study changes in Earth's energy imbalance over the historical period. We suggest that OHC be a fundamental metric for climate model validation and evaluation, especially for forced changes (decadal timescales).*

Study: [Industrial-era global ocean heat uptake doubles in recent decades](http://www.nature.com/nclimate/journal/v6/n4/full/nclimate2915.html)
___

**Abstract**:

*Formal detection and attribution studies have used observations and climate models to identify an anthropogenic warming signature in the upper (0700m) ocean. Recently, as a result of the so-called surface warming hiatus, there has been considerable interest in global ocean heat content (OHC) changes in the deeper ocean, including natural and anthropogenically forced changes identified in observational modelling and data re-analysis studies. Here, we examine OHC changes in the context of the Earths global energy budget since early in the industrial era (circa 18652015) for a range of depths. We rely on OHC change estimates from a diverse collection of measurement systems including data from the nineteenth-century Challenger expedition, a multi-decadal record of ship-based in situ mostly upper-ocean measurements, the more recent near-global Argo floats profiling to intermediate (2,000m) depths, and full-depth repeated transoceanic sections. We show that the multi-model mean constructed from the current generation of historically forced climate models is consistent with the OHC changes from this diverse collection of observational systems. Our model-based analysis suggests that nearly half of the industrial-era increases in global OHC have occurred in recent decades, with over a third of the accumulated heat occurring below 700m and steadily rising.*

Study: [Insights into Earths energy imbalance from multiple sources](http://journals.ametsoc.org/doi/abs/10.1175/JCLI-D-16-0339.1)
___

**Abstract**:

*The current Earths energy imbalance (EEI) can best be estimated from changes in ocean heat content (OHC), complemented by top-of-atmosphere (TOA) radiation measurements and an assessment of the small non-ocean components. Sustained observations from the Argo array of autonomous profiling floats enable near-global estimates of OHC since 2005, which reveal considerable cancellation of variations in the upper 300 m. An analysis of the monthly contributions to EEI from non-ocean (land and ice) using the CESM Large Ensemble reveals standard deviations of 0.3 to 0.4 W m^-2 (global); largest values occur in August, but values are below 0.75 W m^-2 95% of the time. Global standard deviations of EEI of 0.64 W m^-2 based on top-of-atmosphere observations therefore substantially constrain ocean contributions, given by the tendencies of OHC. Instead, monthly standard deviations of many Argo-based OHC tendencies are 6 to 13 W m^-2 and non-physical fluctuations are clearly evident. We show that an ocean reanalysis with multi-variate dynamical data assimilation features much better agreement with TOA radiation, and 44% of the vertically-integrated short-term OHC trend for 2005-14 of 0.80.2 W m^-2 (globally) occurs below 700 m depth. Largest warming occurs from 20 to 50S, especially over the Southern Oceans, and near 40N, in all ocean analyses. The EEI is estimated to be 0.90.3 W m^-2 for 2005-2014.* </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-27 11:38:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> 4.5mm yr^-1 is not the global mean... 

NASA shows [+3.4mm yr^-1](http://climate.nasa.gov/vital-signs/sea-level/) as does aviso at [+3.39mm yr^-1](http://www.aviso.altimetry.fr/en/data/products/ocean-indicators-products/mean-sea-level.html) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-27 00:45:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's not completely open to question, it's a matter of scientific study and the majority of evidence points to the onset of *modern* plate tectonics somewhere in the vicinity of 3-3.2Ga. I pointed this out already in my previous response to your initial word vomit. I'm calling it a word vomit because, much like you have done here, you appear to be all over the place, and take singular studies or authors, and give them just as much weight and credibility as the general consensus.  

 Even if it didn't exist like today, it could have started as sagduction or other mechanisms. 

No one is discussing about how modern plate tectonics could have started though, so why do you feel it necessary to include? 'Sagduction' is a direct result of the underlying belief that plate tectonics could not have operated in a hot early Earth and that another mechanism must have operated to recycle oceanic crust back into the mantle. Again, this was discussed in my previous comment under 'drip tectonics.'    

It's a mental workout trying to tell what point it is that you are trying to make because much of your comment is so tangential, and so much is taken as gospel or does not follow from the study's results (ie. negating the LHB due to [Imbrium impact](https://news.brown.edu/articles/2016/07/imbrium) which the authors themselves conclude *["contributed](http://www.nature.com/nature/journal/v535/n7612/full/nature18278.html) to the LHB")*.

But even with some putative persistent ocean crust before modern island arcs resulted from Cavosie's early plate tectonics, the result is much the same I would think. Vents would be more common, fresh water UV pools or ocean shallows less common.

a) citation needed

b) On the difference between putative and tenuous: 

 - putative putative pyooddiv/ adjective: putative "generally considered or reputed to be."

 - repute rpyoot/ verb past participle: reputed "be widely known and respected."

 - tenuous tenyoos/ adjective adjective: tenuous "very weak or slight."

The evidence for modern plate tectonics, and by extension, island arc volcanism dating back prior to ~3.0 Ga is not widely assumed, or putative, it is tenuous if existent at all.



 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-26 12:04:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Study: [Earths oxygen cycle and the evolution of animal life](http://www.pnas.org/content/early/2016/07/20/1521544113.abstract.html?etoc)
___

**Significance**:

*Earth is currently the only planet known to harbor complex life. Understanding whether terrestrial biotic complexity is a unique phenomenon or can be expected to be widespread in the universe depends on a mechanistic understanding of the factors that led to the emergence of complex life on Earth. Here, we use geochemical constraints and quantitative models to suggest that marine environments may have been unfavorable for the emergence and large-scale proliferation of motile multicellular life for most of Earths history. Further, we argue that a holistic evaluation of environmental variability, organismal life history, and spatial ecological dynamics is essential for a full accounting of the factors that have allowed for the emergence of biological complexity on Earth.*

**Abstract**:

*The emergence and expansion of complex eukaryotic life on Earth is linked at a basic level to the secular evolution of surface oxygen levels. However, the role that planetary redox evolution has played in controlling the timing of metazoan (animal) emergence and diversification, if any, has been intensely debated. Discussion has gravitated toward threshold levels of environmental free oxygen (O2) necessary for early evolving animals to survive under controlled conditions. However, defining such thresholds in practice is not straightforward, and environmental O2 levels can potentially constrain animal life in ways distinct from threshold O2 tolerance. Herein, we quantitatively explore one aspect of the evolutionary coupling between animal life and Earths oxygen cyclethe influence of spatial and temporal variability in surface ocean O2 levels on the ecology of early metazoan organisms. Through the application of a series of quantitative biogeochemical models, we find that large spatiotemporal variations in surface ocean O2 levels and pervasive benthic anoxia are expected in a world with much lower atmospheric pO2 than at present, resulting in severe ecological constraints and a challenging evolutionary landscape for early metazoan life. We argue that these effects, when considered in the light of synergistic interactions with other environmental parameters and variable O2 demand throughout an organisms life history, would have resulted in long-term evolutionary and ecological inhibition of animal life on Earth for much of Middle Proterozoic time (1.80.8 billion years ago).*
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-26 08:23:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [Earth's internal heat content](https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Earth%27s_internal_heat_budget) was certainly greater in the past, and as the Earth evolved so too did the rocks to fit the respective P-T regimes. 'Back then' there were no modern plate tectonics, and there was no continental crust. The Earth was dominated by an ultramafic rock type known as [Komatiite](https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Komatiite) which is incapable of generating thick lava flows, as it's less viscous than basalt (modern oceanic crust), leaving extremely thin lava flows (down to 10 mm thick). Overall, topography would have been far more gentle, seas more shallow, and vents more common. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-26 05:51:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Just some points of possible contention relating to the dates and terminology you've used:

We have a putative 4.1 Ga fossil.

I wouldn't call it putative. Tenuous is [more fitting](http://www.smithsonianmag.com/smart-news/did-life-really-start-41-billion-years-ago-not-so-fast-180957006/?no-ist). Far better to note the oldest confirmed fossil evidence of life at [3.5 Ga](http://www.ucmp.berkeley.edu/bacteria/cyanofr.html).

If life emerged before 4.1 Ga, the amount of land may have been **confined to island arcs**...

Island arcs require plate tectonics, and while there is a good degree of debate surrounding the origin of modern plate tectonics (opposed to [drip tectonics](https://speakingofgeoscience.org/2013/04/28/when-did-plate-tectonics-begin-on-earth-and-what-came-before/)) I don't believe there is sufficient evidence to suggest modern plate tectonics 4.1 Ga. Most believe the onset of modern plate tectonics to be roughly a billion years later [~3.0 Ga](https://i.imgur.com/3Cy5I52.jpg) and younger.

If life emerged before 4.1 Ga, it was before the martian habitability period observed by Curiosity...

Mars is believed to have been habitable to life as we know it at least up to 3.7 Ga. Given our lack of extensive, high resolution evidence of Martian geology, it certainly seems unreasonable to issue a a complete timeline of Martian habitability. All we can currently say is that 3.7 Ga years ago Mars contained a habitable environment. 

We have the new Imbrium impact model of a much larger and shallow angle impactor, which should repudiate the crucial Apollo material dating of key Moon craters. And consistent with that we have the lack of expected shock fractures in zircons from the period. Late bombardment is now a theory looking for its observations.

The LHB is certainly not so easily negated, and remains a theory of serious consideration. One would likely have to refute the [Nice model](https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Nice_model) of planetary migration amongst many others... a feat not so easily achieved as you seem to have implicated. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-26 02:31:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Study: [On cold spells in North America and storminess in western Europe](http://onlinelibrary.wiley.com/doi/10.1002/2016GL069392/abstract)
___

**Abstract**:

*We discuss the dynamical and statistical links between cold extremes over eastern North America and storminess over western Europe, with a focus on the midlatitude jet stream, the North Atlantic Oscillation (NAO) and the Pacific-North American Pattern (PNA). The analysis is performed on the European Centre for Medium-Range Weather Forecasts 20th Century Reanalysis. The large-scale circulation associated with the cold spells corresponds to advection of cold air from the Arctic region into North America and to a very zonal and intense North Atlantic jet, shifted persistently south of its climatological location. These features of the Atlantic jet are conducive to destructive windstorms and intense precipitation over a large part of southern and continental Europe and the British Isles. The cold spells are preceded by a negative NAO and followed by a positive PNA; however, we interpret the associated circulation anomalies as being distinct from these standard modes of climate variability.* </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-26 02:29:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Study: [On cold spells in North America and storminess in western Europe](http://onlinelibrary.wiley.com/doi/10.1002/2016GL069392/abstract)
___

**Abstract**:

*We discuss the dynamical and statistical links between cold extremes over eastern North America and storminess over western Europe, with a focus on the midlatitude jet stream, the North Atlantic Oscillation (NAO) and the Pacific-North American Pattern (PNA). The analysis is performed on the European Centre for Medium-Range Weather Forecasts 20th Century Reanalysis. The large-scale circulation associated with the cold spells corresponds to advection of cold air from the Arctic region into North America and to a very zonal and intense North Atlantic jet, shifted persistently south of its climatological location. These features of the Atlantic jet are conducive to destructive windstorms and intense precipitation over a large part of southern and continental Europe and the British Isles. The cold spells are preceded by a negative NAO and followed by a positive PNA; however, we interpret the associated circulation anomalies as being distinct from these standard modes of climate variability.* </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-26 01:59:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Russian emissions are due [to ongoing wildfires](http://siberiantimes.com/ecology/casestudy/news/n0682-siberias-wildfires-seen-from-1-million-miles-away-even-the-tundra-is-burning/). </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-25 23:23:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Study: [The physiology and habitat of the last universal common ancestor](http://www.nature.com/articles/nmicrobiol2016116)
___

**Abstract**:

*The concept of a last universal common ancestor of all cells (LUCA, or the progenote) is central to the study of early evolution and life's origin, yet information about how and where LUCA lived is lacking. We investigated all clusters and phylogenetic trees for 6.1 million protein coding genes from sequenced prokaryotic genomes in order to reconstruct the microbial ecology of LUCA. Among 286,514 protein clusters, we identified 355 protein families (0.1%) that trace to LUCA by phylogenetic criteria. Because these proteins are not universally distributed, they can shed light on LUCA's physiology. Their functions, properties and prosthetic groups depict LUCA as anaerobic, CO2-fixing, H2-dependent with a WoodLjungdahl pathway, N2-fixing and thermophilic. LUCA's biochemistry was replete with FeS clusters and radical reaction mechanisms. Its cofactors reveal dependence upon transition metals, flavins, S-adenosyl methionine, coenzyme A, ferredoxin, molybdopterin, corrins and selenium. Its genetic code required nucleoside modifications and S-adenosyl methionine-dependent methylations. The 355 phylogenies identify clostridia and methanogens, whose modern lifestyles resemble that of LUCA, as basal among their respective domains. LUCA inhabited a geochemically active environment rich in H2, CO2 and iron. The data support the theory of an autotrophic origin of life involving the WoodLjungdahl pathway in a hydrothermal setting.* </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-25 23:15:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Study: [Armed-conflict risks enhanced by climate-related disasters in ethnically fractionalized countries](http://www.pnas.org/content/early/2016/07/20/1601611113)
___

**Significance**:

*Ethnic divides play a major role in many armed conflicts around the world and might serve as predetermined conflict lines following rapidly emerging societal tensions arising from disruptive events like natural disasters. We find evidence in global datasets that risk of armed-conflict outbreak is enhanced by climate-related disaster occurrence in ethnically fractionalized countries. Although we find no indications that environmental disasters directly trigger armed conflicts, our results imply that disasters might act as a threat multiplier in several of the worlds most conflict-prone regions.*

**Abstract**:

*Social and political tensions keep on fueling armed conflicts around the world. Although each conflict is the result of an individual context-specific mixture of interconnected factors, ethnicity appears to play a prominent and almost ubiquitous role in many of them. This overall state of affairs is likely to be exacerbated by anthropogenic climate change and in particular climate-related natural disasters. Ethnic divides might serve as predetermined conflict lines in case of rapidly emerging societal tensions arising from disruptive events like natural disasters. Here, we hypothesize that climate-related disaster occurrence enhances armed-conflict outbreak risk in ethnically fractionalized countries. Using event coincidence analysis, we test this hypothesis based on data on armed-conflict outbreaks and climate-related natural disasters for the period 19802010. Globally, we find a coincidence rate of 9% regarding armed-conflict outbreak and disaster occurrence such as heat waves or droughts. Our analysis also reveals that, during the period in question, about 23% of conflict outbreaks in ethnically highly fractionalized countries robustly coincide with climatic calamities. Although we do not report evidence that climate-related disasters act as direct triggers of armed conflicts, the disruptive nature of these events seems to play out in ethnically fractionalized societies in a particularly tragic way. This observation has important implications for future security policies as several of the worlds most conflict-prone regions, including North and Central Africa as well as Central Asia, are both exceptionally vulnerable to anthropogenic climate change and characterized by deep ethnic divides.* </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-25 23:10:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Study: [Armed-conflict risks enhanced by climate-related disasters in ethnically fractionalized countries](http://www.pnas.org/content/early/2016/07/20/1601611113)
___

**Significance**:

*Ethnic divides play a major role in many armed conflicts around the world and might serve as predetermined conflict lines following rapidly emerging societal tensions arising from disruptive events like natural disasters. We find evidence in global datasets that risk of armed-conflict outbreak is enhanced by climate-related disaster occurrence in ethnically fractionalized countries. Although we find no indications that environmental disasters directly trigger armed conflicts, our results imply that disasters might act as a threat multiplier in several of the worlds most conflict-prone regions.*

**Abstract**:

*Social and political tensions keep on fueling armed conflicts around the world. Although each conflict is the result of an individual context-specific mixture of interconnected factors, ethnicity appears to play a prominent and almost ubiquitous role in many of them. This overall state of affairs is likely to be exacerbated by anthropogenic climate change and in particular climate-related natural disasters. Ethnic divides might serve as predetermined conflict lines in case of rapidly emerging societal tensions arising from disruptive events like natural disasters. Here, we hypothesize that climate-related disaster occurrence enhances armed-conflict outbreak risk in ethnically fractionalized countries. Using event coincidence analysis, we test this hypothesis based on data on armed-conflict outbreaks and climate-related natural disasters for the period 19802010. Globally, we find a coincidence rate of 9% regarding armed-conflict outbreak and disaster occurrence such as heat waves or droughts. Our analysis also reveals that, during the period in question, about 23% of conflict outbreaks in ethnically highly fractionalized countries robustly coincide with climatic calamities. Although we do not report evidence that climate-related disasters act as direct triggers of armed conflicts, the disruptive nature of these events seems to play out in ethnically fractionalized societies in a particularly tragic way. This observation has important implications for future security policies as several of the worlds most conflict-prone regions, including North and Central Africa as well as Central Asia, are both exceptionally vulnerable to anthropogenic climate change and characterized by deep ethnic divides.* </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-25 09:20:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Study: [Flat meridional temperature gradient in the early Eocene in the subsurface rather than surface ocean](http://www.nature.com/ngeo/journal/vaop/ncurrent/full/ngeo2763.html)
___

**Abstract**:

*The early Eocene (4955 million years ago) is a time interval characterized by elevated surface temperatures and atmospheric CO2, and a flatter-than-present latitudinal surface temperature gradient. The multi-proxy-derived flat temperature gradient has been a challenge to reproduce in model simulations, especially the subtropical warmth at the high-latitude surface oceans, inferred from the archaeal lipid-based palaeothermometry, TEX86 . Here we revisit the TEX86 interpretation by analysing a global collection of multi-proxy temperature estimates from sediment cores spanning millennia to millions of years. Comparing the variability between proxy types, we demonstrate that the present TEX86 interpretation overestimates the magnitude of past climate changes on all timescales. We attribute this to an inappropriate calibration, which reflects subsurface ocean but is calibrated to the sea surface, where the latitudinal temperature gradient is steeper. Recalibrating the proxy to the temperatures of subsurface ocean, where the signal is probably formed, yields colder TEX86-temperatures and latitudinal gradient consistent with standard climate model simulations of the Eocene climate, invalidating the apparent, extremely warm polar sea surface temperatures. We conclude that there is a need to reinterpret TEX86-inferred marine temperature records in the literature, especially for reconstructions of past warm climates that rely heavily on this proxy as reflecting subsurface ocean.* </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-25 09:16:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Study: [Flat meridional temperature gradient in the early Eocene in the subsurface rather than surface ocean](http://www.nature.com/ngeo/journal/vaop/ncurrent/full/ngeo2763.html)
___

**Abstract**:

*The early Eocene (4955 million years ago) is a time interval characterized by elevated surface temperatures and atmospheric CO2, and a flatter-than-present latitudinal surface temperature gradient. The multi-proxy-derived flat temperature gradient has been a challenge to reproduce in model simulations, especially the subtropical warmth at the high-latitude surface oceans, inferred from the archaeal lipid-based palaeothermometry, TEX86 . Here we revisit the TEX86 interpretation by analysing a global collection of multi-proxy temperature estimates from sediment cores spanning millennia to millions of years. Comparing the variability between proxy types, we demonstrate that the present TEX86 interpretation overestimates the magnitude of past climate changes on all timescales. We attribute this to an inappropriate calibration, which reflects subsurface ocean but is calibrated to the sea surface, where the latitudinal temperature gradient is steeper. Recalibrating the proxy to the temperatures of subsurface ocean, where the signal is probably formed, yields colder TEX86 -temperatures and latitudinal gradient consistent with standard climate model simulations of the Eocene climate, invalidating the apparent, extremely warm polar sea surface temperatures. We conclude that there is a need to reinterpret TEX86 -inferred marine temperature records in the literature, especially for reconstructions of past warm climates that rely heavily on this proxy as reflecting subsurface ocean.* </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-25 01:58:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Have a look at my sub if you wish, /r/GlobalClimateChange. Unfortunately it's not very active, but I do try to keep the discussion - if any - to a credible level, requesting comments (when necessary) to be cited from only credible sources. 

The sub is a past time of mine, and still being constructed but hopefully it may assist you. Have a look through the sticky as well for anything that might be able to help answer a number of your questions. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-23 20:01:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> *[sigh](https://i.imgur.com/1Kq6I.gif) 

If you read the actual paper that statement is made because there remain some degree of uncertainty in *some* of the values. Given our current understanding, however, a runaway greenhouse is highly unlikely as to be realistically impossible. 

 What weve shown here is that a runaway greenhouse atmosphere that would sterilize the planet is actually possible for Earth, with the amount of sunlight it receives now, says Goldblatt. Fortunately, it would need 10 times more carbon dioxide in the atmosphere to trigger this than burning all of Earths fossil fuels  every bit of coal, oil and gas that exists - would give. 

- [Runaway greenhouse effect possible but difficult](http://communications.uvic.ca/releases/tip.php?date=26072013)

I get it, you and a number of others like your drama but get a grip on reality already and stop perpetuating bullshit like "*runaway greenhouse effect, in action...Fuck*." </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-23 08:58:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> A runaway greenhouse on Earth is realistically unlikely.

Here, we review what is known about the runaway greenhouse to answer this question, describing the various limits on outgoing radiation and how climate will evolve between these. The good news is that almost all lines of evidence lead us to believe that is unlikely to be possible, even in principle, to trigger full a runaway greenhouse by addition of non-condensible greenhouse gases such as carbon dioxide to the atmosphere. 
___

 [The runaway greenhouse: implications for future climate change, geoengineering and planetary atmospheres](http://rsta.royalsocietypublishing.org/content/370/1974/4197)

EDIT: Due to the large number of downvotes from people who have not read the actual paper or grasp what it's saying, the following may clarify:

What weve shown here is that a runaway greenhouse atmosphere that would sterilize the planet is actually possible for Earth, with the amount of sunlight it receives now, says Goldblatt. Fortunately, it would need 10 times more carbon dioxide in the atmosphere to trigger this than burning all of Earths fossil fuels  every bit of coal, oil and gas that exists - would give.  - [Author of the study](http://communications.uvic.ca/releases/tip.php?date=26072013) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-23 01:40:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> A number of studies have linked climate science denial and/or ignorance with the subject matter to poor education^[1](http://science.sciencemag.org/content/351/6274/664), political alignment^[2](http://onlinelibrary.wiley.com/doi/10.1111/polp.12122/abstract),[3](https://ejas.revues.org/10305),[4](http://drexel.edu/now/archive/2013/December/Climate-Change/),[5](http://www.sciencedirect.com/science/article/pii/S0092656616300666) and personal ideology^[6](https://www.washingtonpost.com/news/energy-environment/wp/2015/05/29/this-fascinating-chart-on-faith-and-climate-change-denial-has-been-reinforced-by-new-research/?postshare=5211432921678546),[7](http://jspp.psychopen.eu/article/view/443) 

While the study's focus is targeted at examining the potential effectiveness of climate policy^[8](http://papers.ssrn.com/sol3/papers.cfm?abstract_id=2732935), it might also be exploited in order to examine - more closely - the links between education, political alignment, and personal ideology within Canada. A cursory look at how Canadian's voted during the 2015 federal election shows a relatively strong correlation, particularly across areas of British Columbia, Alberta, Saskatchewan, and Manitoba, as seen by the following:

(1) [% Canadian's that believe the Earth is warming](https://i.imgur.com/kK24x7L.png)

(2) [2015 Federal election results](https://i.imgur.com/a2x8AwJ.png)^[9](http://www.cbc.ca/news2/interactives/results-2015/) Note: Blue are Conservatives; Red are Liberals; Orange are NDP

While the 2011 federal election certainly shows a different trend overall, a similar pattern persists across much of Alberta, Saskatchewan and Manitoba

(3) [2011 Federal election results](https://i.imgur.com/N9V3h9u.png)

It should also be noted that the authors of this study *did* incorporate many of these aspects into their model, which may explain at least some of the similarities seen above. In regard to their model the authors state the following:

"*For district models, we model the geography-level term as: ... [model equation] ... where, for each political geography, drive is the fraction of residents who report driving a car, truck or van to work, christian is the fraction of residents who report themselves as belonging to the Christian faith, industry is the fraction of residents who are employed by mining, quarrying, and oil and gas extraction industries, and convote is the fraction of votes for the Conservative
Party during the 2011 federal election. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-21 23:33:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Study: [Reconciled climate response estimates from climate models and the energy budget of Earth](http://www.nature.com/nclimate/journal/vaop/ncurrent/full/nclimate3066.html)
___

**Abstract**:

*Climate risks increase with mean global temperature, so knowledge about the amount of future global warming should better inform risk assessments for policymakers. Expected near-term warming is encapsulated by the transient climate response (TCR), formally defined as the warming following 70 years of 1% per year increases in atmospheric CO2 concentration, by which point atmospheric CO2 has doubled. Studies based on Earths historical energy budget have typically estimated lower values of TCR than climate models, suggesting that some models could overestimate future warming. However, energy-budget estimates rely on historical temperature records that are geographically incomplete and blend air temperatures over land and sea ice with water temperatures over open oceans. We show that there is no evidence that climate models overestimate TCR when their output is processed in the same way as the HadCRUT4 observation-based temperature record. Models suggest that air-temperature warming is 24% greater than observed by HadCRUT4 over 18612009 because slower-warming regions are preferentially sampled and water warms less than air. Correcting for these biases and accounting for wider uncertainties in radiative forcing based on recent evidence, we infer an observation-based best estimate for TCR of 1.66 C, with a 595% range of 1.03.3 C, consistent with the climate models considered in the IPCC 5th Assessment Report.* </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-21 23:31:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Study: [Reconciled climate response estimates from climate models and the energy budget of Earth](http://www.nature.com/nclimate/journal/vaop/ncurrent/full/nclimate3066.html)
___

**Abstract**:

Climate risks increase with mean global temperature, so knowledge about the amount of future global warming should better inform risk assessments for policymakers. Expected near-term warming is encapsulated by the transient climate response (TCR), formally defined as the warming following 70 years of 1% per year increases in atmospheric CO2 concentration, by which point atmospheric CO2 has doubled. Studies based on Earths historical energy budget have typically estimated lower values of TCR than climate models, suggesting that some models could overestimate future warming. However, energy-budget estimates rely on historical temperature records that are geographically incomplete and blend air temperatures over land and sea ice with water temperatures over open oceans. We show that there is no evidence that climate models overestimate TCR when their output is processed in the same way as the HadCRUT4 observation-based temperature record. Models suggest that air-temperature warming is 24% greater than observed by HadCRUT4 over 18612009 because slower-warming regions are preferentially sampled and water warms less than air. Correcting for these biases and accounting for wider uncertainties in radiative forcing based on recent evidence, we infer an observation-based best estimate for TCR of 1.66C, with a 595% range of 1.03.3C, consistent with the climate models considered in the IPCC 5th Assessment Report. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-21 22:03:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Study (open access): [The Distribution of Climate Change Public Opinion in Canada](http://papers.ssrn.com/sol3/papers.cfm?abstract_id=2732935)
___

**Abstract**:

Historic Canadian elections in 2015, both federally and provincially, created an opportunity for action on climate policy. While climate scientists have developed high resolution data sets on the distribution of Canadian climate risks, we still lack comparable data on the local distribution of public climate change opinions. This paper provides the first effort to estimate local climate and energy opinion variability outside the United States. Using a multi-level regression and post-stratification (MRP) approach, we estimate opinion in federal electoral districts and provinces. We demonstrate that a majority of the Canadian public consistently believes that climate change is happening. Belief in climate change's causes varies geographically, with more attributing it to human activity in urban as opposed to rural areas. Most prominently, we find majority support for carbon cap and trade policy in every province and district. By contrast, support for carbon taxation is more heterogeneous. Compared to the distribution of US climate opinions, Canadians believe climate change is happening at higher levels. This new opinion data set will support climate policy analysis and climate policy decision making at national, provincial and local levels. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-21 21:55:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Study (open access): [The Distribution of Climate Change Public Opinion in Canada](http://papers.ssrn.com/sol3/papers.cfm?abstract_id=2732935)
___

**Abstract**:

*Historic Canadian elections in 2015, both federally and provincially, created an opportunity for action on climate policy. While climate scientists have developed high resolution data sets on the distribution of Canadian climate risks, we still lack comparable data on the local distribution of public climate change opinions. This paper provides the first effort to estimate local climate and energy opinion variability outside the United States. Using a multi-level regression and post-stratification (MRP) approach, we estimate opinion in federal electoral districts and provinces. We demonstrate that a majority of the Canadian public consistently believes that climate change is happening. Belief in climate change's causes varies geographically, with more attributing it to human activity in urban as opposed to rural areas. Most prominently, we find majority support for carbon cap and trade policy in every province and district. By contrast, support for carbon taxation is more heterogeneous. Compared to the distribution of US climate opinions, Canadians believe climate change is happening at higher levels. This new opinion data set will support climate policy analysis and climate policy decision making at national, provincial and local levels.* </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-21 06:00:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Study: [Reorganization of the North Atlantic Oscillation during early Holocene deglaciation](http://www.nature.com/ngeo/journal/vaop/ncurrent/full/ngeo2767.html)
___

**Abstract**:

*The North Atlantic Oscillation is the dominant atmospheric pressure mode in the North Atlantic region and affects winter temperature and precipitation in the Mediterranean, northwest Europe, Greenland, and Asia. The index that describes the sea-level pressure difference between Iceland and the Azores is correlated with a dipole precipitation pattern over northwest Europe and northwest Africa. How the North Atlantic Oscillation will develop as the Greenland ice sheet melts is unclear. A potential past analogue is the early Holocene, during which melting ice sheets around the North Atlantic freshened surface waters, affecting the strength of the meridional overturning circulation. Here we present a Holocene rainfall record from northwest Africa based on speleothem 18O and compare it against a speleothem-based rainfall record from Europe. The two records are positively correlated during the early Holocene, followed by a shift to an anti-correlation, similar to the modern record, during the mid-Holocene. On the basis of our simulations with an Earth system model, we suggest the shift to the anti-correlation reflects a large-scale atmospheric and oceanic reorganization in response to the demise of the Laurentide ice sheet and a strong reduction of meltwater flux to the North Atlantic, pointing to a potential sensitivity of the North Atlantic Oscillation to the melting of ice sheets.* </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-21 05:55:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Study: [Reorganization of the North Atlantic Oscillation during early Holocene deglaciation](http://www.nature.com/ngeo/journal/vaop/ncurrent/full/ngeo2767.html)
___

**Abstract**:

*The North Atlantic Oscillation is the dominant atmospheric pressure mode in the North Atlantic region and affects winter temperature and precipitation in the Mediterranean, northwest Europe, Greenland, and Asia. The index that describes the sea-level pressure difference between Iceland and the Azores is correlated with a dipole precipitation pattern over northwest Europe and northwest Africa. How the North Atlantic Oscillation will develop as the Greenland ice sheet melts is unclear. A potential past analogue is the early Holocene, during which melting ice sheets around the North Atlantic freshened surface waters, affecting the strength of the meridional overturning circulation. Here we present a Holocene rainfall record from northwest Africa based on speleothem 18O and compare it against a speleothem-based rainfall record from Europe. The two records are positively correlated during the early Holocene, followed by a shift to an anti-correlation, similar to the modern record, during the mid-Holocene. On the basis of our simulations with an Earth system model, we suggest the shift to the anti-correlation reflects a large-scale atmospheric and oceanic reorganization in response to the demise of the Laurentide ice sheet and a strong reduction of meltwater flux to the North Atlantic, pointing to a potential sensitivity of the North Atlantic Oscillation to the melting of ice sheets.* </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-21 02:31:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You did. As I've pointed out elsewhere NASA's observations of current 'boreal greening' do not contradict the future projections of this study. The following is an excerpt from the abstract:

(1) climate change negatively impacted forest growth rates in the interior west and positively impacted forest growth along the western, southeastern and northeastern coasts; (2) shifting climate sensitivities offset positive effects of warming on high-latitude forests, leaving no evidence for continued boreal greening </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-20 23:09:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It appears that you are unable to comprehend what I initially stated so I'll state it another way. 

NASA's observed findings *do not* contradict the studies projections. Note the wording - observations   projections.  

This study does not refute NASA's findings that, for example, 'boreal greening' *has* occurred. It does state, however, that *continued* 'boreal greening' will *eventually* cease under shifting climate sensitivities.

It's not their model that's shit... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-20 22:44:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> According to NASA's data over the last 35 years, leaf coverage has improved substantially.

In part, this can be termed as 'Boreal greening' which the study does consider. The following is directly from the abstract:

(1) climate change negatively impacted forest growth rates in the interior west and positively impacted forest growth along the western, southeastern and northeastern coasts; (2) shifting climate sensitivities offset positive effects of warming on high-latitude forests, leaving no evidence for continued boreal greening

In other words NASA's findings *do not* contradict the findings of this study as you seem to imply. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-20 22:28:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Study: [Observed forest sensitivity to climate implies large changes in 21st century North American forest growth](http://onlinelibrary.wiley.com/doi/10.1111/ele.12650/abstract;jsessionid=E6E58569F6C2A2F0C56B94DF613DAEF2.f03t01)
___

**Abstract**:

*Predicting long-term trends in forest growth requires accurate characterisation of how the relationship between forest productivity and climatic stress varies across climatic regimes. Using a network of over two million tree-ring observations spanning North America and a space-for-time substitution methodology, we forecast climate impacts on future forest growth. We explored differing scenarios of increased water-use efficiency (WUE) due to CO2-fertilisation, which we simulated as increased effective precipitation. In our forecasts: (1) climate change negatively impacted forest growth rates in the interior west and positively impacted forest growth along the western, southeastern and northeastern coasts; (2) shifting climate sensitivities offset positive effects of warming on high-latitude forests, leaving no evidence for continued boreal greening; and (3) it took a 72% WUE enhancement to compensate for continentally averaged growth declines under RCP 8.5. Our results highlight the importance of locally adapted forest management strategies to handle regional differences in growth responses to climate change.* </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-20 20:56:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Furthermore, although the title states the studies findings apply to the atmospheric circulation around Antarctic Peninsula, it's only a small fraction of the Peninsula that has seen a cooling trend as the article clearly states:

Each of the Antarctic Peninsula measurement stations shows an overall warming trend since their measurements began, but those on the very tip of the Peninsula show an apparent cooling over the last couple of decades.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-20 20:09:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Study: [Absence of 21st century warming on Antarctic Peninsula consistent with natural variability](http://www.nature.com/nature/journal/v535/n7612/full/nature18645.html)
___

**Abstract**:

*Since the 1950s, research stations on the Antarctic Peninsula have recorded some of the largest increases in near-surface air temperature in the Southern Hemisphere. This warming has contributed to the regional retreat of glaciers, disintegration of floating ice shelves and a greening through the expansion in range of various flora. Several interlinked processes have been suggested as contributing to the warming, including stratospheric ozone depletion, local sea-ice loss, an increase in westerly winds, and changes in the strength and location of lowhigh-latitude atmospheric teleconnections. Here we use a stacked temperature record to show an absence of regional warming since the late 1990s. The annual mean temperature has decreased at a statistically significant rate, with the most rapid cooling during the Austral summer. Temperatures have decreased as a consequence of a greater frequency of cold, east-to-southeasterly winds, resulting from more cyclonic conditions in the northern Weddell Sea associated with a strengthening mid-latitude jet. These circulation changes have also increased the advection of sea ice towards the east coast of the peninsula, amplifying their effects. Our findings cover only 1% of the Antarctic continent and emphasize that decadal temperature changes in this region are not primarily associated with the drivers of global temperature change but, rather, reflect the extreme natural internal variability of the regional atmospheric circulation.* </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-20 20:06:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Study: [Absence of 21st century warming on Antarctic Peninsula consistent with natural variability](http://www.nature.com/nature/journal/v535/n7612/full/nature18645.html)
___

**Abstract**:

Since the 1950s, research stations on the Antarctic Peninsula have recorded some of the largest increases in near-surface air temperature in the Southern Hemisphere. This warming has contributed to the regional retreat of glaciers, disintegration of floating ice shelves and a greening through the expansion in range of various flora. Several interlinked processes have been suggested as contributing to the warming, including stratospheric ozone depletion, local sea-ice loss, an increase in westerly winds, and changes in the strength and location of lowhigh-latitude atmospheric teleconnections. Here we use a stacked temperature record to show an absence of regional warming since the late 1990s. The annual mean temperature has decreased at a statistically significant rate, with the most rapid cooling during the Austral summer. Temperatures have decreased as a consequence of a greater frequency of cold, east-to-southeasterly winds, resulting from more cyclonic conditions in the northern Weddell Sea associated with a strengthening mid-latitude jet. These circulation changes have also increased the advection of sea ice towards the east coast of the peninsula, amplifying their effects. Our findings cover only 1% of the Antarctic continent and emphasize that decadal temperature changes in this region are not primarily associated with the drivers of global temperature change but, rather, reflect the extreme natural internal variability of the regional atmospheric circulation. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-19 10:09:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Study (open access): [A high-resolution record of Greenland mass balance](http://onlinelibrary.wiley.com/doi/10.1002/2016GL069666/full)
___


**Abstract**:

*We map recent Greenland Ice Sheet elevation change at high spatial (5 km) and temporal (monthly) resolution using CryoSat-2 altimetry. After correcting for the impact of changing snowpack properties associated with unprecedented surface melting in 2012, we find good agreement (3 cm/yr bias) with airborne measurements. With the aid of regional climate and firn modeling, we compute high spatial and temporal resolution records of Greenland mass evolution, which correlate (R = 0.96) with monthly satellite gravimetry and reveal glacier dynamic imbalance. During 20112014, Greenland mass loss averaged 269  51 Gt/yr. Atmospherically driven losses were widespread, with surface melt variability driving large fluctuations in the annual mass deficit. Terminus regions of five dynamically thinning glaciers, which constitute less than 1% of Greenland's area, contributed more than 12% of the net ice loss. This high-resolution record demonstrates that mass deficits extending over small spatial and temporal scales have made a relatively large contribution to recent ice sheet imbalance.* </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-19 10:06:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Study (open access): [A high-resolution record of Greenland mass balance](http://onlinelibrary.wiley.com/doi/10.1002/2016GL069666/full)
___


**Abstract**:

*We map recent Greenland Ice Sheet elevation change at high spatial (5 km) and temporal (monthly) resolution using CryoSat-2 altimetry. After correcting for the impact of changing snowpack properties associated with unprecedented surface melting in 2012, we find good agreement (3cm/yr bias) with airborne measurements. With the aid of regional climate and firn modeling, we compute high spatial and temporal resolution records of Greenland mass evolution, which correlate (R=0.96) with monthly satellite gravimetry and reveal glacier dynamic imbalance. During 20112014, Greenland mass loss averaged 26951Gt/yr. Atmospherically driven losses were widespread, with surface melt variability driving large fluctuations in the annual mass deficit. Terminus regions of five dynamically thinning glaciers, which constitute less than 1% of Greenland's area, contributed more than 12% of the net ice loss. This high-resolution record demonstrates that mass deficits extending over small spatial and temporal scales have made a relatively large contribution to recent ice sheet imbalance.* </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-19 09:52:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> https://twitter.com/JBElsner/status/753997676535046144 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-19 09:51:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Study: [Human influence on tropical cyclone intensity](http://science.sciencemag.org/content/353/6296/242)
___

**Abstract**:

*Recent assessments agree that tropical cyclone intensity should increase as the climate warms. Less agreement exists on the detection of recent historical trends in tropical cyclone intensity. We interpret future and recent historical trends by using the theory of potential intensity, which predicts the maximum intensity achievable by a tropical cyclone in a given local environment. Although greenhouse gasdriven warming increases potential intensity, climate model simulations suggest that aerosol cooling has largely canceled that effect over the historical record. Large natural variability complicates analysis of trends, as do poleward shifts in the latitude of maximum intensity. In the absence of strong reductions in greenhouse gas emissions, future greenhouse gas forcing of potential intensity will increasingly dominate over aerosol forcing, leading to substantially larger increases in tropical cyclone intensities.* </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-19 09:39:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It does, as is provided at the bottom of the article:

https://archinte.jamanetwork.com/article.aspx?articleid=2534153 which is new (July 18 2016) and peer-reviewed: https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/JAMA_Internal_Medicine </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-19 04:41:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Study (open access): [Association Between Unconventional Natural Gas Development in the Marcellus Shale and Asthma Exacerbations](https://archinte.jamanetwork.com/article.aspx?articleid=2534153) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-19 02:40:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> **Abstract**:

*Continuous measurements of atmospheric methane (CH4) mole fractions measured by NOAA's Global Greenhouse Gas Reference Network in Barrow, AK (BRW), show strong enhancements above background values when winds come from the land sector from July to December from 1986 to 2015, indicating that emissions from arctic tundra continue through autumn and into early winter. Twenty-nine years of measurements show little change in seasonal mean land sector CH4 enhancements, despite an increase in annual mean temperatures of 1.20.8C/decade (2). The record does reveal small increases in CH4 enhancements in November and December after 2010 due to increased late-season emissions. The lack of significant long-term trends suggests that more complex biogeochemical processes are counteracting the observed short-term (monthly) temperature sensitivity of 5.03.6ppb CH4/C. Our results suggest that even the observed short-term temperature sensitivity from the Arctic will have little impact on the global atmospheric CH4 budget in the long term if future trajectories evolve with the same temperature sensitivity.* </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-19 01:05:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [No significant increase in long-term CH4 emissions on North Slope of Alaska despite significant increase in air temperature](http://onlinelibrary.wiley.com/doi/10.1002/2016GL069292/abstract) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-19 00:51:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Study: [The tropical Pacific as a key pacemaker of the variable rates of global warming](http://www.nature.com/ngeo/journal/vaop/ncurrent/full/ngeo2770.html)
___

**Abstract**:

*Global mean surface temperature change over the past 120 years resembles a rising staircase: the overall warming trend was interrupted by the mid-twentieth-century big hiatus and the warming slowdown since about 1998. The Interdecadal Pacific Oscillation has been implicated in modulations of global mean surface temperatures but which part of the mode drives the variability in warming rates is unclear. Here we present a successful simulation of the global warming staircase since 1900 with a global oceanatmosphere coupled model where tropical Pacific sea surface temperatures are forced to follow the observed evolution. Without prescribed tropical Pacific variability, the same model, on average, produces a continual warming trend that accelerates after the 1960s. We identify four events where the tropical Pacific decadal cooling markedly slowed down the warming trend. Matching the observed spatial and seasonal fingerprints we identify the tropical Pacific as a key pacemaker of the warming staircase, with radiative forcing driving the overall warming trend. Specifically, tropical Pacific variability amplifies the first warming epoch of the 1910s1940s and determines the timing when the big hiatus starts and ends. Our method of removing internal variability from the observed record can be used for real-time monitoring of anthropogenic warming.* </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-15 22:42:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Study (pdf): [The increasing intensity of the strongest tropical
cyclones](http://myweb.fsu.edu/jelsner/PDF/Research/ElsnerKossinJagger2008.pdf)
___

**Abstract**:

*Atlantic tropical cyclones are getting stronger on average, with a 30-year trend that has been related to an increase in ocean temperatures over the Atlantic Ocean and elsewhere. Over the rest of the tropics, however, possible trends in tropical cyclone intensity are less obvious, owing to the unreliability and incompleteness of the observational record and to a restricted focus, in previous trend analyses, on changes in average intensity. Here we overcome these two limitations by examining trends in the upper quantiles of per-cyclone maximum wind speeds (that is, the maximum intensities that cyclones achieve during their lifetimes), estimated from homogeneous data derived from an archive of satellite records. We find significant upward trends for wind speed quantiles above the 70th percentile, with trends as high as 0.3 plus/minus 0.09 ms^-1 yr^-1 (s.e.) for the strongest cyclones. We note separate upward trends in the estimated lifetime-maximum wind speeds of the very strongest tropical cyclones (99th percentile) over each ocean basin, with the largest increase at this quantile occurring over the North Atlantic, although not all basins show statistically significant increases. Our results are qualitatively consistent with the hypothesis that as the seas warm, the ocean has more energy to convert to tropical cyclone wind.* </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-15 21:03:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Study (open access): [Global climate change driven by soot at the K-Pg boundary as the cause of the mass extinction](http://www.nature.com/articles/srep28427)
___

**Abstract**:

The mass extinction of life 66 million years ago at the Cretaceous/Paleogene boundary, marked by the extinctions of dinosaurs and shallow marine organisms, is important because it led to the macroevolution of mammals and appearance of humans. The current hypothesis for the extinction is that an asteroid impact in present-day Mexico formed condensed aerosols in the stratosphere, which caused the cessation of photosynthesis and global near-freezing conditions. Here, we show that the stratospheric aerosols did not induce darkness that resulted in milder cooling than previously thought. We propose a new hypothesis that latitude-dependent climate changes caused by massive stratospheric soot explain the known mortality and survival on land and in oceans at the Cretaceous/Paleogene boundary. The stratospheric soot was ejected from the oil-rich area by the asteroid impact and was spread globally. The soot aerosols caused sufficiently colder climates at midhigh latitudes and drought with milder cooling at low latitudes on land, in addition to causing limited cessation of photosynthesis in global oceans within a few months to two years after the impact, followed by surface-water cooling in global oceans in a few years. The rapid climate change induced terrestrial extinctions followed by marine extinctions over several years. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-15 21:00:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Study (open access): [Global climate change driven by soot at the K-Pg boundary as the cause of the mass extinction](http://www.nature.com/articles/srep28427)
___

**Abstract**:

The mass extinction of life 66 million years ago at the Cretaceous/Paleogene boundary, marked by the extinctions of dinosaurs and shallow marine organisms, is important because it led to the macroevolution of mammals and appearance of humans. The current hypothesis for the extinction is that an asteroid impact in present-day Mexico formed condensed aerosols in the stratosphere, which caused the cessation of photosynthesis and global near-freezing conditions. Here, we show that the stratospheric aerosols did not induce darkness that resulted in milder cooling than previously thought. We propose a new hypothesis that latitude-dependent climate changes caused by massive stratospheric soot explain the known mortality and survival on land and in oceans at the Cretaceous/Paleogene boundary. The stratospheric soot was ejected from the oil-rich area by the asteroid impact and was spread globally. The soot aerosols caused sufficiently colder climates at midhigh latitudes and drought with milder cooling at low latitudes on land, in addition to causing limited cessation of photosynthesis in global oceans within a few months to two years after the impact, followed by surface-water cooling in global oceans in a few years. The rapid climate change induced terrestrial extinctions followed by marine extinctions over several years. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-15 19:45:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Odd. At the time of posting I had full access and read the paper at length... it appears you are correct though. I'll see if I can find it online through one of the author's websites. Thank you for the notification.

EDIT: Full access provided through author's tweet: https://twitter.com/alessio_r_/status/753285937438814208 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-14 08:30:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hi /u/ILikeNeurons, your submission has been removed as the paper has already been submitted: https://redd.it/4scuzr

Please feel free to comment and share your additional article in the thread shared above. 

Thank you, and the /r/GlobalClimateChange community looks forward to your continued contributions. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-13 16:57:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Study (open access): [The discovery of the Amazonian tree flora with an updated checklist of all known tree taxa](http://www.nature.com/articles/srep29549)
___

**Abstract**:

*Amazonia is the most biodiverse rainforest on Earth, and the debate over how many tree species grow there remains contentious. Here we provide a checklist of all tree species collected to date, and describe spatial and temporal trends in data accumulation. We report 530,025 unique collections of trees in Amazonia, dating between 1707 and 2015, for a total of 11,676 species in 1225 genera and 140 families. These figures support recent estimates of 16,000 total Amazonian tree species based on ecological plot data from the Amazonian Tree Diversity Network. Botanical collection in Amazonia is characterized by three major peaks, centred around 1840, 1920, and 1980, which are associated with flora projects and the establishment of inventory plots. Most collections were made in the 20th century. The number of collections has increased exponentially, but shows a slowdown in the last two decades. We find that a species range size is a better predictor of the number of times it has been collected than the species estimated basin-wide population size. Finding, describing, and documenting the distribution of the remaining species will require coordinated efforts at under-collected sites.* </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-13 09:34:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Study: [Intensification and poleward shift of subtropical western boundary currents in a warming climate](http://onlinelibrary.wiley.com/doi/10.1002/2015JC011513/abstract)
___

**Abstract**:

*A significant increase in sea surface temperature (SST) is observed over the mid-latitude western boundary currents (WBCs) during the past century. However, the mechanism for this phenomenon remains poorly understood due to limited observations. In the present paper, several coupled parameters (i.e., sea surface temperature (SST), ocean surface heat fluxes, ocean water velocity, ocean surface winds and sea level pressure (SLP)) are analyzed to identify the dynamic changes of the WBCs. Three types of independent data sets are used, including reanalysis products, satellite-blended observations and climate model outputs from the fifth phase of the Climate Model Intercomparison Project (CMIP5). Based on these broad ranges of data, we find that the WBCs (except the Gulf Stream) are intensifying and shifting toward the poles as long-term effects of global warming. An intensification and poleward shift of near-surface ocean winds, attributed to positive annular mode-like trends, are proposed to be the forcing of such dynamic changes. In contrast to the other WBCs, the Gulf Stream is expected to be weaker under global warming, which is most likely related to a weakening of the Atlantic Meridional Overturning Circulation (AMOC). However, we also notice that the natural variations of WBCs might conceal the long-term effect of global warming in the available observational data sets, especially over the Northern Hemisphere. Therefore, long-term observations or proxy data are necessary to further evaluate the dynamics of the WBCs.* </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-12 16:34:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You wouldn't believe the amount of nonsense I go through at times watching submissions being downvoted to oblivion and lambasted by climate science deniers.

For example, one submission had a total of 76 votes and landed a net total of a mere 12 upvotes. The comment section was a mess of climate science denial arguments. I deleted the submission in hopes of better results upon resubmitting the article... it did fair slightly better; however, it was still disappointing: 40 total votes resulting in a mere 8 net upvotes. Perhaps I hold the public, specifically those contributing to subs such as /r/science, in too high a regard, but I truly believe that the example above is not a result of their actions, but rather a result of astroturfing (and the like) by ever increasing funding from the right. Unfortunately, it's not just a one time occurrence and happens more often than not.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-12 16:15:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> See: https://news.utexas.edu/2016/07/05/california-droughts-caused-mainly-by-changes-in-wind </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-12 09:52:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Study (open access): [Tipping elements and climate-economic shocks: Pathways toward integrated assessment](http://onlinelibrary.wiley.com/doi/10.1002/2016EF000362/abstract?campaign=wlytk-41855.5282060185)
___

**Abstract**:

*The literature on the costs of climate change often draws a link between climatic tipping points and large economic shocks, frequently called catastrophes. The phrase tipping points in this context can be misleading. In popular and social scientific discourse, tipping points involve abrupt state changes. For some climatic tipping points, the commitment to a state change may occur abruptly, but the change itself may be rate-limited and take centuries or longer to realize. Additionally, the connection between climatic tipping points and economic losses is tenuous, though emerging empirical and process-model-based tools provide pathways for investigating it. We propose terminology to clarify the distinction between tipping points in the popular sense, the critical thresholds exhibited by climatic and social tipping elements, and economic shocks. The last may be associated with tipping elements, gradual climate change, or non-climatic triggers. We illustrate our proposed distinctions by surveying the literature on climatic tipping elements, climatically sensitive social tipping elements, and climate-economic shocks, and we propose a research agenda to advance the integrated assessment of all three.* </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-11 21:56:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Study: [Evidence for climate change in the satellite cloud record](http://www.nature.com/nature/journal/vaop/ncurrent/full/nature18273.html)
___

**Abstract**:

*Clouds substantially affect Earths energy budget by reflecting solar radiation back to space and by restricting emission of thermal radiation to space1. They are perhaps the largest uncertainty in our understanding of climate change, owing to disagreement among climate models and observational datasets over what cloud changes have occurred during recent decades and will occur in response to global warming. This is because observational systems originally designed for monitoring weather have lacked sufficient stability to detect cloud changes reliably over decades unless they have been corrected to remove artefacts. Here we show that several independent, empirically corrected satellite records exhibit large-scale patterns of cloud change between the 1980s and the 2000s that are similar to those produced by model simulations of climate with recent historical external radiative forcing. Observed and simulated cloud change patterns are consistent with poleward retreat of mid-latitude storm tracks, expansion of subtropical dry zones, and increasing height of the highest cloud tops at all latitudes. The primary drivers of these cloud changes appear to be increasing greenhouse gas concentrations and a recovery from volcanic radiative cooling. These results indicate that the cloud changes most consistently predicted by global climate models are currently occurring in nature.* </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-11 21:47:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Study: [Evidence for climate change in the satellite cloud record](http://www.nature.com/nature/journal/vaop/ncurrent/full/nature18273.html)
___

**Abstract**:

*Clouds substantially affect Earths energy budget by reflecting solar radiation back to space and by restricting emission of thermal radiation to space1. They are perhaps the largest uncertainty in our understanding of climate change, owing to disagreement among climate models and observational datasets over what cloud changes have occurred during recent decades and will occur in response to global warming. This is because observational systems originally designed for monitoring weather have lacked sufficient stability to detect cloud changes reliably over decades unless they have been corrected to remove artefacts. Here we show that several independent, empirically corrected satellite records exhibit large-scale patterns of cloud change between the 1980s and the 2000s that are similar to those produced by model simulations of climate with recent historical external radiative forcing. Observed and simulated cloud change patterns are consistent with poleward retreat of mid-latitude storm tracks, expansion of subtropical dry zones, and increasing height of the highest cloud tops at all latitudes. The primary drivers of these cloud changes appear to be increasing greenhouse gas concentrations and a recovery from volcanic radiative cooling. These results indicate that the cloud changes most consistently predicted by global climate models are currently occurring in nature.* </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-11 20:35:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yes, it was a Princeton study iirc... a short summary can be found here: https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=5tu32CCA_Ig

If you're interested in a detailed and quite focused historical review of how the US went from democracy to oligarchy I would recommend Jane Mayer's, "[Dark Money: The Hidden History of the Billionaires Behind the Rise of the Radical Right](https://www.amazon.ca/Dark-Money-History-Billionaires-Radical/dp/0385535597)" </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-11 09:25:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It absolutely is. Spreading misinformation serves no one, and only serves to promote false ideals. If you want an educated public showing that the acceptance of misinformation is not to be tolerated is encouraged. 

Here are but [a few of the people, and organizations](http://drexel.edu/now/archive/2013/December/Climate-Change/) that willfully spread misinformation. If you think the spread of this misinformation hasn't damaged the general populations outlook with regard to climate science you're turning a blind eye to a very serious issue. 

I would also note that the incorrect statement regarding '*the 1970's iceage fear*' is just one example of a frequently touted claim by climate science denialists. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-09 19:33:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Guessing you downvoted me then...

I did, for promoting misinformation.

I'm not a an [sic] idiot...

No one said you are an idiot.

I'm just saying this article is garbage.

I strongly disagree, the article is well written and reports the findings of the study quite clearly. I fail to see how anything has been 'cheery [sic] picked.' </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-09 18:57:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> /r/climateskeptics is leaking again. 

- [Why would anyone believe a climate science denialist?]( https://www.reddit.com/r/climateskeptics/search?q=author%3A%27butch123%27 restrict_sr=on sort=new feature=legacy_search)

This is a garage study as it relies on Computer models that are designed to show alarming results.

*smh -- /r/conspiracy  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-09 16:31:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Nobody remembers the 1970's iceage fear!?

No, because that's a myth all to regularly promoted by climate science denialists:

- (open access) [The Myth of the 1970s Global Cooling Scientific Consensus](http://journals.ametsoc.org/doi/abs/10.1175/2008BAMS2370.1)

Further more [sic] the mini ice age they describe in the late 17th early 18th century is believed to caused by volcanic origins. 

Increased volcanism is but one of multiple proposed causes that include the reversal of the North Atlantic Oscillation (NAO), and variability in solar output which include the Sprer and Maunder Minimum. - [Little Ice Age](https://www.britannica.com/science/Little-Ice-Age) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-09 15:09:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That is utterly and blatantly false. Excuse me for a moment while I rifle through my comment history. It's so frequently brought up I tend to just copy and paste from previous comments...

Copy pasta from previous related comments:

Just to clarify some terminology, ice ages are periods of time when ice is present at the poles. Glacial periods are times within an ice age when the net global mass of ice increases, glacial advances. Interglacial periods are times of net global mass loss of ice or glacial retreat (then there are stadials, and interstadials, etc.). Earth entered the current ice age, which is also called "the Ice Age", ~2.58Ma (million years ago) and marks the beginning of the  Pleistocene epoch. We are still currently within an ice age... "the Ice Age" ;however, we are within an interglacial period that began ~11.7ka (thousand years ago) and marks the start of the Holocene epoch. 

Accounting for natural cycles, ignoring human emissions and other human disturbances, it has been shown that the Earth would likely enter the next glacial period in ~50ka^[1](http://www.nature.com/nature/journal/v529/n7585/full/nature16494.html), ^[2](https://www.pik-potsdam.de/news/press-releases/human-made-climate-change-suppresses-the-next-ice-age) . Several studies in agreement with one another have concluded that under present configurations atmospheric CO2 concentrations are required to be no more than ~240 to 280ppm to trigger the onset of another glacial period ^[3](http://onlinelibrary.wiley.com/doi/10.1029/2004GC000891/abstract), ^[4](http://www.bbc.com/news/science-environment-16439807) . However, as human emissions are above [400ppm](https://scripps.ucsd.edu/programs/keelingcurve/) and [rising](http://www.nature.com/nclimate/journal/v4/n3/fig_tab/nclimate2148_F1.html) as was noted in the first reference, the onset of the next glacial period has already likely been postponed by ~50ka. Should humans manage to burn essentially all of the known fossil fuel reserves it has been suggested that the onset of the next glacial period would not be for another 500ka^[5](http://onlinelibrary.wiley.com/doi/10.1029/2004GC000891/abstract) .

In summary, the Earth is on the cusp of entering a cooling phase, however, human emissions have offset this for a, relatively, long time.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-09 14:29:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Study (open access): [Attributing human mortality during extreme heat waves to anthropogenic climate change](https://iopscience.iop.org/article/10.1088/1748-9326/11/7/074006)
___

**Abstract**:

*It has been argued that climate change is the biggest global health threat of the 21st century. The extreme high temperatures of the summer of 2003 were associated with up to seventy thousand excess deaths across Europe. Previous studies have attributed the meteorological event to the human influence on climate, or examined the role of heat waves on human health. Here, for the first time, we explicitly quantify the role of human activity on climate and heat-related mortality in an event attribution framework, analysing both the Europe-wide temperature response in 2003, and localised responses over London and Paris. Using publicly-donated computing, we perform many thousands of climate simulations of a high-resolution regional climate model. This allows generation of a comprehensive statistical description of the 2003 event and the role of human influence within it, using the results as input to a health impact assessment model of human mortality. We find large-scale dynamical modes of atmospheric variability remain largely unchanged under anthropogenic climate change, and hence the direct thermodynamical response is mainly responsible for the increased mortality. In summer 2003, anthropogenic climate change increased the risk of heat-related mortality in Central Paris by ~70% and by ~20% in London, which experienced lower extreme heat. Out of the estimated ~315 and ~735 summer deaths attributed to the heatwave event in Greater London and Central Paris, respectively, 64 (3) deaths were attributable to anthropogenic climate change in London, and 506 (51) in Paris. Such an ability to robustly attribute specific damages to anthropogenic drivers of increased extreme heat can inform societal responses to, and responsibilities for, climate change.* </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-09 14:26:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Study (open access): [Attributing human mortality during extreme heat waves to anthropogenic climate change](https://iopscience.iop.org/article/10.1088/1748-9326/11/7/074006)
___

**Abstract**:

*It has been argued that climate change is the biggest global health threat of the 21st century. The extreme high temperatures of the summer of 2003 were associated with up to seventy thousand excess deaths across Europe. Previous studies have attributed the meteorological event to the human influence on climate, or examined the role of heat waves on human health. Here, for the first time, we explicitly quantify the role of human activity on climate and heat-related mortality in an event attribution framework, analysing both the Europe-wide temperature response in 2003, and localised responses over London and Paris. Using publicly-donated computing, we perform many thousands of climate simulations of a high-resolution regional climate model. This allows generation of a comprehensive statistical description of the 2003 event and the role of human influence within it, using the results as input to a health impact assessment model of human mortality. We find large-scale dynamical modes of atmospheric variability remain largely unchanged under anthropogenic climate change, and hence the direct thermodynamical response is mainly responsible for the increased mortality. In summer 2003, anthropogenic climate change increased the risk of heat-related mortality in Central Paris by ~70% and by ~20% in London, which experienced lower extreme heat. Out of the estimated ~315 and ~735 summer deaths attributed to the heatwave event in Greater London and Central Paris, respectively, 64 (3) deaths were attributable to anthropogenic climate change in London, and 506 (51) in Paris. Such an ability to robustly attribute specific damages to anthropogenic drivers of increased extreme heat can inform societal responses to, and responsibilities for, climate change.* </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-09 14:25:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Citation needed </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-09 06:27:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Regardless of how bad we heat the planet, it will automatically reverse itself and become an ice age again at some point in the next few hundred years. There is literally nothing humans can do to stop the coming ice age. 

That is utterly and blatantly false. Excuse me for a moment while I rifle through my comment history. It's so frequently brought up I tend to just copy and paste from previous comments...

Copy pasta from previous related comments:

Just to clarify some terminology, ice ages are periods of time when ice is present at the poles. Glacial periods are times within an ice age when the net global mass of ice increases, glacial advances. Interglacial periods are times of net global mass loss of ice or glacial retreat (then there are stadials, and interstadials, etc.). Earth entered the current ice age, which is also called "the Ice Age", ~2.58Ma (million years ago) and marks the beginning of the  Pleistocene epoch. We are still currently within an ice age... "the Ice Age" ;however, we are within an interglacial period that began ~11.7ka (thousand years ago) and marks the start of the Holocene epoch. 

Accounting for natural cycles, ignoring human emissions and other human disturbances, it has been shown that the Earth would likely enter the next glacial period in ~50ka^[1](http://www.nature.com/nature/journal/v529/n7585/full/nature16494.html), ^[2](https://www.pik-potsdam.de/news/press-releases/human-made-climate-change-suppresses-the-next-ice-age) . Several studies in agreement with one another have concluded that under present configurations atmospheric CO2 concentrations are required to be no more than ~240 to 280ppm to trigger the onset of another glacial period ^[3](http://onlinelibrary.wiley.com/doi/10.1029/2004GC000891/abstract), ^[4](http://www.bbc.com/news/science-environment-16439807) . However, as human emissions are above [400ppm](https://scripps.ucsd.edu/programs/keelingcurve/) and [rising](http://www.nature.com/nclimate/journal/v4/n3/fig_tab/nclimate2148_F1.html) as was noted in the first reference, the onset of the next glacial period has already likely been postponed by ~50ka. Should humans manage to burn essentially all of the known fossil fuel reserves it has been suggested that the onset of the next glacial period would not be for another 500ka^[5](http://onlinelibrary.wiley.com/doi/10.1029/2004GC000891/abstract) .

In summary, the Earth is on the cusp of entering a cooling phase, however, human emissions have offset this for a, relatively, long time.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-09 04:35:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> How is this a review article? 

... Here, for the first time, we explicitly quantify the role of human activity on climate and heat-related mortality in an event attribution framework, analysing both the Europe-wide temperature response in 2003, and localised responses over London and Paris. Using publicly-donated computing, we perform many thousands of climate simulations of a high-resolution regional climate model.

That's not considered new research, or new data analysis? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-09 03:29:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Lomborg receives [substantial funding](http://www.desmogblog.com/2014/06/25/millions-behind-bjorn-lomborg-copenhagen-consensus-center) from organizations known for promoting [climate science denial](http://drexel.edu/now/archive/2013/December/Climate-Change/). If that doesn't give you reason enough to question the blatant spin he puts on the studies he cites I don't know what else would. 

Obviously I don't have the time to go through, in detail, all of [Keatinge's works](https://www.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/pubmed/?term=Keatinge%20WR%5BAuthor%5D cauthor=true cauthor_uid=11209660) (and I suspect nor do you, nor have you) so I can't properly state which of Keatinge's works are flawed, or incorrectly interpreted - if any; however, I suspect that Lomborg has spun them to fit his narrative as he is so often known to do... as any think tank is known to do when funded by organizations who actively promote climate science denial. 

A less controversial outlook is provided by the IPCC as follows:

...there still is insufficient European information to quantify this trade-off between heat-associated losses and gains associated with milder winters. Furthermore, the balance will vary by location and adaptive response. - [source](http://www.ipcc.ch/ipccreports/sres/regional/117.htm)

Keep in mind that Lomborg is comparing total seasonal deaths (Winter, ~3 months) to those incurred by extreme weather events (Heatwaves, ~2-3 days to weeks). A more reasonable, less misleading, comparison would have simply been annual projected deaths under ever increasing globally averaged temperatures. I'm quite positive that [the outlook would change](http://www.iflscience.com/environment/climate-change-could-make-middle-east-uninhabitable-no-matter-what-happens/). </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-09 01:42:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You forgot to cite your source article, which is "[Global warming will save millions of lives](http://www.telegraph.co.uk/comment/personal-view/4981028/Global-warming-will-save-millions-of-lives.html)" written by climate change denialist [Bjorn Lomborg](http://www.realclimate.org/index.php/archives/2015/08/bjorn-lomborg-just-a-scientist-with-a-different-opinion/). </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-09 01:30:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Study (open access): [Attributing human mortality during extreme heat waves to anthropogenic climate change](https://iopscience.iop.org/article/10.1088/1748-9326/11/7/074006)
___

**Abstract**:

*It has been argued that climate change is the biggest global health threat of the 21st century. The extreme high temperatures of the summer of 2003 were associated with up to seventy thousand excess deaths across Europe. Previous studies have attributed the meteorological event to the human influence on climate, or examined the role of heat waves on human health. Here, for the first time, we explicitly quantify the role of human activity on climate and heat-related mortality in an event attribution framework, analysing both the Europe-wide temperature response in 2003, and localised responses over London and Paris. Using publicly-donated computing, we perform many thousands of climate simulations of a high-resolution regional climate model. This allows generation of a comprehensive statistical description of the 2003 event and the role of human influence within it, using the results as input to a health impact assessment model of human mortality. We find large-scale dynamical modes of atmospheric variability remain largely unchanged under anthropogenic climate change, and hence the direct thermodynamical response is mainly responsible for the increased mortality. In summer 2003, anthropogenic climate change increased the risk of heat-related mortality in Central Paris by ~70% and by ~20% in London, which experienced lower extreme heat. Out of the estimated ~315 and ~735 summer deaths attributed to the heatwave event in Greater London and Central Paris, respectively, 64 (3) deaths were attributable to anthropogenic climate change in London, and 506 (51) in Paris. Such an ability to robustly attribute specific damages to anthropogenic drivers of increased extreme heat can inform societal responses to, and responsibilities for, climate change.* </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-09 01:28:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Study (open access): [Attributing human mortality during extreme heat waves to anthropogenic climate change](https://iopscience.iop.org/article/10.1088/1748-9326/11/7/074006)
___

**Abstract**:

*It has been argued that climate change is the biggest global health threat of the 21st century. The extreme high temperatures of the summer of 2003 were associated with up to seventy thousand excess deaths across Europe. Previous studies have attributed the meteorological event to the human influence on climate, or examined the role of heat waves on human health. Here, for the first time, we explicitly quantify the role of human activity on climate and heat-related mortality in an event attribution framework, analysing both the Europe-wide temperature response in 2003, and localised responses over London and Paris. Using publicly-donated computing, we perform many thousands of climate simulations of a high-resolution regional climate model. This allows generation of a comprehensive statistical description of the 2003 event and the role of human influence within it, using the results as input to a health impact assessment model of human mortality. We find large-scale dynamical modes of atmospheric variability remain largely unchanged under anthropogenic climate change, and hence the direct thermodynamical response is mainly responsible for the increased mortality. In summer 2003, anthropogenic climate change increased the risk of heat-related mortality in Central Paris by ~70% and by ~20% in London, which experienced lower extreme heat. Out of the estimated ~315 and ~735 summer deaths attributed to the heatwave event in Greater London and Central Paris, respectively, 64 (3) deaths were attributable to anthropogenic climate change in London, and 506 (51) in Paris. Such an ability to robustly attribute specific damages to anthropogenic drivers of increased extreme heat can inform societal responses to, and responsibilities for, climate change.* </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-08 11:35:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Study (open access): [Geologic context of recurring slope lineae in Melas and Coprates Chasmata, Mars](http://onlinelibrary.wiley.com/doi/10.1002/2015JE004991/full)
___

**Abstract**:

One of the major Mars discoveries of recent years is the existence of recurring slope lineae (RSL), which suggests that liquid water occurs on or near the surface of Mars today. These dark and narrow features emerge from steep, rocky exposures and incrementally grow, fade, and reform on a seasonal basis and are detected in images from the High Resolution Imaging Science Experiment camera. RSL are known to occur at scattered midlatitude and equatorial sites with little spatial connection to one another. One major exception is the steep, low-albedo slopes of Melas and Coprates Chasmata, in Valles Marineris where RSL are detected among diverse geologic surfaces (e.g., bedrock and talus) and landforms (e.g., inselbergs and landslides). New images show topographic changes including sediment deposition on active RSL slopes. Midwall locations in Coprates and Melas appear to have more areally extensively abundant RSL and related fans as compared with other RSL sites found on Mars. Water budget estimates for regional RSL are on the order of 10^5 to 10^6  m^3 of fluid, for depths of 10 to 100 mm, and suggest that a significant amount of near-surface water might be present. Many RSL are concentrated near local topographic highs, such as ridge crests or peaks, which is challenging to explain via groundwater or ice without a recharge mechanism. Collectively, results provide additional support for the notion that significant amounts of near-surface water can be found on Mars today and suggest that a widespread mechanism, possibly related to the atmosphere, is recharging RSL sources.* </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-08 11:09:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Study (open access): [Fukushima DaiichiDerived Radionuclides in the Ocean: Transport, Fate, and Impacts](http://www.annualreviews.org/doi/abs/10.1146/annurev-marine-010816-060733)
___

**Abstract**:

*The events that followed the Tohoku earthquake and tsunami on March 11, 2011, included the loss of power and overheating at the Fukushima Daiichi nuclear power plants, which led to extensive releases of radioactive gases, volatiles, and liquids, particularly to the coastal ocean. The fate of these radionuclides depends in large part on their oceanic geochemistry, physical processes, and biological uptake. Whereas radioactivity on land can be resampled and its distribution mapped, releases to the marine environment are harder to characterize owing to variability in ocean currents and the general challenges of sampling at sea. Five years later, it is appropriate to review what happened in terms of the sources, transport, and fate of these radionuclides in the ocean. In addition to the oceanic behavior of these contaminants, this review considers the potential health effects and societal impacts.* </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-07 19:10:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Study: [Impacts of the 20152016 El Nio on the California Current System: Early assessment and comparison to past events](http://onlinelibrary.wiley.com/doi/10.1002/2016GL069716/full)
___

**Abstract**:

*The 20152016 El Nio is by some measures one of the strongest on record, comparable to the 19821983 and 19971998 events that triggered widespread ecosystem change in the northeast Pacific. Here we describe impacts of the 20152016 El Nio on the California Current System (CCS) and place them in historical context using a regional ocean model and underwater glider observations. Impacts on the physical state of the CCS are weaker than expected based on tropical sea surface temperature anomalies; temperature and density fields reflect persistence of multiyear anomalies more than El Nio. While we anticipate El Nio-related impacts on spring/summer 2016 productivity to be similarly weak, their combination with preexisting anomalous conditions likely means continued low phytoplankton biomass. This study highlights the need for regional metrics of El Nio's effects and demonstrates the potential to assess these effects before the upwelling season, when altered ecosystem functioning is most apparent.* </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-07 10:54:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Study: [Impacts of the 20152016 El Nio on the California Current System: Early assessment and comparison to past events](http://onlinelibrary.wiley.com/doi/10.1002/2016GL069716/full)
___

**Abstract**:

*The 20152016 El Nio is by some measures one of the strongest on record, comparable to the 19821983 and 19971998 events that triggered widespread ecosystem change in the northeast Pacific. Here we describe impacts of the 20152016 El Nio on the California Current System (CCS) and place them in historical context using a regional ocean model and underwater glider observations. Impacts on the physical state of the CCS are weaker than expected based on tropical sea surface temperature anomalies; temperature and density fields reflect persistence of multiyear anomalies more than El Nio. While we anticipate El Nio-related impacts on spring/summer 2016 productivity to be similarly weak, their combination with preexisting anomalous conditions likely means continued low phytoplankton biomass. This study highlights the need for regional metrics of El Nio's effects and demonstrates the potential to assess these effects before the upwelling season, when altered ecosystem functioning is most apparent.* </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-07 10:42:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Study (open access): [Flux transfer event observation at Saturn's dayside magnetopause by the Cassini spacecraft](http://onlinelibrary.wiley.com/doi/10.1002/2016GL069260/full)

**Abstract**:

*We present the first observation of a flux rope at Saturn's dayside magnetopause. This is an important result because it shows that the Saturnian magnetopause is conducive to multiple X-line reconnection and flux rope generation. Minimum variance analysis shows that the magnetic signature is consistent with a flux rope. The magnetic observations were well fitted to a constant- force-free flux rope model. The radius and magnetic flux content of the rope are estimated to be 46008300 km and 0.20.8 MWb, respectively. Cassini also observed five traveling compression regions (remote signatures of flux ropes), in the adjacent magnetosphere. The magnetic flux content is compared to other estimates of flux opening via reconnection at Saturn.* </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-06 21:18:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Study: [Role of ocean evaporation in California droughts and floods](http://onlinelibrary.wiley.com/doi/10.1002/2016GL069386/full)
___

**Abstract**:

*Since winter 2011, a record-breaking drought has occurred in California. Studies found that the drought is mainly caused by a persistent high-pressure system off the U.S. West Coast, which is linked to Pacific sea surface temperature anomalies. The water cycles associated with the droughts and floods are still not clearly understood. Here we show that the atmospheric circulation off the West Coast not only controls the atmospheric convergence and formation of precipitation but also largely determines surface wind speed, which further affects the evaporation over the eastern North Pacific, the major evaporative moisture source for California precipitation. Because of this mechanism, the ocean evaporation over the eastern North Pacific has been reduced during the recent drought. However, the ocean evaporation anomalies have little direct influence on California precipitation, especially during dry years, mainly because of their weak amplitudes. The California droughts cannot be readily attributed to the reduced ocean evaporation. The association between increased Pacific evaporation and floods over California is somewhat stronger.*

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-06 07:36:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Study (open access): [End-Cretaceous extinction in Antarctica linked to both Deccan volcanism and meteorite impact via climate change](http://www.nature.com/ncomms/2016/160705/ncomms12079/full/ncomms12079.html)

**Abstract**:

*The cause of the end-Cretaceous (KPg) mass extinction is still debated due to difficulty separating the influences of two closely timed potential causal events: eruption of the Deccan Traps volcanic province and impact of the Chicxulub meteorite. Here we combine published extinction patterns with a new clumped isotope temperature record from a hiatus-free, expanded KPg boundary section from Seymour Island, Antarctica. We document a 7.83.3 C warming synchronous with the onset of Deccan Traps volcanism and a second, smaller warming at the time of meteorite impact. Local warming may have been amplified due to simultaneous disappearance of continental or sea ice. Intra-shell variability indicates a possible reduction in seasonality after Deccan eruptions began, continuing through the meteorite event. Species extinction at Seymour Island occurred in two pulses that coincide with the two observed warming events, directly linking the end-Cretaceous extinction at this site to both volcanic and meteorite events via climate change.* </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-06 07:29:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Study (open access): [End-Cretaceous extinction in Antarctica linked to both Deccan volcanism and meteorite impact via climate change](http://www.nature.com/ncomms/2016/160705/ncomms12079/full/ncomms12079.html)

**Abstract**:

*The cause of the end-Cretaceous (KPg) mass extinction is still debated due to difficulty separating the influences of two closely timed potential causal events: eruption of the Deccan Traps volcanic province and impact of the Chicxulub meteorite. Here we combine published extinction patterns with a new clumped isotope temperature record from a hiatus-free, expanded KPg boundary section from Seymour Island, Antarctica. We document a 7.83.3 C warming synchronous with the onset of Deccan Traps volcanism and a second, smaller warming at the time of meteorite impact. Local warming may have been amplified due to simultaneous disappearance of continental or sea ice. Intra-shell variability indicates a possible reduction in seasonality after Deccan eruptions began, continuing through the meteorite event. Species extinction at Seymour Island occurred in two pulses that coincide with the two observed warming events, directly linking the end-Cretaceous extinction at this site to both volcanic and meteorite events via climate change.* </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-06 07:25:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Study (open access): [End-Cretaceous extinction in Antarctica linked to both Deccan volcanism and meteorite impact via climate change](http://www.nature.com/ncomms/2016/160705/ncomms12079/full/ncomms12079.html)

**Abstract**:

*The cause of the end-Cretaceous (KPg) mass extinction is still debated due to difficulty separating the influences of two closely timed potential causal events: eruption of the Deccan Traps volcanic province and impact of the Chicxulub meteorite. Here we combine published extinction patterns with a new clumped isotope temperature record from a hiatus-free, expanded KPg boundary section from Seymour Island, Antarctica. We document a 7.83.3 C warming synchronous with the onset of Deccan Traps volcanism and a second, smaller warming at the time of meteorite impact. Local warming may have been amplified due to simultaneous disappearance of continental or sea ice. Intra-shell variability indicates a possible reduction in seasonality after Deccan eruptions began, continuing through the meteorite event. Species extinction at Seymour Island occurred in two pulses that coincide with the two observed warming events, directly linking the end-Cretaceous extinction at this site to both volcanic and meteorite events via climate change.* </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-05 19:25:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Study: [Antarctic sea-ice expansion between 2000 and 2014 driven by tropical Pacific decadal climate variability](http://www.nature.com/ngeo/journal/vaop/ncurrent/full/ngeo2751.html)

**Abstract**:

*Antarctic sea-ice extent has been slowly increasing in the satellite record that began in 1979. Since the late 1990s, the increase has accelerated, but the average of all climate models shows a decline. Meanwhile, the Interdecadal Pacific Oscillation, an internally generated mode of climate variability, transitioned from positive to negative, with an average cooling of tropical Pacific sea surface temperatures, a slowdown of the global warming trend and a deepening of the Amundsen Sea Low near Antarctica that has contributed to regional circulation changes in the Ross Sea region and expansion of sea ice. Here we show that the negative phase of the Interdecadal Pacific Oscillation in global coupled climate models is characterized by anomalies similar to the observed sea-level pressure and near-surface 850 hPa wind changes near Antarctica since 2000 that are conducive to expanding Antarctic sea-ice extent, particularly in the Ross Sea region in all seasons, involving a deepening of the Amundsen Sea Low. These atmospheric circulation changes are shown to be mainly driven by precipitation and convective heating anomalies related to the Interdecadal Pacific Oscillation in the equatorial eastern Pacific, with additional contributions from convective heating anomalies in the South Pacific convergence zone and tropical Atlantic regions.* </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-05 19:21:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Study: [Antarctic sea-ice expansion between 2000 and 2014 driven by tropical Pacific decadal climate variability](http://www.nature.com/ngeo/journal/vaop/ncurrent/full/ngeo2751.html)

**Abstract**:

*Antarctic sea-ice extent has been slowly increasing in the satellite record that began in 1979. Since the late 1990s, the increase has accelerated, but the average of all climate models shows a decline. Meanwhile, the Interdecadal Pacific Oscillation, an internally generated mode of climate variability, transitioned from positive to negative, with an average cooling of tropical Pacific sea surface temperatures, a slowdown of the global warming trend and a deepening of the Amundsen Sea Low near Antarctica that has contributed to regional circulation changes in the Ross Sea region and expansion of sea ice. Here we show that the negative phase of the Interdecadal Pacific Oscillation in global coupled climate models is characterized by anomalies similar to the observed sea-level pressure and near-surface 850 hPa wind changes near Antarctica since 2000 that are conducive to expanding Antarctic sea-ice extent, particularly in the Ross Sea region in all seasons, involving a deepening of the Amundsen Sea Low. These atmospheric circulation changes are shown to be mainly driven by precipitation and convective heating anomalies related to the Interdecadal Pacific Oscillation in the equatorial eastern Pacific, with additional contributions from convective heating anomalies in the South Pacific convergence zone and tropical Atlantic regions.* </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-04 08:06:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Study: [Deep time evidence for climate sensitivity increase with warming](http://onlinelibrary.wiley.com/doi/10.1002/2016GL069243/full)
___

**Abstract**:

*Future global warming from anthropogenic greenhouse gas emissions will depend on climate feedbacks, the effect of which is expressed by climate sensitivity, the warming for a doubling of atmospheric CO2 content. It is not clear how feedbacks, sensitivity, and temperature will evolve in our warming world, but past warming events may provide insight. Here we employ paleoreconstructions and new climate-carbon model simulations in a novel framework to explore a wide scenario range for the Paleocene-Eocene Thermal Maximum (PETM) carbon release and global warming event 55.8 Ma ago, a possible future warming analogue. We obtain constrained estimates of CO2 and climate sensitivity before and during the PETM and of the PETM carbon input amount and nature. Sensitivity increased from 3.35.6 to 3.76.5 K (Kelvin) into the PETM. When taken together with Last Glacial Maximum and modern estimates, this result indicates climate sensitivity increase with global warming.* </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-04 08:03:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Study: [Deep time evidence for climate sensitivity increase with warming](http://onlinelibrary.wiley.com/doi/10.1002/2016GL069243/full)
___

**Abstract**:

*Future global warming from anthropogenic greenhouse gas emissions will depend on climate feedbacks, the effect of which is expressed by climate sensitivity, the warming for a doubling of atmospheric CO2 content. It is not clear how feedbacks, sensitivity, and temperature will evolve in our warming world, but past warming events may provide insight. Here we employ paleoreconstructions and new climate-carbon model simulations in a novel framework to explore a wide scenario range for the Paleocene-Eocene Thermal Maximum (PETM) carbon release and global warming event 55.8Ma ago, a possible future warming analogue. We obtain constrained estimates of CO2 and climate sensitivity before and during the PETM and of the PETM carbon input amount and nature. Sensitivity increased from 3.35.6 to 3.76.5K (Kelvin) into the PETM. When taken together with Last Glacial Maximum and modern estimates, this result indicates climate sensitivity increase with global warming.* </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-02 09:42:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Study: [Human-induced greening of the northern extratropical land surface](http://www.nature.com/nclimate/journal/vaop/ncurrent/full/nclimate3056.html)

**Abstract**:

*Significant land greening in the northern extratropical latitudes (NEL) has been documented through satellite observations during the past three decades. This enhanced vegetation growth has broad implications for surface energy, water and carbon budgets, and ecosystem services across multiple scales. Discernible human impacts on the Earths climate system have been revealed by using statistical frameworks of detectionattribution. These impacts, however, were not previously identified on the NEL greening signal, owing to the lack of long-term observational records, possible bias of satellite data, different algorithms used to calculate vegetation greenness, and the lack of suitable simulations from coupled Earth system models (ESMs). Here we have overcome these challenges to attribute recent changes in NEL vegetation activity. We used two 30-year-long remote-sensing-based leaf area index (LAI) data sets, simulations from 19 coupled ESMs with interactive vegetation, and a formal detection and attribution algorithm. Our findings reveal that the observed greening record is consistent with an assumption of anthropogenic forcings, where greenhouse gases play a dominant role, but is not consistent with simulations that include only natural forcings and internal climate variability. These results provide the first clear evidence of a discernible human fingerprint on physiological vegetation changes other than phenology and range shifts.* </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-02 09:40:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Study: [Human-induced greening of the northern extratropical land surface](http://www.nature.com/nclimate/journal/vaop/ncurrent/full/nclimate3056.html)

**Abstract**:

*Significant land greening in the northern extratropical latitudes (NEL) has been documented through satellite observations during the past three decades. This enhanced vegetation growth has broad implications for surface energy, water and carbon budgets, and ecosystem services across multiple scales. Discernible human impacts on the Earths climate system have been revealed by using statistical frameworks of detectionattribution. These impacts, however, were not previously identified on the NEL greening signal, owing to the lack of long-term observational records, possible bias of satellite data, different algorithms used to calculate vegetation greenness, and the lack of suitable simulations from coupled Earth system models (ESMs). Here we have overcome these challenges to attribute recent changes in NEL vegetation activity. We used two 30-year-long remote-sensing-based leaf area index (LAI) data sets, simulations from 19 coupled ESMs with interactive vegetation, and a formal detection and attribution algorithm. Our findings reveal that the observed greening record is consistent with an assumption of anthropogenic forcings, where greenhouse gases play a dominant role, but is not consistent with simulations that include only natural forcings and internal climate variability. These results provide the first clear evidence of a discernible human fingerprint on physiological vegetation changes other than phenology and range shifts.* </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-02 09:25:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Study: [Human-caused Indo-Pacific warm pool expansion](http://advances.sciencemag.org/content/2/7/e1501719)

**Abstract**:

*The Indo-Pacific warm pool (IPWP) has warmed and grown substantially during the past century. The IPWP is Earths largest region of warm sea surface temperatures (SSTs), has the highest rainfall, and is fundamental to global atmospheric circulation and hydrological cycle. The region has also experienced the worlds highest rates of sea-level rise in recent decades, indicating large increases in ocean heat content and leading to substantial impacts on small island states in the region. Previous studies have considered mechanisms for the basin-scale ocean warming, but not the causes of the observed IPWP expansion, where expansion in the Indian Ocean has far exceeded that in the Pacific Ocean. We identify human and natural contributions to the observed IPWP changes since the 1950s by comparing observations with climate model simulations using an optimal fingerprinting technique. Greenhouse gas forcing is found to be the dominant cause of the observed increases in IPWP intensity and size, whereas natural fluctuations associated with the Pacific Decadal Oscillation have played a smaller yet significant role. Further, we show that the shape and impact of human-induced IPWP growth could be asymmetric between the Indian and Pacific basins, the causes of which remain uncertain. Human-induced changes in the IPWP have important implications for understanding and projecting related changes in monsoonal rainfall, and frequency or intensity of tropical storms, which have profound socioeconomic consequences.* </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-02 09:23:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Study: [Human-caused Indo-Pacific warm pool expansion](http://advances.sciencemag.org/content/2/7/e1501719)

**Abstract**:

*The Indo-Pacific warm pool (IPWP) has warmed and grown substantially during the past century. The IPWP is Earths largest region of warm sea surface temperatures (SSTs), has the highest rainfall, and is fundamental to global atmospheric circulation and hydrological cycle. The region has also experienced the worlds highest rates of sea-level rise in recent decades, indicating large increases in ocean heat content and leading to substantial impacts on small island states in the region. Previous studies have considered mechanisms for the basin-scale ocean warming, but not the causes of the observed IPWP expansion, where expansion in the Indian Ocean has far exceeded that in the Pacific Ocean. We identify human and natural contributions to the observed IPWP changes since the 1950s by comparing observations with climate model simulations using an optimal fingerprinting technique. Greenhouse gas forcing is found to be the dominant cause of the observed increases in IPWP intensity and size, whereas natural fluctuations associated with the Pacific Decadal Oscillation have played a smaller yet significant role. Further, we show that the shape and impact of human-induced IPWP growth could be asymmetric between the Indian and Pacific basins, the causes of which remain uncertain. Human-induced changes in the IPWP have important implications for understanding and projecting related changes in monsoonal rainfall, and frequency or intensity of tropical storms, which have profound socioeconomic consequences.* </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-30 20:43:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah, I mean... I was leaning towards that conclusion myself... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-30 11:05:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The consensus is even stronger than it seems.

That depends on the study^[1](https://ourchangingclimate.wordpress.com/2016/06/22/new-survey-of-climate-scientists-by-bray-and-von-storch-confirms-broad-consensus-on-human-causation/),[2](https://iopscience.iop.org/article/10.1088/1748-9326/11/4/048002/meta;jsessionid=CF3D16937B2AEBFF2696CE56CCCCA28D.c3.iopscience.cld.iop.org) ,  though there is no question that a widely accepted consensus exists. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-30 10:43:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What's going on with his charts? His [1^st chart](https://i.imgur.com/cOQaGGZ.png) ~represents our current atmospheric [CO2], while his [2^nd chart](https://i.imgur.com/q88Eh9b.png) has atmospheric [CO2] sitting just below 500ppm for 2015!

https://scripps.ucsd.edu/programs/keelingcurve/wp-content/plugins/sio-bluemoon/graphs/co2_800k.png </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-30 10:19:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I noticed some portions of the Earth 101 video included portions from another video which is related to this, as it was published alongside a study, "[Record Balkan floods of 2014 linked to planetary wave resonance](http://advances.sciencemag.org/content/2/4/e1501428)," co-authored by Rahmstorf. A descriptive, illustrated, video was published on youtube to help explain the studies findings: [Rossby waves and extreme weather](https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=MzW5Isbv2A0 ). </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-29 20:09:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Study: [Bright carbonate deposits as evidence of aqueous alteration on (1) Ceres](http://www.nature.com/nature/journal/vaop/ncurrent/full/nature18290.html)

**Abstract**:

*The typically dark surface of the dwarf planet Ceres is punctuated by areas of much higher albedo, most prominently in the Occator crater. These small bright areas have been tentatively interpreted as containing a large amount of hydrated magnesium sulfate1, in contrast to the average surface, which is a mixture of low-albedo materials and magnesium phyllosilicates, ammoniated phyllosilicates and carbonates. Here we report high spatial and spectral resolution near-infrared observations of the bright areas in the Occator crater on Ceres. Spectra of these bright areas are consistent with a large amount of sodium carbonate, constituting the most concentrated known extraterrestrial occurrence of carbonate on kilometre-wide scales in the Solar System. The carbonates are mixed with a dark component and small amounts of phyllosilicates, as well as ammonium carbonate or ammonium chloride. Some of these compounds have also been detected in the plume of Saturns sixth-largest moon Enceladus. The compounds are endogenous and we propose that they are the solid residue of crystallization of brines and entrained altered solids that reached the surface from below. The heat source may have been transient (triggered by impact heating). Alternatively, internal temperatures may be above the eutectic temperature of subsurface brines, in which case fluids may exist at depth on Ceres today.* </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-29 08:30:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hi /u/BrandonKatrena, your submission has been removed for the following reason. It is a sensationalized title. All submissions must follow the guidelines provided within the "Rules for Submissions" which states:

Not editorialized, sensationalized, or biased. This includes both the submission and its title.

The headlines should reflect the content of the research paper being discussed, generally the title of the article is acceptable so long as it is not excessively sensationalistic. Science journalism is notoriously sensationalist, and care should be taken to modify the headline if it is too much. Claims of curing cancer or AIDS/HIV will always result in the removal of a submission.

If you feel it was removed in error please feel free to [message the moderators](https://www.reddit.com/message/compose?to=%2Fr%2FGlobalClimateChange) for further clarification. Feel free to resubmit the article once you have taken the time to edit the title, and thank you for your contribution to the /r/GlobalClimateChange community. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-29 04:38:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Study (open access): [Radiocarbon evidence for enhanced respired carbon storage in the Atlantic at the Last Glacial Maximum](http://www.nature.com/ncomms/2016/160627/ncomms11998/full/ncomms11998.html)


**Abstract**:

*The influence of ocean circulation changes on atmospheric CO2 hinges primarily on the ability to alter the ocean interiors respired nutrient inventory. Here we investigate the Atlantic overturning circulation at the Last Glacial Maximum and its impact on respired carbon storage using radiocarbon and stable carbon isotope data from the Brazil and Iberian Margins. The data demonstrate the existence of a shallow well-ventilated northern-sourced cell overlying a poorly ventilated, predominantly southern-sourced cell at the Last Glacial Maximum. We also find that organic carbon remineralization rates in the deep Atlantic remained broadly similar to modern, but that ventilation ages in the southern-sourced overturning cell were significantly increased. Respired carbon storage in the deep Atlantic was therefore enhanced during the last glacial period, primarily due to an increase in the residence time of carbon in the deep ocean, rather than an increase in biological carbon export.*

Study (open access): [North Atlantic Deep Water Production during the Last Glacial Maximum](http://www.nature.com/ncomms/2016/160603/ncomms11765/full/ncomms11765.html)

**Abstract**:

*Changes in deep ocean ventilation are commonly invoked as the primary cause of lower glacial atmospheric CO2. The water mass structure of the glacial deep Atlantic Ocean and the mechanism by which it may have sequestered carbon remain elusive. Here we present neodymium isotope measurements from cores throughout the Atlantic that reveal glacialinterglacial changes in water mass distributions. These results demonstrate the sustained production of North Atlantic Deep Water under glacial conditions, indicating that southern-sourced waters were not as spatially extensive during the Last Glacial Maximum as previously believed. We demonstrate that the depleted glacial 13C values in the deep Atlantic Ocean cannot be explained solely by water mass source changes. A greater amount of respired carbon, therefore, must have been stored in the abyssal Atlantic during the Last Glacial Maximum. We infer that this was achieved by a sluggish deep overturning cell, comprised of well-mixed northern- and southern-sourced waters.* </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-29 04:35:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Study (open access): [Radiocarbon evidence for enhanced respired carbon storage in the Atlantic at the Last Glacial Maximum](http://www.nature.com/ncomms/2016/160627/ncomms11998/full/ncomms11998.html)


**Abstract**:

*The influence of ocean circulation changes on atmospheric CO2 hinges primarily on the ability to alter the ocean interiors respired nutrient inventory. Here we investigate the Atlantic overturning circulation at the Last Glacial Maximum and its impact on respired carbon storage using radiocarbon and stable carbon isotope data from the Brazil and Iberian Margins. The data demonstrate the existence of a shallow well-ventilated northern-sourced cell overlying a poorly ventilated, predominantly southern-sourced cell at the Last Glacial Maximum. We also find that organic carbon remineralization rates in the deep Atlantic remained broadly similar to modern, but that ventilation ages in the southern-sourced overturning cell were significantly increased. Respired carbon storage in the deep Atlantic was therefore enhanced during the last glacial period, primarily due to an increase in the residence time of carbon in the deep ocean, rather than an increase in biological carbon export.*

Study (open access): [North Atlantic Deep Water Production during the Last Glacial Maximum](http://www.nature.com/ncomms/2016/160603/ncomms11765/full/ncomms11765.html)

**Abstract**:

*Changes in deep ocean ventilation are commonly invoked as the primary cause of lower glacial atmospheric CO2. The water mass structure of the glacial deep Atlantic Ocean and the mechanism by which it may have sequestered carbon remain elusive. Here we present neodymium isotope measurements from cores throughout the Atlantic that reveal glacialinterglacial changes in water mass distributions. These results demonstrate the sustained production of North Atlantic Deep Water under glacial conditions, indicating that southern-sourced waters were not as spatially extensive during the Last Glacial Maximum as previously believed. We demonstrate that the depleted glacial 13C values in the deep Atlantic Ocean cannot be explained solely by water mass source changes. A greater amount of respired carbon, therefore, must have been stored in the abyssal Atlantic during the Last Glacial Maximum. We infer that this was achieved by a sluggish deep overturning cell, comprised of well-mixed northern- and southern-sourced waters.* </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
