<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject8312</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-19 19:09:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This is my swamp. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-19 18:52:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Whoa, they are great! Mmmm. They're like sex, except I'm having them. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-19 18:43:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> One could even say, He had a blast. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Found this while walking through a parking garage today. He's just livin' a lie. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-16 19:08:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-11 18:39:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> My geology teacher got arrested and convicted for the possession and distribution of child pornography. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-23 04:40:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This is art. This is the kind of art I want as my desktop background. Nice job. Truly.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Another picture I dredged out of the depths of my pictures folder. I hate break room thieves, but this was funny. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-01 19:25:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-01 19:13:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> We're working on that. What I think is going to happen is an escalating ban from the server for cheating. Ending with a perma ban for blatant cheating/exploitation. There will be no tolerance for cheating on this server. It's why I as an admin will likely be abstaining from gym leader/elite four positions. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-01 19:01:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If all corporations cared about their employees as much as this guy does, the world wouldn't be a cesspool of corruption and greed. This guy has my respect. I'd have bought him that car too. Words cannot describe just how amazing this was. A little faith in humanity was restored today. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-01 06:34:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Oh. I had no idea. It's been sitting in my gif folder for years so I figured I'd share with you guys. Thanks for the links. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Found this collecting dust in my pics folder. Hope you like it as much as I do. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-01 06:30:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Help Wanted </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-01 05:30:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hey guys a couple of friends and I are opening a pixelmon server. The server has already been secured. Mod testing is still underway but we will need help soon. We need a few builders to help out. Builders would receive a few benefits once the server is officially open. All benefits are undecided as of yet. The server will include gym battles, shops, tournaments, and an elite four. Gym leaders and elite four will be chosen from the players. Builders will be guaranteed a tryout for gym leader positions. PM me  if you want in or just want more information and I'll get back to you. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-25 06:50:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Oceanus </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-22 05:01:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What restaurant is that? Cause it's now on my list of things to do before I'm too old to enjoy them. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-22 04:50:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> JUST DO IT! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [War] The Builder Hut That Could </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-09-07 04:22:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
