<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject8307</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> TIL The last words of Huey P Newton, founded the Black Panther Party,  were, "You can kill my body, but you can't kill my soul. My soul will live forever!" He was then shot two times in the face. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-01-25 06:30:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> TIL 1 gallon of gasoline equals 124,000 BTUs of energy, however it only takes about 28,000 BTUs of HP to propel an automobile, Meaning about 75% of the energy in each gallon of gas is wasted </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-01-21 02:01:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>  Monsignor Meth: Priest ran meth ring, crossed dressed and had big black dildo sex toys </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-01-19 16:28:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> TIL The US invasion of Iraq was originally called 'Operation Iraqi Liberation', but was quickly changed after realizing that spelled 'OIL'. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-01-15 07:07:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> TIL Elephant's ability to communicate long distances confounded researchers for decades, then they realized infrasound rumblings allow them to secretly communicate even if miles apart. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-01-15 05:41:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> TIL A 4 year old with autism and ADHD was nearly completely cured after the administration of a lead chelating drug.  </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-01-13 08:16:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> U of Alaska Prof lights a lake on fire! Global warming is causing (flammable) methane emissions to bubble up from Alaska's lakes.  </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-01-10 04:03:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> mauxly details his bad ass way of kicking heroin which includes a remote cabin and plenty of Ramen noodles. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-01-08 21:13:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> TIL  Studies show blackened (burnt) meat is highly carcinogenic due to the formation of something called HCA </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-01-04 06:05:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Does coffee really stimulate a morning bowel movement? Decaf? Maybe any hot liquid would do it? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-12-31 21:58:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> TIL The results of one simple blood test can determine if you are 0 - 300% more likely than average to develop Alzheimer's and other types of dementia. it's called the CRP test - C-reactive protein. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-12-28 02:38:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> TIL A 2003 study found that people who ate fish once a week or more had a 60% lower risk for developing Alzheimer's than those who consumed fish less frequently. Far more affective than any known drug.  </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-12-26 20:26:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Man who fatally ambushed firefighters was previously convicted of murdering his own grandmother in '80. Despite this was still able to Easily obtain high-powered sniper rifle. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-12-25 17:34:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Spike Lee slams 'Django Unchained' calling it 'Disrespectful.'  Also, he hasn't seen it. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-12-24 17:33:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> 'Donnie darko' and 'Looper' are essentially the same movie. Hear me out </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-12-19 23:59:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> *Obviously spoilers*

Both movies feature protagonists caught in some kind of time travel loop. Both protagonists are the only ones that ultimately see the truly tragic end of the current timeline.

Both of them work mightily and heroically to somehow alter tragic outcome of the actions of the various people around them, and both ultimately fail.

And ultimately both decide the only resolution to the conundrum is to essentially commit suicide.

Now obviously there's lots of specifics in each movie that are completely different. But if you boil it down to its core, both movies present protagonists with essentially the same problem and those two protagonists deal with, and ultimately solve, the problem in the same way

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Is there any chemical difference between high-end expensive vodka and El Cheapo vodka? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-12-19 21:48:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Adam Lanzas Mother lived on $325,000/yr divorce settlement (ex is GE exec). Plenty to spend on son, Inability to access mental health care was NOT a factor. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-12-17 22:28:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Daily Mail invents entirely fictitious press release from the Met which claims global warming is not real. Refuses to retract. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-12-16 20:05:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> NBA star Kyrie Irving broke a bone in face and so must wear a protective mask. This is what it looks like.  </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-12-16 06:31:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Packers seem to be finished with Finley: Barring a shocking turn of events in the next month or so, he's playing his final season for the Packers </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-12-16 04:45:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Brent accident witness 'had to plead repeatedly with Brent to get a screaming Brown out of overturned vehicle as it burned.' </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-12-13 16:34:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> For nearly 25 minutes, Marshall promptly went off on the Green Bay Packers </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-12-12 22:51:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> TIL Coal power plants release MUCH more radiation than nuclear power plants do, including PU-239.  In fact, enough fissionable material could be recovered from a coal plant to build a nuclear bomb. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-12-11 18:56:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> TIL Nearly all of the most popular Christmas songs including 'Winter Wonderland', 'Chestnuts roasting', and 'I'm Dreaming of a white Christmas' Were written by Jews </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-12-10 22:53:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> famousonmars explains the awesome way he and his wife are kicking back and enjoying retirement 
  </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-12-10 01:45:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Can a cat parasite control humans? New study suggests T. gondii victims have a weak instinct for self survival, more likely to believe in hypnosis, and have poor diplomatic skills </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-12-09 16:34:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> 'Why I won't be cheering for Notre Dame': one rape victim dead, another too terrified to testify, and campus police who refuse to investigate football players </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-12-08 23:15:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Injury to Packers first round pick OL Derek Sherrod might be career ending. Sherrod played in a handful of games last year and has missed this entire season. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-12-07 18:34:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> A tiny church in Alaska, known as a "Christian identity" church, has now spawned three serial killers, including the worst domestic terrorist in American history </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-12-05 17:32:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Researchers at B. U. have discovered 28 new cases of chronic brain damage in deceased football players -- including 15 who played in the NFL </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-12-04 01:40:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> TIL Reindeer love to eat psychedelic mushrooms, may get high off of them, and that this could be the origin of the flying reindeer myth  </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-11-30 19:08:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> 2012 Election demographic stunner: In the 1992 Pres. election 31% of Asian Americans voted Dem, in 2012 almost 75% voted Dem. No one saw this coming. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-11-30 05:08:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> NASA now says their 'big reveal' of 'history changing' data from the Mars mission planned for Dec. is actually no big deal  </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-11-30 04:52:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Susan Rice is worth $35 M, most of which is invested in Canadian oil companies that will skyrocket if Keystone pipeline is approved. As Sec. Of State, Rice would have major influence in approving the pipeline. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-11-29 16:42:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Pat Robertson stuns audience by insisting Earth is much older than 6000 years. "If you fight science you're going to lose your children, and I believe in telling it the way it was." </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-11-29 15:29:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> "If you're trying to shoot somebody and they laugh at you, you go again." Man who shot and killed 2 intruders in his house, waited 24 hours to report the incident, now charged with Murder. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-11-27 00:12:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Milwaukee has seen sharply falling crime numbers for the last few years. Great success Yes? How did they do it? Turns out they just stopped reporting crimes to the public </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-11-25 06:05:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Savages: I really have a problem with the ending of this movie. Anybody else? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-11-24 18:35:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Obviously spoilers

So there were 2 endings, the fake ending and the real one

The fake ending (massive shootout everybody dies) was by far and away the better ending, it was realistic and riveting, it was tragic and kind of romantic all same time. Very butch Cassidy

The real ending was absolute crap. All fluffy and colorful, everybody lives happily ever after, all of the bad guys get their comeuppance, all of the "good" guys ride off into perfectly picturesque sunset to have endless threesomes in some nondescript Third World country

Give me a break. Nobody has the balls to put up real ending on a movie anymore </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Les Stroud (survivor man) discusses his encounter with Bigfoot on the Joe Rogan podcast, how fake the "finding Bigfoot" TV show is, and his plans to make a real Bigfoot TV show for discovery </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-11-23 19:32:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Claim: "Fourth-generation nuclear power plants will use current nuclear waste products as fuel." Is that true? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-11-22 16:03:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> In this Ted talk Stewart Brand makes the claim that fourth-generation nuclear power plants will use the nuclear waste from our current powerplants as fuel

http://www.ted.com/talks/debate_does_the_world_need_nuclear_energy.html

Is there any accuracy to that? is this one of those "in 20 years XYZ will happen!" And then 20 years later somehow that thing is still 20 years in the future? or is it realistically happening right now? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Casualties mount in GOP Civil War: Limbaugh and top level campaign managers exchange vicious blows in latest fracas: " the Republican primary is driving the Republican brand right now to a disaster. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-11-22 00:24:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> TIL Six nations, plus the EU, are collaborating on building the world's first nuclear fusion power plant in France. It aims to achieve 10 times input to output energy ratio, and may totally revolutionize the energy industry. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-11-21 22:39:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Infamous website unskewedpolls.com has rebranded itself as Barackofraudo.com, a website dedicated to explaining how the Democrats stole the election by ballot stuffing </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-11-21 16:02:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Glenn Beck's new dystopian novel describes a terrifying future tyrannical government that forces people to ride bikes and feed squirrels. Problem is - he didn't write one word of it. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-11-20 19:40:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> TIL The New York Times wrote an article about how industrial carbon emissions were going to alter the climate and warm the planet In 1953! </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-11-19 22:58:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Does any player have better individual trophy case than Charles Woodson? Heisman, DROY, DPOY, Super bowl ring, etc. etc.  </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-11-18 02:16:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Career highlights and awards

    AP NFL Defensive Rookie of the Year (1998)
    PFWA Defensive Rookie of the Year (1998)
    8 Pro Bowl (1998, 1999, 2000, 2001, 2008, 2009, 2010, 2011)
    7 All-Pro (1999, 2000, 2001, 2008, 2009, 2010, 2011)
    Super Bowl champion (XLV)
    NFC Defensive Player of the Year (2009)
    AP NFL Defensive Player of the Year (2009)
    NFL interceptions leader (2009)
    NFL interceptions co-leader (2011)
    Big Ten Freshman of the Year (1995)
    Heisman Trophy (1997)
    National Championship (1997)
    First-team All-American (1996, 1997)
    Walter Camp Award (1997)
    Sporting News Player of the Year (1997)
    Chuck Bednarik Award (1997)
    Bronko Nagurski Trophy (1997)
    Jim Thorpe Award (1997)
    Jack Tatum Trophy (1997)
    Mr. Football Award (Ohio) (1994)
    NFL's 2000s All-Decade Team
    50 Interception Club

http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Charles_Woodson </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Fox and Friends co-host Brian Kilmeade says Fox hires female hosts by looking at the Victorias Secret catalog and asking, Can any of these people talk? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-11-17 18:34:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Terry Tautolo, 49ers Former Linebacker, Left Homeless After Brain Damage Allegedly Caused By Concussions  </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-11-16 20:18:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Could we have been wrong about Alzheimers? Billions spent on attacking amyloid has been a collosal failure. Maybe its the tau protein afterall, an idea dismissed years ago  </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-11-11 20:28:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Republican civil war flares up as GOP operatives tear into each other in wake of Linda McMahon's $100 million senatorial bid fiasco  </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-11-11 01:58:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Pres. Obama has now increased his lead in the popular vote to a solid 3%. That means most major national polls really were biased In favor of Mitt Romney. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-11-10 16:41:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Here is a rundown of all of the national polls on Monday, just 24 hours before the election. most of the polls that are regularly reported on CNN and Fox news ABC news etc. were wrong. Every single one of those polls was biased against Obama and towards Romney.

http://imgur.com/81NVw

Notice the average of all of the polls is +1.6 in favor of Obama

I don't have a conspiracy theory here. I'm not accusing anybody of anything. I'm simply pointing out that nearly every major national poll was wrong, and wrong in a way that favored Mitt Romney. I don't know how that happened but it did happen

CNN just reported he will almost certainly win the popular vote by more than 3%.

Here's more on that

http://www.examiner.com/article/obama-likely-to-win-popular-vote-by-more-than-3

In the future I'm going to pay more attention to the Washington Post/ABC polls because that one seems to have been the most accurate. the Rasmussen polls  Error rate is reported as either 3% or 4% depending. Interestingly enough they were wrong by EXACTLY 4%. But I'm sure that's just a big coincidence

Here is another look which clearly shows the overwhelming majority of Polls were heavily skewed in favor of Mr. Romney (thanks to jk 13)

http://themonkeycage.org/blog/2012/11/07/a-second-look-at-national-pollster-accuracy/ </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> "Drunk Nate Silver" takes twitter by storm: 'Drunk Nate Silver arrested for shouting "FIRST ASIAN PRESIDENT" at the stomach of a woman unaware of her pregnancy.' </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-11-09 00:18:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Right-wing billionaire Sheldon Adelson poured tens of millions into this election (thanks to Citizens United), and nearly every single candidate he supported was defeated. If Allen West loses, Adelson would completely strikeout. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-11-07 15:02:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Tammy Baldwin becomes the country's first openly gay candidate elected to Senate seat (Fox now calling Baldwin the winner) </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-11-07 05:36:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> TIL Director Luc Besson started writing The Fifth Element as a novel when he was 16 years old. Twenty-two years later, it opened as the #1 movie in America.  </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-11-07 02:16:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> TIL Humans are capable of running 40 mph according to a study by biomechanical expert Dr. Matthew Bundle. Today's fastest man, Usain Bolt, has a top speed of 28 mph. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-11-06 23:51:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Confused Slowpoke </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-10-31 18:12:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> TIL There is a Greek island famous for its long-lived residents, where people routinely live to be 100 years old, and has been dubbed "the island where people forget to die." </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-10-30 17:57:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> I present the most shockingly stupid and laughingly idiotic computer hacking scene in TV history (NCIS 0:50)  </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-10-29 16:06:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Back in my day, there was only one NFL pre-game show. And they brought it!

 </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-10-28 02:18:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Need Help! Downloaded PrivatizeVpn and my computer is now going all wonky  </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-10-26 15:04:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> was this a huge mistake? fuck 

I downloaded Privatizevpn (from the piratebay) and ever since my comp is fucked

I can't open most programs, including 'add reomove'. I click on 'control panel' and nothing happens at all. Same with Dragon Naturally Speaking, I click on the icon and...nothing. wont open at all. 

Also it has highjacked my homepage, even though I changed it back to google, doesn't matter. It still goes to some other bullshit search site. 

suggestions? 
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> TIL The 3.3 million Residents of Vt, Del, RI, NH, and ME are represented by 10 US senators. The 37 million residents of California are represented by 2 US senators </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-10-21 18:29:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Packers rookie Hayward a solid pick
 </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-10-20 16:15:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> 4 starters out for Sunday game </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-10-20 01:01:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> TIL When Vincent Price did the voiceover for MJ's Thriller album, he was offered either $20k, or a percentage of the album's royalties. He took the $20k. Doh! </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-10-17 23:24:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> TIL Coca-Cola's 130-year-old recipe is one of corporate America's most closely guarded secrets. But Ira glass claims to have found the original recipe, which includes nutmeg, cinnamon, Orange oil, and neroli oil. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-10-16 19:42:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> TIL Communist spy allegations against Alger Hiss set off the 1950s red scare, McCarthyism, blacklisting, and general rampant paranoia. In 1992 Soviet historian Volkogonov revealed Hiss had never been a Soviet spy. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-10-14 16:27:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The pharmacy at the center of the meningitis outbreak (14 deaths and counting) was *repeatedly* warned by the FDA for violating its license, and knew it was an unsafe facility. And yet the FDA did nothing but write warning letters. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-10-12 00:44:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> TIL Sparta's best general, Alcibiades, lead attacks on Athens that nearly destroyed it. Then he switched sides, used his knowledge of Sparta to lead Athens to military victories which forced Sparta to sue for peace. Also Socrates, his homosexual lover, once saved his life in battle. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-10-11 16:27:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> TIL The assassination of Julius Caesar had the exact opposite of its intended effect. He was killed by Senators upset with him declaring himself dictator and eroding the Republic. But he was so popular his death caused rioting, Civil War, and the permanent installation of an Emperor. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-10-10 15:37:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> TIL The Gaia Hypothesis, the idea that the Earth is a self-regulating organism, was partially developed by Lynn Margulis, a.k.a. Carl Sagan's wife. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-10-03 00:18:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> TIL Johnny Appleseed (John Chapman), though he lived like a barefoot vagabond, became a very wealthy man due to his real estate and agricultural holdings. Also, almost all of the apples from the trees he planted became alcoholic hard cider </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-09-30 04:39:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Yet more counties in Florida report suspicious voter registration forms, meanwhile the Republican Party announced it will file elections fraud complaint against the very firm it hired. NYT reports fraudulent activity goes back at least 10 years </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-09-30 02:57:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Let's talk about THC as medicine! Has anybody tried making the concentrated oil Rick Simpson talks about? What kind of results have you had? How did you make it? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-09-22 00:48:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'd like to get a serious discussion going about using this plant as actual medicine, not just a way to get stoned. I think most people here have seen the video Rick Simpson where he makes the concentrated hemp oil and then uses it to treat all kinds of things including cancer

http://www.youtube.com/watch?v=_nm7nqUigFA

Has anybody actually tried to make that concentrated substance? What kind of results did you have? What did you use it for? What was your method of distilling the THC? how much plant do you need to make a fair amount of the concentrated oil?

I'm really interested in making this myself however I'm having a very difficult time getting enough of the plant to make it. I would really love to hear some actual experience and testimonials with this

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Philly man spends $20k of his own money to clean up abandoned lot, removing 40 tons of garbage and debris. Neighbors are thrilled! City response? Sue him for trespassing </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-09-21 23:08:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Low income smokers in New York spend 25% of their income on cigarettes, and paid 40% of New York's cigarette tax income </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-09-20 17:38:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Muslims riot and kill because of imagined insults to their Prophet. Americans invade and kill to steal your oil. Who is worse? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-09-15 19:14:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> even if you think the invasion of Iraq wasn't mainly due to oil, you have to admit controlling the oil was at least one part of the motivation. If you think that oil had absolutely nothing to do with our invasion of Iraq, then I think you are a very nave and blind person.

And then there is project Ajax in 1953, wherein we overthrew a democratically elected government of Iran because that government had recently seized control of its own oil fields out of the hands of British Petroleum. That whole operation was all about oil.

that's just two examples of many many I could come up with.

we kill people to procure oil resources. It's really that simple

Is that somehow better or worse than killing people because they insulted our religion? sure we can make fun and mock and laugh at the stupid Muslims for getting upset about a YouTube video

But we kill people to steal their oil. Are we really any better? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Super annoying conflict between Shockwave flash plug-in and my voice recognition software (Dragon NaturallySpeaking). What can I do about this? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-09-12 23:03:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I cannot have shockwave flash plug-in enabled at the same time I am using Dragon NaturallySpeaking which is a voice recognition software that I use quite a bit.

So without the shockwave flash plug-in most videos don't work. if I want to watch a video I have to shut down completely Dragon, then enable the plug-in, then play the video. Then I have to go and disable the plug-in before I start up Dragon again, and keep it disable the whole time. If I forget and have them both at the same time it totally screws up Dragon and I have to restart my whole computer again

What can I do about this? I've contacted nuance (the maker of Dragon NaturallySpeaking) and their customer support is terrible

I'm using Windows 7 on a Gateway desktop </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> I bought an induction cooktop and I'm having problems finding the right cookware to use with it, specifically nonstick cookware. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-09-12 18:20:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I got myself an induction cooktop

http://www.amazon.com/1800-Watt-Portable-Induction-Countertop-8100MC/dp/B0045QEPYM/ref=sr_1_1?ie=UTF8 qid=1347466476 sr=8-1 keywords=induction+cooktop

So you're supposed to use metal cookware. I used my Cuisinart nonstick frying pan, but it doesn't work. The cooktop keeps giving the error signal which indicates you are not using the proper cookware

http://www.amazon.com/Cuisinart-GG22-30-GreenGourmet-Hard-Anodized-Friendly/dp/B006361L4O/ref=sr_1_13?s=home-garden ie=UTF8 qid=1347466531 sr=1-13 keywords=Nonstick+pan+green+ceramic

That's what I'm using, which is metal and theoretically it should work.

I know they say that an iron skillet is the best, but I have severe arthritis in my hands and they are too heavy for me

Anybody have luck using some kind of nonstick cookware on an induction cooktop? in stainless steel the best option? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Meet  Sam Bacile: Jewish filmmaker who sparked the Libya US Embassy protests- "Islam is a cancer." He fully intended his film to provoke Muslim passions and is unrepentant about the deaths of US diplomats </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-09-12 17:25:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> TIL When Neo shows his passport agent Smith in The Matrix (released in 1999) it shows his birth date as September 11, 2001 - the date that would change the world as we know it </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-09-11 21:04:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The true impact of Bill Clinton's DNC speech: These stats and poll results will blow you away </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-09-10 06:45:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Why care about Arctic ice? A bit of ice melts, who cares? Care because Arctic ice is the "Earth's air conditioner". It reflects massive amounts of solar radiation back into the atmosphere. Without that ice, *devastating* climate change is nearly guaranteed. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-09-09 04:49:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> TIL In five short years (2006  2011) global solar power production increased by 1000%, from 6.9 GW to 69.7 GW, blowing away even the most optimistic predictions </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-09-08 01:11:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> So yeah Just get a good picture of me standing in front of this building </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-09-06 15:55:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Consider this: NONE of the former Republican presidents, VPs, or Presidential/VP candidates are welcome at Republican gatherings because they're all politically toxic and quite frankly embarrassing. What does that say? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-09-06 15:09:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Child pageant freak show "Honey boo-boo" beat out Paul Ryan's RNC speech in TV ratings - 3 million to 1.5 million viewers </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-09-05 18:39:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> How many generations do I have to go back before my ancestors would no longer be considered "human"? Also, how old are human beings? different sources make different claims about how old Homo sapiens are </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-09-03 16:06:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm confused about how old human beings actually are? Some sources say 50,000 years, others say 250,000 years

and I am wondering how many generations that is? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Behind the Eastwood debacle: They gave him talking points, a time limit, and flashed a blinking red light that told him his time was up. He ignored all of it. Romney's PR people thought he was going to sit in the chair, had no idea about "invisible Obama" stunt </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-09-02 04:52:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> TIL America's war on drugs, officially began in 1971. At that time 1 gram of cocaine cost $200 ($1,100 adjusted for inflation). Today that same gram of cocaine cost $50. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-09-01 23:19:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> How to make navigation buttons and menu text larger? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-08-28 17:16:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> just bought a brand-new computer, running Windows 7 with Firefox

The navigation buttons are incredibly tiny as is the menu text for things like "file" and "edit" etc.

How can I make those things larger?

Also the scrollbar is really skinny. Is there anyway I can make that slightly wider? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> TIL Rep. Joe Barton (RTexas) is against wind energy because "wind is God's way of balancing heat," and fears that wind turbines will slow down the wind thus heating up the earth. He also claims wind is a "finite resource." </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-08-25 22:45:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Onion headline: "Nation Celebrates Full Week Without Deadly Mass Shooting" then, after news about the Empire State shootings comes out: "UPDATE: Never Mind" </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-08-24 19:46:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Brand-new Gateway computer does not recognize Dell monitor. What's going on? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-08-24 19:00:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> just bought a brand-new computer ( Gateway - Desktop - 6GB Memory - 1TB Hard Drive Model: DX4870)

http://www.bestbuy.com/site/Gateway---Desktop---6GB-Memory---1TB-Hard-Drive/5424595.p?id=1218644421363 skuId=5424595
 hooked up my Dell monitor to it and Nothing. Completely blank screen. Hooked up that same monitor back to my older Dell computer and it works perfectly fine. Hook it back up to the brand-new Gateway and Nothing.

Call the Gateway tech support and it was the worst tech support in the history of the universe. Absolutely awful. Totally worthless.

Called up Best Buy tech support and he says that he thinks it's a software update issue. Like the Gateway need some kind of an update to recognize the Dell monitor. But since I only have the one monitor I don't know how I'm going to download any kind of software update onto the Gateway

thoughts? Ideas? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Chances we have a repeat of 2000? Obama wins the popular vote, Romney (mainly due to voter suppression in Ohio and Pennsylvania) wins the electoral college, and thus becomes president </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-08-20 16:46:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If the voter suppression measures in Ohio and Pennsylvania are successful, Romney will take both of those states

At that point he the only other swing states he really needs is Florida and maybe Wisconsin

And yet I honestly think Obama will win the popular vote, although not by much

I don't know What you think? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Shia LaBeouf to do porn. Not kidding, Sex Scenes in Lars von Trier's 'Nymphomaniac' Will Be Real </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-08-18 23:50:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> So what are the economic ramifications of poisoning aquifers, and/or depleting groundwater resources as happens with coal ash, tar sands oil extraction, and fracturing? Why should I care? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-08-17 20:32:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Coal ash, tar sands oil extraction, and fracturing to extract natural gas all deeply groundwater resources. They do this either through direct use of them or by poisoning the aquifers

But what are the actual real-world economic ramifications of this?

Why should the average person really care?

Do we have plenty of water?

Saying something like "well in 100 years you'll care" doesn't really register.

what are the real-life economic impacts from destroying freshwater resources? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Are there any respected climatologists who do not believe in the man-made climate change theory? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-08-15 21:23:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Now that Richard Mueller has changed his mind about man-made climate change, are there any well-known well-respected climatologists who still do not believe that carbon emissions are altering our climate? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> In '89 Romney (Bain) bought Damon Corp. The company engaged in massive Medicare fraud, (which Romney profited off of) was prosecuted, pled guilty and paid a fine. Romney sold the company and made $4.7 million. It then went bankrupt and 1000 people lost their jobs </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-08-15 17:36:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Rasmussen poll has Romney up 3%, meanwhile Fox news poll has Obama up 9%. That's a 12% swing. How is that possible? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-08-15 14:42:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> People with type O blood "significantly lower" risk of coronary heart disease than those with Type A, B, or AB </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-08-15 00:52:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Paul Ryan says he was just kidding about that whole thing about liking Ayn Rand </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-08-14 21:08:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> As a Wisconsinite this is how I feel lately </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-08-13 19:43:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> TIL George Koval: Soviet master spy that infiltrated the Manhattan project, stole nearly all of our nuclear secrets, single-handedly provided the key technology for Russia's nuclear arsenal, and was only discovered as a spy in 2002.   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-08-13 18:13:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Soooo annoying!  </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-08-06 18:54:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> 3.2 GHz Pentium D dual core VS Intel core 2 duo 2.2 GHz? About the same thing? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-08-05 18:09:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If all of the specs on the computer about the same would these two processors be about equal? Or would one noticeably outperform the other? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Usually, after running defrag program, it shows 500 to 700 files defragged. Today it showed 4,700. Why? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-08-05 17:45:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I think the most it ever shown as being defragged was maybe 900 or 1000

Yet today that was 4700 files defragmented

Any idea why that might be? It's only been maybe three or four days since I defragmented it previously and have done nothing odd or unusual since then </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> TIL The Bible vigorously condemns obesity (gluttony) well over 20 times.  It only mentions homosexuality 4 times. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-08-03 15:17:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Interesting breakdown of NFL positions by race: 92% receivers are black, 56% tight ends are white, etc. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-08-03 00:42:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> TIL Though doctors are loath to admit it, Lyme disease testing is notoriously inaccurate. Several studies show labs are correct only 45%  55% of the time, about the same as a coin flip. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-08-03 00:19:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> It is a squirrel beer cozy. You know For your beer. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-07-31 01:18:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> TIL Facebook's Sean Parker (played by Justin Timberlake in the movie) has seen his net worth drop by $995 million in the three short months since the IPO </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-07-31 00:41:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Should I put two 512 MB Chips instead of one 1 GB chip into my Dell OptiPlex? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-07-28 21:17:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So I gotta Dell OptiPlex GX 270 and it's only got room for one more gigabyte of RAM. Somebody told me it would be better to put two 512 MB chips in there instead of one 1 GB chip

yea or nay? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> TIL Twinkies and Coca-Cola are heavily subsidized by US taxpayers. Every year $1.3 billion in taxpayer-funded welfare is gifted to the highly profitable junk food industry. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-07-28 17:23:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Romney's economic plan: Toss 13 million people off of food stamps, and give big oil $3.8 billion in subsidies (tax breaks). </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-07-26 22:03:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This is Mitt Romney's economic plan to fix our financial troubles

$3.8 billion  subsidy (tax breaks) for big oil

http://grist.org/news/mr-romney-thinks-we-should-give-big-oil-companies-another-3-8-billion-a-year-in-tax-breaks/

Toss 13 million people off of food stamps

http://thinkprogress.org/economy/2012/05/22/488079/romney-food-stamps-13/ </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Carbon tax - what is it supposed to fund? What will it get spent on? Because if it is just going into the general government slush fund it's a terrible idea </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-07-26 20:49:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So the most common proposal solution to man-made climate change is the imposition of a carbon tax. the more carbon emissions you create the more taxes you pay.

Okay sounds good, But what exactly is that carbon tax supposed to get spent on?

Because if it just goes into the general slush fund and get spent on all the stupid stuff we already spend money on like war, subsidies for major corporations, etc. then it's just a terrible idea and it's going to serve absolutely no purpose. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Desmond Bishop failed his physical, NFI - nonfootball related injury. Is put on PUP. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-07-26 02:46:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> US Chamber of Commerce has a solution to climate change! Turns out we can just make "physiological changes" which allow us to adapt to a hotter climate. No problem! </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-07-24 01:48:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The whole article is great but I just quoted the relevant passage

http://m.rollingstone.com/entry/view/id/29695/pn/all/p/0/?KSID=b521dcc49a4bf5d33eb82a3660b48363

In 2009, for the first time, the U.S. Chamber of Commerce surpassed both the Republican and Democratic National Committees on political spending; the following year, more than 90 percent of the Chamber's cash went to GOP candidates, many of whom deny the existence of global warming. 

Not long ago, the Chamber even filed a brief with the EPA urging the agency not to regulate carbon  should the world's scientists turn out to be right and the planet heats up, the Chamber advised, "populations can acclimatize to warmer climates via a range of behavioral, physiological and technological adaptations." As radical goes, demanding that we change our physiology seems right up there. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> How was James Holmes able to kill and wound so many people? Simple: use of a high-volume assault style magazine that Republicans fought  hard to make legal in 2004.  </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-07-21 17:45:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm posting this as a self, text post because the website is fairly small and will probably get crushed if too many people Click on it

Also note these magazines have NO hunting application whatsoever, nor would they realistically be useful in a self defense scenario

http://mydd.com/

James Holmes, the detained shooter in our latest national mass murder tradegy, bought four guns from various retailers over the last two months.

[Snip]

**A high-volume drum magazine was attached to the rifle, making that rifle an assault weapon and allowing him to fire 50 to 60 rounds in under sixty seconds.**

Led by Senator Dianne Feinstein, Congress passed the Federal Assault Weapons Ban (AWB) on September 13 1994 and signed into law by President Clinton the very same day. But the law expired on September 13, 2004. Despite numerous attempts by Senator Feinstein and others in the Democratic leadership, attempts to renew the AWB have all failed because of Republican opposition. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Shooter James Holmes: neuroscience med student dropout, loner, No one knew him, one neighbor told the newspaper. No one. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-07-20 18:49:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Alien mothership? Nope, owl butterfly egg </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-07-20 03:30:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> CNN's David Gergen has strongly defended Romney against Obama's Bain attacks. Now it turns out Gergen has extensive ties with Bain, Has given paid speeches at Bain HQ's and "admires" its leadership </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-07-18 18:29:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> TIL Chicago Tribune has fired dozens of US news reporters, and outsourced the jobs to Filipinos who crank out "local" news stories at 35 cents a pop. The Filipinos use a fake name generator to mask the fact that local news is being reported by somebody who lives 5000 miles away. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-07-15 20:17:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> TIL Only 3% of the energy in coal is actually used in a lightbulb powered by coal derived electricity. The rest is lost to mining, processing, transporting, and burning the coal. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-07-12 20:24:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> For medical reasons I'm on a low-sodium diet. I am 95% certain some companies blatantly lie about the salt content all their products. What can I do about this? how can I make them be honest? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-07-11 21:59:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Due to a kidney condition it is very important I keep my sodium intake low. So I am always checking the sodium content on food labels.

I know what food taste like that has 500 mg of sodium and I know what food taste like that has 2000 mg sodium.

There are couple companies that I am close to 100% sure are blatantly and massively lying about the sodium content in their food. A very popular brand of frozen burrito's claims to have 500 mg of sodium in each burrito. Absolutely not. The taste of salt is overwhelming. I bet that it is closer to 2500 mg.

Is there anything I can do about this? Is a such thing as a home test kit for salt content in foods?

How can I bust these companies and make them be honest?

Yes I have tried calling and complaining and that has got me nowhere </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What are the true, real world, costs of coal generated electricity? This dude figured it out and the answer will blow you away </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-07-07 18:28:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> This is what global warming looks like in Noblesville, Indiana </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-07-06 16:14:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> TIL The oldest statue at the most ancient temple site on earth (Gobekli Tepe) is of a man holding his engorged penis with both hands </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-07-05 19:24:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> 2010 Packers Super Bowl ring up for auction </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-07-05 00:19:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Intense heat causes WI to highway to buckle, sending SUV airborne
 </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-07-03 18:06:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Kleven, Ukraine's tunnel of love </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-07-01 19:05:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> All hard pulls on credit report (by banks/mortgage co) in 45 day period count as one ding? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-06-29 19:15:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So I guess too many hard pulls on your credit report are not a good thing. But a mortgage broker told me today that all hard pulls in a 45 day period count as one "ding".

Is that true? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> John Roberts likely switched his vote on Obamacare at the last moment </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-06-29 17:05:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> TIL In 1994 two British artists burned 1 million ($1.5 M) of cash money. They earned it producing hit singles as 'The KLF'. They then quit the music business until world peace was declared. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-06-27 19:17:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Here's the wiki article on the burning incident

http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/K_Foundation_Burn_a_Million_Quid

This was their biggest hit: "3 AM eternal"

If you were into the electronic music scene in the early 90s you know the song very well

http://www.youtube.com/watch?v=hVAJL6_UPVc

Years later they  sat down to talk about burning the money on a discussion panel TV show. One of the other guests is some doofus from Def Leppard. He was not amused

Link contains footage of the money being burned

http://www.youtube.com/watch?v=i6q4n5TQnpA </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> PDF form won't allow me to drop in electronic signature? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-06-26 18:37:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> My realtor sent me a form that I need to sign and return to him and I would really love to be able to just drop in an electronic signature and e-mail it back to him

However, it's not cooperating. Adobe Acrobat says it's not authorized to make alterations to the document

I tried uploading it to 'hello fax', but again I get an error message saying it can't upload that PDF

Am I just screwed?

EDIT: case anybody's interested I solve this problem with this software

Elcomsoft Advanced PDF Password Recovery 

Basically it strips away the security settings on the PDF. I tried some freeware versions of this type of program and none of them worked. This one did

[](/solved)  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> TIL Dogs and wolves have essentially identical DNA. Difference is dogs are in permanent arrested development - they've been bred to be perpetual adolescent wolves that will never grow up </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-06-23 00:53:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>  Microsoft.net framework 3.0  service pack 2 - can I remove this? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-06-22 17:14:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Says this is used "rarely"

Can I remove this or is it necessary for certain programs to run? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Program that allows you to sign a PDF document on your computer without printing and scanning it? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-06-22 15:49:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Somebody's e-mailing me a PDF document that I need to sign and return 

I do not own a scanner.

I believe there is a program you can use that allows you to use MS paint to sign the document right on your computer without printing and scanning

Does anybody know what I am talking about? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> TIL Omega-3 supplementation can dramatically improve children diagnosed with depression </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-06-21 18:22:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Madison marijuana laws? Repercussions for getting caught growing one plant? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-06-18 03:18:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Let's just theoretically say I had one single marijuana plant growing on my property in Madison.

And for some stupid reason I got caught with it

What do you think the legal ramifications of that would be?

No priors </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> AOL has infected my computer. I CANNOT get this crap off of here! </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-06-15 17:34:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I open up the list of programs to add/delete and I see no AOL listed whatsoever

Every time I open up a new Internet window AOL is my homepage and the AOL toolbar loads up on my browser

Google.com shows as my homepage in Internet options. But obviously it's being redirected to AOL somehow

 how do I get this crap off of here?

Running windows XP on a Dell

[](/solved) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Was Beth faking it? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-06-11 05:19:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> After the shock treatment Beth apparently does not recognize Pete anymore

I'm not so sure that's how shock treatment works. Do you think she was just faking not recognizing him in order to end it? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> TIL Billionaire Hotelier Conrad Hilton (Paris's grandfather) asked on his deathbed If he had any final words. "Leave the shower curtain on the inside of the tub" he said, then died </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-06-04 23:37:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Fukushima radiation has been found in a California Fish for the first time </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-05-29 17:33:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Have you ever seen anything that could be classified as a UFO? I have. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-05-26 20:18:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Maybe this isn't right up the Reddit alley, but screw it I'm going to tell my story anyway.

It's 1999, about 11 PM. I'm standing on a cliff overlooking the Monterey Bay just south of Santa Cruz California. To my left I can see the city lights of  Monterey,  ahead of me is the Pacific Ocean.

I notice a plane flying slowly over the city of Monterey. It circles around the city and I wait for it to land at the airstrip just outside the city. Instead it starts to circle slowly outwards over the Monterey Bay. It circles very very slowly and when it gets about 1000 yards out over the ocean, it stops in midair 

Okay fine I guess it's not a plane it's a helicopter. 

It starts to emit colorful flashing lights, green blue red and white. It starts flying in very very slow kind of  loop d loops, getting closer to where I'm standing on the shore. The craft stops in midair again, and the white light gets very very bright and it starts sweeping the entire length of the   beach. It sweeps over me and pauses for a moment, it is EXTREMELY bright. I'm starting to kind of freak out now wondering what's going on. It continues to sweep down the beach.

I tried to get a good look at the craft. It's dark and I'm straining to see it, and for all the world it looks somewhat disk shaped. I can see no propellers, no engines, no blades. But again it's very dark and I can't really make out very clearly. It was completely silent. the closest it got to me was maybe 500 yards and I could hear no engine noise.

Suddenly it turns back towards the city of Monterey, accelerates REALLY quickly with absolutely no noise whatsoever, swoops down and flies over the entire city of Monterey, turns back over the ocean, flies out  over the middle of Monterey Bay, and then

And here's where it gets freaky

It flies INTO the ocean. Yes that's right, it flew INTO the ocean. I know what I saw and I saw that craft flying into the ocean. I just stood there stunned not knowing what to think. I turned to look around to see if anybody else saw it, and  there was one other guy maybe 30 yards from me. I walked over to him and asked if he'd seen it. He just looked at me with his mouth gaping open unable to speak. I looked back at the ocean trying to find the craft, when I turned back to find the guy again he was literally RUNNING for his car. He got in his car peeled out and took off like a bat out of hell.

Went home and for the next couple days was looking for news reports about an airplane that crashed into the bay. Nothing.

I still have no idea what the hell I saw. it did not look like it crashed into the ocean. It looked very much like it fully intended to fly into the Bay. I don't know.

TL;DR: saw a strange totally silent craft, that emitted multicolored lights, fly INTO the Monterey Bay. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Suck My Cock </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-05-26 04:04:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Facebook's Sean Parker (played by Justin Timberlake in "the social network") is down $300 million since the company's disastrous IPO three days ago </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-05-22 18:50:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Matt Kahlil (#4 overall to Vikings) on Nick Perry: "the best player that I've ever played against and a future NFL star. Going against him every day, that's why I think it makes it so easy for me in games."  </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-04-27 18:55:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Is South Park still funny? Has it run its course? I think this season has been extraordinarily dull </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-03-29 17:22:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Last night's "Faith Hilling" episode was weak in my opinion. They had the perfect opportunity to lambaste Republican primaries, and yet they chose to go with "people on the Internet do stupid things".

They air old reruns from 1999 through 2003, late at night here. I ALWAYS laugh at them. Even when I'm tired and groggy. I can't help but laugh because well They're fucking hilarious!

This season I really WANT to laugh, I EXPECT to laugh, but mostly I just don't. I chuckle a little bit here and there but the comedy seems less incisive  or cutting to me. I'm just not feeling it.

Do you find South Park as funny as it's always been? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Pat Robertson: A Peyton Manning injury would "serve them right" For treating Tim Tebow  "shabbily" </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-03-23 18:50:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Greece just completed the largest debt write-down in human history </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-03-12 20:57:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> CNN's 'Danny , Syria' caught editing, adding sound effects, to his news broadcasts to make it seem he was in a war zone when he was not </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-03-06 21:41:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> TIL Terrell Owens pissed away almost all the $80M he made playing in the NFL, his properties are being foreclosed on and he can't make his $45k/mo child-support payments </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-03-02 19:59:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Qnexa: New FDA approved weight loss drug. Side effects include suicidal thoughts, memory loss, birth defects, and heart problems </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-02-23 18:31:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Why has man evolved to love the taste of Na, while being repulsed by the taste of K, when both nutrients are needed in equal amounts? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-02-16 18:45:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I've been reading studies which show the critical importance of the K/Na ratio in the human body. In most Americans, the ratio GREATLY favors sodium, but studies have shown when the ratio is equal or when K is favored, significant health benefits are experienced.

And yet, if you fry up some vegetables and season half with potassium chloride and the other half with sodium chloride, and do a taste test, close to 100% will be repulsed by the vegetables seasoned with potassium chloride and will gobble down the veggie seasoned with sodium chloride. 

WHY?

Why would we evolve to be repulsed by the taste of one electrolyte we really really need. And yet crave another electrolyte we also need? it just doesn't make sense to me.

Here's some of the stuff I've been reading. the first link is pretty dense with medical jargon, I provided a short excerpt from the second link.

http://cardiovascres.oxfordjournals.org/content/37/2/335.full

-----------

http://www.thehbpsolution.com/New_Developments.html

After 31 months, they found that compared to the homes which still used table salt (NaCl) in their kitchens, in the homes where a salt mixture with equal amounts of potassium and sodium had been substituted for NaCl, there was a statistically significant:

39% drop in cardiovascular disease
70% decrease in heart failure
50% decrease in cerebral vascular disease
and a 25% drop (though not statistically significant) in diabetes (which I had predicted in the 1980s).

An important aspect of this study is the fact that the K/Na ratio in the salt replacement was only 1/1.  In my book, "The High Blood Pressure Solution," you will find evidence that when the dietary K/Na ratio is above a threshold (between 2 and 4 - close to 3),  problems such as hypertension, become rare. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Murder solve rate steadily going DOWN, despite incredible advances in crime-fighting technology AND plummeting number of murders - Why? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-02-07 18:35:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Scumbag Redditor (Woody Harrelson AMA) </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-02-04 21:56:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> TIL Kurt Vonnegut took Army leave in 1944 to surprise his mother, he burst into her bedroom, only to discover she had committed suicideon Mother's Day </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-01-30 18:24:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Undeniable climate change: USDA revises planting zone map, as warm zones creep steadily northward </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-01-25 19:18:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Audience of self-professed Christians boo Ron Paul's idea of applying Jesus' Golden rule to foreign-policy </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-01-17 07:31:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
