<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject3921</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2011-09-20 20:46:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Movies like the Dark Knight. I still remember when this came out, it was near my birthday and I went on opening night with my parents. I was 4 then I think. Someday when I have kids movie wont be the same. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2011-09-20 20:40:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The hardware problems mostly come at night. Mostly. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2011-09-20 20:36:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Wing Commander. Awesome movie :) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2011-09-20 20:15:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What do you mean - like your life is scrutinized specifically in a law context?

I'm still of the opinion that networking and intelligence are what get you ahead, not names on degrees. For all you know, the you that went to that Ivy League school turned out to be a total arrogant jerk, holding you back from your dreams. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2011-09-20 20:11:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> 1. I wish to be someone who has had his this wish granted.
2. I wish to be someone who has had his next wish granted.
3. I wish to be someone who has not yet made his third wish.

Genie ruptures, destroying the time/space continuum. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2011-09-20 20:01:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I attended the #1 ivy league school for my degree for two years and left for another school because the atmosphere was horrific. That was 5 years ago now, and I'm exactly where I want to be in my career.

Smart people are smart people. Don't hold onto some regret over a *name* on your degree. Out in the working world post-grad school, nobody cares what school you went to. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2011-09-20 18:15:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Good point. I believe there is a large human component in their 'automated processes' because I have seen things get through or not get through purely at random. Often you can simply resubmit a blocked work with no changes and it will go through the second time. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2011-09-20 16:54:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Similar results in my MBA class. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2011-09-20 15:14:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This isn't real. I publish on Amazon and they do not go through and edit books in this fashion. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2011-09-19 22:19:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You can't be out of ideas. Just create a character - any character - and move him along, creating his motivation and actions as you go. A world will form around it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2011-09-19 20:21:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Uh, self-publishing is a blue ocean. You are in no way deluded. Traditional publishing is on a slow decline.

All you can do is produce. You will not succeed with a book. You will succeed with ten books.

On the other hand, they should be shorter than you're used to. 50k to 80k words. Write a natural arc. Write a series.

Keep publishing, and if you're quality, you'll build a readership. Being an author is a full-time job. You do not simply create a book then launch it into space. Readers ascribe to authors like they tune into their favorite TV shows: a TV show is only 'alive' as long as it has new episodes coming eventually. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2011-09-19 18:17:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Interesting. Is there a dodge cap? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2011-09-19 17:02:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Wait, what is 'Armor' then? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2011-09-19 01:34:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's not small. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2011-09-19 01:31:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Here's to growing up on Blink 182 and scoffing at the possibility of ever being that old. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2011-09-18 23:36:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> According to studies, duck face is the angle that gets the most messages on online dating sites.

Seriously. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2011-09-15 14:58:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Right now I only have one book associated with myself, a horror anthology called Psychosis. It's on Amazon.

The rest are pen names. I think most authors should start out with pen names in the ebook market unless you plan to make this a full time job. You don't want potential employers looking up your name and finding books. It'll make you look unfocused.

Amazon and B N's PubIt are the best platforms for me so far. Smashwords is supposed to be good, too, but I just haven't had any sales there at all for some reason.

Basically, read the linked article in the OP, find these platforms, and get to publishing. Join facebook author groups for your genre and *contribute* and you will be helped in turn.

That's what I went through over the course of several months. It seems simple when it's laid out like it is in that article, but your idea of 'professional work' will continually upgrade as you learn more. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2011-09-14 20:51:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Sorry, responded directly to the OP. Yes, this advice is **perfect.** </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2011-09-14 20:50:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Write the way the characters involved would remember it. Setting  problem  thought  action  resolution  emotional reaction. Repeat.

As long as you have the sequence correct, you can't go 'too fast'. The only thing you can do is go too slow by having overlong obnoxious prose. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2011-09-14 20:38:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Jesus Christ. Published indie author here.

**Every single thing the article says, down to the very last detail, is exactly correct.**

Including focusing on smaller novels for more titles, learning to do the books yourself, and publishing regularly.

I learned it all through painful experience. Here it is, for you, for free - the perfect ebook publishing guide. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2011-09-14 15:06:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [Relevant](http://www.reddit.com/r/AskReddit/comments/kfbda/how_do_i_get_the_simple_concept_of_marketing/) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2011-09-14 14:18:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Nope, no idea how to watch for news for a particular area. I always wonder how scary movies showed that sort of thing. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2011-09-13 19:09:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Right, I've seen authors get discouraged if they don't sell in a few days after publishing. That's silly. It take a year to gather a following. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2011-09-13 19:02:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Congrats. I'm also an Amazon published author and it's always good to see others succeeding as well. Check out [/r/selfpublishing](http://www.reddit.com/r/selfpublishing/) if you guys have questions, more than happy to answer them. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2011-09-13 15:22:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I recognized the colors instantly, then the building :) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2011-09-13 14:17:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> They want exclusivity? I publish on multiple platforms. All Smashwords really wants is a 'Smashwords Edition' on the front page (so modify your book by one line) and don't link to Amazon in the Smashwords edition. You can publish on both just fine :)

But be aware they will manually approve your book and then it gets sent out to distribution every 2 weeks or something like that... and THEN there's a week or two delay to show up in stores... and THEN there's a delay to see sales.

So don't get discouraged if you don't see immediate sales :)

I do use the Smashwords Style Guide as a basis for all platforms. It's a free ebook and you have to publish in that format on SW. The format is great, though. It teaches you how to format perfectly. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2011-09-13 14:15:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Randomly and self-market, haven't built a campaign yet for that book. Been working on other pen names first :) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2011-09-12 21:43:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> haha, thanks :) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2011-09-12 20:10:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah, the problem is, everyone uses it. Buyers have no incentive to switch because they have 150% protection (the extra 50% is the fact they can chargeback, get their money, AND keep the item they bought without repercussion).

PayPal is some sort of international non-bank 'financial transfer entity' that doesn't operate under banking regulations. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2011-09-12 20:05:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> They are some sort of international non-bank entity. The laws they operate under are very vague... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2011-09-12 19:53:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That's the idea, it seems. As more and more withdrawals roll up, I've now got maybe $7k in there I can't get out.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2011-09-12 19:51:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Jesus Christ! I knew they could chargeback and so I set up an external account to deal with them... but to collections agencies too? I have to distance myself from PayPal...

It's terrifying knowing that people could simply chargeback at any time and take money out of your *bank account*... and they can. It's not paranoia. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2011-09-12 19:50:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> @AKBWFC and vasmax,
Yep. It takes six months to a year to build an author following just to be decent. I also write under other pen names. That one book just sells substantially well because it's banking on a creepypasta scene that already generated publicity. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2011-09-12 19:46:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Amanda Hocking sells 100,000 copies a month. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2011-09-12 19:46:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yep, Kindle reader (the software) is also free to download for any computer. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2011-09-12 18:40:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Upvote. Other authors want you to succeed, as long as they can succeed too. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2011-09-12 18:32:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Many people won't notice a new ebook, no. You will only sell a few copies as it flits across the front page of whatever site you're publishing on. *However*, you'll have a percentage of those people who go to your blog - and then to all your other books - and the higher your books move in rankings or specific search terms, the more sales you'll start to get.

It's all exponential and each pulse of a new reader hits everything in the network of links you've built.

It's worth it to make friends with reviewers and authors. Go join a facebook group for authors. They're all very helpful.

As for your inclinations about purchasing and reviews, those aren't helpful to selling your book. You have to figure out what your readers do, and intuition isn't necessarily correct. Especially with eBooks, which are so much cheaper than traditional print, readers are more willing to take risks - and more apt to ignore reviews, since it's probably your friends and family until you hit it big.

So just keep writing, build a network of links, and it'll grow. It's important to map your views and clicks in your blog. If views are dropping, publish something new; if clicks are dropping or works are selling less, it may be time to shift strategy slightly. It'll take a month or two for you to realize any trends, though, so don't sit and watch the numbers. You'll go insane.

Edit:
There's also pricing strategies and packaging strategies you'll have to learn for yourself.

Many authors go the 4k - 6k for 99 cent route. Interestingly, people will still pay $2.99 for that range once you build a following. If you're writing 10k words a week, write 10k words a week and sell that as a book. Some authors find success this way because the more publish events you get out there, the more people see you... and plus seeing a few sales on your work will encourage you to continue.

But yeah, 99 cent books carry almost no risk for the reader, and thus are a great starting point for new authors. You'd be surprised how much you still make compared to print books. Royalties for some places, like Smashwords, can be as high as 70%.

Edit2:
Publishing weekly is perfect. That's also why I recommend learning to make your own covers with PrintShop, which is actually exceedingly simple. Find a good stock photo image site, find a good image (search *hard*), stick your title and name on it, and publish it. 'Professional covers' with all their fancy art just look like a bunch of gibberish to me personally, considering the format has changed for ebooks to one of quick online scanning and thumbnails. Covers that have one clear image and a clear title sell just fine. You can even use the same one for a 'book in parts'.

Edit 3:
But I do think that book in parts thing is better once you've built a following. If you're writing 10k words a week now, I recommend you make that 10k into one complete and interesting story arc. It can be the same characters, or the same world, or even the same overarching plot but... remember, people are NOT going to buy 'Awesome Adventures Part 7' when they see it first. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2011-09-12 17:50:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> From what I read they just keep your money, or even charge it all back (stealing it from your bank account), or don't let you close it. Not messing with the sleeping dragon. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2011-09-12 17:38:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Upvote. Printed books are a dying industry. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2011-09-12 17:29:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's actually extremely simple.

You need to create a network of in-roads to your blog. Your blog is a central location to follow you and your work.

These in-roads consist of links from other authors (make friends, learn, and be useful), reviews, and most importantly, *published books*. Every book you publish (I recommend eBooks, print books are dying) should have a link back to that blog.

Then you have to publish, and keep publishing. You will not build a following without at least 2 established works. This part all depends on your genre, book length, and so on (longer is not always better). If you're a short story writer, expect to publish 20+ short stories as you build a following.

Each book you publish is a big splash in the pond, and will continue to produce views and followers for a very long time. Just make sure the books are good quality.

So, in answer to your question about how to build a following for your *first book before it comes out*... you can't. Authors with a following have followers because they continually produce new and great content. Your 'one great idea' is therefore pretty meaningless. You need to have ten great ideas, publish them all, and learn over the course of six months how to really run things.

But you can do it. It's a no-fail situation. If you don't sell, you learn why you didn't sell, and you do better next time.


edit: and your blog is NOT a place you should be posting content to. Make them pay for it (amazon, smashwords) or they won't respect you or your work.

edit2: make use of facebook author pages to increase organic marketing. Many new writers forget this part.

edit3: And don't get caught up on word count. Seriously. Just produce a work that can be packaged effectively and put it out there as a book. Remember, eBooks are 99 cents or $2.99 usually these days. People aren't meticulously analyzing a price-to-word-count ratio before buying. They're looking at your cover, your product description, similar works by other authors, and the title before buying. *Amazon doesn't even list word count.* </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2011-09-12 16:47:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Really? As far as I know it's the only one on Amazon (ebooks) called Psychosis.

Argh, those jerks! Other authors releasing the same name.

http://www.amazon.com/Psychosis-Tales-of-Horror-ebook/dp/B005DSU784/ref=sr_1_9?s=digital-text ie=UTF8 qid=1315838869 sr=1-9 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2011-09-12 16:34:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> oh lol, 'Psychosis', a book of scary stories that I wrote originally for r/nosleep. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2011-09-09 21:08:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Age difference... he's in a totally different phase in his life. He's right to worry, because it's highly likely you will leave him. He's not worried about what you said. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2011-09-09 20:33:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> oh rofl </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2011-09-09 19:10:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> My understanding was that you base protein intake on Lean Body Mass, not total weight. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2011-09-09 19:07:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Someone needs to circle the little shadowed guy at the base of the neck who is throwing his arms in the air to emphasize just how **insanely big this thing is.** Picture doesn't have any reference points. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2011-09-08 20:45:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That's another show where the low ratings don't make sense. 30 Rock is awesome and on a prime network. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Still Life </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2011-09-08 20:36:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I was idly clicking through profiles online one evening when I found something that disturbed me. A friend of a friend of mine had a series of odd pictures... clothing and styles I hadnt seen in the better part of a decade graced his page. I read some of the last comments. They were all, to the last, memorials.

My thoughts raced with confusion as I examined my vague memories of him. I had no idea that he had been dead for several years. I was a little put off by the fact his profile still existed, hanging there silently in space long after he was gone.

I began a search through his list of friends, heading for names I didnt recognize. After a few tries, I found another page that seemed wrong in some subtle manner. There were no memorial posts, but the last activity shed taken was five years past. A chill shock ran across my skin as I realized that this wasnt just a fluke. There were profiles whose owners had died - many, many profiles - gathering dust in the dark corners of the internet.

I lost myself in continuing my search, unearthing page after page of still life. It seemed the deeper I went into the network of ties from that first acquaintance, the more silence I found. Grandmothers, children, husbands, friends they all smiled in cold photos of warm days and danced motionless at unknown parties. These events must have meant the world to these people, but they were nothing now but a few images. A growing sense of dread began to build in me as I continued to search.

My heart beat faster and I began to feel a vague sense of sourceless resentment, as if Id trespassed somewhere I wasnt meant to go. The feeling of distant hostility grew even as I clicked and scanned faster, unable to stop. My rushing pulse and that feeling of empty rage peaked as I found myself in a community of families and friends whose pages all had memorials for some type of tragedy. Ten, twenty, thirty it kept going. Every single picture, every post, every conversation theyd ever had they were dead. They were *all dead!*

I stumbled out of my chair and turned off my computer.

Reality quietly pooled around me, slowing my racing heart. I didnt know what to think about what Id seen. While I tried to focus, my legs took me outside. It was definitely time to go. I was supposed to be somewhere

The gloomy grey evening sky drizzled a fine mist over the parking lot as I approached my car, parked at the far end earlier that day. My steps echoed in the bleak stillness. During that lonely quiet walk, it occurred to me that profiles were not all that the dead left behind. Bodies and bones littered the world, twisted with the pain and suffering that took their lives. Not just graveyards, either surely someone had died, at some point in time, virtually everywhere.

The misty rain swirled around me, but I felt no wind. I looked around, feeling that vague sense of trespass again, as if my dark thoughts and echoing footsteps were treading too far into loneliness and silence. Those that died left so much of themselves behind their bodies, their images, their hopes and dreams What else might remain?

My jaw slackened and I stopped in place halfway to my car. My eyes traced the delicate curtains of mist. A horrible thought had occurred to me: if, somehow, the essence of the dead lived on how many of them were there? What was their existence like? Were they trapped in the ground where they were buried? Did they wander the Earth in eternal exile? Were there countless millions of them all around, flailing without body and screaming without noise, desperate for life to notice them again, even if just for a moment?

My heart furiously pumped in my chest as my eyes followed the lilting path of the droplets of mist drifting around me. I could almost see them now, the barest ethereal outlines of shoulders, arms, faces that vague hostility, that hatred and jealousy and thirst to be acknowledged they had gathered around me like moths to a flame, attracted by my trespass into the realms of despair. I shook my head and laughed nervously. I was imagining things.

My shirt pulled back hard, and I stumbled. Lithe cold tendrils of wind tore at me, pulling my hair, grabbing at my clothes, and shoving me with horrendous force in every direction. I hit the pavement bodily, and struggled in terror and pain. A maelstrom seized me from every angle, and the chaos blinded me for a moment. A microburst, some sort of freak weather occurrence my mind raced for understanding as I struggled to breathe, but my animal instincts cried out.

*Get away!* I screamed at the top of my lungs.

The parking lot was silent. The gloomy grey evening sky drizzled a fine mist over the wet cement. I looked around in panic, but there was nothing to be seen. My clothes were torn and I felt bruised. I stumbled to my car and drove out of that bleak place with one last look back. I saw nothing in the dancing mist, but I knew they were there watching, always watching. My mind had processed my senses. It hadnt been the wind. I knew what I felt. They were *hands* thousands of them, desperate, clawing hungrily for what they would never have again. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2011-09-08 16:40:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Good, because this thing needs to go at least 4 seasons to complete the college arc. I trust them to do a 5th season and beyond, but I can't even guess how they'll do it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2011-09-08 15:32:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What people fail to realize is that *you can meet people.* Building WHO is just like building WHAT. It takes time and effort. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2011-09-08 15:24:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The most important thing isn't figuring out if the person you're with is 'the one'. The most important phase is *when you're single* - you need to:

* 1: Understand yourself.
* 2: Envision the best person for you.
* 3: Improve yourself until you are worthy of that person.
* 4: Date. Date *alot*. Don't settle or compromise until you've mastered being your best, and until you've met the person you envisioned.

If you just 'fell' into a relationship or dated 1-5 people and just stuck with one, you're probably making a mistake. The world is huge now. You can't just let it randomly dictate your life. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2011-09-08 15:18:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I read a study that was probably the creepiest thing I've ever seen: the number of accounts on the Internet (facebook, reddit, etc) for dead people is going to outmatch the number of accounts for living people in the next 30 years. They'll actually have to develop specific technologies to check if someone's dead or the Internet will become a literal 'ghost town'.

Also, in a MMORPG I play, one of our big-name enemies got in a serious car accident and was in a coma for 3 weeks. His character was macroing resources and everyone on the server (even the griefer kiddies) just let it run the entire time. I don't think anyone wanted to be the one who killed his character if he didn't come out okay. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2011-09-07 16:20:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I've been publishing through Smashwords and it's fantastically simple and quick. You can publish immediately and link people to your books for sale, whereas Amazon takes a few days to post any changes. I've also found that Smashwords' Formatting Guide creates books that are perfectly formatted for any platform.

PubIt and Nook - are these included in Amazon and Smashwords distribution? I'll also have to check out Google ebooks.

Did you just sign up for your EIN? It may take a few weeks to enter the IRS' records. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2011-08-23 18:26:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Upvote. They'd all be dead in a few days from viruses and horrible food. Not to mention they'd kill millions with their own pathogens. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2011-08-23 18:23:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Erm, since you are the break-up initiator, you could probably win her back.

You're pretty young, though. In fact, very young to have decided this girl is 'the one' without having dated anyone else as an adult.

I would take the space improving your friendship to mean *you are better at a distance* and remain friends.

In the best of relationships, there should be no 'relationship' or 'back in a relationship', there should just be the two of you, better off together than you are apart. It seems you're better off apart. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2011-08-17 22:17:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Interesting that you mention that. My uncle's expedition was the same year as the expedition in that book. He told me it was actually the worst year Everest ever had, with over a dozen people dying. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The Everest corpses </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2011-08-17 20:53:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> When I read [this](http://www.buzzfeed.com/toddvanluling/dead-bodies-on-mount-everest), I couldn't help but flashback to a story my uncle once told my cousins and I late one night at a family reunion.

He was kind of notorious among the extended family; one of those reasons  was that he went on an Everest expedition when he was younger. As kids, we adored him, even if our families tended to isolate him for reasons they wouldn't say. In retrospect, I realize he was drunk that night, but I think that was the only reason he told us what he did when the other adults weren't paying attention.

My cousin asked him about the Everest expedition, and he told us that he'd lied. They'd climbed it, alright, but they never made it to the top as he had claimed. There were six of them, and they were climbing a standard route on the south face. A little after they crossed into the [death zone](http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Mount_Everest#Death_zone) and they saw their first corpse lodged in a ravine, the bravado of the men in the group dimmed.

Their mood grew even worse when an unexpected snow squall came in and they had to camp for the night prematurely. My uncle visibly paled as he talked about setting up a tent within line of sight of a frozen body that clung to an opposing ridge. He kept peering at its distant contorted face until the snow blocked it out, his thoughts transfixed by how that face seemed twisted in eternal pain and horror. Whoever it was had died begging his friends to somehow save him from the impossible position to which he'd fallen. Sleep was difficult that night, but the rigors of the climb helped.

He awoke at some point, his ears filled with the razor whistle of frozen wind from the storm outside. A hissed whisper kept him from getting up - the other two men in the tent were already awake, lying motionless and listening. Something was scratching around in the crunchy snow outside... but outside, the oxygen levels were too low for anything to survive. A quiet but continual cracking sound followed the scratches, as if something covered in ice was painfully clawing around.

The sounds only lasted for a few minutes, but my uncle lost something of himself that night as he trembled there quietly while the icy horror wheezed "help me... help me..." outside in the dark.

In the morning, their worst fears were confirmed. The high winds had torn open the other tent, and one of the men had been dragged out. On the dark and storm-torn slope, he was unable to find his way back, and had fallen and died on the same ridge as the other unreachable body.

My uncle and his friends knew there was nothing they could have done - if they had gone out there they would have just died, too - but the incident ended the expedition. My uncle quieted as he described packing up in the sight of that nightmarish frozen corpse. It was hard to tell, but, the more he peered at it, the less the expression on its face seemed horrified and pained... and the more it seemed that its unnaturally wide mouth was actually a horrible grin.

My uncle resolved to check the other tent's damage to see if it really was from the wind when they got to base camp, but in all the commotion about the death of their friend, he never got the chance. That decayed and mocking leer has haunted him ever since. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2011-08-17 16:50:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Also, take into account the flow of reading and the process of memory. Make the words easy to parse (flow of reading) and your readers won't notice any problems. Many words, like "said", are completely invisible. That's a good thing. Learn how to make the flow of reading as smooth as possible. Write 'formally' and don't worry about it.

Then for the process of memory, i.e. how someone recalls your dialogue after reading it, it's largely based on the emotions and actions taken during the dialogue. Nobody remembers what was said, only how.

So - skip realism. Your reader has made a contract with you to engage in reading a book. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2011-08-10 15:06:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Creepypasta are bundles of horror-related memes and cliches. They either copy them or originate them. Their format is typically small in order to be spread more effectively.

If you're a good horror writer you should use forums and blogs as testing grounds to define a format and audience, but you should be publishing real work to Kindle or Smashwords. If you're not, you're literally just leaving money on the table. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2011-08-08 23:32:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Not to mention that a huge majority of positions out there are pump-and-dump sales positions. Bring your rolodex!! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2011-08-08 21:16:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> There is only one speed in the universe. It is a 4-dimensional speed involving time and the three physical dimensions; if you go faster in any of the four directions, you go slower in the others - but you are always going the same 'total speed' when all four are added together. This is roughly why time slows down in your perception as you approach the speed of light.

Since these four speeds always sum to the same total, you get the mythical meme 'if you could move faster than the speed of light, you would go back in time'. This is because your three physical speeds sum to more than the universe's One Speed, and thus to balance the equation, the time direction would be negative. Ex: if the One Speed is 1, then 1+1+1-2 = 1.  That -2 is math telling you to go -2 in time to balance the equation.

Unfortunately, math is just a red herring in this regard. All of the numbers are positive by definition. You cannot go 'negative miles per hour' in physical space - you are going a positive speed in another direction. The same is true of time. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2011-08-04 02:41:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This subreddit seems very focused on stories that are a few paragraphs in the format of "I had this experience". I mean, there's tons of horror that doesn't fall into that category that just has no place on the internet? or what? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2011-08-04 02:13:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Sort of, I wish this subreddit wasn't so focused on a single format... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2011-08-03 22:26:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Why is Savage Steve Holland so negative about a movie so awesome? How could anyone hate this movie? It's my favorite! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Something's Wrong </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2011-08-03 16:57:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It was obvious something was wrong, but it took awhile to get the full story out of her.

*Something's wrong.*

She awoke that night with that wordless fearful impression. It was hot, almost uncomfortably so, and exceedingly still. Through the window next to her bed, she saw only black clouds and the silhouettes of motionless trees. Her eyes traced the shallows and depths of darkness across her room, but no movement or sound betrayed the silence. After a few minutes, when her heart stopped racing, she closed her eyes again.

*That! It's that!*

Her subconscious snapped at the flashes of light through her closed eyelids, and she knew what had woken her. She lethargically turned her head to look out the window again at the clouds. Heat lightning! She waited a minute or two, but the clouds remained black. Disappointed, she reached up and pulled the blinds down, then turned back to sleep. The heat lightning flashed through her closed eyelids a few moments later.

*Something's still wrong.*

Something seemed off about the timing or brightness of the lightning... it was unnatural. Her relief faded, and she peered between two of the blinds. The world lay heated and quiet. What had she expected to see? Some sort of monster or spirit or something? She shivered at that thought, and peered around her room again in the darkness. Something felt seriously off, but she couldn't... quite... place it... she started to imagine the sensation of being watched, as if a particular patch of void in the corner was crouching motionless, staring back at her unseen.

*Get out!*

The feeling unnerved her enough that she pretended to get up to go to the bathroom, and instead left the house entirely. I knew that much about the story because I remembered that night, when she showed up in her pajamas disheveled and embarrassed. There was nothing in the house the next morning, of course.

The revelation I had to pry out of her was a new realization. She suddenly went nuts and stormed out of the bar seemingly without cause. I found her outside, alternating between angry rants and frightened sobs. I finally got her to tell me what had bothered her so much: she'd finally recognized that light. It was never heat lightning at all. It was the exact same pattern and brightness as the flash our friend's camera phone had given off as he took our picture in the bar. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2011-08-03 15:37:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I used to be able to hear televisions and lights. It's a function of age mostly. I can still hear lights as a high-pitched whine, but it's not as annoying as it once was. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2011-08-03 15:31:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yep, to get to the secret exit to the star road in the middle of the lake. It tooks us so long to find that before the Internet! ARRRGH!! Especially because that star is *nowhere near* that bridge on the world map... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2011-08-03 15:14:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I've always been curious: in the Frieza saga, after Goku turns Super Saiyan and Frieza goes 100%, at one point Goku gets hit into some lava and stays out of sight for quite awhile while Gohan arrives to temporarily challenge Frieza. Somewhere around those moments, on Earth, they wish for everyone on Namek who was killed by Frieza to come back to life. Goku then emerges from under the ground.

So did Goku *actually die and get revived in that scene?* In which case, due to the nature of Saiyans, he'd then be much more powerful after healnig. Does that mean Frieza actually would have legitly won that fight otherwise?

And how did the Earth dragon revive Goku a second time, if so? (because he was revived once before in the Saiyan saga and there is a one-revival limit at that point in the series, right?) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2011-08-03 15:11:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I believe the 100x kaioken was in the afterworld tournament... or maybe that was 'super kaioken'... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2011-08-03 00:00:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> DON'T BLINK </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2011-08-02 21:52:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Us Canadians all have secret identification codewords </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2011-08-02 19:42:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm a dual citizen. I'm going to visit and exit out the other side just to see what happens (and get away with it) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2011-08-01 22:30:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [I WAS PHONE](http://t0.gstatic.com/images?q=tbn:ANd9GcSUlKGTOfkf5UpD9JaTC70t_U1Pkgl9ss4obmCIvh3Wsk1T5zq8Sw) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2011-08-01 04:57:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Is the first contest on right now? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> An Overheard Conversation </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2011-07-29 16:14:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Its a slow night for my typical excursions, but I do happen to overhear a disturbing exchange between a man and his friend seated nearby at the bar:

Tell me about it, women can be so confusing. I got one that tops it all, though. Way back, when Heather and I had just ended things. You remember her, right?

The friend says: Hah, yeah

Nothing bad, just didnt work. I think Ill never hear from her again til she calls me, says she hears noises outside her house at night. I wasnt sure what to feel, but I stayed over. She spent the whole night lying there awake, keeps waking me up saying Do you hear that? Do you hear that? and I heard some rustling or something, maybe a raccoon, but saw nothing out the window went back to sleep, right?

Anyway, maybe three days later she called asking for me to stay over again. This time she says she heard noises *inside* the house. This girl lived with her sister and that ones four-year old daughter, but says they didnt leave their room that night. Im a bit frustrated at this, you know, since she broke up with me but keeps calling me but Im still a man, so I take my tire iron over there and sleep with it nearby.

The man telling this story takes out a napkin and draws something on it.

But see here this is her room and her backyard, its fenced. Its got this gate. I had this idea then that she might have a stalker from the coffee shop she worked at down the street. The gate was creaky as hell, and if anyone was creeping about, wed listen for the sound of the gate. Instead, about 2 AM, we hear this creaking in the hallway.

The friend says: Damn, whatd you do?

I look over and notice a little movement. Immediately, I realize, Jesus Christ, theres a small crack in the wall  and *an eye is peering in, watching us.* I get up ready to beat someone to hell, when I hear a little girl giggling  kid you not, its just the daughter, learned to escape at night and wander around the house.

The friend says: So she was freaked out over nothing?

No, get this, she *keeps calling me* asking me to stay over, but I tell her I cant do it anymore. Its too hard on me.

The friend says: Wow, thats messed up. Was she just messing with you the whole time? Was there ever a stalker or anything?

Well you know better than I do, right?

The friend says: Whatcha mean?

Well I ran into her about six years later and she says she called you to stay over in the living room after that. Back then I actually suggested she call you, cause youd met once or twice at the coffee shop. I figured you were my friend, but the breakup wasnt bad, so chivalry and all that

The friend says: Seriously? When was this?

Like 02, round August.

The friend says: Now I know youre just messing with me, man.

What? Why?

The friend says: That was my 24th birthday or round, I remember it because my cellphone got stolen and I was too poor to get another one for awhile.

Well that doesnt make any sense

The friend says: Oh my god -

What? What is it?

The friend says: Last time I saw my cellphone. Seriously. I remember this because I was so pissed off and went back there asking around  last time I saw my cellphone was at her coffee shop.

And youre sure you didnt have it then? But she says you came over and slept in her house every night for like a month...

The two men begin talking too quietly to be heard at this point, though I do hear several expletives. They soon hurry out, and I realize that they left the napkin with the drawing of her house on it. It looks something like [this]( http://imgur.com/KQYcqZY), though its a bit inaccurate. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2011-07-29 14:54:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yep, and if you have any questions feel free to ask. Pricing and marketing is really hard! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2011-07-28 14:55:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I worked at Starbucks and I can confirm: customers will order extra hot, stare at you steaming it, then demand that it be iced instead - and then ask if they can 'just have' the hot one, too.

Sadly, it's not some sort of scam or trick. They're really doing that. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2011-07-21 18:42:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> :) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2011-07-20 22:49:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Great idea, we need this. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2011-07-20 15:30:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> And thus the ultimate meta :D </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> "Come closer" </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2011-07-19 20:10:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'd actually seen him on our way home from school. He looked dirty and disturbed, and stared straight at us as our bus went by. We even made jokes about him, probably as our way of pretending we weren't afraid. He was incredibly out of place in our middle class suburb, so his mere presence felt threatening... thus our panic when the three of us got off at our stop and saw him at the corner, about to look in our direction.

He was between us and our houses, and the bus had already pulled away, so we bolted for the bushes of a nearby yard. We weren't sure if he had seen us, but we peered through the leaves and saw him stalking our way, muttering randomly. Tim, my neighbor, insisted that he'd seen a large knife in the man's ragged clothing. Danny, a kid I hardly knew who had just moved into the neighborhood, insisted that he was imagining it - that Tim's glasses must have reflected the sun wrong or something. Still, we were terrified, and the sidewalk was going to bring him right by us.

It was Tim that broke and ran first, keeping low. I followed, my heart pounding, as we dove into the darkness underneath the porch of the unfamiliar house we'd been hiding near. As we squeezed our bodies against the dirt, the grimy wood pressed into our backs, barely giving us enough room to breathe. From our hiding place, we could see the disturbed man turn into the yard in front of us and begin searching around, hitting the bushes and muttering angrily.

I realized then that Danny wasn't with us, but I hadn't seen where he'd gone. Tim had lost his glasses back at the bushes, and he just huddled in the shadows next to me in near-blind terror. We stayed there in silence, waiting. Every so often, whenever I almost thought it was safe to come out, footsteps would creep across the wooden porch above us. Tim almost sneezed, once, but I covered his mouth and nose in stark fear.

We waited there so long that the tone of the sunlight began to change. We hadn't heard the man searching about in awhile, and I was just getting ready to peek out, when footsteps clattered and a thud hit the wood directly above us. A split second later, Danny's face appeared in front of us upside down, and he looked at us through the lattice. A look of shock and surprise crossed his features at finally finding us. He whispered something, but I couldn't hear anything. He seemed to be saying "come closer," so I figured the horrible man was still around and we had to be quiet, and I inched forward.

Danny's features grew fearful, and he kept indicating something above us. Strangely, I still couldn't hear him... his eyes seemed to dim then, and I inched forward a little bit more. I froze for a moment in horror, then backed up. Tim mouthed to me: "What did he say?" and I just shook my head, completely in shock. Danny hadn't conveyed "come closer," he had mimed "he's up there." The drifter was unknowingly sitting right above us, waiting, because he knew we had to be somewhere in that yard. 

There was nothing to do but wait in silence, trying not to scream. I was glad Tim had lost his glasses. I lay there as darkness descended, waiting in unwavering terror and trying not to feel the glassy stare of Danny's severed head as it rested in the grass a foot away. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2011-07-19 19:12:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Creepypasta is just a word for short-form scary stories. With the death of the original forums   communities (like at creepypasta.com), creepypasta production basically just stopped.

This subreddit seems to be in a similar vein, but one dedicated solely to a category of short stories involving 'real incidents' that 'happened to the author'. Of course, given that genre, authors don't get a chance to become skilled, because the 10th or 20th 'this happened to me post' loses all believability...

It's a shame there isn't a more expansive scary story community here. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2011-07-06 16:24:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Do these come with fear and dread? You didn't specifically mention that. It might be purely the discomfort of attempting to resolve paradoxical sensory information.

You should put some medical research (with your doctor) into exploring the conditions of your ears and related nerves. This is not necessarily a brain-based phenomenon. The hearing system actually plays a large role in this kind of thing, and would definitely be something you'd 'sense' coming on without being able to define what's wrong. It's possible that garbled input from your ears is activating things problematically. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2011-07-06 14:44:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The immediate understanding that they're not 'real' definitely means these are hallucinations, if this is really happening to you. Also, the 'sense that one is around' is probably an association to a particular mental state that you've made, one that is conducive to seeing these things. I get something similar with migraines - nothing changes, I feel no different, but I go "oh no, a migraine is coming in a few hours."

I'm interested in the particular neural pathways these hallucinations activate. You said they're not activating emotional responses, which is more evidence that these are symptoms of something happening neurologically. My initial guess is that you are having your spatial-awareness circuits activated when they shouldn't be, specifically in regards to the parts that track other people. Your brain keeps telling you 'someone is there, someone is there' repeatedly, and other circuits may be activated to fill in details of paradoxical sensory input, in the same way your brain attempts to resolve confusing shapes or colors. One problem for you is that the brain is hard-wired for facial recognition - I notice you often describe the hallucinations' faces, which can even be malformed. Next time you have one, try focusing on a non-face aspect instead, such as the texture of their arms. Basically, try to ascertain details that will trip up what you've 'grown used to.' </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2011-07-05 15:10:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I thought for *sure* that the last line was going to be 'I don't care if I did marry her a year ago, this is still my damn house!'

aka Married With Children's lost episode! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2011-06-30 00:07:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> All the guys on OKCupid just message every single girl they think is attractive from their pictures, and then only read profiles upon replies. This is, sadly, the optimum strategy - mainly because everyone else is doing it, so you have to do it, too. You will never meet anyone messaging one person at a time, and you will depress yourself if you stake any emotions in it whatsoever before a third date. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2011-06-29 18:12:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm planning to publish an eBook myself, which will include, among other things, everything I've posted on here. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Smoke and Mirrors </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2011-06-29 18:05:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I reclined in discomfort across from my small television, which erratically radiated light around my dark room. My pervasive caffeine-withdrawal headache permitted me no other activity that evening, but I could take comfort in knowing that I would be free of the demon in only a few days.

I nearly leapt from the bed at a sudden glass knock behind me. I eyed the blinds over the window nervously. I kept my windows constantly locked after an incident a few months ago, so I kept my wits, decided that it was nothing after a moment of silence, and laid back down amid my pillows and pounding temples.

An hour of fatigued sleeplessness later, a flash of lightning mixed with the varied glow of the television and the windows clattered at the impact of an enormously loud roll of thunder. An instant later, I could hear sheets of rain hitting the window. I loved thunderstorms, so I moved to lift the blinds without thinking.

I found myself looking out from my second-story window on to a bright, sunny day. The trees shifted in a slight breeze, and the park across the street seemed verdant and inviting. How long had I been awake? Where was the thunderstorm that I could still hear? I looked to the television, but it displayed only commercials. I ran to the window in the bathroom down the hall and opened the blinds - it showed only a wall of blasting rain and intermittent flashes of lightning.

At that sight, I turned slowly back to face my room. I could see that brightly-lit window across the hall and through my open door, its sunny glare illuminating the walls in stark contrast to the dim shimmering of the television. I walked toward it in thoughtless confusion, ready to run for my life at the slightest hint of danger... 

I stopped at the threshold of my room, staring at the window. What was I seeing? Was it really there? Was I going insane...? As I watched, I saw something appear beyond the glass. A delicate feminine hand with painted red nails reached down from above the window... and knocked twice.

I ran for the stairs, hearing the storm grow even more intense outside. I headed for the back door, but stopped just short as I saw the warm glow of a summer day emanating from the glass panels to either side. To my right, through the kitchen window, I could still see the storm. I looked back at the door, and could just barely detect the side of someone standing outside. I heard a knock... once, twice, three times... I screamed at it and ran toward the basement door.

... and then it all stopped. The glow from outside was gone, the storm was gone, and everything was quiet and dark. Peeks out of the window showed nothing but a normal night, with the odd car passing on the street. Confused and doubting my sanity, I soon had no choice but go back to watching television with no explanation as to what the hell happened. Still, I can't help but wonder... if there is something outside... some *entity* that can deceive... how do I know the calm night outside isn't a deception, too? How do I know that it's *ever* safe to leave...? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> An Unhappy Awakening </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2011-06-28 22:53:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I woke up that morning to a stinging pain in my eyes. I'd slept in my contacts one too many times, and they felt like burning knives against my eyelids. In a surprised fury, I pulled them out and threw them away. I blinked, now hardly able to see, but felt around for my replacements in my backpack. I silently crept out of my still-sleeping girlfriend's dorm room, gripping the contacts. I'd have to put them in with water.

As I hit the hallway and the door closed and autolocked behind me, something seemed wrong. I silently cursed at getting locked out, and felt an immediate desire to go back inside. I couldn't place what was wrong... it was exceedingly quiet... but it was two days after the last day of finals, and practically everyone else had left for the summer. That was normal, right? My blurry, pained eyes couldn't make out any details...

...but as I slowly walked down the hallway to the men's bathroom at the opposite end of the building, I stepped on a piece of paper. I picked it up and stared closely at it, squinting. It was an announcement that had been on the wall. Peering ahead, I could see that there was paper and refuse strewn about the hallway floor ahead. Bulletin boards had been torn off of the walls... and one of the rectangular ceiling lights twenty feet ahead had been ripped down, and now hung dangerously low, blinking sporadically.

What the hell was going on? Had there been a riot or something during the night? At the very far end of the hallway, maybe a hundred feet away, I could see a disheveled shape leaning against the wall. It was right outside my destination, the men's bathroom... but I couldn't tell what it was, even as it seemed to lazily float or stagger around, not seeming to notice me. It had to be a person, right? But what was it doing in the distance just randomly moving around like that?

Feeling horribly vulnerable but unwilling to go back and wake up my girlfriend because I was scared, I inched forward. I ducked low under the hanging light. Its sporadic humming set me on a nervous edge... and still, I approached the figure at the end of the hall. It hadn't yet acknowledged me in any way, continuing to gently walk or bump repeatedly into one of the walls. What the hell was going on here?

I then had a genius idea. Instead of approaching whoever it was that was acting so oddly, I quietly ducked into a stairwell, and decided to use the men's bathroom on the second floor. I felt incredulous when my squinting eyes and searching hand found the second-floor door out of the stairwell had been ripped off of its hinges and was lying on its side in the doorway. It was then that I felt that something dangerous might actually be going on.

I peeked into the second floor hallway to find it equally in disarray. Half of the lights up here were simply out, shrouding most of the floor in dim morning gloom. I could hear someone murmuring in the distance, around the corner of the hall. My heart pumped with adrenaline as I ran for the bathroom and quietly closed the door behind me. I gazed around the tiled white walls in a panic, but saw nothing. My hands shook, but I used the water from the sink to put on my contacts, and finally relaxed.

Now that I could see, I felt silly at my fear. The relief was shortlived, however, as I stepped out of the bathroom and found that the hallway really had been trashed. I made my way back down the stairs, bumping right into a police officer. After a few questions, he shook his head and explained that I didn't want to go 'out there.'

A student had apparently had some sort of mental breakdown, trashed the building, and committed suicide... and, if I hadn't gone upstairs, I would have blithely walked right up to his body, hanging there in the hallway. The shock hit me hard... the officer said that he had died in the night, but then... admittedly it was bleary-eyed and from down the hall... how had I seen the body moving? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2011-06-27 21:12:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Awesome :) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2011-06-24 21:59:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hah, thanks :) I'd be more than willing to mod here. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2011-06-24 14:34:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Have to agree, unless Gilroy's gets its act together, it's actually damaging the community rather than helping it. I remember how, prior to this last year, it was always the place to go for new people, questions, idea discussions, and so on.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2011-06-23 14:58:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That's what I think must have happened. I think they were crazy or something... or it could have been, of course, GhostBro. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The Unseen Hands </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2011-06-21 18:10:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Greeted by blurry darkness, I slid halfway out of a long dreamworld I was not unhappy to leave behind. As I lay there on my side while my awareness returned, the insistent hand pressed against my bare shoulder blade again. I froze at the realization that my girlfriend hadn't stayed the night - behind me could only have been rumpled sheets and empty space.

My thoughts immediately jumped to the possibility of sleep paralysis, something I'd never experienced, but my subtly tested toes proved that this was all too real. The hand shook me gently again, and I felt the delicate fingers squeeze my shoulder. I could feel now a sense of lazy interest in that grip, not malice or fear... but the hand was oriented as if the other was *sitting hunched on the bed behind me*, not lying down. I could feel no weight or tilt in the mattress underneath me.

The hand moved and shook my arm, growing more insistent. Still, I maintained my charade of slumber... and another hand joined the first, shaking me by the shoulder and arm. My heart pounded as I imagined what horror might be trying to get my attention... and then I felt the hands shift, as if the other had turned and looked behind us.

Suddenly, the grip of those fingers tightened, and the intensity of their shaking turned from lazy interest to one of marked fear. I knew then that I had to act, to do *something*, but... before I could, a third hand of the same size and feel joined the others by shaking my forearm. I leapt up and out of the bed in abject terror, scanning the bed and the room.

My pounding heart reverberated in my ears, but I saw nothing unusual at first glance. After a few moments of fading adrenaline, I felt a slight breeze - the window next to my bed was open behind the blinds. Confused, I climbed up on my bed and slid it shut. This window had been behind me, where the *other* would have looked before it grew fearful. Not one to resist the unknown, I pushed up a blind and peered between.

My eyes first jumped to the white of a passing police car on the street outside, but then to movement to my left - I saw the shocking gray tufts of hair of two disheveled and withered old men, dressed in torn and horrid rags, as they leapt over a fence into the next yard. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2011-06-17 19:50:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Would it be possible to write stories specifically to be heard in this format? And submit sounds to go with them? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2011-06-17 19:36:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> DO NOT DRINK DIET SODA. It is literally poison; along with all sorts of behavioral and psychological effects that cause you to gain MORE weight than if you drank regular soda. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2011-06-16 22:31:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> lol, I don't know why people are somehow thinking the bear was there for 300 years. I was more scared by thinking someone had literally been there moments before our arrival, or was still there in the nearby shadows. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2011-06-16 18:50:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's out somewhere near Grove City. I didn't drive either time - I'll try to find out where it is. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2011-06-16 16:55:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hah, yeah. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2011-06-16 16:06:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [right now!](http://www.reddit.com/r/nosleep/comments/i17xf/the_lonely_grave/) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The Lonely Grave </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2011-06-16 16:01:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Two months after [our first visit to the ancient and forgotten graveyard](http://www.reddit.com/r/nosleep/comments/i0kkl/strangers_in_a_graveyard/), we decided to go back with a friend. Shed heard us talk about the first incident repeatedly, and kept pushing us to take here there. By then, that night of terror seemed like a story that had happened to someone else, so we finally gave in and decided to drive out there. I was also a bit excited to explore that graveyard more, as it had an amazing scary atmosphere.

We also went prepared with flashlights and a newer cellphone whose coverage for that area we verified. I was jaded when it came to fear, but I wasnt stupid. We also made sure to hide our car perfectly, and to be observant on our walk down the old country road. It started raining on us, and the whole thing felt like a terrible idea but we soon realized that the chances of seeing that same mysterious truck again were probably zero. When the chilly drizzle stopped, we started to feel much better, and the rest of the walk went quickly.

As the three of us stepped onto the dirt ridge that led toward the old graveyard, our good cheer faded in favor of quiet apprehension. The place truly was terrifying, now that we could see more of it. The stars were out by then, and the trees were half-bare with oncoming autumn. A slight chill in the air made me shiver as we walked up the long leaf-covered path, approaching the first hill. That hills crest directly melded into the second and bigger hill, whose grassy paths ran up into darkness. The entire double-hill was surrounded by huge skeletal trees whose leaves were almost entirely gone, and everything sat in stark and unmoving silence.

Although wed been drinking on the walk over, my girlfriend and I were quiet. Though that night seemed distant, we both vividly remembered the danger wed been in last time we were here... but our friend had no such qualms. She stumbled around excitedly, looking at gravestones and shouting out her discoveries.

The stones themselves were cracked and weathered, and most were impossible to read. We did locate one of the dates  the name had been scoured away, but the person had died in 1764. That surprised me, as I knew that meant the graveyard literally pre-dated Ohio itself. I had expected the headstones to be from the Civil War era, for some reason.

Our friend picked up a broken piece of headstone and carried it over to us, joking about souvenirs. I shared a glance of discomfort with my girlfriend at this, but we all continued our exploration. We hiked up the larger hill, entering the dark shadows that the crown of trees hung over the older and seemingly sadder section of the graveyard. A distinct feeling of privacy and sorrow seemed built into the worn stone nubs and monoliths that represented long forgotten loved ones.

It was then that the three of us stopped simultaneously at the sight of something strikingly out of place. The graveyard stopped at the crest of the hill, where we were nearly at level with the tops of the more distant trees but we could see, down the slope and almost hidden by the undergrowth, a small headstone set far apart from all of the others. Immediately our friend ran toward it, and we hurriedly followed her in apprehension.

The lonely spot felt decidedly cut off from the graveyard and even more alone, if that was possible. The barely readable inscription had one letter remaining, M, and two dates: 1752 - 1759. The grave was for a young child I began to feel strange but I knew for certain that something was wrong when our friend laughed and looked down. She shone her flashlight on her discovery for us to see: a teddy bear, clean and in perfect condition so much so that someone had to have placed it there recently.

My thoughts immediately grew fearful. Why was this grave set so far apart? Who was this child that had died so tragically young? And, most of all who the hell was visiting this forgotten graveyard in the middle of nowhere to leave a toy at the headstone of a child that had died three hundred years ago? I had no time to guess before our friend reached down. My girlfriend and I both shouted, but it was too late: she picked up the teddy bear.

Immediately, a sharp blast of wind hit the surrounding trees all at once. Against the stark silence that we had grown accustomed to, it sounded like an angry explosion. Our friend screamed, dropped the teddy bear, and ran. My girlfriend followed. The blasting wind in the skeletal trees grew in intensity as I turned to bolt with them  but I turned back for just a moment to replace the teddy bear in its spot.

Our fearful flight turned to nervous laughter as we pelted back down the hill. As the wind continued to rise, we decided it was time to get back to the car before the oncoming storm clouds  sharp black against the stars  decided to drench us. I couldnt resist taking one look back up the hill as we travelled across the dirt ridge

and my eyes focused on something a darker patch in the shaded sorrows we had come from, as if someone was standing there watching us leave. At first, I actually smiled. I was a hardcore skeptic, but the thought that the unknown childs spirit might be watching us go and appreciating our visit was genuinely enticing. Still, I couldnt quite make it out, and I figured it was just a trick of the shadows. As we finally exited onto the country road, I looked back, and a darker patch between the gravestones on the first hill - much closer than before - seemed to catch my eye. My smile faded, and I hurried the girls out of there.

It was on the drive home that the fear really hit us, prompted by something our friend told us. As it began to drizzle again, she suddenly insisted we pull over, and immediately threw up out the opened car door. We asked her what was wrong, and it took a few moments for her to tell us the horrible thing that had occurred to her wed been rained on only a few minutes before we got to the graveyard on foot but the bear the bear shed picked up had been dry. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2011-06-16 14:59:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  Well after getting destroyed in HoN due to my incompetent teammates,

This line is how I know this story is 100% true. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2011-06-16 05:03:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hah, actually, all the scary movies we'd watched advised on exactly what to do: hide where nobody can find you and wait a ridiculously long time. I'm certain we'd be dead (this happened in June of last year) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2011-06-16 05:02:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> We actually did go back to that graveyard with a friend. Some pretty horrifying things happened there, but this time it was on account of the actual graveyard... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2011-06-16 00:51:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yes, got to leave an anonymous tip... will never know what happened </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2011-06-16 00:51:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> No suitable spot for a car to be left at, but the truck just briefly turned around on the beginning of the ridge. The truck was coasting down the slight incline in neutral, I imagine. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2011-06-15 22:50:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Oh lord, it was Videodrome. Most surreal and horrific movie choice *possible*... and awesome. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2011-06-15 22:25:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Wow, this subreddit is like a secret chronicle of my time on Meridian 59. That's me winning that tournament :P </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2011-06-15 22:18:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I got pissed at some of the comments and was about to make one...

Then I see one from myself advertising the game already...

In early 2010...

zomg </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2011-06-15 22:14:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Wow, someone noticed this? That entire page was my crafting. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2011-06-15 22:11:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You'll find a vast amount of otherwise unavailable information there. Also, there's a Meridian 59 subreddit? WTF? :D </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2011-06-15 22:10:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Er... an alarm on other players entering would most definitely be a cheat. The botting parts are legal, though. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Strangers in a Graveyard </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2011-06-15 21:43:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> A girl Id been seeing suggested that, for our third date, we take a bottle of wine, a laptop, and a scary movie to the most remote graveyard we could possibly find. As horror movie aficionados, we both felt jaded and immune to fear so putting ourselves into the ideal situation for terror sounded like an exciting adventure.

The proposed night came, and she drove us an hour out into deep back-country, heading for a graveyard that we had found in ancient public record but which was not on any map. When we finally found its supposed location, we ended up having to park three miles away behind some large undergrowth. There had been no other place to turn off along the forested country road. The night air was cool, though, so the walk wasnt bad.

We walked down a kind of raised ridge of dirt towards the unmarked graveyard, trying not to slip off into the pools of sludge and undergrowth on either side. The trees ringed an open double-hill that led up into darkness, and the century-old gravestones sat about in silence. We set up our laptop on a blanket, unafraid, and started the movie. The atmosphere was powerfully creepy, but I still felt nothing until the unexpected happened.

Less than ten minutes into the movie, we saw a pick-up truck go by on the country road outside the graveyard. We could see its lights through the trees as it passed  the only vehicle wed seen that night. We shrugged, thinking nothing of it until it came back the other way. Its headlights were distinctive. It was definitely the same truck.

When it approached the dirt ridge to the graveyard, moving very slowly, I closed the laptop, and we froze as its headlights fell on us for a moment. The truck backed up, apparently turning around, and then proceeded to park right outside the entrance. We couldnt be sure if they had seen us, and we certainly had no idea what they were doing I suggested we pack up, and my date agreed. We had just gathered all of our things when the truck went dark.

We stood there in the pitch black for a few moments, confused. Who was in the truck? Had they seen us? Were they coming this way? There was no other way out of this graveyard the hill was surrounded by what amounted to impassable swamp. I started imagining how we might escape through it, regardless, but I realized that the attempt would make far too much noise. Wed never make it.

We had no choice. Carrying our stuff, I grabbed her free hand with mine. We crept forward along the dirt ridge, wincing at every dried leaf that our shoes crumpled. I could see the trucks dark outline parked in our path, but I heard nothing. There was nothing else to do but creep past the truck which we did slowly, one silent and carefully placed step at a time. I kept trying to discern shapes inside the truck, but saw nothing but darkness. I looked around constantly, but heard and saw nothing. Still, in the pitch black night, I could hardly see the girl I was with, let alone somebody creeping about or following us

We made it past the truck, but the lack of any incident only increased our fear. Where were the trucks occupants? What were they doing? They had to be out here somewhere meaning we were out here in the middles of the night and nowhere, playing a potentially deadly game of hide and seek. My heart pounded even harder as I led her down the road toward our car. Where the hell were they?

We were maybe half a mile down the road when we heard a scream in the woods  and a distant gunshot. In that moment, we both immediately realized what was happening. The trucks occupants hadnt been here for us at all  but they would never let us leave if they knew we were here. We both started running in total panic, and actually made it another mile or two before we saw the trucks distinctive headlights coming up on us.

I grabbed her, jumped off of the road, and dove into the undergrowth and sludge between the trees. We peered through the bushes, waist deep in mud, and watched the truck go by. To our horror, the truck began to slow  Id dropped the blanket! Theyd seen it on the side of the road!

The truck stopped there, only a few feet away, for what seemed like an hour. At any moment, I expected its occupants to get out and come for us instead, finally, amazingly, it pulled away and sped on down the road. I tried to see its license plate, but couldnt see anything through the glare of its lights. When I was convinced it was gone, we slogged out, and started walking toward our car again.

It was then that I had a horrible thought  what if they had found her car? What if they were waiting there? I talked it over with her, and we decided to find a good hiding spot in the muddy undergrowth and literally wait the entire night. We had heard a gunshot  this was serious. Neither of our cell phones had reception  there was no choice.

The hours passed, and, the longer we felt safe, the sillier we started to think ourselves. There had to have been another explanation, right? Even if there was something horrible going on in the woods, the trucks occupants couldnt have found our car. Or, even if they did, they wouldnt wait so long, would they? After two hours, we almost talked ourselves out of our cold, horrid hiding place  until I heard a slight sound, like shifting gravel. I peered intensely at the road.

It was the same truck  lights off, engine off, rolling ever so slowly along in the night - waiting, looking, and listening for the fools that almost gave themselves up.

It was noon the next day before we felt safe enough to leave our hiding spot, and begin the confused and terrified walk back to civilization. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2011-06-14 14:44:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Whenever I have a bad day I read comments like these ^_^ Thanks guys! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2011-06-14 14:37:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Can't wait to listen to these. I had no idea this was going on and apparently my stories Psychosis and The Basement are part of this/going to be part of this (I'm all for it :)!)

Thanks guys! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2011-06-13 15:05:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> THEN WHO WAS SAND? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2011-06-11 06:40:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The "you might not know everything" argument doesn't work anymore. Like I said, we do know everything now - just not 'why everything.' </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The Basement </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2011-06-08 16:58:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I was home alone for the week, as my family had gone on vacation while I had to stay and work. It was around 2 AM, and I'd stayed up to watch a scary movie in the dark in my basement. I was intent on really scaring myself and seeing how far into terror I could really go - while still knowing I was safe in my own home.

It was then that I heard pounding footsteps on the first floor. This was a common annoying occurrence when my family was home - every time they passed through the front hallway, past the basement door, I heard their footsteps. This time, fear immediately shot through me at the sound. My reflex was to turn the television off immediately... the basement door was up a flight of steps and around a corner, so whoever it was would not have seen any light.

I heard the basement door handle click and turn as I sat in absolute darkness. I moved slowly so as to be absolutely silent, and crawled behind our large television. As I passed it inch by inch, I noted with panic that its black screen still dimly glowed. I heard footsteps coming down the carpeted but creaky stairs.

I froze in my hiding place, listening. For many long minutes, I heard nothing. Had the intruder seen the television's afterglow, or had it faded in time? Was he standing in the pitch dark listening for me? I seemed to lie there in total silence for an interminably long time. My panic began to fade, and I began to think more clearly.

Had I really heard an intruder? Could someone possibly be standing there in silence for so long without making *any* noise? The basement was so exceedingly quiet that the silence itself began to hurt my ears. Could the unknown person really avoid any noise from shuffling or breathing or anything else? If there was an intruder, he was still in the basement, because the creaky stairs were incredibly loud, the door handle clicked, and he wouldn't know to mask his footsteps on the first floor so that they couldn't be heard down here...

I began counting in my head trying to pass the time, as drool fell from my mouth onto the carpet - I didn't dare risk the sound of swallowing. I reached sixty seconds once, twice... thirty times... sixty times... by now my fear had faded and I was more confused than anything. I estimated I'd been crouched in the absolute black for almost two hours, and had still heard nothing. If there was an intruder, none of this made sense... finally, I decided I'd have to make a move. If I did nothing, eventually the sun would come up, and shine in through the small basement windows... and, worse, I began to smell something horrible and cloying.

Slowly, ever so slowly, I began inching my way towards the stairs by way of the walls. If someone was standing there in the dark, I should be able to go around them and then make a break up the stairs... meanwhile, the horrible odor grew stronger. Had something died down here in the night? No living person would smell like that... terrible images of some sort of corpse-monster listening for me in the dark erupted in my thoughts, and I moved as fast as I could without making a sound.

Just as I finally approached the stairs, there was an enormous clatter, as of something falling or collapsing on the floor. It was at that moment I leapt forward and crashed up the stairs, running out through the open basement door and my wide-open front door. Now certain that someone was in the house, I called the police from my cellphone and watched my house from afar.

The police came, checked inside the house, and then grimly came back out to question me. They'd found a body in the house - my elderly neighbor, who seemed to have died of a heart attack. Their belief was that I must have left the front door unlocked, and he must have wandered in my house while dying, looking for help. At first, I felt horrible, thinking that I had sat there in the dark while the old man literally died a few feet away.

Then it occurred to me - what the hell was that loud noise of things falling, that last prompted me to bolt up the stairs and out of the house? I asked the police and they confirmed - the back door of my house had been left open as well, near a single bare footprint in the mud. Somehow, for some reason I'll never know, there was someone else in that basement with us... silent, waiting, and listening in the dark over the fresh corpse of an old man. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The hungry lights </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2011-06-07 17:30:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I can't stand the new LED Christmas lights that debuted a few years ago. I'm the only one among my friends that holds this opinion, and it's a bone of contention during holiday time... but I can't bring myself to tell them why certain previously-unseen colors of light fill me with uncontrollable dread.

I had almost forgotten the incidents... a few more years, and they might have been lost in the fog of childhood forever. When I first saw that unreal color in the new lights, my memories sparked, and I remembered everything.

My room was on the back of the first floor of our house, then. We lived fairly far out from the city, and our back yard was old Florida swamp - filled with age-old twisted trees and thick underbrush. My childhood was not altogether happy, but I got through the bad times by lying in bed at night and watching the swamp from my window. Something about its quiet immensity always made me calm... and that sentiment is probably why I reacted to the first incident with only curiosity.

I wasn't sure what I was seeing the first night. While the vast darkness between the trees roiled with storm, I began seeing movement that was not part of the rain and wind. It was barely detectable at first, and I had to look away and see it out of the corners of my vision. As it grew closer, I began to realize I was seeing light of some kind - a strange color and cast that seemed somehow impossible to me. Even then, I couldn't describe it until I got my first clear look at it - the next night, as the hurricane grew to dangerous strength.

I remember that moment vividly. I peered from between my curtains in my dark room, observing from what I felt was a safe hiding spot from the storm. I had been observing the phenomenon for almost an hour... but only felt fear when I finally saw it clearly.

A hundred feet deep in the undergrowth, through the wind and rain, a point moved above the ground. It smoldered with a strange sort of un-purple that seemed to pull in and crush light rather than radiate it. It moved laterally deeper into the swamp, seeming to bob slightly maybe ten feet off of the ground. As it moved off and disappeared, I realized that my curious game had become all too real. Still, I couldn't resist peeking out my window again the next night, which I now know in retrospect was the worst night of Hurricane Andrew. The storm was fierce, and battered the trees mercilessly. Our house creaked and groaned constantly with the force of the wind. Engrossed in my investigation, I hardly noticed.

This time, I had binoculars. When I saw the un-purple radiating darkness again, I watched it closely. It seemed to be less a point and more a half-circle of some kind... I stared intently at it until it suddenly stopped, something I had never seen it do... and the half-circle moved and became a full circle. Confused, I dropped my binoculars, and they clattered to the floor. It was then that I saw a second light near the first, a deep bright blue point that made my vision feel strange in a different way than the purple darklight.

It was then that I realized what I was looking at. Ten feet off of the ground, among the storm-battered trees, I was seeing an impossible pair of eyes... and they were looking right at my hiding spot. The mismatched points of light began to bob and grow in size and seeming  malevolence... approaching my curtained window.

It was then that I was scooped up from behind, screaming, and carried out of the house by my father. Stinging rain and lashing wind blasted us painfully as he ran us to the car, and then drove our family to a storm shelter.

I was never able to get the straight story out of my father about why he suddenly chose to change his stubborn opinion about staying home despite the storm, or why he chose to evacuate us to safety at that moment. What I did remember, before the new colors in LED lights jogged my nightmarish memories, was that we returned two days later, after the hurricane had passed... to find the back of our house seemingly imploded, its contents inexplicably thrown about hundreds of feet in the opposite direction of the damage, and my room completely gone.

My father decided to use the insurance money from the 'storm damage' to move us cross-country, and I have never been back. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The television </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2011-06-03 15:54:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> After we moved into our new house around fifteen years ago, I used to fall asleep listening to the comforting sounds of the television downstairs. I figured my parents watched it long past my bedtime. They had no idea I could hear them, and I never mentioned it to them.

I would listen to the muted voices as they switched between different tones of conversation, though I was never able to make out the words. These conversations were below the threshold of hearing, but the random noise in my ears definitely carried the markers of human voices. The more I listened, the more they gained definition, but they were always ethereal and impossible to decipher.

I imagined it was often some sort of news program, as the conversations didn't seem very emotional and they talked for hours on end in the same monotone - but, every so often, my parents must have watched a scary movie, because sometimes the voices were terrified, angry, or even screaming.

In fact, I soon began to suspect they were watching the same scary movie over and over again through the years... as I would hear the same 'sound bites', the most recognizable being a twenty-second conversation between two men and a woman that grew into a heated argument and ended with the woman screaming in terror - before being cut off abruptly. This movie had that sound bite play multiple times before I would fall asleep, and I often wondered if I was hearing it right. What could the plot of this movie possibly be, to have the same argument and screaming so many times?

Finally, when I was older and had experienced years of this ongoing sleepy confusion, I suddenly awoke and decided that this night I would confront my parents about exactly what the hell it was they were watching. I had heard the same muted argument and barely-heard screaming get cut off only moments ago, so I knew it was *that* movie.

In a righteous indignation, I opened my door to head downstairs and confront them - and then froze. The hallway was black. The house was silent. The living room was empty... and the television was off.

Completely in shock, my thoughts raced as I tried to make sense of the last several years' sleepy experiences. I laid back down in bed, burning with adrenaline, and shivered as the barely audible voices resumed. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Strange things: Theories </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2011-06-01 22:12:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I used some of my Memorial Weekend to further investigate [whats been happening](http://www.reddit.com/r/nosleep/comments/hk3wm/strange_things_investigation/), and I found some interesting facts. The geography behind my building involves a few miles of heavy forest, struck through by a large abrupt canyon  a feature that Ohio residents are probably familiar with. The canyon causes a natural wedge between developed areas, and on the other side of this untouched wilderness is a major construction site.

My initial theory was that infrasound from that construction site caused the things I experienced last week. There are [articles](http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Infrasound) that detail how infrasound can cause unexplainable fear and other sensations, and perhaps infrasound had something to do with the spontaneous opening of the doors. The loud impact on one of the windows still went unexplained, but that could have been anything.

Tuesdays events made me question the simplicity of my answer. Confident in my explanation, I walked the back hallways at 8 AM. I felt the inexplicable fear as I expected, and could even detect the illusory motion sensation again when I looked out at the trees. I paced along the tinted windows, feeling the invisible wellspring of fear and vertigo seem to follow me keeping step with me just beyond the glass. I felt intensely watched, despite knowing that the windows should only show a reflection from the outside.

Even knowing that it was just a reaction to infrasound, the fear was still very real, and hard to handle. I decided to overcome it once and for all by stepping outside during the 10 AM event. When the fear and vertigo came, and it began to follow me along the back windows again, I walked down to the side door usually used by maintenance. It was metal and rectangular, and had a traditional handle. The fear was more muted here away from the windows, but I could still feel it, and my thoughts ran through all sorts of horrible things that could be on the other side of the door.

Still, I knew there was nothing out there. Even if there was, its not like it could have even seen me to follow me as I imagined it had been doing. I was about to open the outwardly-locked door when something occurred to me the windows were only reflective from a distance. Up close, they could be seen through. Something up against the glass could have been staring right at me the entire time so I hesitated.

The door shook.

I ran back down the hallway in a panic and watched it from around a corner. I watched the handle in intense fear  real fear this time  but nothing further happened. The more my thoughts analyzed the sound, the more I became convinced that it was the same impact I had heard on a window last week and it had come from outside. I was careful to stay away from the windows during the 3 PM event, but I heard another impact on that same door around that time.

Today, Wednesday, I stayed at my desk through the first half of the day. I felt slight waves of fear at 8 and 10, but I couldnt be sure if it was my imagination. I spent the entire day configuring ideas in my head, trying to make sense of things. I couldnt accept infrasound as the cause of physical impacts but certain symptoms of what I was experiencing definitely matched. I finally came up with something that got past my cynical mental armor and actually shocked me to my core.

What if there really is some sort of entity out there in the woods? The area is completely undeveloped, rarely traveled, and heavily forested something old or strange could certainly exist there. What if the infrasound symptoms Im experiencing arent from the construction a few miles away, but *from the entity itself*, and its being driven out of its natural habitat by the constructions infrasound pollution?

Whatever it is, it doesnt seem to understand what a building is, as it hasnt tried other sides of the structure yet  like the front doors  but it does seem to have a sort of animal intellect, enough to understand that I am something alive inside some sort of shelter and its trying to get inside. At todays 3 PM event, I stood at the two sets of glass double doors that originally opened by themselves last week, and watched the forest.

I stood there, in what was probably a very stupid move, and felt the fear and vertigo approach. As terrifying as the result of that move was, I now know for sure that something more is going on. As I stood there, watching empty space that made me feel heady, the outer doors slid open of their own accord. Last week, the inner doors were then pulled apart as far as their short locking mechanism allowed.

This time they didnt move.

The outer doors stayed open for almost two minutes. I felt paralyzed, struck through by my painfully beating heart, but I continued to stare at the nothing that was standing there staring back at me. I feel that somewhere in that long moment was a clear declaration of intent on both our parts acknowledgement that the game of cat and mouse wed been playing had just gotten serious. Then, the fear faded, and the doors slid closed again. That was an hour ago.

Im engaged in this now. Ive never believed in anything strange or paranormal  not for real  but now Im dead certain something is happening. Im going to look into getting a camera and audio equipment, and Im going to try to collect actual evidence on this. Theres nothing more to say for now, except that I feel like Im going to war. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Strange things: Investigation </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2011-05-25 23:14:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I've never experienced something creepy yet truly unexplainable, so this morning I decided to investigate [what happened yesterday](http://www.reddit.com/r/nosleep/comments/hj326/strange_things/). My first instinct, of course, was to check the door from the inside when I first arrived. I thought that some sort of air pressure or mechanical failure might have caused the doors to attempt to open on their own, though the powerful fear and urge to hide was still inexplicable.

I pried the inner doors open to their limit while locked, the same quarter inch I'd seen yesterday. They were heavy enough that I can't accept air pressure as the cause... two sets of sealed glass doors simply wouldn't respond to pressure fluctuations by opening sideways... and the outer doors slid open by sensor activation yesterday, not by force. The problem, of course, is that I saw nothing at the doors that would have activated them one time, let alone three. Also, looking up - the mechanisms for each door were separate. Mechanical failure on one should have had no effect on the other.

I wasn't prepared to actually open the doors yet, as I still felt lingering traces of the unexplainable fear from yesterday. Instead, I opted to look through the glass and see what I could of the lonely back area that I'd never actually been in. As I expected, I could see a bit of old sidewalk and some grass that ended abruptly at a towering wall of old-growth trees about twenty feet away from my building. I was a bit relieved at seeing the cut grass, as that meant someone had to go back there and mow it every week or so...

As I stood there, I began to feel uncomfortable. The trees seemed to crowd closer with gloom, and I found myself staring into the thick underbrush. I had the strangest impression that I was seeing fragments of movement among the thick leaves, but couldn't pinpoint anything concrete in the seemingly motionless thicket. I'd most closely relate the sensation to that felt when looking at an [illusory motion image](http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/File:Motion_illusion_in_star_arrangement.png). The vertigo passed after a few moments. This was around 8 AM, the time of the first door incident yesterday. Nothing else happened at that time, but it occurred to me that, standing in the door as I was, I was highly visible from a distance.

That realization, of course, inspired me to watch the doors more discretely at 10 AM, the time of yesterday's second incident. I watched the doors intently, but nothing happened for a long while... until my vigil was interrupted by a loud impact on glass, as if something had bounced off of a nearby window. It sounded like it came from a little further down the side of the building, rather than the door. I did check each of the darkly tinted office windows in the nearby back hallways, but none showed any signs of damage. Not the same event as yesterday, but the timing was oddly coincidental...

The third incident yesterday happened around 3 PM. Today, the third incident convinced me that something really might be happening... I was walking the back halls around that time, hoping to see or hear the thud from earlier, when I felt that familiar fear that I should run and hide. There was nothing between me and the outside but a series of long windows... but they were tinted, and should look like nothing but reflections from the outside. I fought the urge to run away, and instead ever so slowly approached the windows. The apprehension in me was a powerful single note that kept rising the closer that I got... but when I stopped moving inches from the glass, it did not. The fear rose to an almost unbearable level, and then... leveled off at just below total panic.

Confused, I looked back and forth, scrutinizing the shaded sidewalk and grass while my heart pounded painfully. The treeline towered closer here, covering the corner of the building in gloom. It seemed like a perfectly ordinary day outside, yet looking out there made me feel slightly disoriented, like the illusory-motion feeling from before... and then I understood what I was feeling. If I was unconsciously reacting to the presence of something outside, I knew now why the feeling had leveled off... it had stopped moving.

Right in front of me.

I'd been staring right at it...

I, of course, leapt away like a startled animal and bolted to my desk, while the uncontrollable fear faded with distance. I huddled here, hiding, for the remainder of the day. Now I'm sitting here trying to think it through - my coworkers all left 15 minutes ago, at 5 PM. I still haven't seen anything unexplainable. Maybe I'm just playing to my own fears. Still, I feel watched... circled... as if something out there in the woods is trying to figure out a way in... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Strange things </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2011-05-24 20:17:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Never had the opportunity to write about something creepy as it's happening... and it's definitely not at all what you'd expect. I'm in my office building right now, broad daylight, open windows, sunny outside, coworkers sort of nearby... but I sit closest to the back entrance of the building, which is comprised of two automatically opening double doors made of glass.

The outer glass doors slide open if anyone walks near them. The inner ones are always locked and someone has to walk up and use a remote to open them for visitors, as there are very few walk-ins at a financial company like ours. We're also in the back of an office park, so the area is very nice and filled with tall trees, but very lonely and empty. Directly outside the back entrance, an old-growth forest stretches away for miles.

I was inspired to start writing about what I've seen today after it happened for a third time, just now. Twice today, once at around 8 am, and once at 10 am, I saw the outer doors open spontaneously. I am the only one that can see them from where I sit, and I'm partially hidden behind a plant that I put up in my cubicle so the rare visitor wouldn't see me and assume I was a secretary or something. I've worked here for a year, and never seen those doors open by themselves... but that's not the weird part.

All three times today that I've seen this happen, a few moments later the inner doors clinked against their locking mechanism and I could see them split apart about a quarter of an inch - as far as the lock allowed. I've now sat here and watched the phenomenon three times, and these doors are completely transparent, so I can see that nobody's there...

Each time, I also felt overwhelming fear and the urge to hide in the corner of my cubicle behind the obscuring plant. At first I chalked it up to playing along with my inner child, but I realize now that I felt the inexplicable fear at the first occurrence, too... before I knew something weird was happening. It's like my animal brain is terrified of something over there, something testing the doors, something looking in through the glass... something from the dim forest behind the building, testing the edges of civilization, looking in on another world... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The Lodge </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2011-04-29 16:07:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It was our second night at the old hunters lodge that it happened. Im not clear on who owned it at the time; but we had borrowed the keys from a friend of a friend who let people vacation there from time to time.

The only thing he told us was to stay out of the unfinished basement, as it hadnt been used in years, and there was old hunters gear down there that could be dangerous. The door was locked and the key had been lost, regardless, so we didnt even think about it as we unpacked and explored the place wed be spending a relaxing week at.

I was in a very happy mood that second night, as my family and I sat around the bonfire eating hamburgers and telling scary stories. My younger sister had gone inside to change into warmer clothes and had been gone for a few minutes when I went inside to get another drink. Upon entering, I immediately saw the basement door sitting a good two inches ajar.

My thoughts jumped to the mundane dangers that I had been told about, and I knew I had to get my eight-year-old sister out of there. Opening the door wider, I stared down the tilted wooden steps, wondering what she was doing in the dark. I flipped the old dirt-encrusted light switch, but nothing happened.

Hello? I projected loudly down the stairs.

A strange sound of moving air came first in reply, as if a furnace pipe had sprung a leak and then I heard her.

Hey! came my sisters small, high voice. Come down here!

Perplexed and worried, I slowly stepped down the rotten wooden steps and onto the dirt floor. My feet crunched the glass of a broken light bulb one mystery solved. The furnace breathed and pulsed like the lodges heart somewhere in the darkness, making it difficult for me to listen for my sister.

Where are you? I asked to my left, where I thought I had heard her.

Over here, she said, from my right. Im stuck!

Now my heart pounded with fear for her safety. I slowly inched toward her, not wanting to injure myself on old hunting gear. As I moved, the deep breathing of the furnace grew louder, and I slowly became completely disoriented in the warm, flowing pitch black. For many long, terrible moments, I had no idea where I was. I only knew that I had to keep going forward and rescue my little sister.

Right there! she said, very close now. Could she see my silhouette against the dim light from the stairway? That surely must have been thirty or forty feet away by then, for as far as Id crept and for how long it took. How big was the basement?

My face brushed against something metal, hanging on what seemed to be a wooden structural post. It was flat and round, and very rusty. It had given very slightly when my nose bumped it in the dark, and it was only the rust that had prevented it from moving further.

Thats the latch! she said loudly, trying to be heard over the heated air from the now-roaring furnace right next to us. What was she stuck in? I couldnt understand.

Press it! she said, and I put my hand up to it, touching its ingrained patterns of rust.

I paused, trying to figure out what she might be stuck in that would have a latch on the wall. I figured she must know, so I began to press it.

Hey, whos down there? came a voice from above the stairs my sisters.

My hand snapped back. My instincts had told me something was terribly wrong; now I knew.

Im stuck! said the voice right next to me, also my sisters. Press it!

I stumbled backward, scrambling in the dirt toward the stairs. A blast of warm, humid air followed me almost up the steps as I burst out, covered in cobwebs and dust. My sister stood there, confused and scared. I breathed heavily, but kept my story to myself until I found my father.

In the morning, we went downstairs to investigate. My father didnt believe me at first, even as I found several details that chilled me to the bone. First, the furnace was in a back room on the first floor  not in the basement. What Id mistaken for a furnace, with its massive breath and warm, moist air, Ill never know. My father chalked this up to faulty ducts or my imagination.

Second, the basement was only about ten feet wide. Again, my father suggested that I had simply become disoriented in the dark and miscalculated how far Id gone.

The third and final detail, however, silenced his arguments with grim impact. Hanging on a post was the object Id touched first with my face, and then my hand. The voice had wanted me to press the center piece, and both my father and I could plainly see where Id rubbed some of the dirt and rust off of it. The object hung there with grim menace, impossible and terrifying. I felt my face compulsively to reassure myself that I was actually alright. Id touched a latch, as the voice had said, but it was not for what it had claimed.

It was the release for a bear trap, hanging where a hunter must have placed it many years ago, but inexplicably left loaded and ready to snap shut </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
