<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject7993</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-18 00:32:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> In English quebec it's called a "soft drink" </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-13 00:07:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Reddit noob here, I've gotten lost following the white rabbit... I started with Keanu... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-08 21:27:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I don't think I would give any. First there no guarantee that if I gave 5 years I'd live long enough to spending it. It could die that next day. Also seeing my parents with their grandkids is special, thinking that my dad took 5 years away from my child having a grandpa doesn't seem worth any sum of money to me personally. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-07 18:11:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> On work trips our meal per diem was automatically added to our pay. We could eat less, more or make our own food when we rented condos. The money was the same, 70$/day </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-02 19:38:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What is in a hot dog?
 I will never google this and in fact I will not check the replies to this thread incase someone decides to enlighten me. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-02 16:10:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> 100% of time in a superbowl you make Belichick's call and it works </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-31 19:30:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Since it sounds like you didn't put the milk in yet do this. Go and borrow a spaceship threaten with the golf cub if necessary , Travel to the nearest galaxy at exactly 5mph past light-speed. This will take you back in time to a point when you had spoons. 
Use chocolate milk, it will taste better, </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-12-26 02:42:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> When I created the account I was just looking for something that was definitely not taken. As I habs fan I should have taken something for their rich history but I wasn't  feeling creative at the time either. The username does suck. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-12-24 17:01:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm not saying that android is better. This isn't comparison post. It's simply my thoughts after a week with android. Lg g2 with mod camera is superior to my 4s and I have a the apps I need. Google integration is surprisingly useful. The point of my post is that I immediately thought " must jailbreak" upon putting hands on the phone. It wasn't as necessary as being on an iPhone.
Tl:dr; android is not better or worse. Just easier to customize in my opinion. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Thoughts from a long time iOS user who recently switched to Android. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-12-24 16:34:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Tl:Dr; made the switch immediately rooted. Realized that I was conditioned to by iOS. Didn't Need to root 90% of wanted "tweaks" available out of the box.

I'll probably get downloaded down to h*ll but here I go:)
I had a 4s with iOS 8.1.1. Jailbroken and tweaked to my liking. Recently I wanted to upgrade my phone. I didn't have the money to buy an iPhone 6 outright and I had a great plan that I didn't want to change so subsiding was out. I was looking for a used phone when came across the LG G2 32gb for a great price. It had a 5.2" screen but no ad slot. Being a Apple user I was used to not having expandable memory. I bought it and started my android journey. My first act was to research and root my phone, Which I did. After playing around I quickly realized that I could do most things out of the box. Themes, installing unsigned apps, changing fonts, system sounds, default apps, icon layout, having more than 4 dock icons, Plex, Chromecast mirroring, stock notifications manager was good and a few more things.
Apple had conditioned me to immediately jailbreak any phone I get. It wasn't necessary with this phone. I love iOS, its great. I gave my wife my new phone and she gave it back after about a minute saying "that's way too complicated for me" Which it was:) I appreciate the guided experience with iOS it's perfect for most people and I still recommend the iPhone to everyone however android is a power users dream.
I did keep root access so I could change the camera driver and to install xposed framework which is similar to Flex.
Anyways the post is just to share my thoughts, when the iPhone 6plus comes down in price I'll probably which back to iOS. Apple simply makes superior hardware. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-12-16 19:46:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I disagree.

iOS 7 = Forest Gump

Win XP/7 =  Dustin Hoffman 's "Rainman"

Windows 8 = Full Retard </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-12-16 19:22:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Making a joke about death, dying or pregnancy rarely ends well. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-12-16 19:01:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> To Kill a Mockingbird ended the same way... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-12-15 15:16:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> TIL that I was just being an ignorant dick for laughing at many items with a "gluten-free" tag on it.

Edit: I'm referring to myself not the OP Btw :) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-12-15 15:05:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> In my country our format is dd/mm/yr, so there's nothing special about that day... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-12-14 03:37:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> "Your Mom is hard"
FTFY </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-12-11 08:41:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I watched ceremony on YouTube because I missed it live. I saw that was 14mins long and I expected to watch some and skip through most of it. However I ended up watching every second of it. I read the comments below of people saying how moving it was and how it brought tears to their eyes and thought they were being dramatic. But when the moment of silence came it was so quiet and I could feel the emotion I found myself sitting their with tears rolling down my face. It was totally unexpected. 
It was so well done and Mr. Beliveau was such a great man that any sports fan should watch it.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-12-11 08:33:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I watched ceremony on YouTube because I missed it live. I saw that was 14mins long and I expected to watch some and skip through most of it. However I ended up watching every second of it. I read the comments below of people saying how moving it was and how it brought tears to their eyes and thought they were being dramatic. But when the moment of silence came it was so quiet and I could feel the emotion I found myself sitting their with tears rolling down my face. It was totally unexpected. 
It was so well done and Mr. Beliveau was such a great man that any sports fan should watch it.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-12-11 03:09:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I see what you did there </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Has winterboard been updated to iOS 8? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-11-24 22:41:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-11-24 15:45:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Dodecahedron my friends. The only way to go is with the "do" </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-11-22 04:52:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I run home sharing from my P4 2.8 Win 7 machine. The PC itself struggles with 720p but through iTunes home sharing to my ATV 3 I get 1080p smooth as butter:)
Plus AirPlay for big screen gaming, I love my Apple TV! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-11-21 14:58:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This whole comment thread is why I love reddit :)
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Nintendo games on iOS anytime before pigs fly? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-11-21 14:39:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-11-20 20:23:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Super Hexagon. I know that it's made to be hard. I lasted 48 seconds on the "easiest"  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-11-20 18:23:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thanks, I fixed it :) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-11-20 17:12:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm old, Burgertime any version. I first played it the Coleco Vision. It was impossible. A close second is NES Commando </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-11-20 17:08:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I found NES ghouls and ghost just as hard. The way they taunted you by showing you  how little progress you actually made after repeatedly dying ... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-11-20 16:48:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I also enjoy console gaming and you have a great setup. My biggest gaming regret is trading my Chronotrigger cart for Tecmo Super Bowl 3 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Goldeneye N64 still rocks!! </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-11-20 16:19:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I recently brought out my N64 for my son because our Wii was broken.  Played some games and then Goldeneye. I had fun with him. Last night my brother and some friends came over and we played. Once we started we were hooked. Four 40ish old men yelling and arguing like kids ( one of them tried to use Oddjob, we all yelled "No" simultaneously.) We played until 1am.
It reminds of  the one gamer truth. 
A good game is a good game. 

Edit: A good game is a good game. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-11-19 23:30:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You guys must be parents :) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-11-19 23:29:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Forgot all about that! She loves paintball too :) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-11-19 23:28:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Okay, some of you are not understand this properly. My wife was mad because her son talking about killing and shooting people doesn't make her happy. I'd feel the same why if I came home and found my 6 year old daughter in full make-up and high heels. She is by no means a "bitch" or " my mother" 
She was mad, I understand why and accept it.  Bottom line is we're definitely going to play again, she'll get over it. 
P.S. Back in the day I remember by owned by a 4 year old kid. He was awesome :) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> TIFU by letting my son play Goldeneye </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-11-19 17:35:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> My son is 5 years old and loves video games. We don't let him play often, only on weekends, because he gets carried away and he cries when he has to stop. (We understand that he's a kid..) We have a Wii but it's broken right now. He's been really good so last weekend I bust out my N64 for him to try. We play some Mario Tennis, F-Zero, Snowboard Kids and Conker's Bad Fur Day multiplayer. Now Conker's was borderline inappropriate but it was still "cartoony" so it was OK. 
Then I see Goldeneye. Those of you of a certain age know about Goldeneye, it was the COD of our time. Great memories were made ,4 people one screen... ahh the good old days. Anyway I decide to share this experience with my son. We play, we have hunting each other down with machine guns, proximity mines, grenades, sniper rifles. After about 20 mins we stop and put it a away.
My wife comes home from the store and my son runs up to her and tells her all about the new games I found. Of course his favorite is Goldeneye and he goes on and on about how we shot each other and blew up people and how is favorite gun is the gold one because it kills the fastest. 
My wife is listening, nodding , smiling but   she gives me the "look". 
Now I'm in the doghouse, no lovin' tonight ;) I know it was not appropriate for him but it was damn fun though. 

TL;DR: Played  N64 FPS Goldeneye with my too young 5 year old son. We had fun. He told Mom gory details. I'm in doghouse. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-11-19 03:55:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Living the dream with my NES and SNES emulators. Currently playing FFVI. (And yes I own the original carts) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-11-18 16:21:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Try r/writingprompts </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-11-18 16:17:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That'd both amazing and frightening.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-11-17 19:35:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> While I dislike the freemium model, I have played candy crush and have enjoyed it.  I know plenty of people who are definitely not "gamers" but have put many many hours into it without spending a time. These same people don't understand why I can put so much time in to FF3, Super Hexagon or Device 6. Personally I believe that freemium games = Adam Sandler movies, I get why people enjoy them and why  they make a lot of money.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> DAE find blue LED lights uncomfortable to look at? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-11-17 03:04:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Whenever I see blue LEDs such as Christmas lights or on signs I find that I have to squint or look away. I feel like the vibrations they give off hurt my eyes </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-11-14 15:50:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> These days I alternate between Chronotrigger and FF VI on my SNES emulator. Sometimes I play a random NES game, so many surprises. I just discovered R.C. Pro-AM :) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-11-14 15:45:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Five nights at Freddie's 2 !!!! I loved the first one and it was just released for the PC recently  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-11-04 04:14:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Not to get too geeky but to me it seems like you said "fuck you " </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-10-31 15:39:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I rarely do on a Windows PC but I always eject first on a Mac. Even if I'm using iTunes on a PC I always eject first. Now that I think about it I don't know why I behave this way. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-10-16 17:15:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I couldn't watch more than 1 minute, I wish that somehow George Carlin could have walked in to the audience partway through. This guy would have seen the ponytail and started to go off on him. George Carlin would have ripped him up in such epic proportions, THAT would have cringeworthy gold. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-10-14 20:17:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Douchebag </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> I got bored waiting for the protagonist to finish his speech so I decided to climb through the window in the four wall. I didn't realize how ugly women were on this side... </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-10-13 20:12:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
