<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject4819</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Oh my god. I really liked Deadpool and have realized I want more superhero movies like this [SPOILERS] </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-30 01:31:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Unconventional while conventional at the same time.

More comic book movies with little known characters with different backstories to the overly well known "my parents are dead" or "my planet fitness was destroyed" or "with great powder comes great clam chowder" and whatnot.

I mean it's still a conventional story, it's just told in such an unconventional way (which is surprising considering it's 2016) and I love that about the movie. 

I mean, I thought the story would be bigger like maybe Morena's character is actually a mutant or Deadpool breaks up a high conspiracy organization's  giant factory of mutants or some shit like that but nope, it's all about him just wanting to be with his love. You'd think one would not like such a simple story but it's likable, and dare I say it, actually charming. Something I was not expecting at all.

Even the sex scenes, are actually really sweet. Usually an R rating or such means springing for lots of titillation but without any love thinking "oh gross we don't want love we just want boobies" but I thought it was incredibly romantic how they used sex as actually part of establishing a relationship, part of the actual human experience, because yes sex is a part of that, a part of loving someone, and I thought that came across very well, especially because of how they are actually together even after he is suffering from cancer and stuff. 


All in all, I really liked this movie and while I had a feeling that I would, I did not know I would find it so charming.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> This scene is one of my favorites simply for the Alec Baldwin HD at the end. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-26 01:24:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> "The Dr Wen sketch isn't working, we have to cut it" (from My Sketch Show) </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-26 00:29:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Lol that does make me wonder what exactly is it about Dr Wen that made the director cut him, was there a problem with the actor, problems on set, or did he just not find the actor funny?

I always assumed Dr Wen was supposed to be more grounded to contrast with the bizarreness of the rest of the hospital and staff.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The Nightman Cometh may have been my first episode, but The Gang Dances Their Asses Off is still the greatest finale of all time. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-25 20:23:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> These are well regarded as some of the toppiest tippity top season finales of all time.

I love nightman because it's the very first episode I ever saw, just a random episode from this show I knew nothing about, and I initially thought the premise was "struggling/out of work actors doing an  off off off-broadway type musical" due to the nature of the episode, before finding out the actual premise as I watched the older episodes.

But The Gang Dances Their Asses Off is still the best finale of the show, full of scheming, an excellent plot, hilarious scenes (I can't not laugh at "I'm throwing my cream all over his face/I'm about to show you the white hot cream of an 8th grade boy" every single time) and a great representation of the characters. It's fantastic.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Ya know... current Dennis would have no problems banging old ladies and then eventually moving on to dudes. Just saying. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-25 18:55:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Things have changed from season 3 the gang gets whacked, I think Dennis in his current form would work the prostitution angle again if it's brought up.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> I just love Violette Pure/Pink [pic] </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-25 16:28:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Louis CK goodbye jews does anyone have the actual video to accompany the bit? All I could find on youtube was this audio version. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-22 23:58:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=rGfDXMnQw7g

But I could have sworn I encountered the actual video on youtube 3 years ago, now for the life of me I can't find it.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Arrested Development doesn't make any sense (Major Spoilers beware!) </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-22 20:47:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Why wouldn't GOB want to sleep with Kitty? She's not an unattractive person, no matter how the show tries to convince us otherwise. She's a cutie. 

The only way GOB would feel uncomfortable sleeping with her is if he has qualms about sharing his father's sloppy seconds, but GOB doesn't seem like the type to care about that... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Star Burns is part of the cool group with Owen Wilson? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-21 23:33:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That's just insane!  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Just for the record did Heatherfeather pretty much pioneer the sk sk sound for asmr? [Discussion] </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-21 02:05:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> In the wake of all these new people springing up overnight the last few years making their own asmr, a ton have adopted the sk sk sk sound for at least one of their videos, and I'm wondering if the credit belongs to Heatherfeather for it   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Which episode where Charlie is handling the ice and the gang tells him to wear gloves? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-21 01:04:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Something about cleaning the bathrooms and then directly handling the ice with his bare hands </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> How much older is Charlie from Dennis and Dee? Maybe Frank isn't his father after all... </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-21 00:09:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Didn't Charlie go to the same high school as Dennis and Mac and Dee? Even if they were a few years apart in age, it would mean Frank had the affair with Bonnie a lot later in life and when he was married or close to married to Barbara (which isn't an impossibility I admit)

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> I don't think Mentos explosion works with diet Coke/Coca cola light... </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-18 21:53:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I mean, at least when last we tried it 12 years ago. Hehe what an old and very innocently childlike joke... that was a nice set up. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> So JD considers Kylie's boyfriend a sleazeball because he cheated on her right? (safety spoilers) </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-18 15:05:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The guy slept with another girl, got gonorrhea, ok. 

*A few episodes later in season 4*

JD is about to cheat on Kylie by sleeping with Molly. I always found that hilariously ironic that he thought that other boyfriend was a jerk and yet he was about to do the same thing. And it was ultimately his undoing even if he didn't sleep with Molly because Kylie broke up with him anyway.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Something amusing happened at the boardwalk today </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-18 10:33:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I was walking with my friend on the boardwalk and there were a bunch of rowdy guys sitting by some steps/benches just goofing off right. 

They were pretty loud and stuff, when suddenly these 2 women in rollerblades/rollerskates passed by, moving really slowly and chatting with each other. Now, these were extremely attractive women. And not just regular hot women which you see every day at the beach or whatever, they were wearing very low amount of clothes and had that young/jailbait look of hotness, that makes them increasingly more desirable. 

Anyway the amusing thing is that these rowdy guys goofing off and making a lot of noise all of a sudden just... stopped. They just stopped, and all eyes were on these 2 girls. One of the guys even had his chin literally hang and his mouth open a bit. 

I was talking to my friend during this time and I saw the women, then saw the guys' reaction to the women, and after walking a couple of paces I couldn't help bursting out laughing at how perfectly picturesque that scene was. It was like something out of a cheesy high schoolish movie.

My friend is gay (and a bit vain, though not without good reason since he's incredibly good looking) so he thought the guys were staring at him and he couldn't appreciate the scene so I didn't bother telling him what happened exactly but I thought reddit might get a kick out of it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Why wouldn't season 11 have 11 episodes? Talk about a missed opportunity! </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-18 00:16:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Don't they care about  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> You know, kenneth's gold case game show idea back in season 1 could still work. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-18 00:03:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I don't know why they gave up so quickly. It's just missing a quick fix that I thought was rather obvious when I first saw the episode, in that instead having all the cases empty except for one case filled with gold, all the cases would be filled with lead or something and one filled with gold. That way they're all equally heavy and no one can immediately tell which one has gold in it. 

Just saying, that's what I thought gold case meant, not that all the briefcases would be empty.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Everybody was kungfu fighting is probably the best soundtrack in movies/tv ever. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-17 20:18:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's never not amazing when it's used. It's always awesome. You've got Scrubs, Kungfu Panda, Bowfinger... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> You know, back in Basic Genealogy, "coffee" really WAS code for sex, despite Jeff and the girl saying no. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-17 15:10:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I just thought that was funny. Pierce asks them if coffee was code for sex and the cop demands they answer and they're like "no" but then in the next scene they do proceed to have sex after all.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Quick question about the recent star wars. Spoilers of the whole series. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-12 12:12:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> When kylo Ren starts hitting himself in the place he was injured as he's fighting finn/rey, what is that? I recognize that from somewhere, what is that? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Goddamn. I didn't even know they MADE a superman 3 and 4. Thought it was just 2 </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-12 10:54:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I would have been fine never knowing that. 

There was a superman movie that had superman hanging out with comedian Richard Pryor, **think about that for a second.**










Still better than the turd piles by Zack Snyder *bad tums dish*
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Which episode of Drunk Sex Orgy is this </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-11 23:12:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> http://www.xvideos.com/video5116775/party_babes_loving_big_dicks 

This is part of the video, and I'm looking for the video title to find the full thing. You can see yvette yukiko and a cameo in the background of ferrera gomez </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> A lot of people dislike season 3, but season 2's ultimate twist is the one I disliked. I just felt it was TOO big. (spoilers) </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-10 21:17:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Beaver, behind the whole thing? I can't remember if there were some inconsistencies with his placement at the time of the various crimes, but I will say this, how are we expected to believe he, a teenager, was able to put a bomb on a *plane*, in a post 9/11 world? I mean that's a pretty big plot element, and it's something hard to just suspend disbelief for. 

In addition to this, the fact that they made the guy from Police Academy a molester is so... weird. He was able to molest a *bunch* of boys? I could understand only one, but nearly all of them? That's just highly unlikely. It's like that it's always sunny episode when dennis and Charlie go to report a false rape for the shusher and the detective skeptically asks "so he was raping... both of you? At the same time?" 

I also felt we never really got to see Guttenburg as a creepy molester guy. It all happens offscreen so we don't know why he was doing it, a scene showing him being fucked up in the privacy of his own home just to clue the viewers in, something like that.

It's just that, by not doing this, it seems like the villain of season 2 is actually Beaver, with just an offhanded remark that "oh he got molested and that's why he is the way he is"

I just felt that season 2 was too ambitious in that regard, it wasn't as tightly crafted as season 1 while still having an insanely shocking (but still fits) revelation with the Logan's dad having sex with his son's girlfriend thing. That one was so good and it fit so well and was so terrifyingly fitting, because throughout the season we DID see glimpses of Logan's father being terrifying and having a temper, beating his kid, etc etc.  

At least, that was kind of my initial thoughts when I was blown away by the awesomeness of VM in season 1 and then 2 leading up to the revelation.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Having grown up watching Scrubs, I've been wondering are pagers still used by doctors? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-09 19:06:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Scrubs went well into the 2000s and doctors seem to still be the few that use pagers in the modern era.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> So many hentai comics posted, but are any of them even remotely in the same league as Pretty Cool? [somewhat a request] </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-09 15:29:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Wonderfully drawn, endearing dialogue and characters, lots of creampie/impregnation out of love scenes, oh and actually uncensored?

It's probably the greatest sex comic I've ever read. Proof that you don't even need color for a great comic porn story. 

Anyway at this point I'd be willing to start with just having uncensored comics. Should we start including tags or flairs to comics that are uncensored?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Foggy, get a haircut! </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-08 23:02:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Loving this show, loving season 2, just thought of this while Foggy was running around. Dude needs a haircut, I don't care if it's true to the comics. Shape up son, you're in a place of business, you can't rock such awful long hair. Be strait laced and clean cut. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Wait was seth Cohen from the oc listening to the veronica mars opening in the beginning of the episode? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-08 09:46:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> https://youtu.be/lZmfriA-s38

I recognized it instantly. Don't know if it was a reference or not  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The godfather part 2 is a lot more depressing than I remember. *Spoilers </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-05 23:19:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I find it much more depressing than I used to as a teen:
In an effort to win all the mafias, Michael has become... so cold, so cold and calculating. And what has he lost in the process?
 His wife, who no longer loves him, their marriage no more.
 His brother, whom he has killed
And you can feel the tensions rise up between Tom Hagen and Michael Corleone.
That last scene, in which Michael reflects while remembering his father's birthday where he enlists in the Marines, what is the purpose of that scene? There are so many layers to it, I want to see what other people thought of it.
Also, what was the purpose of seeing Vito's rise to mafianess in parallel to Michael's story? I've always wondered that. Is it to see how Vito handled things compared to Michael?
I always thought it was meant to show why everything fell to pieces around Michael but it didn't for Vito, but I don't think it was Michael's fault. For example, Vito had an Italian wife same as him, so they had the same cultural background, but Michael had an American wife, and American women are much different from women in the old country. Different belief and thinking systems, less accepting of "men handle the business and we don't ask questions"
I thought that was a theme in the movie. How the ways of Sicily family mafia thing just don't work in America's way of thinking, like how Kay questions everything Michael does. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Always wanted to ask, why was the It's Always Sunny Christmas episode uncensored and they could say the f word? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-05 21:08:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> And why can't the regular episodes say it? Charlie once said it in the season 4 episode premiere when he said "I ate a fucking monkey Dee" but they bleeped it out. They didn't for the Christmas one. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> I don't care how emotionally detached you are, who goes to their high school reunion with their DAD? I mean... ??? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-04 23:47:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> For some reason this bothers me a lot more than Dennis going to a sex orgy place with his dad lol, absentee father or not. For some reason it's that much more... I don't know, weird, or even maybe pathetic, to go to your high school reunion with your dad. 

And I mean that for not just the twins, but Charlie too lol. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Lol Star Wars 7. They couldn't make a more intimidating name than Snoke? Snokes? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-02 22:05:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Sounds like someone thought of the website Snopes and then accidentally said snorkel. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> So... Charlie really did get molested after all hehe </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-01 01:24:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Wait why am I laughing that's horrible.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Whatever happened to "Damn girl you conceited, ain't nobody wanna have your babies" (safety spoilers?) </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-31 23:44:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> One season later "I'm in love with Alie" (or however you spell her name)

Are the writers really running out of material that much? They couldn't have just a close friendship between the 2 cops?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Where did you guys get the picture at the top of this subreddit with Liv's pronounced green eyes and short hair? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-29 21:23:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm trying to find it for myself if anyone knows where it is? There's another one sort of like that with Liv's long hair but I kinda want the one that's exactly like the picture at the top of this subreddit </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Wait I thought Scully was the one who was married and Hitchcock was the one who was single? (safety spoilers) </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-28 15:18:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> In one of the recent episodes with the "Operation Beans" where Jake gives the pair what turns out to be a high stakes drug ring, Hitchcock says to Scully "if anything happens to me I want you to marry my wife" 

I was waiting for this to be an intentional goof by the show where Jake or Terry would say "no you idiot, Scully's the one who's married, you're the one who is single" and Hitchcock would go "oh right" 

Something like that. I know that Scully mentions his wife in Ray's birthday party episode, and I don't think Hitchcock has been married but can't confirm, will have to rewatch the episodes from the beginning. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Who is this black haired scarjo lookalike? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-27 22:45:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> https://giant.gfycat.com/FixedTeemingCassowary.webm </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Which episode of Drunk Sex Orgy is this? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-26 11:35:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> http://www.xvideos.com/video5116775/party_babes_loving_big_dicks
This is part of the video, and I'm looking for the video title to find the full thing. You can see yvette yukiko and a cameo in the background of ferrera gomez </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What WAS frank's brother episode meant to parody? Dreamgirls? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-25 13:55:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I felt at first like that was what they were going for,  but not necessarily.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Help, spaghetti sauce is not saucy/watery enough, it's too... chunky. How do I make it more like a typical spaghetti tomato sauce? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-23 10:06:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It has the right ingredients like tomatoes and ground beef and green peppers and such, but how to make it more saucy and less... chunky? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The gang had an awesome dance routine in Frank's Little Beauties, why would their high school dance routine suck so much? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-21 21:04:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> We never talk about it but their opening dance routine for the pageant is really unironically good, even though it's meant as a comedy. And Dee looks really hot in it, usually the show tries  to make the actress look as unattractive as a bird but she looked good their in that black shirt and pants.

And the choreography, the dance sequence with Dennis and Charlie, and even Mac, it's awesome. 

Makes you wonder why their high school dance routine wasn't as well received.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> In the Gladys Knight episode of 30 Rock, who exactly were those 2 women in red burlesque suits walking throughout the episode? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-17 23:20:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> https://youtu.be/e6jqWe4ODjc?t=35

I feel like it's supposed to be a reference to something, but I don't know what. They were walking throughout the entire episode, without revealing their face, until the end here. Gosh they look so cute, the one on the left looks a little like amy smart, I love her. 

The look they share with each other before looking at Tracy and crew... I love it so much.

By the way, I could listen to Jack and C.C. sing that one part for hours, literally hours. If anyone knows how to... like, make a video of just that part? Right before Lemon butts in.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Was Vontella supposed to be a spoof of the tyra banks show that she had for a while? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-16 21:35:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> In the deal breakers episode of the season 3 finale, I always thought Vontella was real and really wished it was, plus I liked the black actress hostess in it. Always wondered if it was supposed to spoof Tyra Banks or an amalgamation of that and those jerry springer/maury/whatever they're called type shows of america.

Also, I always thought Liz Lemon looked *really* good in that sketch with the flower blouse and the hairstyle and she just looked really cool, I don't know how to describe it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Greta Gerwig movies like Damsels in Distress and Mistress America have a quality to them that I just absolutely love. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-14 20:57:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I mean I just love this woman and the movies she's in. There's something about the dialogue that I love, 20something people that think they have it all figured out and consider themselves so introspective only by the end to realize that they don't really have it all figured out after all. 

And the women, the women in these movies are so gorgeous, analeigh tipton in that movie is just drop dead gorgeous, makes my heart stop every time.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Just saw a commercial for this show. How is it, any good? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-14 20:44:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I saw the guy from psych from disney's luck of the irish, was surprised I hadn't heard of this series before.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What the heck does "blotter dynamite" even mean? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-12 19:06:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Amy says it about dave majors in s02e21 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> There need to be porn girls who are known for only doing creampies. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-10 22:37:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Like, that should be their thing, they exclusively do creampies only, so we know what we're getting if we were to watch their videos. Do any girls do that?

I was just watching a Taylor Sands video and adding her as a favorite porn girl with cute/adorable face. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Are there anymore Tracyscops comics with Spider-Man and whatnot? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-08 13:38:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> I've always found something funny about James Marsden's character on the show (spoilers) </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-05 16:45:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> He's the only character that sticks with Liz until the end and she ends up marrying him, finally achieving a happy ending with this guest star (guest star boyfriends/girlfriends in shows are usually only for a couple of episodes and then that's it)

But here's the thing; like  Sean Bean, James Marsden had a running joke in the movie world back in the 2000s where he, a generally nice guy, never ends up with the girl. 

You've got The Notebook where this happens, you've got Superman Returns where he plays the boyfriend of Lois Lane while Superman is away, and even in the X-Men series you had his girlfriend Jean Grey flirting with Wolverine and then that thing that happens at the end of the 2nd movie. Enchanted half counts in that he doesn't end up with the princess but does have a potential romance with the future queen of Frozen Arendelle. 

So in a ton of movies where the girl ends up choosing some other guy despite James Marsden being an extremely decent fellow and (usually) a much better person than the guy the girl chose, it's like Tina Fey made a reference to this by having James Marsden on the show and not leaving him but actually ended up marrying him and adopting a kid together. 

Just thought that was funny. Not sure if overthinking it but that's the first thing that came to my mind way back when season 6 and then 7 were airing. Just kinda sweet in a way, isn't it? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> There's a scene in Frozen that's such a cheat after the twist happens. SPOILERS </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-05 11:27:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> http://33.media.tumblr.com/d2135671ab46ee72288f96b8dca5d007/tumblr_inline_n01bpamUgr1rjau39.gif

So we all know Hans is the bad guy and this scene does foreshadow it:

http://i.imgur.com/iGlQiPp.jpg

And that's fair, but the scene in the beginning where Hans falls in the water and smiles at his horse, there was no one around to see that, whose benefit was that for, the audience? Not to mention the whole going out of his way to help the citizens, help Elsa from being shot with a crossbow arrow, only to haphazardly go out in the ice to slice her with a sword? It just seems like such a cheat to make him all of a sudden evil to force fit the sister love ending and the awfully fast (not to mention anticlimactic) way everything wraps up.

I'm just saying, it was clear there were a lot of re-writes with the Frozen script. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> I like how they brought in Danny, only to forget about him later. Series spoilers. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-04 23:40:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Poor Josh... at least he could do voices. That episode where he's copying Jack and Tracy's voice back in season 1 was a classic. 

Then they brought in Jack er I mean Danny in season 4 but by mid to the end of the season, forgot him just the same and didn't know what other stories to include him in. The show has always been about Liz Jack, Tracy and Jenna, and Kenneth, with some subplots about the writers and Hornberger (yes!) . There just wasn't room for anything with him. 

I like that episode where they reminisce and Danny tries to convince himself that the past memories were of him as Josh.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Can anyone identify this girl? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-26 21:57:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> https://vk.com/video?gid=102033396 z=video-102033396_171412540%2Fpl_-102033396

It's a vk link so I don't know if you can see it, the video is only 40 seconds long.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Which do you like more, Janie Jimplin, or Jackie Jormp Jomp? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-25 21:34:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Both have their strengths.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Chrome has started to refresh tabs automatically on my computer, why is this happening/how to stop it? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-25 19:53:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I don't know what happened but all of a sudden if I've got like 20 tabs open it refreshes them constantly and before it didn't used to do that, even with my low 4 gb ram computer that I'm using. 

Is this a permanent thing that google's gonna do now, is there a fix?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Nine is one of the weirdest movie roles that Daniel Day-Lewis has ever chosen. (safety spoilers) </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-23 21:33:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Here's a guy with such a selective choice of movies that he only does a couple every decade, and has now won 3 oscars, securing the most out of any actor in history.

9 is not a bad movie per se, it's just... eh, you know? A cliche riddled meh movie that DDL had decided to star in, and in the movie itself has Marion Cotillard as a wife but decides to cheat with Penlope Cruz? Over Marion Cotillard? Absolutely absurd.

I've always wondered why he chose that, when in the past the kind of movies he's chosen were My Left Foot, Last of the Mohicans, Gangs of New York, There Will Be Blood,  and Lincoln. Nine seems like an odd misstep (again not a bad movie but... considering DDL's picky tastes, what made him choose this over other roles)

The movie is a musical and I guess it's alright, the songs are kinda catchy and I guess that's all that matters, I'm assuming he chose the role because he wanted to try his hand at singing. But otherwise it's a very uninteresting movie. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Wait which movie is this Charlize Theron gif from? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-23 17:28:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> http://i.imgur.com/V8zef76.gif

Also is there a subreddit for this kinda thing? Wanna know which movie this Amanda Seyfried gif is from too:

http://i.imgur.com/r5GMDUN.gif </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Wait has Charlie been wearing the same thermal underwear pajamas thing since the very beginning? *Safety Spoilers* </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-19 11:24:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm watching the gang goes jihad in season 2 and those thermal underwear he's wearing are stark white, they look so damn clean and not worn out/torn etc.

Do you think they actually committed to having him wearing the exact same pair for over a decade? That would be some pretty damn awesome dedication if true wouldn't it! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Mac says "GODAMMIT" the best out of the main gang. Agree or disagree? Spoilers </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-16 15:19:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I just love it when he's like proven wrong or something contrary happens and he's like God-*Dammit*

Like in that episode where they're stranded in the woods and set the bunny free and the hawk eats it. There should be a gif of that.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What do you guys think the gang did to the guy who shushes people? (SPOILERS) </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-11 19:04:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> One of the few times the gang quote unquote "won one" ?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> How to download Arabic to english camera translator language pack for a samsung galaxy s5 phone? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-10 11:41:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Does google translate have camera translation for arabic to english language pack? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-10 10:58:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I can't seem to find it and don't know how/where to request it, this feature would be very useful on my phone when I'm getting papers in arabic and want to translate them.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Something that always struck me as weird in season 4, concerning Frank. (SPOILERS) </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-08 20:48:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> In the premiere episode Manhunters, Frank questions why Dennis and Mac want to put their balls in each other's mouths and twist their nipples, saying stuff like "I just don't understand your generation"

And yet... literally just a few episodes later is Who Pooped the Bed, where Frank admits to doing all the poops and concludes by saying "poop is funny". 

How does he question Dennis and Mac's generation of ball dipping but not the same thing with poop, which I lump in the same category?

Always struck me as weird in a funny kind of way whenever I rewatch the series.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Just beat the entire series over the past 4 months. My god... *ENTIRE SERIES SPOILERS* </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-07 15:44:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What must it have even been like back in 2008 when MGS 4 came out and answered the plot lines in the way that it did? I don't even know what to think right now. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Just beat the entire series over the past 4 months. My god... *ENTIRE SERIES SPOILERS* </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-07 15:18:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What must it have even been like back in 2008 when MGS 4 came out and answered the plot lines in the way that it did? I don't even know what to think right now. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Spectre simultaneously manages to do everything I've ever wanted in a Bond sequel and not do it at the same time/do it terribly, isn't that weird? (SPOILERS) </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-06 12:24:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Linking Quantum again, that's what I've always wanted. Saying that Silva and quantum and le chiffe and s*** were all under blofeld? Not so sure about that. Silva didn't seem like a team player, what with being a joker rip-off.

This felt so forced I feel like blofeld on the whole thing should have taken up 2 movies, or at least been developed FAR more in Spectre. Too much of it and him felt underdeveloped and rushed.

There's no explanation as to how all these pieces fit together. It's just "oh I was behind everything you ever knew, mwahahaha!"

What's to stop another villain in the next movie from taking credit and saying "you know how that guy said he was behind everything the whole time? Well *I* was actually behind **that** the whole time!"

And it just goes on and on forever.

I think the motivation behind having everything linked is flimsy.


Okay. So Blofeld installed C in MI6 and organized terrorist attacks to pressure South Africa into signing on to the Nine Eyes program. He's really running this intelligence sharing apparatus. Okay. What's he going to do with it once it's up and running? We're never given a clear idea of what Spectre's goals are. They do things - have a hand in human trafficking, plus the activities witnessed in the last three movies - but what's the endgame?

But the real bit where it fell apart for me was the revelation that Blofeld was Bond's brother, and was intentionally directing the events of the previous movies in an attempt to make his life miserable, because jealousy. The hell? That's Iron Man 3 levels of underwhelming villain motivation. The fact that Bond himself is unphased by this revelation also serves to make it even more pointless.


It really feels like they wanted to do a bunch of different concepts for Bond 24 and tried to Frankenstein them together. Let's see, we have:

Judi Dench's M sends Bond on one last mission from beyond the grave.
MI6 is ensnared in a paranoia-fueled intelligence/surveillance ring that's being manipulated by the very people they're trying to combat.
Tie up loose ends from the first two films of the reboot, specifically Mister White and the Quantum organization.
Bring back SPECTRE into the new continuity.
Bond vs his never-before mentioned lost evil step-brother; rectify contradictory background information in Casino Royale and Skyfall
Bond finds true love and considers quitting OHMSS style or whatever.


It's just too much to juggle in two and a half hours. If they'd limited themselves to two, maybe three of these concepts, they could have something more cohesive. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Dammit iZombie, I came up with the term porny first to describe the combination of porn and horny! </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-03 17:14:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> They have to give me credit where credit is due, where's my copyright claim check in the mail!?

Lol but seriously I'm glad to see a mainstream tv show use a term I'd been using a lot over the past few years.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> I'm reading a comic called Doomsday My Dear. It takes a while to take off but then it gets freaking fantastic. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-03 17:00:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Just finished this series. Really wish it would be more popular/talked about around the internet. (SPOILERS) </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-02 19:34:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm just... wow. I absolutely loved it. I remember seeing a couple of commercials way back in the summer and thinking it looked interesting, but I was never around when it was actually airing to watch it, so I never did and now in the new year I finally get all the episodes and start watching and... freaking amazing. 

Who do you root for or like best? I weirdly really like Peepers the more the show went on, is that strange? I also wonder if Garfield is meant to be "the innocent" that gets corrupted by this evil family. 

Anyway if I were to compare it to other shows, I'd say it sort of feels like an it's always sunny series but in the early 20th century. And I love it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> OH my god who is she? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-01 21:16:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> http://www.xvideos.com/video8967065/blonde_bombshell_rides_her_bf_to_premature#_tabComments
This is literally the kind of cute adorable personality I'm looking for in a porn girl, I love her. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Did Terry lose the weight kinda um, quickly? *SPOILERS* </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-31 01:35:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> I just realized in 4 seasons they never once mentioned anything about Cece's mom. (Spoilers) </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-29 09:07:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Funny isn't it. I just realized something I never really payed attention to before, why wasn't Cece's mom in season 2 when Cece was about to get married of all things. I can't remember if they told a reason. 

Also with how strict she seems, no way she remotely approves of her daughter having been a model, she probably didn't give her approval there. 

I suppose Cece not even finishing high school could probably be explained by her taking the modeling job in defiance of her mother, that seems to make the most sense. 

I wonder if it explains more or less about the Cece character.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> I found x-men says of future past to be incredibly disappointing quite frankly. (Xmen franchise spoilers) </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-28 13:12:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> For all the hate the also disappointing x-men 3 gets, I found days of future past to be just as disappointing. 

With the terrible mystique performance by j-law that might actually be worse than her initial terrible performance in first class, the boring past segments saved only by the quicksilver performance, I would have much rather seen a movie with that future only and find out how all those new x-men interacted with each other. 

It seems its entire existence hinged on resetting the universe, not like it was that great a universe to begin with (only X2 stands as bring the greatest in the franchise) and the actors not getting any younger anyway. 

I mean, all the comic book nerds were telling me that dofp was one of the greatest xmen stories ever, something like the killing joke for batman, and in the end I found the movie just ok, with quite a few detriments like mystique's performance and everything with past magneto and killing off the first class actors off screen  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> No one seems to talk about how hot Rosa looked with a blond wig in the jimmy jab games. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-27 18:34:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It was very... surreal. And attractive.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> That was... kinda disappointing. (Season 7 episode 9 discussion) *SPOILERS* </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-26 10:03:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The writers took the easy way out by making it so that Beth was cheating this whole time so that Andy wouldn't have to make a difficult choice or conversation? I would expect that from a lesser show, like a laugh track "comedy" but didn't think Modern Family would do it like that.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> So let's peel the layers to Maeby's name? (spoilers) </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-24 12:10:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> As in, maybe she's George Michael's cousin, maybe she was developed in a test tube, maybe she actually had a surrogate mother and Lindsey didn't even carry her, just donated her egg?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> I'm playing the Metal Gear (and Solid) series for the first time, is this the best place to discuss the mainline games? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-23 21:28:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I've got so much I want to say about this series and am interested in reading up on so many of others' opinions on the story and series overall. Is this the best place for it?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Playing the Metal Gear Solid series for the first time, is this the best place to discuss the 4 mainline games? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-23 21:18:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I've got so much I want to say about this series and am interested in reading up on so many of others' opinions on the story and series overall. Is this the best place for it? 

I just finished:

 Metal Gear

 Metal Gear 2

 Metal Gear Solid

Metal Gear Solid 2

Metal Gear Solid 3

Partway through mgs 4. But I really want to discuss the stories of those first 5 games. Wish I could have been there at the time they came out and read people's thoughts, opinions, fan theories, and so on. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> I'm rewatching the series now... IN HD! It's so great (spoilers) </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-22 17:32:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Not only is the quality amazing, but it's even better to rewatch and catch all the little in-jokes, foreshadowing, and references, for such a spectacular show. 

I also never realized how attractive Lindsey looked... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> You WANT to be Yoko? (Spoilers) </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-17 12:44:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I don't know why but this line plus Liz's expression always kills me every time.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> So basically they took Jerry from Parks and Rec, and... split him into two people :P ? (SPOILERS) </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-15 13:54:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Does anyone have that speech by Ron Swanson about the guy who spills the soup, and the guy who gets the soup spilled on him? There was a term he used, schmitzel and schamatzel or something, I can't remember. 

Which one do you consider Scully and Hitchcock to be? Though remember they're a package deal (their words lol) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> I was fully expecting to like kingsman... but I didn't. I was fully expecting to hate Spy... but I didn't. [Spoilers for both movies] </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-13 01:32:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Isn't it funny how that works? In terms of the number of spy movies last year and just fun movies in general, I thought Kingsman was all around immature and terrible, even though I love colin firth. I mean parts of it were ok, but none of the characters were likable, and that definitely includes the main character "eggsy". And that villain plan was just plain old stupid, and I'm not talking about the entertaining kind of stupid that Bond villains have like starting a civilization under the sea or building a base on the moon. 

It just didn't click with me. Which is a shame. 

Now as for Spy, the trailers made it look like the typical "epic movie" parody crap, but what we got instead was something surprisingly funny and even more surprisingly heartwarming with a great performance by the lead female. I also love the nod to action comedy in scenes like the kitchen area where they were fighting and she was improvising with pots and pans, now that is the kind of organic fighting that jackie Chan would be proud of, as the king of action comedy scenes. 

All in all, I just thought it was an interesting twist in how trailers and expectations can be shattered when seeing a movie.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [TOMT] Looking for picture of a creepy guy with a shirt that says "I liked lindsay lohan before the tits yeah thats right" </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-12 21:01:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The guy is fat and does a creepy look/pose to the camera </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [TOMT] Is there a name for this kind of expression? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-08 21:36:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> http://bodylanguageproject.com/the-only-book-on-body-language-that-everybody-needs-to-read/wp-content/uploads/2013/03/BodyLanguageProjectCom-Finger-moving-up-the-chin-3.jpg

Essentially putt the index finger and thumb to the side of the head while giving a wry smile as if to say "oh you"

I want to google some reaction images with namely this kinda pose but don't know what to search for. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Late to the party, but I finished season 1 and kinda want to talk about a certain plot point (SPOILERS for season) </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-03 01:03:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> They kinda just glossed over the whole Suzuki is a zombie thing. I mean he saw the crime scene then decided to cover everything up and suicide them in the process? I just... I mean maybe an episode dedicated to Suzuki would have helped with this glossing over. Sure we can probably infer that Blaine scratched him/infected him in some way (wonder how though, as captain he probably doesn't go on street calls, so how Blaine came into contact is a bit less obvious)

But what about how Suzuki felt over the whole thing. Probably regret, but did he not want to tell anybody? And if he did regret it then why did he help Blaine by telling her about Liv in the morgue (even thought Blaine already knew) and why did he never talk with Liv? I kept waiting for a scene with the two that never actually happened. That surprised me. 

Did he torch the place because he thought that there might be some evidence linking back to him, or... ? It just wrapped up so quickly I kind of can't get over it. 

Thoughts/comments on that particular plot point? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Just started watching this show, really like it as a Veronica Mars fan. Ever wonder behind the zombie biology of it all? (Safety Spoilers) </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-02 22:38:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I mean, do they still need to go to the bathroom, How does digestion work. Is it they just need one tiny human brain to survive for a couple of days, they no longer need 3 square meals a day like humans? Can they gorge themselves on brains or is one enough for them to feel "full"

Can't help but wonder the science of it all when it comes to these things. Especially since they show that their skin loses all color and their hair becomes bleached (why does their hair become bleached by the way?) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Chrome has really been slow and buggy the past few weeks since the recent update, what the hell happened? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-24 10:48:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I click on the browser and it takes forever to load, the keyboard takes forever to show up, there's all this bugging out and glitchiness and I just can't understand why? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Is there a way to set default video quality on the inhouse youtube app? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-23 01:27:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I want it at 360p, and I'm tired of youtube changing the quality higher or lower based on its interpretation of my internet speed. I just want it one default quality. 

I can't believe there's no option like that in settings. Christ, Google... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> It's Beardfac! Why do you people insist on calling me Beardface? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-21 02:46:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Damn you all. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Google ncr no longer working? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-20 19:55:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I've always hated google in the past decade because all of a sudden they change not just the domain but the language of google products (such as google books, google flights, etc) depending on what IP address they read, so if you're in a chinese area, it's in chinese, if you're in an Arabian area, it's in Arabic, completing ignoring the fact that most people would want English unless they specifically ask for a different language, would should be an option, no the standard. And not to mention people who happen to travel a lot.

I mean good god I'm so pissed right now because even the no country redirect extension is no longer working, and I just... graah. I literally hating feeling this helpless while megalomaniac google does what they want and I just have no say in it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> I have to say, am I the only one who really wanted Jess to be with... [SPOILERS] </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-20 17:52:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I really wanted her and Ryan to be together. I thought he was really likable, and they could have written out his character much better. I mean the guy who flew halfway around the world to see Jess in one episode, then they say that he's the kind of boyfriend who's never there for Jess? 

I actually wanted Jess to leave with Ryan to England and have  them live happily ever after together there... I know that might change up the show a little bit though so I understand why they didn't do that. But last year I was really invested in the Ryan and Jess relationship. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Seriously there needs to be more playfulness in porn (gifv included) </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-17 12:20:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> http://i.imgur.com/MzG6t3y.gifv

I don't even like mainstream American porn since they don't have creampie videos and instead moneyshot the girl's face, but this was really adorable. 

Riley Reid has so much potential, she should work for the x-art/joymii companies...

There was also a video with alice wonderbang where prior to sex they're just teasing each other and the guy is blowing raspberries in her stomach and she's giggling and it's all incredibly intimate and way more emotionally satisfying to deed to than regular porn.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Does this count as dirty small? [gif] </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-16 17:40:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> You know I actually used to get asmr from reading? That's right, from reading books, typically containing a character whispering/softly speaking something to another character. What about you? [Discussion] </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-15 23:26:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So even though the whispering was all in my head and not out loud, I'd still get a tingling sensation in the back of my head when I'd read a passage in the book. And I just did it, I didn't even understand that feeling of tingliness and pleasant sensation, that even with an actual term attributed to it, is STILL difficult to describe or put into accurate words. 

We all have those memories of someone speaking directly to us and getting what is now known as asmr, but do any of you have stories of different ways you experienced asmr before it become so conveniently widespread on youtube and the internet?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Could someone make a gif of when Coach says "Like, for real" to Schmidt in season 4's "Girl Fight" episode (safety spoilers) </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-14 19:57:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's when Schmidt is asking Jess if he should spend MORE time with Cece instead of staying away from her. I just love Coach's expression I have to have it in gif form please.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The more I think about it the more I lament about how this show was canceled and there aren't any more seasons. [SPOILERS] </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-12 14:49:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hell, it didn't even have a full first season, only 14 episodes! That's just a little over half the typical episode count of a typical broadcast season in America.
I didn't feel this sad when I first finished the 14 episodes and movie. It's only something that's been stewing inside me again and again as I go to sleep at night, wondering what kind of episodes and direction and plot lines we would have gotten had it gone on for 7 seasons like say, Buffy.
I do like the movie but I can't help but wonder how awesome it would be for River's badassness to gradually progress as we saw hints of it in the show, culminating in the badass warrior she became by like, the 3rd or 4th season, or something like that.
As for the Reavers plot line... I dunno if they could do what they did in the movie on a TV budget? With the whole Operative guy and the spaceship battle and whatnot, I just wonder. I look at the show and I think the special effects must have been really expensive way back in frickin 2002.
Anyway, that brings me to another plot line concerning the operative, Shepherd book. Seeing his backstory gradually unfold over the seasons instead of in a comic would have been so much better. Not to mention probably would have been much different and better than what we got (which admittedly is still better than nothing)
I dunno, I'm just feeling really melancholic over the whole thing. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Rewatching the series, something that really bothers me about season 2 [SPOILERS] </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-12 14:37:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Skye's mom and her sudden turn to absolute uncompromising evil. I mean, I was angry sure when she murdered edwards james olmos (regardless of my feelings towards the hypocritical secret "real" shield plotline) like that and started her plan, and was killing agents willy nilly, but the moment where she was truly irredeemable, like freaking SELFISH evil, is when she tried to kill Skye/suck up her life. What in the actual fuck, that's her daughter, the daughter that she apparently turned Cal into a monster just to find, and this is how the series ends, with her trying to kill her daughter?

I mean... with the way they played out the little tiny bits of her past, I just don't... that just really rubs me the wrong way. Up until then, everything she did was "extremist but looking out for her inhumans a la magneto and mutants, horribly misguided and wrong, but would never hurt one of her own like that" and yet she literally hurt her own, her own flesh and blood. 

With how intensive season 2 was especially the last bits, I was still reeling but had these thoughts, and after rewatching the episodes I'm able to process that whole transformation into evil.

I mean even if she did succeed, what was her end game after making the world inhumans and all regular humans dead? More importantly they just all of a sudden dropped the whole Afterlife storyline, specifically there was supposed to be this secret council that Sky's mom reports to/answers to/etc, where are they. If she had taken over the world, was her intention to rule it or just make everyone inhumans and then sit back.

I dunno there's just so much I wanted to ask about and yet they got rid of skye's mom just as quickly as they introduced her, and there's just a large juxtaposition between the woman that was captured by whitehall in the beginning of season 2 and the woman at the end of season 2. More backstory would have helped ease that punch to the gut, at least when they did the punch gut with Ward's reveal, they actually went through his entire past and history. 

Thoughts/comments on this matter? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> This is one of those shows that will forever sit comfortably as one of my favorites and the greatest in all the universe. (safety spoilers) </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-09 01:28:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I just love everything about the show </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> I played this game/series for the first time this year and I absolutely loved the first 2 games. (safety spoilers) </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-08 23:26:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I've always known about Bioshock, a friend once let me try their copy back in 2008, and I'd always hear about it having a great story, but I was never a fan of shooters so dismissed it for so long. 

Then this year I was able to get my own copy, and I tried out the game... and bam. I loved it IMMEDIATELY. Andrew Ryan, his whole dogma, Rapture the city under the sea, this game was fan freaking tastic. I just had so much damn fun with it. 

From the very beginning I was enthralled and utterly captivated by the mood and setting. Was freaked out by the big daddies and even more so by the little girls (never did understand how they were like that but then also easily able to be "fixed" and return back to being little girls that I assume grow up and age normally and can bear children and everything no complications, but then again the endings for this series have always been... a jarring tonal shift that's not too great) 

Was shocked at the twist (so glad I was able to avoid it for so long) and while I feel it all ended kinda... rapidly, up until we were in Andrew Ryan's lair it was great. And I love that face down with Andrew Ryan and his line "a man chooses a slave obeys"

Basically, I just want to share my love for a series I never thought I'd like but proved me wrong with just how good it was, to the point that I wanted to get the other games just to experience them after this one.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> If a girl is willing to do creampie videos then who the fuck authorizes finishing on her face instead of inside? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-03 19:24:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I dunno this really grinds my goat. When I see porn from Veronica Rodriguez or Veronica Radke, or Gina Devine or Angelica Ebbi, and only some of their videos have creampies, I'm wondering who exactly makes them not have it inside in other videos, is it the director, is it the girls themselves, I'm honestly just curious. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> It's pretty amazing that this show has had a consistent quality going on 7 seasons now. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-02 19:24:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> How long do you think the show will last? I mean the kids are a big part of the show and Luke/Manny are eventually going to be going off to college as well, and the girls even possibly getting married, how much will the series go on? How far will we see Lily and Joe age? We've grown to love these 3 families and their everyday lives.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> This show is so good. I'm on my second rewatch, season 1 and 2 have such a consistent high quality to them. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-02 11:12:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I remember when I first started watching season 1 last year, and every episode was great, the consistency in the likability of the characters and the plot lines, in the fact that it's not cliched jokes, in the relationship between Jake and Holt, that it's just fantastic overall. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> source/name of girl? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-11-29 19:34:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> http://45.media.tumblr.com/02604db31b07fab7c6a98e666ed12e57/tumblr_n13k9quBiU1r87gdto1_500.gif </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> So what exactly is app optimization? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-11-28 10:40:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Just got a notification for this and I'm just wondering what that means exactly.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> You can still be a grandfather even if you never married __ </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-11-28 06:15:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm just saying Book </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The thing I love most about female agent is that the girls take control and still act real. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-11-27 00:38:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I love the part where she tells him no to taking off her shirt while he's fucking her and she's smiling, that is actually more orgasmic than the actual fucking itself.

https://www.playvids.com/v/gyVSaVaUSLx </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> I have to admit exploited college girls DOES have the right idea of split screen porn. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-11-26 20:09:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> One side showing the fucking, the other side showing the girls' faces as they moan and writhe in pleasure. It would certainly help because some of the best/most pleasure sex positions are not the best ones for camera angles to shoot, so having this split screen thing works pretty well. I wonder if other porn companies do it? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> I have to say after letting it fester a while, I really disliked bioshock infinite. [SPOILERS] </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-11-25 20:14:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's just such a disappointing game. The more I do research the more I realize just how much they had presented in promotional trailers in comparison to the meh final product. 

I actually thought the dlc would change my mind but I'm not really a fan of them shoehorning the creation of the big daddies and songbird like that. 

Overall it's just an extremely subpar game with one of the most disappointing underutilized stories (not to mention gameplay elements) that I've come across.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> I still can't believe jennifer lawrence is an Oscar winner. She won an Academy award for silver linings playbook </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-11-25 05:57:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Tried using Firefox. Why is it so awful on this device? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-11-25 04:51:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The text size option may as well not exist. I've tried putting it on the largest size, and I've tried putting it on the smallest size. Neither option seems to affect websites, they all have the same default size (which BTW is too small for my liking)

Why is there no home button like literally every browser known to man? For the life of me I can't find an option to "add home button next to address bar" or something like that. 

this is a default regular samsung galaxy s5, no rooting, in case that affects Firefox's level of quality. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Is there a general porn discussion subreddit? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-11-23 20:15:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Or is it mainly just this place? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> I watched this show 2 years ago to the day and I still remember absolutely loving it. [safety spoilers] </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-11-23 17:19:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I had only caught it on tv once a long time ago and it was a season 3 episode with Shawn from Boy Meets World, but I immediately felt it was something I would like to see.  

It was only 2 years ago where I finally had all the episodes and I decided to see it and wow, was it a great show. It's one of those shows I'd love to be able to discuss with people in real life. 

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The more I think about it the more I lament about how this show was canceled and there aren't any more seasons. [SPOILERS] </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-11-23 14:40:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hell, it didn't even have a full first season, only 14 episodes! That's just a little over half the typical episode count of a typical broadcast season in America.

I didn't feel this sad when I first finished the 14 episodes and movie. It's only something that's been stewing inside me again and again as I go to sleep at night, wondering what kind of episodes and direction and plot lines we would have gotten had it gone on for 7 seasons like say, Buffy. 

I do like the movie but I can't help but wonder how awesome it would be for River's badassness to gradually progress as we saw hints of it in the show, culminating in the badass warrior she became by like, the 3rd or 4th season, or something like that. 

As for the Reavers plot line... I dunno if they could do what they did in the movie on a TV budget? With the whole Operative guy and the spaceship battle and whatnot, I just wonder. I look at the show and I think the special effects must have been really expensive way back in frickin 2002. 

Anyway, that brings me to another plot line concerning the operative, Shepherd book. Seeing his backstory gradually unfold over the seasons instead of in a comic would have been so much better. Not to mention probably would have been much different and better than what we got (which admittedly is still better than nothing)

I dunno, I'm just feeling really melancholic over the whole thing.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Does ecg/collegerules/girlsdoporn actually find random girls that they pay, I dunno, a thousand bucks to fuck on camera for that one time? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-11-22 16:35:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I mean, for some of the girls they're actually porn girls and porn "stars" that have been in other videos, but for certain others I actually haven't seen them in any other video ever, and I'm wondering if they actually do just happen to find random girls that open up their vaginas for a penis on camera for that one time, without being worried about this haunting them life/career wise considering just how interconnected the world has become thanks to social media, like scarily so. 

If so, how does that work in America, is that even legal? Is there like a corner street office or building that girls apply to where they're screened and then given the cash and fucked by that one guy who never shows his face? 

I'm honestly just curious over how it all works, especially when I see relatively normal looking girls like that one cutie from gdp ep 286:

http://picsee.net/upload/2014-11-01/b697473979c2.jpg http://33.media.tumblr.com/ca17dd44dd9c47b888ede83361f095ea/tumblr_njphc6dHV41sj1qcfo1_500.gif http://33.media.tumblr.com/cc8a866d949aa9effeffa218aeacbe95/tumblr_njphc6dHV41sj1qcfo3_500.gif http://33.media.tumblr.com/20ddd7a5bda1330812a6d4e614e0555b/tumblr_njphc6dHV41sj1qcfo4_500.gif http://38.media.tumblr.com/70175daa25f7c190c26bcfc49bb25e00/tumblr_njphc6dHV41sj1qcfo6_500.gif http://38.media.tumblr.com/c19beffca37449c2c2148cd6747321ef/tumblr_njphc6dHV41sj1qcfo5_500.gif http://33.media.tumblr.com/b5f7907fb248fedc3e1f9c36ded3c1a2/tumblr_njphc6dHV41sj1qcfo8_500.gif </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> videos where the girl says she how much she loves the guy </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-11-21 19:41:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  She should say things like "I love you" and other romantic sayings. It should be clear she's enjoying it, and bonus points if they say something like "let's make a baby together" or such. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What do you guys think a pleasant nightmare even means? [Spoilers] </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-11-21 08:06:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I like how in season 2 they had it used for the premiere and for the finale, sorta coming full circle like that. But what do you guys interpret it to mean? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Rewatching the show, and I've got a few questions. [Discussion] [SPOILERS] </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-11-20 14:36:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> First off just wanna preface this topic by saying I started watching this show at the beginning of 2015 after hearing about it for ages and dismissing it. Started from the pilot and... I immediately loved this show. I've gone all around the internet seeing posts how you should "stick with it since by midseason it gets better" but I loved it absolutely immediately, and liked all the characters, so by the time that whole Hydra thing exploded onto the scene, I was on a wild rollercoaster of thrills. This was... this was the show I always wanted, this was the show to replace my bitter sentiments towards Lost. I hadn't been hyped up or actively watching/engaging in discussion about a show since Lost 10 years ago, and Agents of Shield is already proving that it can present mysteries and intrigue, AND wrap them up. Really showcases how we're in a golden age of television with phenomenal writing, displaying character development and strong plotlines hand in hand. 

Anyway on to the topic, my question is, how much DID they have planned out or written? The show premiered fall 2013. Was there always an intention before the Hydra reveal and the Winter Soldier to have all that stuff happen, introducing Hydra, Ward being an evil villain all along (when that happened and he shot the agents and the woman, I literally screamed noooo, literally. It was like a punch to the gut. I still remember that feeling)

How much cross collaboration and screenwriting was there, if any, between Winter Soldier people and agents of shield people? I'm just wondering how much was planned ahead. 

And this ties into the second question of introducing the inhumans, since they had that "tahiti" and the kree body and Skye stuff happen from the very beginning, so how how much are they planning ahead? It seems rather amazing, since again I'm going by the last episodic show I used to be into, Lost, whose writers just made up shit as they went along. How much did they plan ahead in order to introduce the inhumans, was it always meant that way, did they always mean to introduce Hydra, have Ward turn evil, etc etc? 

Also, who here agrees that Skye's transformation (both literal and character development wise) is one of the best things this show ever had. In  the beginning she was kinda... well you could even classify her as annoying, an almost teen like character straight from the gossip girl/cw show crap of characters and the like, with early episodes trying to maybe boast off her sex appeal more so than likability. And then that all changed when she matured, was able to handle her own, and become one of the best characters on the show, the character the audience identifies with and looks to as the moral compass (especially in season 2, felt so bad for her when they didn't know what they were dealing with and had her locked up in the lab). I just love that about this already magnificent show.

How much are they planning ahead, and this being part of the larger MCU, it's making me wonder, is there an endpoint they're all leading up to, will they ever have universe crossings like with previous Whedon shows Angel and Buffy? I ask because of the villains they se up in the beginning of the show, especially one in particular, Gravitron. I know it's the other Whedon who is in charge of Agents of Shield, I'm just wondering how much they're planning out, because I'm loving the show and was so glad ABC didn't cancel it because it's just phenomenal. I actually was more invested in the season 2 finale movie-length episode than Avengers 2! That's how much I've become drawn to the show. 

Appreciate any comments and thoughts on the show. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> So they made an all new opening in season 4... only for damon wayans jr to leave the show :( ? [spoilers maybe?] </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-11-19 21:04:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So they had an all new opening (which is nice to include all the other characters) and then coach ends up leaving by the end of the season? Come on. 

I hope it's not true, because Coach's inclusion in season 4 really shifted the dynamic and made the show even more fantastic than thought possible, and as hilarious as it is for 5 people to live in one tiny loft with only 1 bathroom, they had a lot of great stories with the characters.

 I'd just be really sad to see him go. Season 4's greatness was a silver lining to Happy Endings being canceled, since it meant Coach returning, but if he's leaving New Girl as well... I dunno, what do you guys think? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Name of girl or source of this video? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-11-19 15:20:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> http://www.xvideos.com/video6181009/hottie_with_her_hardcore_riding </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Girls saying they can feel the creampie inside of them, smiling, etc </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-11-19 14:37:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> http://i.minus.com/iWouUvHrchs8l.gif
Sort of like that. Super hot </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> I kinda miss when asmr videos had time stamps in the description to which kind of triggers you prefer. [discussion] </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-11-17 00:19:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> sorta like this:

https://youtu.be/E_wJz0-fbmI

Not the best example since that video is 2 hours long, but you get my point. Just a timestamp/tag to let us know if the video is worth our time. 

This one is 18 minutes only:

https://youtu.be/e5TKNB56fjI </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> source? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-11-15 20:22:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> https://gfycat.com/RepulsiveGrossFoxhound

Only thing that would make a scene like this more perfect is if he creampies her as well. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Is there a way to know (like a tag) if a story is going to feature condoms in the story so I don't waste my time reading it? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-11-12 23:07:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm interested in the first time stories on literotica, but I just wasted my time on not 1 but 2 long first time stories that absolutely ruined my mood when the characters stop their destined passionate love making to "go buy a condom" and my mood was sullen after that.

For my tastes it's not real love or even remotely romantic if they don't actually want to BE with each other, mind body and soul. 

Just wanted a heads up/recommendation for any good first time stories where the guy finishes inside and actually fills the girl as their love blossoms for the first time.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Does anyone have a gif of jessica biel holding the men's bathroom door closed and shaking her head ominously at some guy? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-11-11 11:18:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That scene from the season 4 premiere episode figuratively kills me every time I see it.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Is there an adblock for Samsung galaxy s5's in-house youtube app that doesn't require rooting yet? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-11-09 05:19:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This is getting ridiculous. I heard pray tell that the adblock currently available on the store was going to include an update that will finally block those ads before videos, not sure if true, if anyone can confirm?

You know how horrible it is to be listening to an asmr video to try to sleep and BAM huge loud ad. It's fucking bullshit.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> I don't get it. Why did this show have poor ratings and get cancelled? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-11-07 16:54:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I mean, Desperate Housewives was pretty damn popular and successful for ABC, how come Suburgatory, a very enjoyable show on its own, not have that much success leading to ABC cancelling it? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Girls riding a guy even after they visibly creampied are the best. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-10-31 18:44:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> http://i.imgur.com/4Iw2phG.gif

There should be more. Anyone got any hot ones and particular favorites? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Looking for a tumblr I once found with porn gifs and pseudoscience captions on them about how finishing inside is always superior </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-10-31 17:54:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Like, it releases chemicals that bring even more pleasure to the woman, and that going raw inside a woman brings infinitely more pleasurable and makes her more satisfied throughout the day. 

I can't even remember when or how I stumbled across it, but the captions coupled with the porn gifs of creampies and such were surprisingly... arousing. Would hope to find it again.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> That hip raise that Janice Griffith does at the end of this gif... I want more of it. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-10-29 20:32:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> http://gfycat.com/CrazyIcyAlbertosaurus

Oh good god that hip raise. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Was there a sub where you could literally see a guy's penis bump on a woman's mon pubis when he's fucking her? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-10-29 20:03:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> https://gfycat.com/RepulsiveGrossFoxhound

Like actually see her belly shift, that sort of thing?

If not, could anyone link to such videos and gifs? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Girls saying they can feel the creampie inside of them, smiling, etc </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-10-29 18:55:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> http://i.minus.com/iWouUvHrchs8l.gif


 Sort of like that. Super hot. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Watched the show and the show and the movie. Absolutely loved them. [Spoilers] </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-10-21 22:27:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I can't believe that all this time, I have been sitting on a great series that I avoided because the commercials on tv completely misrepresented how great the show was. There are so many great things I want to say that I don't know where to start.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> episode 286 still has the best looking girl of them all in my eyes </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-10-17 23:52:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Holy crap Alfie by Incase is the best sex comic I've ever read, does anyone know if Incase finished it yet? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-10-14 21:58:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> I've long since gotten seemingly permanent asmr immunity. I'm surprised the rest of you haven't if you watch asmr everyday. [Discussion] </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-10-08 00:48:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It would probably take at least a year of no asmr videos before I could ever get tingles ever again, but I can't stop watching the videos at night when I lie in bed. It's become habit more than anything else, I almost do it absent-mindedly. 

I'm surprised no one else has gotten here, and would like to know what your secret is if you watch asmr everyday and yet still haven't developed any immunity towards it.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Cowgirl where the girl moves back and forth instead of up and down? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-10-07 06:24:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I much prefer back and forth grinding. If it's European girls and generally attractive girls, even better. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> So what's going on? I can't seem to find torrents for recent TV episodes like Agents of Shield season 3 episode 1. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-10-05 18:24:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I hope the age of the torrent isn't completely gone, with the deaths of sites like mininova and isohunt, it's really worrisome that us non Americans who don't have Netlfix or any type of software ever are unable to watch movies and tv shows. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> So what's going on? I can't seem to find torrents for recent TV episodes like Agents of Shield season 3 episode 1 </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-10-05 15:52:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I hope the age of the torrent isn't completely gone, with the deaths of sites like mininova and isohunt, it's really scary that us non Americans who don't have Netlfix or any type of software ever are unable to watch movies and tv shows. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Why does the Dumbing of Age guy have his characters use condoms when he's drawing his rule 34 stuff? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-10-04 15:25:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Cowgirl where the girl moves back and forth instead of up and down? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-10-01 17:01:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I much prefer back and forth. If it's European girls and generally attractive girls, even better. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Rate: missasmr and give reasons why you like her [discussion] </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-10-01 16:01:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Girl being "knighted", need to know who she is. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-09-30 20:04:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> http://m.xhamster.com/movies/2369984/being_knighted.html </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Found her! What can you guys tell me about chloe toy? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-09-30 14:38:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> A few months ago I asked for help on here on a blonde british girl trying out lingerie "for your wife" in a store and being all naughty asking questions like "what would your wife say if she saw you getting hard watching another women try out lingerie for her."

Anyway I didn't get any help but I found the model, her name is chloe toy apparently and also she's a cam-ish girl, so she doesn't do hardcore scenes, so this was a bust. 

This is an example of a video of hers:

http://www.pornhub.com/view_video.php?viewkey=447836163

I still haven't found the video in question or a hardcore one.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> More videos like this where the guy just wants to stay inside her vagina even after finishing </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-09-29 15:12:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> http://www.pornhub.com/view_video.php?viewkey=468766813

Preferably romantic based. Where after finishing inside they don't immediately take it out but just lie there cuddling and stroking each other while he's still inside her.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Does anyone have the source for the full link to this video? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-09-29 14:55:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> http://www.xvideos.com/video6810168/perfect_gorgeous_creampie_gangbang

http://www.xvideos.com/video6825187/lucianna_karel_-_creampie_gangbang#_tabComments

I always forget the name of the chick with glasses, she'd actually look really hot if she didn't do the European thing of having one side of her head shaved off, what the hell even is that. Or in this case just cut short. But she'd still look really hot with long flowing hair. 

Girl in green has a such great smile but midway in the video it almost looks like she's shaking her head and regretting this charade. Why are they even finishing on her face instead of inside her is my main concern.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The problem with deleted scenes in animated movies is they're always just storyboards. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-09-27 16:45:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Unlike live action movies which don't need much besides the camera and actors, cg and animated movies require a ton of effort to create their scenes, so the deleted scenes are never actually drawn or computer generated, they're just in black and white rough sketches and/or feature  rudimentary cg work like in that one canceled opening scene for how to train your dragon 2.

It's just a shame because I love seeing the deleted scenes for Disney's animated movies like snow white or Aladdin or jungle book.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Girls saying they can feel the creampie inside of them, smiling, etc </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-09-22 18:08:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> http://i.minus.com/iWouUvHrchs8l.gif

Sort of like that. Super hot.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Recently rewatches And Justice for All. That last scene always gets me. [Spoilers] </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-09-20 23:58:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> People really forget that other than the godfather, al Pacino was fantastic in his other 70s roles serpico and this movie. Such a powerful courtroom scene. 

There's also an earlier scene that I absolutely love. Its with the guy who dropped the ball and let the black dude go to jail who later hanged himself. He's talking about how they don't matter, its just nickel and dimes, and al Pacino goes "don't you care? They're people. They're just... people"

Gets me every time v_v </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Does hentai even have uncensored videos anymore? Any hentai video post 2010 that's uncensored? [reqq] </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-09-16 16:21:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I remember on another forum there'd be all these jokes about how the Yakuza were doing an underground black market where they'd sell the uncensored versions of hentai, and make sure that it never becomes uncensored publicly so their business thrives. That was some hilarious stuff. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> That anime thing where characters put their 2 pointer fingers together when they are nervous about something or shyly talking to another character </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-09-02 21:45:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  Does anyone have pics of that trope? Looking for examples. It's sort of like this:

http://images6.fanpop.com/image/photos/33800000/Hinata-hinata-hyuga-33890528-308-385.jpg
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Infinitely Polar Bear official discussion [SPOILERS] </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-08-28 10:10:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Did anyone go see this movie? I really connected with it, and just absolutely loved it so much. 

Mark Ruffalo was stupendous, so many comedic moments and heartfelt moments. 

I felt so sorry for Zoe Saldana's character since she was just trying to have the best for her girls. 

And the 2 children actresses were great, I'm surprised with how organic their acting was. 

This movie truly deserves a lot of recognition. It had a lot of laughs, and a lot of heart.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Someone needs to explain gentlewhispering to me and her 1 million - 2 million view count [discussion] </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-08-20 04:12:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> There are so many asmr artists, how did she get so many million views compared to others that put out more videos like Heather feather or have very strikingly accurate roleplays like visualsounds1?

I remember when I first started watching gentlewhispering 3.5 years ago, back then I didn't really know much about asmr, I just enjoyed her one video where she has her hand in front of the mirror and does this really surreal effect that's very fun to watch. 

I had no idea then that this woman would have the most views out of any of the asmrtists ever. 

How did that happen? I'd like to know asmr history.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Putting a desmume rom game onto a ds? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-08-19 23:25:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I want to play that english fan translation download for Ace Attorney Investigations 2, but I really dislike playing on the computer or laptop. Is it possible to put it on the DS? I've heard a little bit about R4 cards back in the day but my friend's only had NES and SNES roms. So I don't know if I'm to use these for a desmume rom. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Looking for goofy porn where the guy "knights" the woman with his penis. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-08-17 16:22:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You know like how queen elizabeth knights a someone with a sword, something like that only the dude does it with his penis and they just have fun with it.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Seriously, has no one made a game similar to Simgirls? Perhaps with more polish? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-08-15 23:55:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Just a fullblown full sex porn game with the RPG stats that made Simgirls so enticing to me as a teen and sex scenes with actual penetration and stuff. 

I'm really surprised there weren't more of its kind  over on Newgrounds. For such a simple Flash type game it seems to still be popular even a whopping 10+ years later.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Does anyone know the last name of this British porn girl? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-08-15 23:28:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> www.pornhub.com/view_video.php?viewkey=1108381210

They call her Jess in both videos I've seen of her, but I'm unsure if she's a mainstream porn actress.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Has Chloe Foster done any creampie videos? If not how come? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-08-15 20:03:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I love her cute petite look but she does way too much crappy mainstream American porn and not enough X-Art/Joymii porn, or anything that features some real natural sexiness going on instead of just boring fucking.

I just don't understand why these girls wouldn't want it inside their vaginas instead of on their face. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Has janice griffith done any creampie videos? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-08-15 16:47:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The fact that she smiles during sex instantly bumped her up to the top of my list and I just need this one little thing for her to be a top 5 porn girl </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Rewatching a few episodes of Justice League Unlimited. God I love this show (spoilers) </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-28 01:09:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Just finished For the Man who has Everything, which makes me cry every single time. Ah superheroes and their daddy issues.

Then Kid's stuff, which is an episode that cracks me up every time. 

Now I'm on this little piggy. I just... there are so many great episodes and great moments from this show, I don't even know where to start. Wish it had gone on for longer. It's still THE default number 1 cartoon for an assembly of heroes.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [Request] balls deep creampie, not just on the outer rim, and a lot of it. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-22 01:43:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Like he actually grabs her back and she has her legs wrapped around him and squeezes it in so deep you can barely see it dripping out. But because there's so much semen there's still cum seeping out.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Does anybody have missasmr's private or deleted videos saved? [Missasmr] </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-15 14:21:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Does anyone use the in-house youtube app for Samsung galaxy s5? Wish there was adblock for it. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-12 22:37:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I can't believe there still isn't an app for blocking apps for people who don't want to root their phone. These youtube ads are insane.
It's 2015, hasn't there been any solution yet? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Cowgirl where the girl moves back and forth instead of up and down? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-11 22:56:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I much prefer back and forth. If it's European girls and generally attractive girls, even better.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> About to play this game, general questions. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-11 16:30:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Does this also have different endings like bioshock 1 and 2? If I start killing innocent people left and right to collect their money, is that bad karma? Does it affect anything like dialogue or endings? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Looking for a place where to buy these, I can't believe amazon doesn't sell them </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-10 21:21:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> http://i.imgur.com/SvxdtdH.png

Http://i.imgur.com/lBZgA5Q.png

The only place I've ever been able to find them is Eastern Europe, I cannot believe America of all places wouldn't have them.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Watched Me and Earl and the dying girl. It's really good (spoilers in the topic) </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-30 17:38:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Like really good. Only part I didn't agree with was they kept calling rachel ugly. I think she is beautiful. Like come on movie, you cant expect us to suspend our disbelief and think of this woman as ugly. 

One part I liked is how I saw the "hot" girl that the main character likens to a moose trampling a chipmunk. When she first appeared I was like "lol what, this is your movie's *hot girl*? With those eyebrows and that face?" She wasn't ugly per se just a bit... I don't want to say homely, but... regular. 

But as the movie went on, I ended up finding her very attractive because of her personality. She wasn't the stereotypical haughty popular girl with a sour face the entire movie or b**** "hot" as it were. She was actually really nice, and sweet, and smart, with no bulls***. I liked that about her. It was actually the main character who I wanted to punch just like earl did and I love that about the movie, showcasing the almost crippling self-loathing and narcissism of the protagonist. 

Also liked a lot of the supporting players. 

All around, I knew I was gonna like this movie and just when you think you're gonna hate its inevitable ending it does something to redeem it somewhat. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Any porn where the girl wraps her legs around the guy just as he's about to cum? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-30 04:10:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> And squeezes all the semen deep inside her?
Either that or the Lotus position where she just squeezes everything out of him with nothing but her vagina and hip gyrations. No hands. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Any porn where the girl wraps her legs around the guy just as he's about to cum? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-29 18:01:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> And squeezes all the semen deep inside her?

Either that or the Lotus position where she just squeezes everything out of him with nothing but her vagina and hip gyrations. No hands. 
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Does anybody have missasmr's private or deleted videos saved? [Missasmr] </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-28 15:40:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Looking for attractive blonde British girl that plays a woman's lingerie shop saleswoman </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-26 23:01:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> She tries on different clothes in the guise of "seeing how well it would look on your wife" and then cheekily asks what your wife would say if she saw you getting hard looking at another woman stripping completely. She has a bunch of other videos but that's the only one I remember, if I could just get a name or find that video again </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Why do you guys think softAnna never reveals her face? [SoftAnnaPL] </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-26 16:42:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Does anybody have missasmr's private or deleted videos saved? [Missasmr] </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-22 14:50:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Does anyone here even know who she is? Her videos were available last year and then suddenly bam it all disappeared. 

From experience I've known a lot of people to save and repost deleted asmr videos, like thewhiterabbitasmr </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Does anyone know which publicagent video this is? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-20 20:57:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> http://www.youporn.com/watch/8297875/publicagent-blonde-college-girl-fucks-me-at-her-student-apartment/

I can't remember the name of the girl or which number this public agent video this is.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What's up with missasmr why are 80% of her asmr videos private? [Missasmr] </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-20 16:53:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Will Dr Dark on 8muses ever be finished? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-18 15:23:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I really want to know how the story ends. I kind of really like the art style with its soft water based colors and really got into the mystery. 


8muses has a lot of strips from it but it seems to end on a cliffhanger and I have no idea how old this story is or if the artist is still doing it, I just discovered it a few weeks ago.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Looking for attractive blonde British girl that plays a woman's lingerie shop saleswoman </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-13 19:07:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> She tries on different clothes in the guise of "seeing how well it would look on your wife" and then cheekily asks what your wife would say if she saw you getting hard looking at another woman stripping completely.
She has a bunch of other videos but that's the only one I remember, if I could just get a name or find that video again </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Looking for romantic porn where the guy fingers the girl and then she sucks his finger. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-13 04:37:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thereby sucking her own pussy juices of his finger. 

That turns me on a lot. But it has to be romantic, none of that hateful mainstream American porn.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Looking for attractive blond British girl that plays a woman's lingerie shop saleswoman </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-10 13:11:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> She tries on different clothes in the guise of "seeing how well it would look on your wife" and then cheekily asks what your wife would say if she saw you getting hard looking at another woman stripping completely. 

She has a bunch of other videos but that's the only one I remember, if I could just get a name or find that video again... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Who is this girl? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-09 12:39:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> http://www.pornhub.com/view_video.php?viewkey=1661770695

And does anyone have any more videos of the guy or girl saying how they're going to fill them with cum, and rub their womb saying they're gonna feel it all in there? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Does anyone have English subtitles for the creampie clinic videos? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-09 11:38:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> They're a series of Japanese videos and I've only been able to find one that was subbed. I kinda wanna know what they're saying because I love the outlandish premise of what makes the doctors/nurses have sex with the patients. It's usually pretty hot.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Anyone know Carrie from Carrie's playhouse? Looking for vids before the boob job. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-06 15:28:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Now don't get me wrong she has probably the greatest boob job of all time, but I'm looking of videos when she has her original small boobs. Don't know what they're called or what to search for.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Any full-fledged comics here instead of just pictures? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-19 23:45:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I remember seeing one in color with Rukia and Ichigo, and I was wondering if there are a couple of others you guys might know about or already have on this subreddit? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Any good uncensored vanilla hentai like "Pretty Cool" </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-19 22:45:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That one was amazing.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Interested in a good comic, preferably colored, something like Justice League Hentai "the great scott saga" </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-19 16:40:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Honestly the only comics I've ever liked were that, and a black and white comic that was pretty damn amazing called "Pretty Cool", I love vanilla stuff like that where he and she want to be inside each other as much as possible and feature impregnation. 

I also read a kim possible story called the tale of kiki possible and... I kinda liked it __ 

More stuff like that. I honestly don't know what exact criteria to look for, I just know it has to be good. And colorful/vibrant soft artstyle, not that uncanny valley realistic style.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
