<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject4635</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2011-05-20 05:59:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> SHUT UP AND TAKE MY MONEY VALVE.

Valve has shut up already, they are just staring at the money.  #3232;\_ #3232;
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2011-05-20 03:32:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The Earth's graphics engine is over 4 billion years old and we still haven't caught up to it yet. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2011-05-20 03:28:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I beta tested Metal Drift. The guys who made it were close with the IA community...RIP IA (InstantAction). </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2011-05-19 04:24:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> He needs to do one for every video :D </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2011-05-19 04:16:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> In theory yes, in practice no. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2011-05-08 19:22:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Rhode Island would drown in its own corruption. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2011-05-06 03:36:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This. Valve has actually never officially named "G-Man". G-Man is a fan name. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> DAE (Did anybody else) like Clippy from Microsoft Word? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2011-05-05 00:42:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> He was so helpful when I was trying to make letters in like 4th grade. He was like, "Looks like you are writing a letter, do you need help with that?"

Answer was yes everytime. When they took him out of word I was sad :( </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> You have a problem with not seeing the Osama death picture? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2011-05-05 00:32:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2011-05-04 03:26:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Every Backyard Game.

Pablo Sanchez on your team. Guaranteed win. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Reddit, when did realize you liked boys/girls? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2011-04-27 05:45:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> When we are wee, society tells us to like boys or girls or whatever. You are told to like a group of people but when did you actually really realized that you were attracted to them. This might be confusing as it is confusing to explain but let me give my example.

I'm 16, almost 17 IRL, 17 on the internet  #3232;\_ #3232;, anyway my I like girls moment (I'm a guy) happened when I was around 14. It was just like a dawning on me that, HEY! I find girls attractive, not I just want to like them. Then I looked back on the incident where I was in 7th grade and a girl liked me but I brushed her off because I liked girls but didn't really yet.  #3232;\_ #3232;

The reason I ask this question was I saw like 2 7th graders holding hands after school and I was like  #3232;\_ #3232; I didn't even like girls back then.

EDIT: People are just posting ages which is boring, I kind of wanted to know if it was like HEY I like boys/girls or it was just like yeah boys/girls.

Anyway, share your stories reddit!
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2011-04-26 15:54:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm 16 and I install my own drivers. Does that mean I'm old too?

_ </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2011-04-26 15:33:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's like when I played Super Mario Galaxy. Beat it. Completely. All 121 stars. With both Mario and Luigi. Fuck you Purple Coin Luigi. It took me about 40 hours. That is the reason why I will never touch that game again and will never buy SMG2.

_ </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2011-04-26 03:50:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This is how you should take decision making, from Cave Johnson of course:

I pay the bills here, I can make the decisions here all damn day.

I however do not know if you pay the bills there...so :| </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2011-04-26 03:26:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yep.

Oh you have nice prominent veins.

(Proceed to stab you 3 times before drawing blood.) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2011-04-25 15:15:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Front Right: Phone   Headphones

Front Left: Wallet   Keys

Back Pockets: Empty </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2011-04-24 06:00:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Got my first game system at 15. It was a Wii, I'm 16 now. Can't even buy T games. :| </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2011-04-23 21:36:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> When I read that I actually went like this.

http://i.imgur.com/Y1xmH.png

Yep, I backed away from my computer in terror. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2011-04-23 18:45:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I would love Team Fortress 2

http://steamcommunity.com/id/subject4635

Here is some epic fan art for Bad Company 2, I can't think of anything amusing right now :|

http://www.deviantart.com/download/147117924/Bad_Company_2___Fan_ART_by_bfg_dayjay.png

Source: http://bfg-dayjay.deviantart.com/art/Bad-Company-2-Fan-ART-147117924 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Pin Tabs to Taskbar like IE9 in Windows 7 </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2011-04-12 23:52:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2011-04-05 01:37:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I just want to say downvoting other people does not give you a better chance. The OP gets to decide not based on downvotes but based on what he likes. So stop downvoting everybody.

_ </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2011-04-05 00:49:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> http://steamcommunity.com/id/subject4635

16 year old redditor :D

Made these a few days ago:

http://i.imgur.com/XG5IF.png

http://i.imgur.com/m0EU8.png </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2011-04-05 00:44:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It is because since this guy said it should go to Japan now he has to pick this guy. It looks really bad if he doesn't. What would be cool was if he donated $60 to Japan and still bought somebody else a game. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2011-03-31 01:08:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> _

I feel bad for you... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2011-03-31 00:39:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Fuck that teacher. I'm a Rhode Islander not a Conn Islander or a Rhodecunticut. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2011-03-30 00:54:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Cheat Codes: Change the name of a person in the park, different stuff happens depending on the one you put in.
http://www.gamespot.com/pc/strategy/rollercoastertycoon3/hints.html </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2011-03-29 02:32:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Ok here are the vids of the park. Sorry about the bad quality. Thats the only way it would load without crashing :D. I just watched them and I realized LiveStream has really bad quality D:

Park and some rides: http://livestre.am/Gj4M

Driving buggy through park before it crashing :| : http://livestre.am/Gj4L </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2011-03-29 00:59:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yep with all the files it loads! Videos coming up soon. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2011-03-29 00:23:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Best way to troll Gamestop, a couple months after the game is out release an update that allows you to get the skin after completing a challenge or something. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2011-03-29 00:16:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You try to make as money as possible while also gaining as much money as possible from other people. Building hotels on your numerous monopolies to screw people over when they land on them. Of course it teaches about the evils of capitalism. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2011-03-28 05:15:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I tried opening the file...it crashes on Initializing Park: 1% :( </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2011-03-28 00:58:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Was going to make a video going through your park and stuff. However I don't have the Wild extension...sorry :(
EDIT: After aquirring the Wild extension pack just for you. I'll make a couple videos of your park. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2011-03-18 15:00:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It still blows my mind that I can convert one file type into another type. Thanks for letting me put Minecraft music on my WP7 (.ogg to .mp3). :D :D </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2011-03-15 07:28:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Epic troll is epic. After watching her first video which was completely normal and watching one where she said she just heard of WoW I was like. So when she said. LOL I BE TROLZ, I was like :| . I do respect her for her epic troll skill however. It takes dedication and skill to troll for that long. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2011-03-12 18:12:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Also slavery </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2011-03-05 21:08:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> When I first saw the original image, I got scared. It reminded me of the people protesting against the Civil Rights movement. So I made this. What is America becoming?


http://i.imgur.com/mSO78.png </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2011-03-02 21:31:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> My mom works for the State government in Rhode Island.
If she gets laid off...
;_; </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2011-03-02 21:31:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> My mom works for the State government.
If she gets laid off...
;_; </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2011-02-20 17:20:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hope you don't corrupt your save. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2011-02-18 22:26:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> :D PVE MAP :D
Now to find some clay. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2011-02-17 20:50:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> WP7 ftw?! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2011-02-17 20:45:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If they get it working on my AMD Integrated 4200 HD graphics card (desktop not laptop) then sure! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2011-02-14 18:28:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I thought the reason why we are not posting the PVE map is because it's just so big. It takes hours to render so Nat said it would only update once a day and he still has to do a couple more things for it to update. Most people on the forums were in support of mapping PVE.

http://www.nerd.nu/forum/index.php?p=/discussion/22/mapping-pve#Item_8 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2011-02-13 05:24:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thanks for the info. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Bucketapocalypse </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2011-02-13 04:50:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Meinkraft: It's a struggle </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2011-02-12 23:16:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2011-02-08 23:45:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Wait wait wait, they DON'T want my money? Lol. Why are we the biggest and best Minecraft server to date? Because we are awesome. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2011-02-02 15:30:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I am also on the IRC chat. So if you need a mod just say golf and my IRC client tells me that somebody mentioned me.

EDIT: I changed it so it also notifies me if somebody says mod so type mod or include mod in your statement so I can go log on.

EDIT again: I took out mod so only golf notifies me if somebody needs me. Mod was interfering with my other channels. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2011-01-31 19:58:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You had no door on your house. I broke one block. Killed you after you logged out then took your stuff and fixed the hole I made. Don't build so close to spawn anymore. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2011-01-30 15:11:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Best thing to do now is not play on PVE. I love PVE but I don't want to loose my hard work. Play on creative or survival until PVE is 100% </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2011-01-29 00:57:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Did you notice this and do you know what it is?

Do you think the CTA Spawn Station Entrance should be more noticeable or do you think it should be more minimalist? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> CTA Station At Spawn </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2011-01-29 00:56:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2011-01-28 23:17:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> No. I waited almost 2 months after I played the free weekend before I could play Minecraft again. All that waiting was for my bank to transfer my money to PayPal. Waiting for my conformation amounts. Waiting for my bank statements. It was a long process but it payed off. I never pirate myself because I think its wrong in every situation. I can see why other people would pirate the game though. But pirating talk shouldn't be done here. If you are on the border for buying the game. Try to get somebody you know to let you try the game on their account or petition Notch to do more free weekends. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2011-01-26 00:26:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Took me a couple hours to do. I created a custom texture pack to get the right feel and i turned up fog 2 notches.

Here is the texture file: http://cid-ed7da04267ba1979.office.live.com/self.aspx/Public/Portal%20Pack.zip

If you want to see the real thing turn on the texture pack and go to the server c.nerd.nu and type in /warp portal </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Portal: Cake Room In Minecraft </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2011-01-26 00:24:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2011-01-24 04:32:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The server will be down for tonight. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2011-01-23 14:58:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Server went down last night. My dad turned off the computer. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> A More Reliable Chaos Server </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2011-01-22 18:53:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> IP: 74.97.191.94

I'm hosting a plain vanilla server as a replacement to the chaos server because we all know that Bukkit has weird problems with it. I'll only keep it up until Bukkit gets better or something. The server will be handled by me not by mcpublic so don't complain to mcpeople if anything happens. Complain to me. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2011-01-22 16:06:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> 30 seconds to generate. About 5 minutes to open in Paint.Net. Here is the corner of the sun at 100%. http://i.imgur.com/WNKEx.png

It took about 4GB of RAM just for Paint.Net to open it and when I tried to do sepia on the pic it took about 6GB of RAM so I just killed the process. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2011-01-18 03:20:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That means i will need the .jar instead...hmmmm </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2011-01-18 00:29:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> After editing more TNT in underground...it crashed when it got to 1000 mb usage from the server. There must be a limit to how much the server can handle. If there is a set limit and that limit was nothing the server could probably handle anything. Notch/Mojang remove the limit on how much ram a server can use :D. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2011-01-18 00:13:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Update: I just used MCEdit to put more tnt in. Check the livestream to see it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2011-01-17 23:56:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> LiveStream: http://www.livestream.com/subject4635
Server IP: 74.97.191.94

I want to see how far my server can go. I want to crash my server.
CPU: amd phenom ii x4 830 2.8 gig with 4 cores
Ram: 8 gigs of ram
OS: Windows 7 x64 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> I think we need more TNT: Trying to crash my personal server...I don't think its possible </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2011-01-17 23:54:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2011-01-17 20:08:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Its built in with bukkit. We cant change what bukkit natively does. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2011-01-17 14:46:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's built in with Bukkit. Not removable at this time. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2011-01-14 14:50:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> My own personal pack which took me about 10 minutes to update. It is a simple pack but I like it. The only thing I haven't changed yet is the new tree leaves.
http://dl.dropbox.com/u/7912305/Golf1052%20Pack.zip </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2011-01-14 05:52:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Pure Epicness </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2011-01-12 19:20:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The cartograph is before anything was built. Admins get to decide if we do future cartographs. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2011-01-12 16:52:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> FYI for all voters: This is what the spawn area looks like.

http://i.imgur.com/dI5ZK.png

http://i.imgur.com/svcKx.jpg

http://i.imgur.com/O3TF6.png

Don't choose a spawn that looks really ugly in context (in PVE). </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2011-01-12 05:04:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> No it actually has to be 3000 people. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2011-01-12 03:50:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> However if you tell everybody you know to donate to the server we will reach the goal :D </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Challenge Accepted: If 3000 each donate $1 to the server by Friday then chest and inventories will not be reset on PVE </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2011-01-12 01:09:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> http://nerd.nu/donate

You must donate at least $1 for you to be counted as a person.

From Reddit Mumble:

sirmalloc: there's 170ish people in the whitelist, there are over 3000 on survival over it's lifetime

sirmalloc: if 3000 people donate, i won't reset, how's that?

subject4635: http://images1.memegenerator.net/ImageMacro/4548516/Challenge-accepted.jpg?imageSize=Large generatorName=challenge-accepted </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2011-01-12 00:59:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You must donate at least $1 for you to be counted as a person.

From Reddit Mumble: 

sirmalloc: there's 170ish people in the whitelist, there are over 3000 on survival over it's lifetime

sirmalloc: if 3000 people donate, i won't reset, how's that?

subject4635: http://images1.memegenerator.net/ImageMacro/4548516/Challenge-accepted.jpg?imageSize=Large generatorName=challenge-accepted </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2011-01-12 00:37:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I made it :D so first off

+1

The glass wall around the spawn area with lightstone makes the spawn visible from far away and acts as a light filled area all the time. The spawn is then linear to make sure people can see all the rules while walking out. The banned items are not stashed in a corner but are pillars for everybody to see. The rules, staff, and other signs are between these pillars so they are easy to see while leaving spawn. The gold and iron blocks in the middle point east and west. The golden blocks representing the sun rising in the east after a long night and the iron blocks representing the moon setting in the west after a long night.

The pillars are also setup to show the banned items are also set up in a specific way. The right side contains the more passive banned blocks. Obsidian, water, and ice. These do not cause major catastrophic destruction. The left side the contains the active banned blocks. TNT, lava, and fire. They are also set up in pairs, TNT and obsidian, the most destructive and the hardest blocks. Lava and water, the two flowing elements. And fire and ice...fire and ice. :D </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2011-01-12 00:29:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Seeds can be used for bad things. Because bad things can be used with seeds, seeds are now banned. Read ModChat to find out more. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2011-01-09 06:22:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I forgot to ask this before I left. Will resetting the chests reset mob spawner chests also? How will you make the distinction between player chests and mob spawn chests? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2011-01-08 07:10:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The amount of gray area for the survival rules sickens me. I say that this grey area bullshit needs to be addressed now before anything else happens with survival. Right now it's a pve but you are able to kill people. No taking their buildings or belongings in chests, you can only kill them OUTSIDE THEIR BASE and then go home. It really is no fun for anybody.
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2011-01-05 00:58:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> We try our best. I don't think we are that organized though. If you listen to some of the convos we have in Mumble :) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2010-12-30 17:56:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I accidentally broke into your house and killed you because I saw your name through the dirt. I was trying to find the entrance and I was like screw it and broke into the hill which looked like a hill which instead was your house. I did fix your house. I then proceeded to burn you to death because lava is one of the best tactics for pvp. It is kind of boring to only do mod stuff all day so I wanted to do some pvp. I didn't use any kind of mod hacks or anything. I was playing like a regular player. Lava is a hard weapon to use but its very useful.

Once I was being chased by a diamond armor diamond sword wielding person and when I got them to walk into the lava I got he got distracted from chasing me and went to find water and then I hacked him to death. Very useful tactic an it should be kept. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2010-12-29 04:53:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Other </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2010-12-29 04:53:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Mainly PvP server with small PvE areas (this is what we have now) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2010-12-29 04:53:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Mainly PvE server with small PvP arenas </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2010-12-29 04:52:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> PvE (player vs environment) only server </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2010-12-29 04:52:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> PvP (Player vs player) only server "chaos" server </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What should future survival be like? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2010-12-29 04:51:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> With all the confusion of whats right and whats wrong in the current survival server I want see what the community thinks about the survival server now and what kind of setup they would like in the future. Comment under each idea you want or comment under the other section for posting your own idea. Just because this is posted here it might not actually happen but input would be good for the server. THIS IS NOT AN OFFICIAL DECISION OR POST. I just want to know what people want. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2010-12-28 13:42:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Really? After I read this I made a randomly generated 10 character password for my Minecraft account. Minecraft is the most valuable thing I own right now. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Minecraft Is Beautiful </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2010-12-26 00:22:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2010-12-23 05:28:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Made this house on the Reddit server. I think it's amazing.
Here are more pics: http://subject4635.imgur.com/house_1
I got my inspiration from this: http://www.reddit.com/r/Minecraft/comments/epl90/my_attempt_to_build_a_cool_house/ </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> My House on the Temp Reddit Server </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2010-12-23 05:26:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2010-11-30 00:03:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> if you want to see the final one right now check this out

http://www.reddit.com/r/mcpublic/comments/echdj/cartographs_of_the_childs_play_map_final_map/ </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Cartographs of the Child's Play map. Final map. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2010-11-27 15:59:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> When we were done!

I uploaded them on my skydrive for maximum quality and imgur doesnt like huge files.

Map Download: http://cid-ed7da04267ba1979.office.live.com/self.aspx/24%20hour%20Child%5E4s%20Play%20Map/map.zip

Normal
http://mh8aaq.blu.livefilestore.com/y1pciNacVfxmqhwEZLblmBWHrJO_J2HqsCPZHXEbKOKnmJ0lVx_QLz3U9YNYbdrfqFGYuaW65YPJu5pMATJWK9ArUnLr3ka5_kQ/custom-map-normal-day.png

Heightmap
http://mh8aaq.blu.livefilestore.com/y1pQ4OwuQKlw9pcRz9WPJYtD1SHFJxH2GQv86VMnXyMg0Uy7RcP1rOuO6greW5ZnYOBbcyGw8Wtl4dtkvcjtrgNyGYpq_pHgfOS/custom-map-heightcolor.png

Heightmap Greyscale
http://mh8aaq.blu.livefilestore.com/y1p01QE9bVBAwjwOmGwNnjpefXEOR7BSW_fsK2JZSMH0BBpp8BhDeG8orzB9GiBE_cN9N1MdmfN-TxTTZAGnMSsnomGx_7hSNe1/custom-map-heightgray.png

Oblique
http://mh8aaq.blu.livefilestore.com/y1ppg401tIaWC4EIPOGKIXtmCX2LuKQ-gV31wh_2UIBgIkc_jGNqZgvK1cyOibfeDoVHVlpzia3kK1IzArU2sFAanSwgUyQVI1-/custom-map-oblique-day.png

Oblique Angle
http://mh8aaq.blu.livefilestore.com/y1p40Dt7fMstONznzUqsGLWkatSD8VYoQ-FoxWnCjIgQJMHgye_743ZjW5cXe2Zf6Mm54hJPQpZuVO_1VUfX3mDhdvoFQWQX0Ct/custom-map-obliqueangle-day.png

Isometric
http://mh8aaq.blu.livefilestore.com/y1pclKXQD4chSqEXo2A1J5MsuP-Mf4s97ymOh3NJWabe-hYjEk-mqAB2lml18N2iltbEh2f0pNCSw8x5qPllOEyw7UvAFBWtaHg/custom-map-day.png </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Cartographs of Child's Play Map of 7:20 </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2010-11-27 01:49:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Top down and iso of Child's Play map after it came back up.

Top Down
http://i.imgur.com/is2Kw.jpg

Iso
http://i51.tinypic.com/1z3td9s.jpg </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2010-11-11 01:12:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm surprised that nobody knows who the real culprit is, its obviously Herobrine. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2010-11-03 20:47:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> 2b.
Cubiod is cool and all but after reading it makes me feel that building awesome things by hand is 10x more awesome than building awesome things with Cuboid. When i saw MegaDome I was amazed but now that I know it was build with Cuboid it makes it less amazing. Do I think its possible with out Cuboid, yes but it would take a really really long time. But if somebody has enough drive and manpower anything can happen. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2010-11-03 02:30:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I vote for 2 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2010-11-01 21:01:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I think Herobrine has the answer. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2010-10-20 01:05:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> FUCK YES </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2010-06-26 21:29:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Im updating code regularly. If you want more features or stuff just request it. Im basically just going to add stuff and make it conform to the UI Panoramic Specifications. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2010-06-21 18:39:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> well panoramic menus in WP7 are always in portrait but i could put it in landscape if people really want it. and if you want some code ill put it up soon. i just need to get it more organized so others can understand it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Panorama Menu For XNA Games </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2010-06-19 04:25:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I created a panorama menu for XNA games. Here is a link to a video showing it off.
http://www.youtube.com/watch?v=7nxzT4FqQlI
Comment if you want to see more! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
