<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject3307</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-04-22 20:45:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I got a 6-pack of VHS tapes from my aunt. I subsequently made a "video" with my then boyfriend, which was found by his aunt and uncle. I was 15. Worst gift EVER! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-04-15 22:50:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I understand you were posting your experience. However, I still don't understand how what you described could have been so traumatic for you. It sounds like the hospital ran some tests and placed you in a room until you could be evaluated by a doctor.

I felt so bad for the people who were staying behind. I had been there for one night; what had they been through staying there for days? I wouldn't have wished that place on my worst enemies.

Who are YOU to judge that that hospital was so bad and their experiences were just as traumatic as yours?

all I wanted was help to get back on track with my classes, and I got locked up like a crazy person.

You got "locked up" because you told your counselor you were feeling suicidal. The counselor took you to the hospital because she was afraid of what you yourself admitted to thinking of doing. And not all people that spend time in a hospital for psychiatric reasons are "crazy" people.

And I take personal offense with your use of the term "loonie bin". It is because of people like you and your use of derogatory terms, i.e. "crazy person" and "loonie bin" that mental illness has a negative stigma associated with it.
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-04-15 21:26:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I really think you are doing a disservice to other people struggling with depression and in need of serious help, i.e. hospitalization. Your experience doesn't sound terrible at all; it's right on par with what happens when you are committed to a mental hospital.

Time to put on your big girl panties and stop being a drama queen about it. There are tons of other people that have and will get great results from being in the hospital for a few days or more. Shame on you for portraying it as "the worst experience" of your life and scaring others away from possibly getting the treatment that can save their lives! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-03-27 02:29:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I hear you; I understand. PM me. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-03-21 05:30:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> YES, it is completely acceptable. Being a woman, my mother always taught me not to go beating up on boys/men because if you do they have every right to hit you back. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-03-20 04:33:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I've always thought about just driving over to the airport, walking up to the ticket counter and buying a ticket to whatever destination sounds good to me at that very moment. I thought I was the only one... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-02-22 05:55:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I didn't feel like the meds were working. What's the point of taking them if they aren't going to do what they're supposed to?

I feel almost exactly the same as I did while on meds, except for the fact that I feel terrible physically as well as mentally/emotionally. I also am sleeping a lot more than I did with the meds, but I think that just has to do with my physical state. (I was on 450mg of Effexor.) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-02-22 01:59:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I stopped without my doctor's knowledge. I'm expecting a huge lecture when I go see him on Friday... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-02-22 01:55:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Me too. I'm tired of fighting to live. I just don't understand why it has to be so hard for us, yet so easy for everyone else. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-02-18 06:13:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I've just stopped taking my meds, too. I was on 8 different ones. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-02-05 05:31:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I live close to SF, around Alameda. Where exactly are you located? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-02-04 21:57:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm in the SF area. PM me so we can grab some tacos. I hate being alone... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-02-04 21:46:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> PM me if you want to talk. I have been dealing with depression for 15 years so I understand how you feel. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-02-04 21:25:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I added you as well. Let's talk. I know how you feel. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2011-11-28 05:50:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> HOLY JESUS!!! I'm scarred for life... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
