<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject5311</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-07 14:16:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I don't know why I didn't think of this before, thanks for the idea. 
And I cut the basic shape with a bandsaw, then I took it to a router table with a straight flute bit in it, but in a couple spots it would jump and take out big chunks of it. 

I'll keep on working on this one as it is, but for my next one I'll definitely use a template. Might look into getting some of my drawings laser cut. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Attempting an electric ukulele out of a piece of curly cherry. Any suggestions on how to keep my router from bouncing where it shouldn't and making me wanna kill myself? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-07 04:35:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-29 05:26:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Is that a 1x1 piece of ebony you used?

Also I'm no expert, but it looks like you get your wood from Bell </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-10 16:57:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm interested in a test drive, where do I sign up? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [MS] Scout </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-06 20:40:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I was a huge animal lover growing up. Birds of prey, specifically eagles, were always my favorite.
I would go to the zoo every chance I got, at least once a week, and I'd go visit the eagle enclosure. Before long all the trainers knew me by name, and they even let me in and let me hold one of the bald eagles they had, named Scout.

After a while, they started letting me in there regularly, and Scout grew to trust me enough that he'd come right up to me when I walked in. 
But after a few weeks of regular visits, I noticed Scout acting strangely. He couldn't keep his balance very well, he wouldn't eat hardly at all, and I also noticed the back of his neck started to break out in this weird rash. 
I asked the trainers and they told me it was fine, it was just a reaction to a change in food at the zoo.

A few days later, I came in and Scout wasn't there. I asked where he was, and they said he was in for a regular checkup. I left and just figured I came in on a bad day.
I came in the next week to the same thing. All the eagles were there except Scout.
I asked another trainer, and he gave me the same excuse. "He's in for a regular checkup".

Something wasn't right here. I had no idea what was happening, but I was going to find out.
I came in the next day, a little later than usual, toward the end of the day. I hid behind some stuff, enough to be out of sight from the workers, and waited for everyone to leave.

I'd been around enough that they all trusted me, so I've been in the back round plenty, I've seen them put in the code to the door probably over a hundred times. I punched in the code, and made my way to where they kept the eagles, and looked for Scout's cage. It didn't take me long to find his cage, it smelled like death, I could hardly breathe while I was close to it.
I finally found him, and he looked terrible. His eyes were blood red, the rash on his neck was even worse than before, and he could barely stand straight.

I felt he needed out of that cramped cage, with all the droppings and his half-eaten food starting to rot, and he needed it badly.
I searched the room for some spare keys to the cages, and after a few minutes I found some. I went to his cage and turned the key in the lock. As soon as he heard the click, his head turned and he looked straight at me.
I slowly opened the cage, then he burst out and started flying all around the enclosure.

I sat and watched him for a few minutes, free and majestic, before I noticed red and blue flashes in the windows. I didn't even think there might've been an alarm, but I must've tripped it when I opened Scout's cage.
A few seconds after I noticed the lights, a heard a loud crash as someone broke down the door to the building. I saw about a dozen men with body armor and guns burst in, I saw a big "S.W.A.T." on all their chests, and I was scared to death as they leveled their guns at me.

They kept screaming at me to get down and put my hands up, so I did. I got on my knees and put my hands up, and two of them came up to me to handcuff me. Right as they approached me, Scout came out of nowhere and swooped down on top of the two headed toward me, knocking them down.

I looked at him add he flew toward the others, and I watched as they all opened fire and shot him down.

He landed a few feet in front of me, and I ran to him with tears in my eyes, screaming his name and holding him as the others ran at me to arrest me. I screamed at them and asked why they had to kill him. He simply responded, "for the same reason we're arresting you".

I asked what that was supposed to mean, and he looked me in the eyes and said "you were participating in ill eagle activities". </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-24 21:04:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Okay so here's one that I've been weirded out about for a while but I didn't know it was a thing until I heard the term "mandela effect".

Does anyone else remember Denis Leary dying a few years ago? 2010 or somewhere around there. I distinctly remember my mom mentioning it and me asking who that was, and finding out it was the dude from the sandlot and ice age. I distinctly remember him being dead. Then I see him in the news last week and I could've sworn he died years ago. I searched and he'd been doing stuff still, and my mom doesn't remember him being dead or anything like that. 

Anyone else remember? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-02 19:25:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> being a straight white male </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-25 01:28:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> FALCOR </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-21 04:01:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> "So a horse walks into a bar.." </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Perfection </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-14 08:53:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> We've all heard it our entire lives. "One day you'll find that one person that'll change your life forever".
I, like alot of people my age, believed that was absolute bull. One person can't affect us like that. Especially not someone like me, not that weird outcast kid.

But when I was 15, I learned that I was wrong. I met the girl that changed my life forever.

She was beautiful, smart, and she had an air about her that couldn't help but make everyone that was around her smile.

She was perfect.

But there was just one problem. She had no idea who I was. We'd never spoken, and I doubt she'd even seen me around school, she always hung around her friends. Besides, why would she ever speak to an acne-ridden geek like me?

My first instinct was to just give up and move on, she was out of my league, and there was no way I'd ever reach her level. But after a minute to think, I decided to screw instinct, I was going to try.

I spent the next few days learning about her, who she was, who her friends were, her hobbies and interests. Honestly I was kinda turning into a bit of a stalker. But I was head over heels in love.

After a couple weeks of fighting myself to finally get the courage to actually talk to her, I did.
I made a complete idiot out of myself, but I talked to her.

Thanks to my previous stalking, I was able to learn enough to pretend to like some of the stuff she did, just so we'd have something to talk about instead of awkward silence. And apparently that worked, she seemed to at least not hate me, so that was good.

We talked alot for the next few weeks. My life was honestly changing, and for the better. I wasn't as stressed anymore, I was actually looking forward to school instead of fearing it, my whole outlook on life was better, and I owed it all to her.

I'll admit though, I did kinda keep stalking her a little just so I could keep learning about her, because I was always nervous to talk to her, and I didn't want to ask her a bunch of random things about herself. I just wanted to observe her so I could learn.

Admittedly, it went a little too far sometimes. I followed her home from school one day because I was curious where she lived, but I found myself going back more and more frequently, sometimes even at night, just to watch her play video games and laugh. 

I didn't mean anything by it, I just didn't have anything to look forward to at home, so I wanted to spend as much time as I could with her, even though they weren't exactly "with" her.

But one night, I lost track of time and stayed out later than usual. I didn't even realize it until after I saw her shut off her game and start being ready for bed. I should've left right then, but I couldn't leave yet. I needed to see what she's like at night, at least before bed.

Then she started undressing. 

She didn't even close the shades, but why would she? The closest neighbor was nearly a mile away, she didn't think there'd be a kid in a tree watching.

I tried, I honestly tried to look away, but I couldn't. I needed to see what the rest of her was like.

Perfect. 

She was truly perfect. As she lifted her shirt up to reveal her stomach and her hips, then up over her head to where I could see it all. Her perfect form was laid out right in front of me, and she had no idea. 

Part of me wanted her to know, I didn't want to keep secrets from her, but I couldn't let her know that I'd been watching and learning abut her, she'd never speak to me again.

I just ignored the voice in my head telling me to just go home and forget it, and I kept watching. 

She turned around to sit on her bed, then slipped on a big t shirt. I sat there for a couple more minutes, watching her read in bed, before I realized how late it was and decided to go home.

The next day at school, I tried to act like nothing was wrong, but I just ended up avoiding her. I couldn't face her right after that. 

But deep inside, I needed more. I craved it, I craved her.
That voice kept showing up to tell me to forget about it, but I couldn't. How could I possibly forget something like that?

I had an idea.

It was starting to rain, and we were supposed to get thunderstorms that night. As soon as school was over, I ran home to search for my old Polaroid camera that I've had for years.

I found it, waited a couple hours till my normal time, then went back to her house. I sat in my spot in the tree, and waited for the show.

It got dark pretty quick after I got there, and the storms were starting. After about an hour or so of watching her play games, as usual, she shut them off just like last night. I watched as she walked over to her bed and started undressing again.

My Polaroid was stupid and had this ridiculously bright flash on it, but I figured I can time it right and make it seem like lightning.

It worked like a charm, and by the time she put that big t shirt back on, I had about a half dozen photos of her.

All this time I kept thinking to myself "I need more", but I couldn't risk it. It was getting late and I needed to get back home.

I went home and dug around in my room for my old journal that I hadn't written in since I was like 6 years old. I finally found it, and made a new entry with the date and her name, then I set the Polaroids I took between the pages and hid the book under my pillow.

We didn't have any more storms for a while, so I never hit the chance to take more pictures, but I did still go over there nearly every night, and I wrote in the journal what she'd spend her nights doing.

This went on for a couple weeks, then that nagging voice in my head finally took over, and I realized that I needed to stop.

So I did. I never went back to her house again.

But after all this, I was way braver than I'd ever been before. I was ready to do the impossible and ask her to be mine.

So one day that week when I saw her at school, I just went up to her and straight up asked her out.
To my bewilderment, she said yes and within a minute we had our first date planned.

I took her out to go eat and then watch a movie, and it honestly went extremely well. I was falling more in love with her every day.

We went on a couple more dates like that, then after the third, I invited her over to hang out and play some video games for a while. 

We got to my house and went up to my room. She plopped down on my bed, and I sat down next to her, not knowing what the heck to do, I'd never been anywhere with a girl before. 

I asked her what she wanted to do, and she said she didn't know, that I should decide. Suddenly, I felt that huge burst of courage that I felt that same moment that I decided to ask her out.

Then I just leaned over and kissed her.

While I did that, everything in me was screaming, hoping I didn't just ruin everything, but judging by her reaction, I don't think I did.

She was a bit shocked at first, but she quickly placed her arms around me and leaned into it to the point that I was laying on my back on the bed.

We kept that up for a couple minutes, just enjoying it. Then she stopped, so I looked up into her eyes. She had a huge smile on her face, then she grabbed my hand and placed it on her side, to where it was lightly lifting up her shirt.

Did she want me to take it off?

I looked at her in a way to ask her if that's what she was saying, and she smiled and nodded. I started lifting her shirt up slowly, but when my hands got just above her ribs, I stopped. Her expression had completely changed, and she want looking at me, but past me. I looked over to see what she could possibly be looking at, then I saw it.

I froze, realizing what just happened. 

My head had shifted my pillow, moving my journal out from under it. In the process, a couple of the pictures had slipped out and were hanging out of the book.

Pictures of her. From outside her window.

She saw them, and she instantly knew.

She pushed me into the bed and jumped up, too freaked out to even say anything. She just stared at me with a look of terror in her eyes. The only word she managed to get out was "why?".

I had no idea what to say, I couldn't possibly explain myself out of this. So I just told her the truth.

"I'm in love with you. I have been for months, I saw you the first time by accident, but I needed more so I took some pictures to keep for myself. I just needed to have you with me".

She started to tear up and she backed away, telling me to never speak to her again, and if I showed up at her house again, she'd call the police.

I couldn't let her leave, I needed her more than anything. I didn't even think before I did anything, I just grabbed a big chunk of quartz that I kept on my shelf, and threw it at her.

It hit her right in the head, and she collapsed. I ran up to her, barely being able to process what just happened, and I tried to see if she was okay.

She wasn't breathing. She wasn't waking up and I couldn't feel a heartbeat.

She was dead.

I sat there next to her for a second, letting everything that just happened sink in, and trying to stay focused.

"I can't let anyone know"

Luckily my parents weren't home yet, so I was able to pull her out of the house without anyone seeing. 

But I had to do something with the body, I couldn't just let it sit in the yard. 

Then I remembered that my neighbors had just filled in the hole for their old swimming pool, and they had been on vacation for a few days now.

I grabbed a shovel and started digging in the loose soil. When I got a few feet deep, I dropped her in and filled the hole the best I could.

Nobody would ever know anything. 

I went inside and took a shower, washing blood and dirt off me, then went and played video games until my parents came home. They asked how my day was, and I just said it was fine, as usual. That got em to leave me alone, so I just played for a little longer, then went to bed.

"They were right all along", I thought.
"One person really can change a life."

She was the first person I ever loved, and the only person I ever loved.

She was perfect. 

She was also the first person I ever killed. But no matter how many more I take, no matter how close I get to one like her, that one will always be my favorite.

It was perfect. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> I win. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-12-12 07:54:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> They tell me it's a gift.
They've always told me that I was gifted.
I'm not gifted, this is the furthest possible thing from a gift I could ever have.

I should explain.

Long story short, I know when people are going to die.

It's been happening as long as I can remember, but I have no idea why I can and nobody else.
Now I can't just look at someone and say "Yeah you're gonna die at 2:48 on June 22, 2038", I can only see it a few days out, from past experiences, a maximum of 4 days.

It starts with the smell.
4 days before a person dies, every time I'm near them, I can smell this stench, like a mixture of something rotting and something burning. It's been 26 years, and I still can't get used to that horrible smell. 
It starts off faint, but by now I'm pretty quick to tell what it is. By day 2 it's pretty intense, and I can't be around the person for more than a couple minutes.

By day 3, things start getting strange.
I start hearing things when I get near them, like voices, but they're scattered and I can never tell what they're saying. 

But day 4, the day they die, I'm terrified to even look near them. All around them are these... things. I've never looked long enough to see what they look like, or even if they have a look. They're just black figures that I've been able to tell, like walking shadows. They might have faces, but I really never wanted to find out. 
They're always right in front of the person, within inches, but nobody can see them but me. If I'm close enough, I can hear them whispering something to the person. Around them, they usually only have one, but sometimes two or more, and one time I've seen up to 8 around a single person.

Sometimes the first 3 days are skipped, and it goes straight to seeing them, the Whisperers.

If it goes normally, from the smell all the way through, it means they just die. Natural causes, sickness, something like that.

But if it skips, they're killed somehow. Murder, accidents, I've seen it all.

And yes, I've seen it. I've seen it hundreds of times in my life, and I've never been able to do a single thing about it, no matter how much I try.

They always die. Death finds a way.

When I was younger, about 6 or 7, I had finally realized what all the signs meant. I would go up to someone I didn't know, but could smell, and I would tell them that they're going to die. I didn't know any better, and my parents just apologized for me and hurried me away.

But it wasn't for a couple years, until it happened to my grandfather. I smelled him, and by then it was already a pretty strong smell, and I knew what was happening. I walked up to him, gave him the biggest hug that 10 year old me could give, and told him that I loved him.

My mom saw me, and asked me later why I did that, and I told her. "Papa's going to die in a few days".
She didn't know how to react to that, and I don't blame her, but she sent me to my room after that.

2 days later, she came up to me and gave me a huge hug. I knew what happened. She told me that he died in his sleep that morning. She asked me how I knew, and I told her everything. She didn't believe me at first, but I told her the next time I smelled someone, and 3 days later, he was in the obituaries.

My mom made me promise not to tell anyone, and to this day, I've never told a soul. My mom died 4 years ago, and I've still kept her promise.

But I'm telling you today because I need someone else to know. I need help.

My girlfriend and I have lived together for nearly 2 years now, and she doesn't know yet, I don't know if I'll tell her.
But I woke up this morning to voices. Whispers.
I didn't know if it was for me or for her. I didn't want to find out.

I laid there for what felt like hours, listening to them, before I had the courage to open my eyes.
I looked, and it was there. The Whisperer.

Its face, it didn't have anything that could be called a face, but at the same time it did. I can't explain it in words, but they most definitely do have faces, and I can't stand looking at them.

I needed to find out which one of us it was here for. I got up to go use the bathroom, careful not to let it know I could see it, and it followed me. 

I was the one, it's finally my time.

I walked out of the bathroom to go back to bed, pretending I didn't see them, and when I saw my bed, I froze.
There was another one.
It was standing over her.

They were here for both of us.

But I don't want to die. And I don't want her to die.

I've never been able to stop it before, but I'm not going to let them have this. They can't have us.

I just need these voices to stop.

As I write this, she still isn't awake.
I know how to keep them from getting us.

I won't tell her, but she won't have to worry. She won't have to wake up.

I'm getting rid of the voices, once and for all. They won't be able to take us.

This is my note.

Goodbye.
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-06-02 00:03:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm on the south side of Dallas, he was on the north side of Houston, it's just shy of 3 hours </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> He knows where I live </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-06-01 18:44:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> My story is a reminder to you that people online aren't all who they claim to be.

It starts about 4 months ago, mid-February. I'm 22, Christian, living with my parents, almost done with my sophomore year of college, single as could be, and there was no sign of that changing anytime soon seeing as all the single guys in college were just people that wanted nothing but a one night stand. 
Some of my friends told me I should try an online dating service, but I was a bit iffy because I felt it would be hard keeping something with distance, plus I have trust issues when it comes to guys.
So not long after that, I saw an ad for "christianmingle.com", and at first I thought that was stupid, that they were the only way to find your "soul mate". But I thought about what my friends told me about online dating, and I thought that I'd give it a shot. I decided on that Christian mingle thing because I figured that there would be less guys there just looking for sex as opposed to the other websites.

So I set up a profile, and of course I exaggerated a few things, but not too much. I set it up and waited for something to happen. 
After about two weeks, I'd gotten a few messages, mostly spam, but a couple hopefuls that I ended up giving up on after they asked me for "special" pictures. But then I got a message from a guy named Marc, and he seemed like a really nice guy, plus he didn't seem to exaggerate every single detail of his profile. He was 24, and he was apparently a carpenter. He lived in an outskirt of Houston, I lived in Dallas, so we weren't too far away, and I decided I might give him a shot.

We talked alot over the next few weeks, and he just kept getting better and better. All our interests were alike, with the exception that he loved country music and I couldn't stand it, but I thought we could make that work. He seemed genuinely interested in me, and in something long term, and that made me really hopeful that we could make things work out between us.

About the middle of April, we decided to make things real, and get serious about this. We wanted to meet in person, and so we decided that he would come to Dallas and spend a weekend together so he could meet my parents, and hopefully they would approve.
So the next Saturday morning, he drove to Dallas and we finally met at my parents' house. I was a nervous wreck the entire time, it's such a rush seeing the person you're so close to for the first time, and realizing that they're actually real.
We spent the day together, doing typical date stuff, we went out to some fancy place for lunch, caught a movie after that, then we went home and spent the evening with my parents.

We sat down for dinner, and they did their usual interrogation of anyone I get close to, but a little more intense because of the fact we meet online. He seemed to be okay with it, and it was like he knew exactly what to say to make my parents happy. After they were satisfied, they gave us their blessing to carry on.
Dinner ended about 8, and Marc wanted to get home before it got any darker so he didn't have to deal with night traffic. We all told him goodnight and wished him a good trip home, then he took my hand and kissed it, and I just melted inside. My parents thought it was a bit odd because nobody really did that anymore, especially in the heart of Texas, but I didn't even care at this point, I was the happiest I'd been in a long time because my parents loved the guy almost as much as I did. We kept talking over time, with a newfound fire inside of us since we met, and I was convinced he was the one for me. 
In the middle of all this, I started getting sick, and I wasn't sure why. I discovered a small rash on my hand, and it just got bigger over time. Last week it started itching real bad, so I decided to just go to a doctor to ask what it was. He came back and asked if I'd been to any other countries lately, or been around any wild animals, and I told him I hadn't. 

The doctor told me that I had an illness from the rash, and he said it's spread by contact with animals that have eaten human flesh. I told him that was impossible, nothing had happened with animals, I'm allergic to dogs and cats so we never had pets, and the only thing that came close to that was when Marc kissed my hand.

Then I froze, and I realized what it all meant. I told the doctor my story, and he told me I should give the police his name just to check and make sure. He gave me a prescription to help get rid of the rash,
I called the Houston police and told them that what I thought, and they said they'd check him out.
The next night, I saw on the news that there was a police raid on a house in Houston, they had found human remains inside, with evidence that he had been eating them. All the remains belonged to 3 missing girls from the area, who had all been talking to him on various dating websites. The news showed a picture of Marc, and it disgusted me to see his face on that screen, it made me sick to my stomach knowing that I was almost his next meal.

Then they said three words that chilled me to the bone.

"Still at large"

He knows where I live. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> I didn't dream last night and I'm terrified </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-05-29 06:53:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Every night, for as long as I can remember, I've dreamed extremely vivid dreams.
I didn't realize anything odd for years, but about the time I was 9, I started having these crazy fits of deja vu. Every day it happened. Sometimes it was on the way to school, sometimes it was during class, sometimes it was just something someone said and the way they said it.

This went on for a couple years before I finally put together that the deja vu was coming from my dreams. Every dream I had was something that happened the next day. 
I don't know how, I don't know why, but it happened to me every night without fail. I never told anyone because I didn't want to be labeled a freak.

Over the years, I learned to somewhat "control" it. I started keeping a dream journal and writing my dreams down as best I could remember every morning, and when it happened in the day, I pulled out the book and wrote down the time. But it was never anything important, it was just random junk that happened.

And then we come to today. 
Last night, for the first time in my life, I didn't have a dream.

I didn't see my future.

And I'm terrified that that **was** my future. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-05-29 06:19:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thank you so much, I tried this and I made it to today. I can't thank you enough </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-05-27 19:39:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> No, today is just another birthday, but the first one I decided to post this. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-05-27 19:25:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Surprisingly, I haven't tried this yet, will do tonight. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-05-27 19:25:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Tried it, didn't do a thing. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-05-27 19:24:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I've been living it differently for months. There's only so much you can do differently in a day.

And I've tried killing myself over a dozen times, a dozen different ways. 
Every time my heart stops, I wake up. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-05-27 19:21:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hundreds. Before I lived a full life, I went through maybe 5 months of the same day.
Between the time I woke up and now, probably 2 more months. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> I don't want to wake up anymore </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-05-27 13:48:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> When I was a boy, I believed pretty much anything you threw at me. I believed in Santa, the tooth fairy, heck I even believed in monsters under the bed til I was into my late teens.
About 12-13, all the other kids tried to convince me it was all fake, but I couldn't let go of that truth I had had my entire life. Unfortunately this turned me into a freak in high school. Nobody wanted to be my friend, nobody wanted to even speak to me. They didn't believe.
Then came the first day of 12th grade, and I was nearly 18. So I decided that I wanted this year to be different, I wanted to make some friends for once, so I started to keep it all to myself, to make the others think I'd changed and believed in what they called normal.
Fortunately, it worked, and I started to make some friends. Not alot, but I had a good little "friend circle" thing going, and I really liked it. It was a nice change from the shyness and the fear of rejection I'd had the bigger part of my life.
So then came my 18th birthday. I've never been one for big spectacles, so I wanted a small party, family, a couple of my new friends, just spending a little time goofing off for once. That Saturday was the day my life changed.

It started off with me waking up. I went downstairs to get breakfast, and my parents greeted me with a hearty "Happy birthday!". I thanked them and ate my food, then went out to meet my friends, Matt, Hunter, and Christiana.
The day mainly consisted of me and my three best friends spending a day on the town, eating some pizza and ice cream, seeing a movie at the theater, and then afterwards we met back at my house for the actual party. That day had turned out to be the greatest day of my life, and I so wished I had done all this sooner. 
But then night came, and we got to my house to the party. It was just your standard birthday party, but probably more what you'd expect for a 12 year old than an 18 year old. Cake, candles, balloons, a couple presents, nothing special. 
When it finally came time to sit down and light the candles, it was as if something inside me opened up, and the rush of my childhood came back to me. Then my mom lit the candles, and my family and friends all sang "Happy Birthday" to me and I couldn't wipe this stupid grin off my face, because this had truly been a perfect day.
When the song ended and I heard my mom say "Make a wish and blow out your candles!", something inside me, all those old beliefs woke up, and I just really wanted to make a wish. 
So I wished with all my heart that this day could never end. 
The rest of the night went by pretty quickly after that, we ate cake, opened presents, played some games, then my friends went home. I walked them out where they said goodbye, then they thanked me for the good day, but then right as they were leaving, the only girl friend I had, Christiana, turned around and gave me a quick kiss on the lips and then just ran off to join the others on their walk home. 
I stood there in shock for a second, I didn't know what to do, nothing like this had ever happened before. As I stood there with that stupid look on my face, my mom called me back inside, so I snapped out of it and got on with my life. 
We cleaned up the mess, then I decided to just head to bed since I was exhausted from the day's events. I laid there with a dumb grin on my face, and I replayed what happened on my doorstep over and over again in my head until I finally fell asleep.

And then I woke up.

But it was different somehow, I didn't remember changing into my pajamas last night, and I didn't have any of my presents from before. Had my parents come and gotten them for some reason? 
I went downstairs to ask them if everything was alright, but when I got there, I was greeted by the same "happy birthday" I'd received yesterday. I told them that my birthday was yesterday, and they looked at me like I was insane. I went along with it, then I decided to go meet up with my friends to see if they were playing along with this too. 
I went to town to the place we met yesterday, and there they were, waiting for me as usual. I gave Christiana a quick smile, remembering what happened last night, but she just turned her head and shied away. I figured she was just embarrassed about the whole thing, so I decided to leave it alone. 
We all went and did the same stuff we did yesterday, and I had just as much fun as before. My friends, whatever game they were playing, had managed to make this day just as perfect as the day before. 
After all that, we went back to my house to finish up the day with the party, and everything was laid out the same as yesterday, so much as to confuse and slightly freak me out. 
Then came the cake. The candles. The song. 
Then my mom said those 8 words that haunt my memories to this day.
"Make a wish and blow out your candles!"

And at that second, I finally realized what was happening, I remembered the wish I made last night. That this day would never end.
I had believed that with all my heart, I knew that it would happen, but I forgot. But it was true. Magic, wishes, all of it. And I could make it happen again.
So I made my wish. "I wish that this day would last forever". Then I blew out the candles.
The rest of the night happened like last night, and then it was time to send off my friends for the night. And I remembered last time.
This time I told myself over and over that I was going to do it right and kiss her back, but when it finally happened and I stood on the porch and she kissed me, I freaked out, same as last time, and stood there with that stupid smile on my face. After that, I went inside and cleaned up, then went to sleep excited for the day to start again.

And then I woke up.

But today, I wanted to embrace the "groundhog day" of all this, and I decided to mess with my friends a bit. I decided to relive each day exactly the same, and I would memorize every little thing that happened, and then after a few days, I would be able to tell my friends the future, what they're thinking, all kinds of fun stuff.
So I did. And oddly enough, I could never get the nerve to kiss her back at the end of each day.

Unfortunately, this got old after a while. And since I've always been the angel of the family, I thought it was time to make a little change and be a little bit of a devil.
I started off with little things to see what I could get away with, and then I worked my way up to bigger things. More dangerous things.
After several weeks of this, I decided to buy a toy gun from the store, and try and rob a gas station. I got as far as the counter, then I pulled it out like an idiot and told him to give me the money, but what I didn't expect was for him to have a gun of his own. He pointed it at me and I just completely lost it. I threw the toy gun and ran out of the store and never looked back. 
On my run home, I had time to think, and I didn't want this anymore. It'd been going on for weeks, and I couldn't stand it never changing, never ending. I needed to make it stop.
I got home, ran through the motions, and made my wish.
But this time, I wished that I had never made that first wish, to take it all back and just move on with my life. I had ditched my friends when I decided to rob a store, so they weren't here tonight, so after the cake I just went to bed.

And then I woke up.

Nothing had changed.
The wish didn't work. The wish never mattered, I already made the first wish to make the day last forever.
I needed to find out how to stop this wish, to break this curse. I needed help.
I decided to tell my friends the truth, I could use my "psychic powers" to prove it to them when they didn't believe me. 
We met at the same spot we'd been meeting for the last months, and I told them. I told them everything, from the wish, to the kiss, all the way to the failed robbery.
They didn't believe me at first, but after I showed them that there was something to all this by telling them what was about to happen in the restaurant, they were a little more willing to listen.
I asked for their help, for ideas on how to fix all this. We came up with a few ideas, like changing something that happens that day, wishing this day wouldn't exist, wishing I had been born on a different day, and others.
We tried every single one of them, we spent 2 weeks trying out new ideas. Nothing worked, not even a little bit. But I finally had an idea, and I was going to try it on my own, without my friends' help this time.

I went through the day as normal, trying my very best to enjoy myself, but I just couldn't. Every minute ate me up inside, knowing I was doomed to relive this for the rest of my life. 
But I still had my final idea, so we went home at the end of the day, and it was finally time. 
They all sang "Happy Birthday", and I heard those horrible words for the thousandth time, "Make a wish and blow out your candles!".

"I wish that I could live the rest of my life outside this day".

Then I blew out the candles.
And I hoped and prayed that this would be the last today I'd ever see. 
I spent the rest of the day a little happier, with a skip in my step, hoping this would be the end of it.
Even to the point that at the end of the day when Christiana kissed me, I just pulled her close and kissed her with all that was in me.
This time she was the one with the dumb look on her face, but I just smiled and sent her on her way. "I'll see you tomorrow", I said as she left.
I went back inside, cleaned up as usual, and went to bed.
I went to sleep smiling that night, I had the amount of confidence in myself that I'd only had once before, when I made that first wish.

And then I woke up.

But this time, my room was exactly the same as I'd left it last night. 
I'd done it. I was free.
This horrible curse was finally broken.

I jumped up and ran downstairs to make sure it was true, where I found my parents passed out on the couch, not a "happy birthday" within ears' reach, and I almost screamed out loud with excitement.
I ran out and called my friends and told them to meet me at the usual spot in 10 minutes, and I went to go wait on them there. 
Christiana was the first to show up, and as soon as I saw her, I just ran up to her and hugged her, and we sat down to wait on Matt and Hunter. When they got there, I told them everything in hope they'd believe me, but they just said it was a dream and I had too much cake.
But I didn't mind.
It was over. 
I had my whole life ahead of me, so I'd better make it a good one.

Starting that night, Christiana and I started dating. And we built a new life together, better than I ever would've imagined while growing up, even believing in magic.
Everything was perfect, all the way up to the day I died.
I was 78 years old. I was in the hospital, they were trying to keep me alive, but my body was just ready to let go.
I spent my last moments with my children, my grandchildren, and my wife by my side.
I slipped away that night, October 24th, 2072.

And then I woke up.

Help me, please. I'm all out of ideas and I just want this to end. 
I don't want to wake up anymore.

EDIT: Wednesday, May 28th, 2014.
I made it.
I used the advice given by KAKiR in the comments, and wished that I would only live my life once more without starting over, and as far as I know, I'm still here. 
Sorry I got to you so late, I spent the entire day finally being able to do something new, and it was the most amazing day of my life.

I just hope this time I can die for good.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Don't open the cellar door. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-05-25 17:13:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> "Don't open the cellar door"
Those familiar words haunt my ears once more as my parents leave for work.
They said that to me every day they left me home alone, nearly every day for the past 19 years.
And in those 19 years, I've never opened it, for fear of what lie behind it, for surely it had to be something terrible for them to stress how much they wanted me to stay away.

Now don't get me wrong, I love my parents, and I believe they're only doing what's best for me. 
But sometimes, I get this incredible urge to open the cellar door. I just need to know what's on the other side, so I can put to rest all the terrible theories I've had bouncing in my head over the years. 

But no matter how much that curiosity grows inside the back of my mind, a fear deepens in the pit of my stomach, this overwhelming fear that my parents are not who they say they are, not the loving parents they've pretended to be these 19 years. 
What if they're horrible people? I couldn't live with myself knowing they're these horrible people, so I'd rather keep the truth as far away as possible than know it.

But today, everything was different. Why? 
Tomorrow was my birthday. 
20 years old. 2 decades I've been living in constant fear, 2 decades I've been the perfect angel my parents say I have to be, 2 decades hearing the faint echo of my mother's voice saying "Don't open the cellar door" rattle around in my head.

Today, I was going to open the door. I was done with fear, I was ready to finally prove that I was brave. I needed to prove it to myself, nobody else.
I needed to know.

I looked at that basement door for hours. Sometimes I sat, others I paced, sometimes I just stood there, face to face with this sinister door.
As I looked, I couldn't see anything wrong with it. It was just a plain wooden door. It had an old paint job that looked as if the faded red paint had been peeling for the past 40 years to reveal the brown wood underneath, with a little black knob on either side.

It was just an ordinary wooden door. It wasn't evil, it couldn't hurt me. It was just old wood.

And so I reached for the knob, with every fiber of my being screaming at me to stop, to go back and just leave it, that I'd be better off not knowing. 
But I needed to know what was so terrible, so evil that I couldn't ever open the cellar door.

I put my hand on the cold iron knob, and I slowly turned it. Before I pushed it open, I closed my eyes and thought one last time of just putting it down, going back to bed, and never touching the door again.

"I need to know!" I screamed at the door, as I rammed into it, exposing me to the great horror that lie behind it.

Except, there was no horror.

Just beauty.

At first, I didn't want to open my eyes. But even with my eyes closed, the light was blinding, and the heat on my skin was intense yet refreshing. 

I had to open my eyes. I had to see.

Slowly I opened my eyes, and the wave of light and color hit me like a brick wall. 

There was green everywhere, the floor was covered with this thick green carpet, and there were these tall brown poles everywhere with green all over them.
Then I looked up, and I saw the most amazing thing I'd ever seen. There was no ceiling, just this endless blue, with white patches everywere. And then off to the side, there was a bright yellow light, the brightest thing I'd ever seen in my life.

Everything was so beautiful, I don't understand why they were keeping it from me, or how they fit all this behind one old, worn out, wooden door.

But now I knew the truth. They weren't hiding any of the things I feared, they were still the same loving parents I've had my entire life, and I still love them with all my heart. And I'll still obey everything they say.

And I'll never open the cellar door again. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Everything's going to be alright. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-05-24 16:26:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I opened my eyes, same as I did every morning, and then as my eyes were adjusting to the light, I watched her beautiful face for a few minutes as she slept. 
There was always something wonderful about this moment, waking up to the one you love, the look on their face as they sleep. It's as if that's the only time where they can't hide who they truly are. But I've always found it oddly beautiful.

I watched Allison for a bit before it was time to get up and move on with my day, but I decided not to wake her this morning, she deserved a little sleep after everything we've been through. 
I went through my morning rituals, always sure to stay quiet enough to keep her from waking up, and then I headed to work.
I walked up the road to the little diner where I met my friends to eat breakfast, then carpool to work every morning. It's been nearly 8 months now since we started carpooling, I haven't driven since that night in September.

I was driving back from vacation with my wife, we'd decided to take a weekend up to Maine, where my uncle had a cabin he let us use when we wanted a getaway. We were almost back home to Louisville, but we were on some dirt highway in the middle of Ohio. It was around 8:30, and we were trying to decide whether we could outrun the sun, or just rest for the night.
But that night, we decided to keep going, even though it was getting darker by the second. I should've stopped when I saw the rain start to fall on the windshield, but I had these stupid instincts that make me think I can beat anyone, or anything, even time.

But not this time I didn't. 

The rain started turning the dirt road to mud, and I should've stopped right then and there, but I didn't.
I took a turn just a tiny bit too fast, and I never saw it until it was too late.
I saw the car ahead, stalled and abandoned, but by the time I saw it, we were already just inches away it seemed. I swerved as quick as I could, and at that moment, time just stood still. To this day I can still see everything as vividly as if it were laid out before me on the table.
The hood unlatching and smacking the windshield, the entire left side of the car lifting up 6 feet off the ground, the feeling of complete weightlessness as you fly through the air, and the indescribable terror of the inevitable.
Luckily, I had my seatbelt on, and that kept me from being flung out during the crash.
Unfortunately, Allison had forgotten to put it on.

I woke up God knows how long after it happened, the rain was seeping through the broken glass and onto me, but I somehow had the strength in me to get out of the car, and scream at the top of my lungs looking for her.

Looking back now, I still have no idea how I found her, but I did. She was probably 200 feet from where our car came to a stop, and I couldn't see her moving.
I ran to her, picked her up and held her in my arms with the rain pouring down on us, the moonlight was just enough for me to see the rain mixing with the blood on my arms, and the blood in her hair.
I held her close and kissed her, telling her everything's going to be alright, that I would get her home safely, and I did just that.

Our car was a mangled up mess, torn to shreds, and I still don't know how I got out of there alive. But with me being the mechanic of my family, I was able to get the abandoned car running just well enough to get us home.

We made it home about 30 minutes later, and I quickly brought her inside and got her head cleaned up and bandaged. I thought for sure I had lost her that night, but I promised her I'd get her back safe, and so I did. 

That was 8 months ago this week. She doesn't talk about it at all. In fact, she keeps pretty quiet all the time really, and she doesn't even get out of bed much.
It's just stress though, she's still in shock about it all. She'll be back to normal soon.

Her coworkers keep sending me flowers and cards about how they're "sorry for my loss", and my friends keep telling me they're sorry about Allison. But they don't understand that I never lost her, she's still right here by my side, always with me when I go to bed every night.
Even though she doesn't say it back anymore, I still love her, I always will, and I know she loves me too.

And so as another day rolls by, I get ready for bed, then I slip in next to her and give her a light kiss and a smile as I close my eyes.
"I love you, Allison. Everything's going to be alright." </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-05-23 17:39:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thank you, this is the first time I've written anything since a 6th grade book report, so I was a bit worried how well it would turn out.
But yeah, I'm glad it's all over too.

Glad you enjoyed it though! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-05-23 17:37:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Nah, I make it a point not to get involved with the devil. Too complicated. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-05-23 17:31:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> http://www.reddit.com/r/nosleep/comments/26aef7/steve/ </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Steve </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-05-23 12:45:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This is my story.
A story I've never told a single soul, not family, not even my closest friends. You're the first.

But it starts around the time I was 10-11.
A bit of history on me first, I was a very lonely child. I never had many friends, I just kept to myself and found ways to make use of my time. So as you may imagine, I had quite a few imaginary friends growing up. I mean, it's just something you do when you're a kid.
So among these friends, I had some animals, some people, just someone, or really anyone that I could talk to. 

But there was one in particular, one... /thing/ that stands out among all my friends. He's the reason for this story. 
I called him Steve, although he never gave me his name. But since he never protested Steve, I guess it stuck.

He was tall and very thin, only about 6 feet tall now that I think about it, but he seemed so much taller when I was just a boy. He was quite pale, and his eyes were dark and sunk into his head, like someone who was in their final stages of a terminal illness. He always wore the same clothes though, it was this dark trench coat looking thing, with a black suit underneath.
One thing that I remember most, although I didn't think about it when I was younger, was that he never spoke, or even so much as opened his mouth. 

His mouth.

That's another thing about him.

Although he never opened his mouth, I never really wanted him to. There was something about it that frightened me, just an odd shape about it.
You know how if you take something familiar that you see all the time, and you change it ever so slightly to the point that it becomes something unfamiliar, and even disturbing?

It was like that. It seemed to be just a tiny bit longer than a normal mouth, and it was always in a twisted sort of smile, almost as if he were mocking you.
And he never opened it, but I just knew there was something terrible behind those pale, twisted lips. Maybe some huge, terrible teeth, like those alien-looking fish you see on those nature shows about the deep ocean.

Whatever lie behind those lips, I knew I never wanted to see it.

But moving on, there's another thing about me you should know.
About the age of 11, my family life started to fall apart. My parents were always fighting, my siblings were always picking on me, and I was bullied at school with no end in sight.
Eventually it became too much, and one day I just couldn't handle it anymore. 

So I hurt myself.

I took a razor blade I found in my mom's medicine cabinet, and I just ran it across my arm and watched it bleed. 

It felt good. 

To this day, I'll never understand how it felt good, but it did. The quick, sharp pain in my arm just drowned out all the other pain in my life, at least for a while.

But if I had known what it would do to me, I never would've done it.
It became something I needed, something my body craved. It hurt me even worse if I DIDN'T cut myself. I couldn't stop, and eventually I had to wear long sleeves to school so that people didn't see.

But the first time I did it, the first time I looked at myself in the mirror after releasing all that pain, that was the first time I saw him. 

He just stood in the doorway and smiled at me, while glancing at the fresh blood dripping down my arm
.
Perhaps that's why he became my best friend, because he was there the time I needed someone the most, but nobody came. 

Except for him. 

He was there, every time I needed someone, every time I cut my arm or my leg, he was always there, smiling at me, looking at my freshest cut with a strange bewilderment in his eyes. 
Sometimes I would accidentally go a little deeper, and he would smile extra big, and sometimes even give me a quick thumbs up, as if he knew how much pleasure the pain brought, and wanted to encourage me.

After about a year or so of this, I started seeing him other places too. At school, in the store, even in passing cars when we would drive down the road. But he wasn't looking at me, he would look at other people, just stare at them. He only seemed to look at me when I hurt myself.

You may find this childish, but I got very jealous of that simple truth. And I would even hurt myself more often, and worse, just so I could get him to look at me more often when nobody else would. And as it went on, I noticed he had a different look in his eyes as he watched me. Almost as if he were beckoning me to come with him, to be with him, wherever he was from. 
It was the same look a father gives his son when it's time to go home after a long day on the playground, but at the same time, it was the same look a father gives his son when he's just gotten in trouble and it's time to come home without question.

Then after a few years of this, around age 15, I made the biggest mistake of my life.

I attempted to kill myself.

I had no idea what I was doing, even made a few google searches just to figure out how I would do it, but I decided I couldn't take life anymore, seeing as my parents had now divorced, my mom hardly even noticed me unless I got in trouble, and the siblings that stayed with me and mom all hated my guts.

It seemed like Steve was the only person who cared, who wanted me as I was. 

So I decided I would go home with him.

I decided to fashion a noose out of some rope I had in my closet, and I hung it from my ceiling fan. 
After saying prayer upon prayer, and crying every drop of moisture I had in my body, I finally decided I was ready.
I slowly slipped the noose around my neck, and I saw him standing there. I looked straight into his dark, sunken eyes, and then I just let my body fall upon the rope.

It wasn't anything like I had expected, it was literally the worst agony I'd ever experienced. I couldn't breathe, I couldn't scream, I couldn't think, I just kept getting dizzier and dizzier, and it was all total confusion for those few seconds which felt like hours in themselves. 

But a few seconds in, I noticed that Steve was walking closer to me. 

I had never realized it before this moment, but he never walked, or even moved anything more than his eyes when I saw him. He just kind of appeared when I needed him.

But this time, he walked toward me.

And as I looked at his face for what I thought would be the final time, it was different.
He was /laughing/ at me. 

My only friend in the world, the one person I could always depend on, and he was feeding off all my pain, everything important in my life, and making a mockery of it.
He had wanted this all along, he had tricked me. And too late I finally saw where I had gone wrong in accepting his simple gesture of "love", his smile which I mistook for kindness, that turned out to be nothing but a malicious ploy for my very soul.

And as he laughed and looked me in the eye, I saw his mouth open for the first, last, and only time. 

There was nothing.
No teeth, no tongue, no black, no white, just absolute nothingness. 
In that instant, I knew that I had just caught a glimpse of my impending doom. 

I had made my foolish choice.

I tried to look away, I tried to close my eyes, but his gaze held me in a viselike grip, unable to look away until he was mere inches from my face, his sneer slowly twisting into a fiendish laugh that sounded as if it was coming from the fiery pits of hell itself.

And that brief moment, that one second was all it took.
I now knew that I was face to face with Death, the devil himself, my "friend".

So with my last breath, I closed my eyes and grabbed the rope, and I pulled down with all my might, hoping I could break the fan and free myself from his deathly gaze.
I opened my eyes as I heard the snap of splintering wood as the fan broke, the rope fell, and suddenly all clarity rushed back into my head, and Steve was gone.

For good.

I never saw Steve again, and that was nearly 10 years ago now. 
I never cut myself or attempted to kill myself again, for fear that I would look up and see HIM. 
His icy cold stare, his suit as black as the moonless night, his dastardly sneer, and the nothing that lie behind it.

I buried this memory in the deepest recesses of my mind, hoping it was all just a dream, my imagination.
But today I saw something that changed how I saw the incident. 

I was browsing the internet, and I came across a post made by someone talking about their imaginary friends, and one of them I had realized bore a striking resemblance to Steve. Upon closer investigation, the person had an eerily similar experience with Steve.
It was at that moment, when the icy chills ran up and down my spine, that I realized that Steve was not my imaginary friend at all. 

He was certainly not my friend, I had known that for years now, but now I knew that he was, beyond a shadow of a doubt, NOT imaginary.

And so I write this as a warning, if you see Steve, whatever his name may be, in his black suit and coat, his pale skin, dark eyes, and that horrifically twisted smile, you need to stop what you're doing to draw him in, stop bringing pain upon yourself, and don't let him get any closer to you.

Or else you could fail where I succeeded, you may end up in his prison of emptiness. 

You may be what lies behind his smile.
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-04-23 01:56:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> How did you choose people to be in your local commercials? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
