<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject886</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-23 20:19:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So you're voting for Stein? As I pointed out in the preface to my question, there is no evidence that your vote will help Stein in any way, shape, or form. On the contrary, there is pletny of evidence that a vote for Stein will undermine the progressive cause for at least 50 years by letting a conservative xenophobic nut-job name up to three Supreme Court justices.

And btw, in case you want a quick history lesson: the Supreme Court is primarily the cause of why we still have large pieces of FDR's New Deal and LBJ's Great Society, those having nothing to do with a protest vote or any kind of vote for a third party. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-23 19:17:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's not "shitting on people" to bring up facts, nor do facts mean "tearing someone down," unless you watch Fox News or are a Tea Partier. Leave the mythologizing to them - as the left-of-center, we should be better than that.

Also, I would say voting for someone who you know is certain to lose is "not productive".

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-22 21:57:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Bush was elected for two terms even though he killed millions of Americans in his Iraq War [not to mention the deaths in his war in Afghanistan], and he put two Justices on the Supreme Court, both of which are shifting the highest court in the land right.

Where was this progressive left movement then? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-22 21:48:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Trump has successfully incited violence many times against [immigrants](http://www.reuters.com/article/us-usa-mexico-beating-idUSKCN0Y805K), [religious minorities](http://bridge.georgetown.edu/when-islamophobia-turns-violent-the-2016-u-s-presidential-elections/) [mostly Muslim], ethnic minorities, and LGBTQ+ Americans [and he demonstrably doesn't care about LGBTQ+ rights](https://www.splcenter.org/hatewatch/2016/06/22/trump-evangelical-board-stacked-anti-lgbt-activists), [his platform also actively opposes equality for the LGBTQ+ community](http://www.hrc.org/2016RepublicanFacts/donald-trump-opposes-nationwide-marriage-equality). [Hate crimes are rising precipitously](http://www.theatlantic.com/politics/archive/2015/08/a-trump-inspired-hate-crime-in-boston/401906/), and all of those perpetrators were self-described Trump fans. Saying your friends are not scared neither diminishes this reality nor does it mean my family will be safe from more anti-immigrant prejudice or even violence even more so than they already have. 

Electing a President teaches future generations what values are acceptable in this country. Electing anyone but Trump means the values he spews will never be legitimated by the seal of the President of the United States. I take it as a given that Hillary Clinton - whether I or my friends like her or not - will at the very least not legitimate the hate culture Trump has demonstrably inspired. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-22 21:25:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> And do you remember that she keeps repeating that she'd expand immigration reform, expand pro-immigration policies, and that as a Democrat, she's more likely to be pressured from her left-progressive flank to be pass more progressive legislation than if Trump were president?

Do you honestly think progressive left priorities have more of a chance under Trump than Clinton? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-22 21:19:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Did you even read the rest of my reply in which I describe more than half of my family of having very unstable, very precarious immigration stauses? Did you read the part where I have children in my family whose parents would be deported under a Trump presidency? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-22 21:14:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If Jill Stein doesn't win, Trump wins. How does this put pressure on Clinton from the left?

Are you thinking a progressive movement has more of a chance to be emboldened and mobilized more effectively under a Trump presidency than a Clinton presidency in time for the 2020 presidential election?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-22 20:53:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Not until you answer my question whether if I vote for Jill Stein, I could still deny Trump the presidency and not let him win. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-22 20:38:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So would you risk Trump winning? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-22 20:36:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Politics and elections are about protecting people I love. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-22 20:29:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I am a white heterosexual, cis first-generation American (first-gen on one side) with many immigrants in my family with ambiguous and very precarious documentation status. 

That includes children whose parents are at risk of being deported to a third-world, vastly underdeveloped country, where they cannot hope to have the same educational or career opportunities, and anywhere near the same standard of living of someone in a developed country.

All of them are scared shitless of a Trump presidency.

Before you ask, I will not specify which country or the nature of my family members' precarious immigration status. I think you can figure the rest out.
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-22 20:15:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Considering her past electoral history, do you think she can?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-22 20:10:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm asking you to explain the point. I would be interested in a non-hostile answer. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-22 18:57:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So, you're going to vote Jill Stein? After she lost her MA governor race - she came in third at 3.5% -, lost her 2004 State Senate run  for MA's 9th Middlesex District ( 59.6%-21.3%), lost the race for MA's Secretary of the Commonwealth after being nominated (she got 18% of the vote), and lost her second [2010] MA governor race with 1.4% of the vote?

The only official office she EVER won was Town Meeting Representative, in 2005 and 2008. And you think she can be President?

Throughout all of her runs - and still now - MA is reliably blue, meaning that MA would have been much easier for Jill Stein to win than an entire country where close to half of the voting population is Republican.

Now, the question is this: Do you actually care who our next President is? Do you care who is elected? And are you willing to gamble with your country's future?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-22 18:05:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> As the article says, 1969. That was the end of the Warren Court. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-22 18:04:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Why "Facepalm"? The SUpreme COurt - whether you think so or not, is a fact of life in the United States. It is the highest court in the land. Without it, we would not have had much of FDR's New Deal state, nor preserved it, we wouldn't have had LBJ's Great Society.

Bringing up the Supreme Court in the election season simply means bringing up one of the most consequential institutions that can shape our lives and this country for at least 50 years. 

But then again, if you're a white heterosexual non-immigrant, I guess you'll be fine. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-17 02:02:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You might find [German Ordoliberalism](http://bruegel.org/2014/08/blogs-review-ordoliberalism-and-germanys-approach-to-the-euro-crisis/) very interesting. Here's [another link](https://sweettalkconversation.com/2015/01/01/ordoliberalism-and-the-myth-of-laissez-faire/), and here's [another link directly addressing issues Stiglitz brings up](https://sweettalkconversation.com/2015/01/01/ordoliberalism-and-the-myth-of-laissez-faire/).

[Does Liberty Need Rules? The Link Between German Ordoliberalism And F.A. Hayek](https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=dChh1-t7r94) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-09 02:09:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Trump's spokesperson admits that he can be personally repugnant in his relations to women, but she still somehow thinks he's a cool dude </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-05 19:50:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> ***Exactly*** </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-04 23:21:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I agree with you on many different levels, but electing Trump and having him as President would legitimize the fear, hate, and xenophobia he ran on for millions of Americans </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-03 19:57:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> 1) ***You*** brought up Chomsky to attack Clinton. So ***you*** made that relevant. 

2) President Obama has demonstrably made every effort to keep many of his promises. And he [did](http://www.vox.com/2015/6/26/8849925/obama-obamacare-history-presidents) where he [could](http://www.politico.com/magazine/story/2016/01/obama-biggest-achievements-213487?paginate=false). It is also fact that he's scaled-back our military in the Middle East to the lowest levels since that start of the Iraq War [***that was under Bush btw***], and by all accounts, he has been [relentlessly pursuing that policy where he can](http://www.theatlantic.com/magazine/archive/2016/04/the-obama-doctrine/471525/)

3) Assuming that you are a progressive or identify as an activist on the left-wing of the political spectrum, I find it utterly laughable that you don't know how our own government takes action. Our presidential democracy was not set up as a monarchy or a dictatorship - Presidents need to be constantly pushed and held accountable - yet it is ***fact*** that for the last several decades, we have seen a pitiful decline in voter turnout all across the American political spectrum. And a lot of that decline is coming from the segment of voters who happen to be the most anti-war and pro-peace. While turnout among these voters declined, we see a consequent upsurge of support for right-wing pro-war congressional candidates and politicians all across this country, including in the Republican takeover of Congress in 2010. Do you think President Obama - as President of the USA not just of the progressive antiwar left - could have somehow ignored the people ***who actually vote*** and magically divine the wishes and desires of the silent antiwar left who apparently doesn't care enough about voting out pro-war Republicans just because they feel that their government betrayed them on student loans?! Tell me again who puts America first and screw the rest?
 
It's funny how you accuse those who support President Obama of not caring about any non-American life. Yet - and I'm assuming you are among those who supported Sanders - only ***one*** of the Democratic candidates ***constantly*** spoke out against immigration and free trade deals in the most [appallingly nativist](http://www.vox.com/2016/3/1/11139718/bernie-sanders-trade-global-poverty) and [sectarian](https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=vf-k6qOfXz0) ways, even to the point of [embracing the insidious xenophobia of Lou Dobbs on Fox News](https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=38M9vfg4TPE).

And you call **us** lazy? You didn't even bother to think about what Sanders ***himself*** was saying as to why he always offered blatantly nativist comments regarding his stances on immigration and free trade.

Go ahead, prove me wrong. Actually look at the links I put here. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-02 15:17:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Good thing 2016 ***Hillary*** Clinton isn't 1994 ***Bill*** Clinton. 

Stop judging Hillary based on the actions of Bill's administration. That is disgustingly sexist. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-02 14:45:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Trump is clearly the worst choice for the second- and third-world. And by the way, he said he'd ***deliberately target*** terrorist's families. Repeat and thoughtless caricature you want about President Obama or Clinton, but they do not ***target*** families and innocent people.

[And Chomsky has said in no uncertain terms that he would vote for Clinton in a swing state](https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=3qFWGE1oDoA)

And as a progressive, I am deeply offended by your comment that progressives only care about "first-world problems". That is a ***disgusting generalization*** and very sloppy [and intellectually-lazy] statement, and I hope you know better than to actually think that's true. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-02 01:24:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Trump has stated that the whole regions he doesn't encourage Putin to colonize, he will bomb and attack. Trump is the only candidate of the two major ones who said he'd kill the families of suspected terrorists. It is very apparent that not only does Trump not care about human life - but he also takes active pleasure in destroying it (i.e., he has repeated several times now "I like firing people.") </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-02 01:18:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So I'm assuming that by replying to this post with these links, you're implying that since other black people are Bernie Or Bust, it's ok to ignore or dismiss this guy?

How is that ***not*** effectively saying "All black Bernie supporters are alike and any exception is an anomaly"? 

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-30 05:09:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm willing to "put a pin in it," but the DNC emails were between private staffers (I assume you're referring to the recent ones). Are you trying to say individual people who express their own personal irritation constitute a conspiracy? It's well known that both camps did things the other did not like, and I don't particularly think Bernie Sanders' team looking at Hillary's voter lists when they shouldn't have been particularly endeared him to the people at the DNC, so it's not very surprising that some DNC people who like rules got pissed off. Both sides could have run better campaigns, but please don't blame Hillary for everything because that'd simply be misguided.

And anyway, that is immaterial to the question of allowing a racist sociopath shape how the country's laws are implemented for the next 50+ years.

So, yes, I can put a "pin in it," but that would take both of us. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-26 19:29:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Nope. Sorry. Your comment is bordering on slander. I'd appreciate it if you stop. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-18 16:42:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Tom Perez would be an amazing pick.

He's not only super-qualified, but can kneecap Trump on his 'whites-only' "law and order" image. Perez going down to Florida to meet with Trayvon Martin's family when he headed DOJ's investigation, getting a police chief fired for failing his duties, would be a powerful story when anxieties over police brutality and extrajudicial vigilantism are still fresh.

On top of bringing down Joe Arpaio under [Bill] Clinton's Crime Bill and the CRA, and then fighting Voter ID in SC and Texas?
That would be the end of Trump.

And it would be a hugely important symbolic victory to retake "law and order" from a blandly white ticket headed by a [suspected] racist.

A Perez pick would not only cement the bridge between Obama and the ticket and the future admin, but can remind everyone that being tough on law and order issues can also mean being pro-labor and pro-civil rights, and being strongly for immigration. Would be a an incredibly important story to tell.

Picking him would also have the added bonus of tying gun violence to issues of racial justice and police brutality.

And it would be a stunningly powerful image to see Tom Perez and Sybrina Fulton (mother of Trayvon Martin) on the stage together at the DNC. Would send us all a very important wake up call to carry into future generations. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-18 16:42:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Tom Perez would be an amazing pick.

He's not only super-qualified, but can kneecap Trump on his 'whites-only' "law and order" image. Perez going down to Florida to meet with Trayvon Martin's family when he headed DOJ's investigation, getting a police chief fired for failing his duties, would be a powerful story when anxieties over police brutality and extrajudicial vigilantism are still fresh.

On top of bringing down Joe Arpaio under [Bill] Clinton's Crime Bill and the CRA, and then fighting Voter ID in SC and Texas?
That would be the end of Trump.

And it would be a hugely important symbolic victory to retake "law and order" from a blandly white ticket headed by a [suspected] racist.

A Perez pick would not only cement the bridge between Obama and the ticket and the future admin, but can remind everyone that being tough on law and order issues can also mean being pro-labor and pro-civil rights, and being strongly for immigration. Would be a an incredibly important story to tell.

Picking him would also have the added bonus of tying gun violence to issues of racial justice and police brutality.

And it would be a stunningly powerful image to see Tom Perez and Sybrina Fulton (mother of Trayvon Martin) on the stage together at the DNC. Would send us all a very important wake up call to carry into future generations. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-18 16:41:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Tom Perez would be an amazing pick.

He's not only super-qualified, but can kneecap Trump on his 'whites-only' "law and order" image. Perez going down to Florida to meet with Trayvon Martin's family when he headed DOJ's investigation, getting a police chief fired for failing his duties, would be a powerful story when anxieties over police brutality and extrajudicial vigilantism are still fresh.

On top of bringing down Joe Arpaio under [Bill] Clinton's Crime Bill and the CRA, and then fighting Voter ID in SC and Texas?
That would be the end of Trump.

And it would be a hugely important symbolic victory to retake "law and order" from a blandly white ticket headed by a [suspected] racist.

A Perez pick would not only cement the bridge between Obama and the ticket and the future admin, but can remind everyone that being tough on law and order issues can also mean being pro-labor and pro-civil rights, and being strongly for immigration. Would be a an incredibly important story to tell.

Picking him would also have the added bonus of tying gun violence to issues of racial justice and police brutality.

And it would be a stunningly powerful image to see Tom Perez and Sybrina Fulton (mother of Trayvon Martin) on the stage together at the DNC. Would send us all a very important wake up call to carry into future generations. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-18 16:41:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Tom Perez would be an amazing pick.

He's not only super-qualified, but can kneecap Trump on his 'whites-only' "law and order" image. Perez going down to Florida to meet with Trayvon Martin's family when he headed DOJ's investigation, getting a police chief fired for failing his duties, would be a powerful story when anxieties over police brutality and extrajudicial vigilantism are still fresh.

On top of bringing down Joe Arpaio under [Bill] Clinton's Crime Bill and the CRA, and then fighting Voter ID in SC and Texas?
That would be the end of Trump.

And it would be a hugely important symbolic victory to retake "law and order" from a blandly white ticket headed by a [suspected] racist.

A Perez pick would not only cement the bridge between Obama and the ticket and the future admin, but can remind everyone that being tough on law and order issues can also mean being pro-labor and pro-civil rights, and being strongly for immigration. Would be a an incredibly important story to tell.

Picking him would also have the added bonus of tying gun violence to issues of racial justice and police brutality.

And it would be a stunningly powerful image to see Tom Perez and Sybrina Fulton (mother of Trayvon Martin) on the stage together at the DNC. Would send us all a very important wake up call to carry into future generations. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-18 16:41:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Tom Perez would be an amazing pick.

He's not only super-qualified, but can kneecap Trump on his 'whites-only' "law and order" image. Perez going down to Florida to meet with Trayvon Martin's family when he headed DOJ's investigation, getting a police chief fired for failing his duties, would be a powerful story when anxieties over police brutality and extrajudicial vigilantism are still fresh.

On top of bringing down Joe Arpaio under [Bill] Clinton's Crime Bill and the CRA, and then fighting Voter ID in SC and Texas?
That would be the end of Trump.

And it would be a hugely important symbolic victory to retake "law and order" from a blandly white ticket headed by a [suspected] racist.

A Perez pick would not only cement the bridge between Obama and the ticket and the future admin, but can remind everyone that being tough on law and order issues can also mean being pro-labor and pro-civil rights, and being strongly for immigration. Would be a an incredibly important story to tell.

Picking him would also have the added bonus of tying gun violence to issues of racial justice and police brutality.

And it would be a stunningly powerful image to see Tom Perez and Sybrina Fulton (mother of Trayvon Martin) on the stage together at the DNC. Would send us all a very important wake up call to carry into future generations. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-18 15:38:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Tom Perez would be an amazing pick.

He's not only super-qualified, but can kneecap Trump on his 'whites-only' "law and order" image. Perez going down to Florida to meet with Trayvon Martin's family when he headed DOJ's investigation, getting a police chief fired for failing his duties, would be a powerful story when anxieties over police brutality are still fresh.

On top of bringing down Joe Arpaio under [Bill] Clinton's Crime Bill and the CRA, and then fighting Voter ID in SC and Texas? 

That would be the end of Trump. 


And it would be a hugely important symbolic victory to retake "law and order" from a blandly white ticket headed by a [suspected] racist.

A Perez pick would not only cement the bridge between Obama and the ticket and the future admin, but can remind everyone that being tough on law and order issues can also mean being pro-labor and pro-civil rights, and being strongly for immigration. Would be a an incredibly important story to tell.

Picking him would also have the added bonus of tying gun violence to issues of racial justice and police brutality.

And it would be a stunningly powerful image to see Tom Perez and Sybrina Fulton (mother of Trayvon Martin) on the stage together at the DNC. Would send us all a very important wake up call to carry into future generations.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-08 08:04:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hillary would beat him in a debate hands down. She's sharp as a nail. Look at any of her interviews, speeches, debates, etc.

Certainly next to Clinton, he's just smoke and mirrors. A showman beat him, don't forget. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-07 23:40:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I don't believe it is. I just thought that the idea of fulfillment can be useful in framing the urgency to rethink how society compensates creativity, and how it might be self-defeatist to confine creativity's value to ideas of the profit motive as opposed to fulfillment.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-07 02:55:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Because it took so long. This means white college students owerwhelmingly voted Republican up to and through G.W. Bush. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-06 06:35:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I will be waiting to see which lower-income or below-poverty POC community she moves to. She'd probably change her tune really fast living in a lower-income minority-majority community by the end of Trump's firs term.

Honestly, this kind of statement is ridiculously irresponsible - and I say this because 

***A)*** She knows she would rather not be a POC in a minority-majority lower-income neighborhood for four years under Trump, let alone eight, 

***B)*** She grew up in a household more affluent than the average American [even likely adjusting for inflation over time), 

***C)*** She was able to afford to go to Harvard - a place less likely than a lower-income city college to be patrolled and harassed by Trump-approved police-state tactics or affected by violent rallies.

***D)*** She pulled in a physician's income that was probably higher than most Americans for most of her adult life.

There's just ***so*** much wrong with this statement. I am stunned by the intellectual laziness it represents. Maybe she knows better though, which makes it infinitely worse.

I'm just embarrassed I ever thought that she was ***"the serious one"*** in this election. Historically-insensitive and careless statements like this made me defect big-time to Hillary [just putting all my cards on the table lest I'm called biased]. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-05 06:29:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> To go off on the last part of your comment, I find it startlingly unsettling that Bernie Or Bust people said they'd defect to Bush if Hillary is the nominee [I guess they still contest that...].

I don't think the link is on their YouTube page, but the Daily Show's Jessica Williams did her last interview with those Bernie or Bust supporters. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-05 01:48:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This is from March, but its analysis is still deeply urgent </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-05 01:40:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Actually, I've been quite consistent in this thread regarding the principles of anarcho-capitalism. That doesn't seem to support your idea that I "shift[ed] the conversation". 

And I did not argue that you shouldn't post here - I merely stated that you may have mistaken this subreddit for something else. 

Now, I'm under the impression that you might just be mistaking trollish personal attacks with political debate or civil conversation. Notice how I didn't attack you nearly as frequently or as viciously as you attacked me? That's because I believe in free, open conversation - and free and open conversation shouldn't involve any sort of bullying.

Now, if you don't believe in civil conversation, I have to conclude that you don't believe in engaging anyone on the basis of self-awareness or intellectual humility and an openness to others' differing views.

In which case, I will not be interested in continuing any conversation with you.

That's not any form of dishonest "shift" or underhanded manipulative ploy - that's just a sign that I'm interested in mature, more substantive, and less shrill political conversations. 

For future reference, personal attacks don't equal fully-formed political opinion.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-05 01:23:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If you're not an anarcho-capitalist, you must have mistaken this subreddit for something else. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-05 01:14:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> How do you know what I care about and what I don't? 

Pretty paternalistic and authoritarian assumption for an anarcho-capitalist, hmm? What ever happened to the free exchange of information or ideas, or opinions in a competitive market? 

Or do you believe that your opinions should have special rent-controlled, monopolistic status? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-05 01:04:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [He co-sponsored in an amendment to an immigration reform bill](https://www.congress.gov/amendment/109th-congress/house-amendment/971) that protected the anti-immigrant Minuteman militia from any form of accountability, such as delivering Miranda rights or any other form of due process.

He has [consistently spoken out against the anarcho-capitalist ideas of open borders](https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=vf-k6qOfXz0)

People in this country - especially on the self-identified "Progressive Left" - forget that the example of a "political revolution" they hold so dear - essentially [was made possible only through an ethnic statist compromise](http://www.historyandpolicy.org/policy-papers/papers/when-affirmative-action-was-white}. FDR still had out-and-out xenophobes in his party leftover from past electoral realignments, and he couldn't pass most if not all of his central New Deal programs without them. So, he had to make concessions to the cultural populists on ***both*** sides of the aisle [after he realized he was politically-outnumbered](http://www.wsj.com/articles/SB10001424052748704631504575532371905049074). 

One supporter of Bernie or Bust also gave me the example of LBJ''s Great Society as an example of a successful political revolution. Unfortunately, such a claim reveals historical ignorance as well [assuming that Bernie's supporters do not want ethnic statism]. One of LBJ's closest aides wrote a memoir reflecting on the administration's [failure to upend entrenched ethnic statism in his own party](http://sites.middlebury.edu/presidentialpower/tag/harry-mcpherson/). In his book on post-Civil Rights regulatory agencies, Hanes Walton [documents how these agencies enforcement and compliance capabilities were utterly laughable](http://www.sunypress.edu/p-893-when-the-marching-stopped.aspx). 

Walton doesn't go on to make these speculations, but I believe this effectively buffered the institutionalized ethnic statism of the Democratic Party - and I think this very same ethnic statism leads to the predominantly white supporters of Bernie Or Bust throwing temper tantrums that the economy is "rigged" against them, while an increasing amount of [polls] (https://fivethirtyeight.com/features/for-blacks-and-hispanics-the-economic-glass-is-still-half-full/) show a [more positive economic outlook among communities of color](http://www.pewhispanic.org/2016/06/08/latinos-increasingly-confident-in-personal-finances-see-better-economic-times-ahead/) as we come out of the last recession.

I don't believe this is an historical coincidence. I believe Bernie Sanders was able to tap into the anxieties and resentments of white kids who see that their white parents were able to benefit from an [unidentified] white statism, while POC communities who are unfortunately on aggregate used to getting a smaller piece of the economic pie are "more optimistic" because they are seeing that their kids and grand-kids have more opportunities too rise up the economic ladder than they did, and these younger generations in POC communities are told this through family stories or shown this by the wealth or income gaps between them and their parent and grandparents.

Bernie's supporters are used to benefiting from the racialized economic rents of the New Deal, or at least used to seeing their parents and grandparents benefit from these institutionalized rents.

So, in summation, both Bernie and his supporters remember a closed-border white statist utopia where they didn't have to compete on the free/open market with as many skilled immigrants, and getting back to that is their idea of revolution. 

Even if they don't identify the goal as ethnic statism, it is. They just might not recognize that that is what they want, but that doesn't change the fact that Bernie's appeal is based on statist disenfranchisement.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-05 00:03:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Does the fact that I support Hillary make historical lessons disappear?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-04 18:39:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The Republicans are trying to make this election a referendum on immigration an globalization, painting the Democrats as extreme in "pro-trade globalists" who are "pro-amnesty".

And with his short-sightedness, Bernie made it easier for the Republicans to use his own words against ***any*** Democratic pro-immigration platform.

That's some team spirit right there, eh?
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-04 18:25:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The Republicans are trying to make this election a referendum on immigration an globalization, painting the Democrats as extreme in "pro-trade globalists" who are "pro-amnesty".

And with his short-sightedness, Bernie made it easier for the Republicans to use his own words against ***any*** Democratic pro-immigration platform.

That's some team spirit right there, eh?
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-04 18:16:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  German ideology within the EU is internal devaluation and austerity position which has had the effect of being pro cyclical. Though that did not stop them from deception to meet Eurozone convergence criteria in the 90's.
 From a draft of Bill Mitchell's EU dysopia book (probably best to get the book as it will either give you all the answers for the paper or rich sources of information to pursue): http://bilbo.economicoutlook.net/blog/?p=27968
 Here is a blog post exploring the 'deficit hawk' vs 'deficit dove' approach to budgets which would be important when discussing the magnitude of a pro/counter cyclical policy: http://bilbo.economicoutlook.net/blog/?p=22542
 Mitchell wrote about the EU automatic stabilizers were not enough to be an effective tool for proper counter cyclical policy to be effective. In short budgets had to spend more. http://bilbo.economicoutlook.net/blog/?p=27406 "Alexander Italianer and Jean Pisani-Ferry (1992) claimed that the new EMU would not need a large federal budget because sufficient stabilisation (via automatic stabilisers) would be forthcoming at the national level." http://bilbo.economicoutlook.net/blog/?p=27418
 The price stability German ideology is derived in part from their fear of the hyperinflation in the weimar republic years. http://bilbo.economicoutlook.net/blog/?p=27974
 Also look at Robert Barro's theory to understand why German policy makers would see austerity as anti-cyclical in some way. http://bilbo.economicoutlook.net/blog/?p=8252

Thank you so much for all these links and your response - all of this will be very, very helpful. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-04 18:12:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> And the media wondered why ***she*** never attacked ***him***: Because you ***always*** have to assume there's a chance that the other person will be nominated and have to face off the Republican in the general. 

Just ask yourself if Hillary said anything that can be used in an attack ad against him. No? 

Wonder why? Maybe team spirit? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-04 09:32:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So tell me how you'd like to be identified, and I'll do the exact opposite or simply ignore you and call you whatever I want. Is that fair to you? 

I assume that your identity is important to you. For example, if you are a straight male, I think it's safe to assume you'd get tired pretty quickly of constantly being referred to as a female or in feminine terms. Or if you are proud to be an American, I don't think you'd take too kindly to constantly being referred to as something not American or even being called un-American. 

If you want people to respect how you identify yourself, respect others' right to do that for themselves too.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-04 08:57:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> July 4th is a political event. It's when we declared our political and military victory over the British.

Also, if you somehow haven't noticed, LGBTQ+ equality is still threatened by many politicians. Hence, this article is political on both counts.

Was that honestly an innocent/earnest question? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-04 08:30:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You clearly cannot imagine the power of trolls getting into power based on racism and xenophobia. And if you think it's all an act - like many people do - just wait until he's pressured by his followers to use state power to promote ethnic statism. And by the way, if you're a libertarian, you won't [**or at least shouldn't**] like that too much.

I agree Trump's a clown. But as with all clowns who want to keep a crowd, he wont be ditching his act any time soon.

You may feel comfortable gambling with your own life, and maybe even gambling with your family's and friend's, but don't try to clothe your trollish "protest" vote in the guise of an enlightened patriotism or in the garb of any libertarian ideal. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-04 07:37:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I don't know what "imo" means.

I'm of course of the opinion that this can raise important issues. Particularly with the speculation going around now that Corbyn didn't really give the "Remain" campaign his best effort because of his euroscepticism, I believe it's important for people to realize that calling oneself a progressive champion of labor does not automatically mean that they are pro-immigration. 

Oftentimes, people unfortunately conflate the economic left with a cultural left, and assume that an "enlightened" economic leftist is "enlightened" when it comes to issues of culture, immigration, or cosmopolitanism as well.

Particularly in parliamentary democracies the world over, this should never be assumed by voters. And judging from this video, voters in presidential democracies shouldn't assume so either. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-04 07:01:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> 1) July 4th is an event when we declared political victory over our own country's destiny.

2) This is a humorous reminder to not be an asshole to your pets. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-04 02:35:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What do you mean? I don't see how there is a qualitative difference. Both titles conclude: "there's no market-liberal difference for Brexit" </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-03 21:00:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I also suggest picking up his book ['*How Much Money Is Enough*'](http://www.nytimes.com/2012/08/19/books/review/how-much-is-enough-by-robert-skidelsky-and-edward-skidelsky.html). 

It's really great. 

His father, [Robert Skidelsky](http://www.skidelskyr.com/), is a big [Keynesian economist](https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Keynesian_economics) and wrote a book on the need to return to [Keynes](https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Keynes:_The_Return_of_the_Master) in our economic thinking </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-03 07:35:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So, it looks like most people who commented on this thread didn't read the actual article. Which kinda proves the central relevance of it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-02 01:56:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Do you mean me? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-28 23:33:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> via Bloomberg Markets: [Brexit-proof your portfolio](http://www.bloomberg.com/news/articles/2016-06-27/bofaml-three-ways-to-invest-for-the-coming-age-of-populism)

1. Buy gold. And volatility.

2. Long "Main Street" plays (such as regional banks and mass retailers); short Wall Street plays (such as broker-dealers and luxury retailers).

3. Play the tails of deflation and attempted-reflation trades.

'"Investors should be long an 'uber-barbell' of high-growth/high-quality stocks (FANG stocks, global Best-of-Breed stocks, and "yield plays") and underowned inflation assets (commodities, TIPS, EM and the UK)," he wrote.' </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-20 22:50:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I have a very minimal grasp on what ESOPs are (Employee Owned Stock Plans), but I'm having a hard time seeing how ESOPs are different from other retirement plans or 401(k)s.

San anyone help me understand ESOPs, and its benefits, advantages, or disadvantages? 

Supporters of ESOPs say they're better than other retirement plans for both the company and the employee, but the most advantage to an employee that I could ascertain is that ESOPs can borrow money. 

So, I guess my initial questions are:

1) What is an ESOP?

2) Why/How are they unique?

3) Are ESOPs more advantageous than other employee benefit plans, and how?

4) Specifically, what is the difference between an ESOP and 401(k), and which is "Better" [for both employers and employees]?

Thanks to anyone will to educate me!! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-20 03:22:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Nativism_(politics) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-19 19:47:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What American "progressive leftists" don't get is that Bernie Sanders is an economic ultra-nationalist and a nativist.

What none of his supporters seem to get is that Sanders, like many right-wing European nativists, only believes in redistributing state resources AWAY from non-citizens and immigrants. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-19 19:46:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What American "progressive leftists" don't get is that Bernie Sanders is an economic ultra-nationalist and a nativist.

What none of his supporters seem to get is that Sanders, like many right-wing European nativists, only believes in redistributing state resources AWAY from non-citizens and immigrants. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-19 19:46:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What American "progressive leftists" don't get is that Bernie Sanders is an economic ultra-nationalist and a nativist.

What none of his supporters seem to get is that Sanders, like many right-wing European nativists, only believes in redistributing state resources AWAY from non-citizens and immigrants. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-19 19:46:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What American "progressive leftists" don't get is that Bernie Sanders is an economic ultra-nationalist and a nativist.

What none of his supporters seem to get is that Sanders, like many right-wing European nativists, only believes in redistributing state resources AWAY from non-citizens and immigrants. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-19 19:44:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's not. What American progressives don't get is that Bernie Sanders is an economic ultra-nationalist and a nativist.

Too many of us were hoodwinked into believing that overlap of economic preferences (i.e., of distribution) signaled that Sanders identified with all of our other Left principles. 

What none of his supporters seem to get is that Sanders, like many right-wing European nativists, only believes in redistributing state resources AWAY from non-citizens and immigrants. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-19 19:05:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Be civil. We need to convince her with logic, not alienate her with attacks.

Please educate her in the comments section to her video. But remember: We're going for unbeatable logic, not personal attacks.

She is just in an echo chamber made by Bernie, through no fault of her own. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-19 19:03:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> But be civil. We need to convince her with logic, not alienate her with attacks.

Please educate her in the comments section to her video. But remember: We're going for unbeatable logic, not personal attacks.

She is just in an echo chamber made by Bernie, through no fault of her own. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-18 22:00:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I suggest you do read this. It's not helpful to revolutions for us to ignore facts. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-18 20:46:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah. No. His defense of the EU is weak, and he stated that he approved of the UK's referendum. I don't believe you watched that interview. If you did and still believe he appreciates the conceptual framework of the EU, I'm not sure I can convince you otherwise.

Btw, quit it with the personal attacks. Our political discourse deserves better.

If you are cynical about politics, it's time for self-reflection. Personal attacks like yours contribute to the cynicism.

Btw, read up on history:

https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Schengen_Agreement

http://eur-lex.europa.eu/legal-content/EN/TXT/?uri=URISERV%3Al33020

http://www.schengenvisainfo.com/

http://www.bbc.com/news/world-europe-13194723

http://europe.newsweek.com/five-things-you-need-know-about-schengen-agreement-332976?rx=us </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-18 16:55:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This is a newer video. From 2015.

He doesn't seem to quite grasp [one of the essential concepts behind the aspirations of the EU]](https://youtu.be/vf-k6qOfXz0), namely the free movement of people and open borders.

Bernie Sanders has leveraged the same quality of economic nationalism that Bexiters have campaigned on, and that the EU was envisioned to rise above. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-17 20:01:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> How about you actually read all of the article before you comment? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-17 05:00:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> He doesn't seem to quite grasp [one of the essential concepts] (https://youtu.be/vf-k6qOfXz0) behind the aspirations of the EU.

Bernie Sanders has leveraged the same quality of economic nationalism that Bexiters have campaigned on, and that the EU was envisioned to rise above. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-15 18:35:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Ok thank you for your reply </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-11 06:20:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Oh, ok. Than you for your patient explanation.

If you don't mind, can you post a link to where I can further familiarize myself with this issue? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-11 05:55:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Oh, I didn't think of that angle - that makes sense.

But where does the money go? Doesn't MMT say that whatever was in circulation at some point has to go somewhere - that it can't just disappear into the ether? Am I wrong in assuming that this is one of the larger premises of MMT?   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-08 19:27:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I think you should re-read the word "nominated"  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-27 20:26:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thanks, this was a very helpful explanation.

I'm fairly new to the whole topic, so I don't know how I could start trading in the Forex markets. On his YouTube channel, Norman says that he uses OANDA as his computer client, but I saw a few bad reviews on it when I searched around online.

I sent Norman a message asking him if he could write a general principles book on MMT investing, but he was not receptive to the idea at all [it's hard to figure out through electronic communication, but it might have been with a little hostility]. 

Instead, he kept on insisting I sign up for his 30-day free trial [with the catch, of course, that you have to physically cancel it before it automatically starts charging your card]. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-25 22:56:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Unless you are trying to be ironic, you are only undermining your own political priorities by seeking to start a witch-hunt, trying to silence anyone who might or might not believe something as strongly as you do.

And no, I am not a CTR troll. Believe it or not, I like Bernie. I just don't like when his supporters make him look bad. 

And right now, you're doing that.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-23 23:40:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> ** **UPDATE** **: Senator Sanders has named  Cornel West, Keith Ellison, Bill McKibben, James Zogby, and Deborah Parker to the platform committee. http://thehill.com/blogs/ballot-box/presidential-races/280941-sanders-names-cornel-west-keith-ellison-to-platform </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-23 23:36:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So, I am very curious. I do not mean this question to be confrontational at all, so I apologize if it is read as anything but respectful.

As I read the comments from what I assume are supporters of Senator Sanders' and/or the "Bernie Or Bust" movement, has support for Senator Sanders himself always been an animating factor in the movement, or just a resentment directed towards Hillary Clinton and "party elites"?

I guess what I'm confused by is this: If Bernie is given input in a leading role formulating policy decisions for the next President, is the continuing to refuse to support Clinton really genuinely pro-Sanders to begin with? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-19 04:24:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Because Bernie's claims of being an exceptional figure in politics should be scrutinized more consistently than they are </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-18 18:28:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> http://usatoday30.usatoday.com/news/washington/2006-04-21-clinton-democrats_x.htm </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-18 00:20:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Oh, I am really sorry - I did not know that this was already posted on the sub.

Sincere apologies!! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-17 08:12:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If you know anyone registered to vote in NYC, **make them aware that something like this might happen**.

If any of you have social media accounts, **please share this**

If any of you have friends in the press/media or know anyone who might have media contacts, **please pass this article onto them**.

If you are in NY and plan on trying to help prevent deliberately anti-democratic obstruction of voting, **it helps reaching out and forming alliances. The more of you informed and well-prepared, the better**.

Whatever happen, **do not** let any potential confrontation devolve into a he said/she said cloud of attacks. **Filming will help prevent crazy he said/she said situations - you will have proof to show to authorities or to the media**. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-17 02:00:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That's why we need to film it - so there's not as much of a chance for a "he said, she said" kind of situation. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-16 08:25:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> He's invested in the banks he says "screws the average investor". He took their money, including the big pharma companies that jack up drug prices because of monopolies on patents, big oil companies that pollute the environment.

For the sake of democracy and the future of the informed citizenry in which you live, please stay honest with yourself. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-15 21:49:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I think this excerpt is pretty relevant though: 

 The campaign for Sanders, who has a long record in support of LGBT rights and voted against the anti-gay Defense of Marriage Act in 1996, didnt respond to repeated requests from the Washington Blade to comment on whether Sanders was aware hes raising money against gay congressional candidates and **whether he thinks the endorsements are undermining LGBT representation in Congress.** </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-15 00:06:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Here's a novel idea: Independents, who notoriously don't vote in down-ballot or local elections, start voting in local elections to change election rules...!!

Nope? Oh, ok... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-13 04:44:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> "Bernie or Bust" is deeply self-defeatist. 

If we look at electoral history and the history of GOTV strategy, both Parties move to where voters are. They shift their efforts to where they can find voters. 

In other words, "Bernie or Bust," by not voting in the presidential election if Hillary is the nominee, is not where the voters are because they would ensure that they themselves are not counted among the people most engaged and who vote.

Put more simply, "Bernie or Bust" would only ensure that progressive leaders like Bernie are made even more irrelevant and marginal to the DNC's electoral, political, and GOTV strategies..

This outcome wouldn't simply be because the DNC is somehow being nefarious; Bernie supporters who don't vote will just be making themselves invisible to the Party and the political establishment. The DNC won't know where to look for those voters in the next election cycle, and they wouldn't know how to engage that crowd.

Also, according to exit polls so far in local races, there is a statistically-significant correlation between Sanders voters and nonvoters in state and local elections. If the "Bernie or Bust" crowd truly want a political revolution, the answer is not to sit out of the election - it is to vote in ALL races no matter how insignificant they seem to be. If the more Sanders supporters elect pro-Sanders candidates to Congress and other local offices, Hillary and/or other center-left Democrats can be given a chance to move left without becoming politically and electorally vulnerable. 

Thus, Sanders' "revolution" would have a better shot at succeeding in the election booth rather than not voting in protest. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-13 02:01:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> And people in poverty and welfare recipients are legally free too. Your point? 

Freedom is not quantifiable. It can only be measured and clarified in quality. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-11 20:30:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You might want to check out Nootropics Depot. I am also relatively new to the noot world, but ever since my intro to this world, I have become very fond of ND. http://nootropicsdepot.com/

My stack largely is oriented towards improving abstract and visual-spatial reasoning, so this list might help.

Adrafinil, Aniracetam, Caffeine + L-Theanine, Centrophenoxine, Oxiracetam, Noopept, Phenylpiracetam, and Teacrine.

However, what I would call my "base stack" does not include the Caffeine + L-Theanine or the Teacrine. I've added those more recently after the others, but don't know yet if I'll keep them in my stack. 

In my understanding, those two noots are the more naturalistic noots in my stack, and so a lot of the newer members of the noot community decide to start with those and gradually work up towards the more synthetic/experimental/investigational noots. Some, like a few friends of mine, opt to stay with these kinds of noots, citing some concerns over perceived risk. 

I personally don't mind any of the risk factors [I haven't encountered any noticeable issues], but if you also share these concerns, I think you might want to start out gradually with the natural noots first. 

Even though I don't think there is any base for concern around taking the more synthetic noots, you are theoretically more liable to **psych yourself out** and have a negative **placebo** effects. So, if you are currently in this head-space, I'd suggest **starting off slow** so you don't trick your own brain/mind into magnifying any bad side-effects. The placebo effect, as you know, can be **incredibly powerful**, so even if there is **absolutely nothing** there, the expectation that something bad will happen **itself** will bias your experience.

This is most of the stack I am currently using, and Nootropics Depot is a great place to get these from. They have really awesome customer service as well, so you can totally ask them for any other pointers or suggestions.

Also, Ceretropic is also a great place too: http://ceretropic.com/ </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-08 22:34:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Actually, Bernie has mentioned the emails, once calling them "a very serious issue." http://www.huffingtonpost.com/entry/bernie-sanders-hillary-clinton-emails_us_56ae254be4b077d4fe8e7023

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-06 22:24:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> "This president will go down in history as one of the smartest presidents. Brilliant guy," Bernie Sanders said about Obama, adding jokingly: "And especially the more people hear from the Republicans, the smarter they think he is." </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-02 20:03:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This article is from April of last year (2015), but it's worth a read again to see just how successful Tesla has been. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-27 17:38:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This is a joint presentation by two leading economists examining a common error that many of our economy's observers and political commentators make: the government spending is somehow the same thing as household spending. 

This false equivalency is repeated quite frequently, often having very distorting effects on socioeconomic and sociopolitical discourse in this country. http://www.modernmoneynetwork.org/?q=symposia/governments-are-not-households

This seminar will examine the legal and institutional structure of the current global monetary system, with a particular emphasis on the economic freedoms afforded to nations such as the U.S., U.K., Japan, Canada and Australia that use a non-convertible fiat currency with a floating exchange rate. Questions to be addressed include:

How does a fiat currency with a floating exchange rate differ from other types of currencies?

How does government spending and taxation work?

Why is accounting important for understanding the economy?

How can monetarily sovereign nations address their current economic problems?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-26 03:53:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Usually, people don't have the patience to read titles as long that one, so I wanted to cut it down and make it a succinct as possible without sacrificing substance. I think I found a happy medium. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-25 19:40:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> There is absolutely no way I can understate how important the outcome of this months-long legal battle will be to the future of homelessness and to the victims of domestic abuse in NYC.

Whatever legal precedent that results from this lawsuit can [and probably will] have systemic legal ramifications on the future of affordable housing in this city.

No matter how distant we think we are from this, every last one of us has a stake in this fight.

As Tip O'Neil said, all politics is local. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-25 03:53:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So... exactly who is scripted and sticks to talking-points and memes?! 

Oh wait... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-22 21:11:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Michael Grunwald reviews Obama's domestic policy legacy here: http://www.politico.com/magazine/story/2016/01/obama-biggest-achievements-213487?paginate=false

And this article explains how Obama is officially one of the most consequential presidents in U.S. history: http://www.vox.com/2015/6/26/8849925/obama-obamacare-history-presidents </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-22 21:07:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> He actually never criticized Obama's legacy. This is awfully lazy journalism. The article's source is a misleadingly edited clip of a Bill Clinton speech he gave.

Bill Clinton clarified:

"When Republicans controlled the White House, their trickle-down approach drove our economy to the brink of a collapse. After President Obama was elected, Republicans made it their number one goal to block him at every turn, spokesman Angel Urena said in a statement. That unprecedented obstruction these last eight years is their legacy, and the American people should reject it by electing Hillary Clinton to build on President Obamas success so we can all grow and succeed together.

http://www.thepeoplesview.net/main/2016/3/21/attacking-bill-clinton-wont-help-bernie-hide-record-of-undermining-obama-legacy

Sanders' has been adopting GOP talking-points on Obama's jobs record for the longest time, without the media calling him on it:
http://www.thepeoplesview.net/main/2016/2/5/dontbernmebro-why-sanders-is-parroting-gop-talking-points-on-obamas-jobs-record </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-17 19:51:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This paper is a fascinating reappraisal of stress and anxiety. 

Essentially, the study concluded that people who associate stress with something bad had worse health outcomes [physiological, neurological, and psychological] than people who considered stress as a helpful indicator that a behavior or activity will result in negative consequences.

In other words, participants who view stress as a "friend" who politely suggests to them that they do something different or to avoid something bad is more likely to have healthier outcomes than participants who saw stress itself as something bad and something to avoid. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-17 19:41:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This paper is very interesting. To paraphrase, the study observes that having a dense, intimate social network in which close, face-to-face contact is frequent, this reduces both stress and the risks of premature mortality. 

The study also concludes that if the act of giving, altruism, or mutual support are frequent themes in such intimate relationships, this also reduces stress and the risk of premature mortality to a notable degree.

The authors conclude with policy proposals of encouraging communal mutual support and one-on-one supportive and mentoring relationships.

I should note that by 'intimacy', I do not only mean it in a romantic or sexual context. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-16 21:08:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I did not make any such assumption. I don't think the article did either. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-16 03:55:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hillary was liberal, and she is still liberal
https://fivethirtyeight.com/datalab/hillary-clinton-was-liberal-hillary-clinton-is-liberal/ </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-16 03:31:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I believe that that brief summary excludes variation in markets. Which Flowers takes as a given, and I believe rightfully so. 

Undoubtedly, all markets go down eventually when a market they have economic ties to goes down. But Flowers seems to be more concerned with variation. 

For any example of this, it should be easy to compare cross-country recessions and their relative impacts and recoveries. Many countries experienced different kinds of market decline, at a different pace. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-16 03:02:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I don't particularly have the time to look at all of these - I will when I have time.

Though, since you seem well-informed, why don't you explain it to me? It would be a lot easier and quicker for me to read your explanation. It's just not convenient for me at the time to go through all of those links. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-16 01:22:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Democracies are too. Point being? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-16 00:51:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So go into it.  

Btw, Flowers' central claim is that our markets **were not** previously correlated. It seems that you're assuming that Flowers said what he didn't actually say.

Again, I do want to emphasize that I don't understand why you insist on being so antagonistic, but if being so is gratifying to you, then I suppose that's cool being that I apparently don't care or am as invested in who is right or wrong here.

I am very interested in the insights you can provide, but I do have to say, if you persist at the subtle digs at my intelligence or indulge in any form of subtle attacks, I'll see no further use in continuing this conversation. They may be gratifying to you, but it's certainly not to me. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-16 00:16:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Not unless you cannot correlate "15 year analysis" and "a country that has an equivalent or similar level of economic co-dependence or economic relations between China and the U.S."

I get a sense that you're offended or otherwise hostile to the premise of this article, and I don't really get why. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-16 00:06:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Kinda, although only if you ignore the part where Flowers' includes a 15-year historical analysis proving that the last months where we seemed to slip as China slipped was a heretofore historical anomaly:

"Over the last 15 years, U.S. markets have not moved in tandem with those in China. Since 2000, the rolling 90-day correlation looks like an EKG printout." </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-15 23:48:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I don't believe that's against the subredditt's rules. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-15 22:09:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Then, it's my mistake. I understood you to say you only vote when you think it's necessary to influence politician's decisions. 

Hence, I assumed you meant that once your policy preferences are given priority among politicians and policymakers, you don't see voting as a necessity. 

Totally my mistake. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-15 21:57:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> And I would reply to that, as I did in my previous response, that voting 'when necessary' to influence elections (I take this to means you don't vote when you don't think it's necessary and/or your ideals are not under threat) can - according to most of political history - be misguided. 

Parties need to constantly hear from their voters to know if the direction they are going in is the voters' direction. If they don't constantly hear from certain demos of voters, they start looking for other demos who vote more reliably and consistently.

Conversely, back to your initial idea that the youth vote lost faith with the DNC due to unpalatable policy shifts and the absence of voter outreach, too many voters only vote due to perceived necessity in presidential elections to a significantly greater degree than in local and state elections. 

Unfortunately, too many voters [you're likely not included] seems to have forgotten their civics and their Constitution, particularly the Separation of Powers. 

If voters vote only due to necessity, *Congress* [and probably the *Presidency*] will only act out of necessity - their behavior in other words will reflect what their voters want and what they view necessary. Congress only sees issues as necessary if voters see them as necessary - that's how popular representation, Congressional behavior, and executive (Presidential) behavior works.

If voters don't see the need to consistently vote or support a party's agenda because they perceive that their ideals are sufficiently entrenched in the Party and their ideology is not under threat, the Party will inevitably decide to look where they get more consistent, reliable voter feedback. 

Example: lots of Democratic voters loved Obamacare when it was introduced and a few months in, but voters became complacent and stopped seeing a need to sustain these policy changes. The 2010 and 2014 elections are two of the more recent examples of this. 

Three underlying assumptions that voters who vote only due to "necessity" seem to take as givens: 
1. Political parties are monolithic, 
2. Because of this, Parties have a monopoly over policy decisions/policy agendas.
3. Thus, once voters help secure an agenda, politicians have a mandate that is effective until he or she gets out of office. 

Two really good articles that examine what I am trying to tell you are these: https://fivethirtyeight.com/features/donald-trump-incites-his-crowds-and-his-crowds-incite-him/

http://www.vox.com/mischiefs-of-faction/2016/1/26/10834512/party-decides-establishment

I very much enjoy this conversation. Talking politics and electoral history is fun for me. I hope we can continue this.

PS: I never alleged that you don't vote [it might be helpful to re-examine my previous comments].  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-15 20:37:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Unfortunately, voting only for "necessity" is not enough to induce either Party to mobilize voters in your demographics or geographical area.

I've long had a semi-beef with fellow progressives on this very issue. For example, many Sanders supporters say they won't support Clinton if she is the nominee. 

Their arguments largely are to the effect that letting the GOP nominee win will convince the DNC to start supporting candidates more progressive than Clinton in future election cycles.

As a long-time political observer and as a political scientist and historian, this is a glaring mistake in political and electoral causation.

Political parties move to where **voters are**. Conversely, where there are no voters, **there is no Party**. 

Generally, it is an assumption that smart electoral practice demands that parties go where the voters are, because otherwise, they are wasting their own time and their bases' time. And if Parties waste their bases' time, Parties risk losing the voters they have. And those voters that the Democratic Party will be worried about losing won't be progressives as long as they don't vote.

Political parties allocate more delegates and superdelegates to high-turnout states. In this case, if voter turnout is depressed in blue states relative to purple or even red states, delegates are allocated to where more viable (i.e., more conservative or centrist) Democrats are.

In fact, one of the reasons the delegate and superdelegate system was created was to ensure that if depressed voter turnout is low enough to allow a totally unpopular or unelectable or destructive candidate to win due to miserable turnout numbers [i.e., Trump], the delegates would step in to offset the low voter turnout.

In the Bernie vs. Hillary example, if his supporters *don't* vote for a Democratic nominee who is decidedly **not** the most conservative Democrat ideologically, not only will the DNC look for someone more conservative than Hillary to support, but Sanders' own supporters will have misguidedly caused figures similar to Bernie irrelevant and marginal to the Party's electoral calculus. 

Political parties - particularly the DNC - are more responsive to voters than many people seem to realize. And one of the larger ways they are able to "read" the electorate and the country's mood is through voter turnout. Thus, if only conservative or moderate Democrats vote, and progressives don not, parties have no choice but to listen to the conservative/moderate Democrat vote. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-15 20:09:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yes, but since your alternative perspective relies on falsifiable reductionism, it is for the most part invalid.

Your assumptions rephrased: 

1) The youth vote was vibrant and strong enough to influence elections in meaningful ways.

2) The DNC drifted away ideologically from the electorate, thus disenchanting the youth voter.

3) The absence of the Democratic youth vote hurts the Democrats in meaningful, fundamental ways.

4) The depression of the youth vote is the Democratic Party's own fault. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-15 19:51:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> By my statement, I meant that capitalism had yet to be completely infused into society and had yet to be democratized to the extent that it is now, which led to the type of economic stratification that seems to be intrinsic to our practice of capitalism. 

Spanning the 18th and 19th centuries, artists, poets, and philosophers were largely protected from the instabilities of the market because of the patronage that they received. 

http://www.theatlantic.com/magazine/archive/2015/01/the-death-of-the-artist-and-the-birth-of-the-creative-entrepreneur/383497/ </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-15 19:36:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I contest your premise that the youth demo ever voted in local elections in meaningful numbers. Extensive longitudinal reports and analyses from Pew and academic papers have documented the long trend of the negligible turnout among young voters in both state legislative elections, other local elections, and midterms.

Blaming the Democratic Party for that is getting causation backwards. http://www.politico.com/magazine/story/2015/11/barney-frank-voters-cause-washington-gridlock-213325 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-15 15:01:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Did you even read the article? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-15 02:10:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Why does the date matter if the commentary is still relevant? It brings up concerns that many Democrats still have. Case in point: Most Congressional Dems are actively campaigning against Sanders and endorsed Hillary.

You might not like the commentary, but considering that the endorsement and super-delegate count is overwhelmingly not in Sanders' favor - a big theme and main concern in Frank's piece - this is still relevant. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-15 02:02:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's not outdated if the commentary is still relevant  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-15 01:59:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That's actually not completely true. It's a very successful meme, though. Unfortunately, like all memes, it is both not contextualized and exaggerated.

http://www.cnn.com/2016/03/01/politics/donald-trump-hillary-clinton-bernie-sanders-poll/

http://www.politifact.com/truth-o-meter/statements/2016/mar/08/bernie-s/bernie-sanders-says-he-consistently-beats-donald-t/ </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-14 20:36:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> No, I'm not. Is that relevant?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-09 21:33:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I have cerebellar dysgenesis, and I'm wondering if you'd be so kind to let me know how Semax effected you if you already tried it.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-07 19:26:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Oh, also, I should note, my very first dosing of this stack was this morning, and I tried it with NSI-189 Phosphate. Second dosig was about 30-40 minutes ago. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-07 19:25:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I just got Ani, Oxi, and Centro in the mail a few days ago. Tried it out,  upped them to two capsules each. Didn't really feel anything. I read on other threads that it might take 2-3 days to work (some say a week), but I am wondering if any of you shared a similar issue. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-03 20:05:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Oh, scheisse. Do you do anything to counteract the insomnia and narcolepsy?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-03 16:06:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Have you tried centro and didn't like it? How is your stack now? What are your experiences on it, and how did you find that it was the better one for you? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-03 16:04:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What effects do you notice? Any particular reason you chose that particular stack? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-11-22 17:52:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If you ever use MRI to measure the effects, can you let me know? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-11-21 16:22:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> To clarify, I mean any nootropic you've tried. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-10-25 00:08:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Ok, I'm sorry. I didn't think the video's original title made sense. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-26 10:27:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Ceretropic </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-23 20:50:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Ceretropic </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-20 07:07:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I would really like that! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-17 01:05:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  Lions mane mushroom

Which vendor/supplier is good for this? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-16 23:24:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Interesting... do you know why? Is the composition different? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-16 23:23:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah, just read that somewhere. Thanks for letting me know! Any tips on where to purchase good sublingual Noopept? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-16 23:17:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I will try to take it sublingually from now on, but for experimentation's sake, I just would like to know how many mgs are necessary in capsule form. Again, thanks for the tip. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-16 23:12:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Any particular time-frame?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-10 20:43:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I just did, and they sent me back an email saying it was not normal, and they'd reship a new batch with the safety seal. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-08 18:58:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What do you mean by wishing to get your memory back? Did taking noopept degrade your memory? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-08 18:57:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thank you for pointing that out - that is a very helpful thread. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
