<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject9139</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2009-12-08 15:55:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I am copying the answer I gave above:

Yes, I have been on antidepressants for two years now. I have worked with several therapists and I saw a psychiatrist regularly for about a year. I strongly wanted the therapy to work, I gave it my best and it just wasn't enough. The medication (Prozac) did help a lot in the beginning, but when I started feeling worse again and I went to the doctor, he simply doubled my dose. This didn't work at all and I went through hell trying to go back to the original dose, 20 mgs, which is what I am taking now. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2009-12-08 15:54:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yes, I have been on antidepressants for two years now. I have worked with several therapists and I saw a psychiatrist regularly for about a year. I strongly wanted the therapy to work, I gave it my best and it just wasn't enough. The medication (Prozac) did help a lot in the beginning, but when I started feeling worse again and I went to the doctor, he simply doubled my dose. This didn't work at all and I went through hell trying to go back to the original dose, 20 mgs, which is what I am taking now. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2009-12-08 15:48:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> To answer your other question, I do think about it a lot (I can't help it) and about once a day I get a really strong urge to act upon it. It is a terrible compulsion and it takes a lot of effort not to follow through. Sometimes talking about it helps, hence this AMA.

Of course there are also times when I feel a bit more positive and hope that I can eventually beat this and live a normal live, but they are becoming increasingly rare. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2009-12-08 15:42:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Actually, I feel I have to struggle to achieve many things that people take for granted every day, like getting out of bed, taking a shower, going to work... the list goes on.

I definitely hate myself, I feel I am a failure and a disgrace and the world is better off without me. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2009-12-08 15:40:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> In the beginning the doctors held me back, they assured me that they could cure my depression, that I would be well again. Now I don't believe that any more and the only holding me back is my husband. I love him deeply and he doesn't deserve to suffer so much. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> I have everything I could reasonably ask for, and still I want to kill myself every day. AMA. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2009-12-08 15:28:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> EDIT: A comment on this post helped me find out the reason for my depression and now it's gone! I explained the story [here](http://www.reddit.com/r/reddit.com/comments/alpyt/thank_you_reddit_you_have_saved_my_life). THANK YOU to all of those who posted, who cared, but a very special thanks to [frinklestein](http://www.reddit.com/r/IAmA/comments/acdy7/i_have_everything_i_could_reasonably_ask_for_and/c0gvt51). You saved my life.

----------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------
A roof over my head and food on the table - check.

A loving, devoted, intelligent, sexy husband that I adore - check.

A job that I love and that I'm good at - check.

Youth and health (except for mental health, I suppose) - check.

People that would like to be my friends if only I would let them - check.

A supportive family - check.

Hobbies and interests (if I ever had the energy to pursue them) - check.

Money for chocolate - check.

*Edited whenever I remember more blessings. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
