<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject832</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-13 11:45:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Because of a hypothetical situation? What?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-11 13:54:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This made me cry. I want this. I dont think he does. :'( </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-11 13:23:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I hardly think not receiving a balloon constitutes as abuse </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-10 11:15:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Since when does not wearing makeup and not wearing your best clothes every day make you a slob?? TIL I am a slob..! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-10 01:43:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> To be fair, basically every comment you make references this- when that may not be the problem at all, its just how you perceive it. If you're anything like this irl I can undersrand why people may not want to stay friends with you. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-09 22:34:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> How often do you poop..?? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-07 15:20:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I knew it looked familiar!!! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-07 00:24:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yep! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-05 17:03:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Are you kidding? The rail network here is an absolute shitshow!! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-02 15:42:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Dude you look awesome. Good job. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-02 14:57:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Close the thread, we have a winner </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-02 14:55:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Job-seeker trigger alert </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [Friendship] 23/F/UK, seeking online or local friendship </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-02 14:51:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'll get the boring stuff out of the way first!!

I'm looking for someone who wants to make a close and trustworthy friend, but is not going to panic if we don't talk for a few days or weeks at a time. Sort of like an online pen-pal. Longer messages rather than IMs, it's more exciting that way. Who doesn't like to get a long(ish) message just for them? :)

I'm based in Yorkshire, if you're local then that's cool but I'm not intending with meeting anyone on here until we've messaged for a few weeks/months/until we're both comfortable with that.

A few things about me:

* My biggest hobby is gaming online. TF2 is my favourite!

* I also enjoy reading, movies and listening to music.

* I am in a relationship, so platonic friendship only please.

* I am friendly and I like to make other people happy

* At times I can suffer from poor self-confidence. I'd like to know that anyone I make friends with on here is okay with me talking about my problems occasionally. I am happy to help you with yours too :)

* I'd ideally like to make friends with people age 20+ but don't let this put you off, PM me if you'd like to chat regardless of your age.

Hopefully this won't put too many of you off haha.

Hope to hear from you soon :)
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-02 14:37:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Dude don't lead on 2 women at once that's beyond cruel.

What /u/nazibloodtastesgreat said is absolutely right. You can't use other people to try to justify that what you do is okay, find the REAL you. You would be happier with the guilt lifted from betraying 2 people that care about you. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-02 14:34:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Try giving us a little more information.

Are you looking for a particular type of person? How old are you? What are some of your hobbies? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-01 13:13:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I totally get where you're coming from. If it's any comfort I am fond of dark humour! Maybe we would get on :) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-31 13:52:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You have to take things slowly with people. Saying something that would require a 'filter' in normal situations should maybe wait until later, don't go in full guns blazing waving your 'if you can't handle me at my worst, you don't deserve me at my best' flag because that will put off so many people. You won't make a good impression by showing them your worst straight away.

If you at least acknowledged that it was a shitty thing to say then at least you're getting somewhere and learning things..you're right that you shouldn't have to change for them, but at the same time you shouldn't expect THEM to change for YOU, i.e. forced acceptance of your offensive humour. Just try and start small with any jokes you might have and build them up rather than jumping in with everything you have. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-31 13:47:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Dude. Look at yourself. You're picking on someone that is going through a really hard time in their lives, what possible gain does that give to you? Have some goddamn humanity. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-30 21:45:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Dude I thought this was funny and an amazing coincidence until I realised they're both your account. You made me sad today :( </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-30 18:34:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Corgee </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-28 19:03:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You dont start paying it back until you're receiving a fairly high salary though, do you? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-28 18:29:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Awh man thats so awesome!! How do you get into work like that, I'm intrigued! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-28 11:42:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Dude you've done an amazing job. I lived on that street in my second and third year of uni and that alleyway down to the park looked like you'd get murdered or at the very least catch HIV just from walking down there. It looks amazing now! 

Are you likely to do any more work in Sheffield? 

Great work :) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-27 19:44:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah sure, let me just hop in my fucking time machine </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-26 23:47:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I've got no prospects in life FTFY </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-26 12:12:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Same story for me.  7 months ago, at the 2 1/2 year mark. Is anyone still with their partner? I'm reading all theae and feeling alone in the fact that I'm still with him. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-26 11:09:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> He commented 5 hours after posting too. So 16 hr shift, vibrator fail which must have been a couple of hours, post TIFU, then still awake 5 hours after? Nah mate </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-25 18:06:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Microsofts AI that recently got let loose on twitter and rapidly became very very racist </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-24 17:39:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It....it almost tricks the mind into seeing a full monobrow, with the way it graduates from full opacity to 0 and then back again. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-24 05:17:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Nah mate. The context is a bit out. She was telling him they were exclusive, which he believed; but it turned out they were not exclusive and he was one of several guys she was involved with. Why do you think he had a house key? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> I've got an interview with a job tomorrow, but I don't know if I really want it. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-23 16:43:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The trouble with applying through websites like cv-library.co.uk  is that so many of them are done through agencies that provide no information on their location, and as someone who has to rely on public transport this is an issue for me. Some roles I apply for may not be attainable for me at all.

This is the issue with the job interview I have tomorrow. It's a role that I'm not particularly keen on, however I need to have a job before I can start working on my primary career target. I need to get 2 buses, or a bus and a tram to get to this place, and I'm really worried I'll be late often because of the transport issue. That and I'm not sure I want that job.

The agency that has put me forward is also putting me forward for a different job which I'm really, really keen on. Should I hold out on job #1 in case I do get an interview at job #2? i'm worried that my consultant will think me unreliable or a risk-taker if I turn down job #1 for the mere chance of job #2.

Should I just snap up the first opportunity I'm given? I've only been searching for about 4 weeks.

Sorry for the garble. I'm just letting the brain waves flow out onto the page :) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-23 13:14:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Ace advice, thank you very much.

Just to confirm what you said about putting a battery on a tender, what's a tender?

I'll be using the scooter for commuting so it'll be daily usage. Would I need to put the battery on a tender if I went away for a week or 2 weeks holiday for example? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Absolute beginner to scooters, looking for some advice! </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-23 12:39:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hey guys! For reference, I'm based in the UK.

I am looking to get a scooter as an inexpensive form of travel for commuting to prospective jobs. Most of my questions involve some aspect of money as I don't have a job right now and I don't want to run out of rent money! I have a few total noob questions and I'm also looking for open-ended advice, perhaps something you wish you knew when you started out scootering.

1) Is it a good idea to purchase the scooter before taking the CBT test? I feel a little unsure about learning on a different scooter to the one I will eventually have- or are they pretty similar in terms of mechanics?

2) Would you buy new or second-hand? I am drawn to the low prices on gumtree, but knowing next to nothing about scooters I'm a little cautious about buying from there in case I get lumped with something terrible/has lots of problems. I really love Vespas but perhaps I should wait a couple of years before getting one of those!

3) How do you recommend storing a scooter? I have a back yard, but where I live is incredibly hilly and I wouldn't be able to get it in the shed at the back of the yard. Is keeping it under a cover acceptable?

4) How much should I spend on gear? (jackets helmets etc.) I'm not willing to skimp on safety but I want to know what's a good price so I'm not going to get ripped off.

5) Is there any other advice you'd like to give me? Really anything is helpful. Please feel free to rip to shreds anything I've said above if you disagree with it, I want to know your thoughts!

Thank you so much for your time. :)

edited to add another: what kind of scooter would you recommend for an absolute beginner? I'm not looking above 50cc.

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-22 23:02:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> PM me if you want a friend. I need a friend too. Maybe we can help each other. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-22 00:50:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> My partner works from home and we do not want children, so these arent issues.
 I wouldnt even consider dog ownership if we both worked full time.

I am aware of their difficulty in training; I plan to meet some breeders and their animals at some local shows this summer :) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-21 20:08:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> UK cars.
Not all European cars are like this. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-21 15:31:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thanks for your help! 

I'm based in Sheffield, I'll get looking for local dog shows! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-21 15:30:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thanks so much for the help- will be saving this post for the future for sure! This is really excellent advice :) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [HELP] When researching what dogs might fit my lifestyle, I came across the Basenji. Can anyone offer advice where to find one in the UK? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-21 15:14:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I've never owned a dog and this is prospective searching for in the future, probably 1-2 years away from now when my partner and I have our own house. Where we live now will not accept dogs.

I had my heart set on italian greyhounds for years, but having done some more research on the Basenji I may have changed my mind. 

Would this dog be recommended for a first time dog-owner? Where in the UK might I find a Basenji? I've looked into getting italian greyhounds from reputable breeders before, and from my research it seems like they almost never sell to first-time dog owners. I'm assuming this breed will be the same since they're very uncommon. Am I hoping for the impossible?

Some thoughts on this from the experts would be lovely :)

Thank you for your time! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-20 11:28:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Doesn't work for non-US accents. Thet pronounce t's as d's over there. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-19 12:11:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You can buy these in the UK too. They're premixed with coke and stuff. You can get smirnoff vodka cans and captain morgans too. Cheaper than buying a whole bottle, but not as good value for money. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-18 22:15:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hey you are exactly how I was when I was 17. I felt so boring. But there's other people like you too, you just have to find them. Believe me, drugs and smoking are definitely not cool. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
