<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject323</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-25 23:46:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I see what you did there. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> How would you fix Battlefield Earth? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-25 21:58:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I would start by going back in time and when they were coming up with the idea of the film, tell them it's not a good idea.

Then they scrap the idea, and the movie world becomes a better place. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-25 21:29:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Have you ever been charged with...


Answer... yes.

There's no way around it.

Employers don't care so much about what you've been charged with (albeit fraud, violent, and embezzlement are exceptions), but more about being honest about previously committing crimes. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-25 21:24:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You don't own the rights to these videos once you submit them to any large profile site.

They have a disclaimer prior to submitting. If they don't claim the rights to the videos, then most affiliates will.

It's a huge web of interconnectedness that makes involvement with this type of business a pain if you want to pull out and bring your content with you too. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-25 21:23:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Get an attorney. When it comes to injury liability, I always tell people to go through insurance immediately as it creates a paper trail.

Get an injury lawyer, provide all the pertinent information, then let him work his magic. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-25 21:21:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If you didn't contract the services, then you don't owe the money. But you do owe an explanation, and some evidence as to why it wasn't you.

Unfortunately for you, this will take time and effort to prove.

Also, someone is out there fraudulently using your person as a means of paying for services. You need to nip that in the ass as quickly as possible. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-25 20:46:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The player customization tools make me more frustrated than the actual game. So I end up just taking a premade and changing his eyes to blue and hair to brown.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-25 20:42:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Really cool. 

Would love to have seen that myself.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-25 20:39:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> When climbing onto a train trestle, a train would be more of my concern than a goat man.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-25 20:32:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Very cute.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-25 08:04:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Settle down, ok.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-25 08:01:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Lol, the people who don't watch GoT are going to be confused.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-25 04:16:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Why were you down voted for this? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-24 22:04:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What kind of PC? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-24 22:02:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Nicely done. Plane didn't see it coming.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-24 21:27:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This is the standard definition of fraud. 

Go get a lawyer, have the courts deal with it.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-24 21:17:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This is exactly why title jumping is a felony. I despise people who purposely use fraud to con innocent people. 

Some may see title jumping as benign, but in your case, and a lot of other people's cases a car is a huge investment and a necessity for the work commute. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-24 21:10:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Lol. 

It can't be that bad. I hope.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-24 20:45:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Dolphins are the coolest animals on the planet. You don't need a reason to buy them.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-24 20:43:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Oh roller coaster tycoon. 

You so silly.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-24 20:41:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> While you're right. 

Retroactive child support must be requested. It isn't automatic. And the custodial parent must prove need, or that the non-custodial parent withheld contact information or tried to hide and avoid paying support. 

I know this isn't the place to advocate changes in legalities, but I hate how much leeway judges have over retroactive child support. Too much uncertainty for both custodial and non-custodial parent.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-24 15:41:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This is hilarious. The look on his face when he gets interrupted.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-24 14:45:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Sounds like mould.

The kitchen drawers won't be cause for the dwelling to be untenable, but the mould and it's effects (smell, health concerns, etc) will be cause for the dwelling to be considered untenable. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-24 14:37:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Many states require you to remove your plates, and if it is a requirement, its imperative to do so.
Illinois is one of those states you are required to remove your plates.
They will suspend your license if you fail to surrender your plates.

Lastly, title jumping is a felony, and it's something I would try to avoid being apart of. Report your title issues to the DMV as soon as you can. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-24 14:29:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Most states give you certain rights.

1) Notice of right to estimate. Which is supposed to give you a price and detail of the work, in which you can agree or disagree on moving forward with the work.

2) Detailed invoices which detail exactly what they are doing, plus the cost.

3) Any extenuating costs will be documented and presented to you prior to the work being done, where you can either agree to the costs and work being done, or reject them,

4) They must give you the right of taking your old parts back, as a record for you to keep.


Usually if you have issues with your repair, their is a paper and parts trail, where you can seek recourse through the auto shop first. If they refuse to rectify the situation, you'll need to go the civil route, and if you have evidence from all 4 of the rights I listed, then you should be able to prove that they didn't uphold their part of the deal. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-24 14:12:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Has she already given him her house? Or she plans to after he declares bankruptcy?

Typically any acknowledged sums of money or property accrued, or known to be accrued are property of the bankruptcy estate if they are known prior to claiming bankruptcy + 180 days (6 months).

Now, if he were to come into possession of that property afterwards, *without* prior knowledge after filing bankruptcy + 180 days (6 months), he would be in the clear to keep his newly acquired asset.

So to be clear. 

He files bankruptcy. Anything he currently owns, or inherits is property of the bankruptcy estate. Anything after 180 days of declaring bankruptcy is his to keep. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-24 11:18:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I remember taking a legal philosophy course.

One of the topics was domestic abuse, how stand your ground plays into it; also the brevity of battered women (partner) defense in such cases.

Domestic abuse, usually becomes one of those things that is mechanical between couples, to the point sometimes they don't even realize how loud and aggressive they become. 

If I were you, either:

a) ignore it and make a noise complaint.

b) phone the police every time you hear it.

They'll eventually stop being abusive (not likely), or move out (likely), because they won't be able to deal with the repeated police visits, or landlord intervening. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-24 10:21:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The default PS4 theme is great. The music is annoying though. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-24 08:40:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Elder law and power of attorney law is complicated; not to mention, your family situation sounds like a train wreck. You need a lawyer, go get one. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-24 07:46:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Without the water main, the property is untenable. Landlords are required by law to provide tenable dwellings for their renters.

Case closed. If she doesn't give you your safety deposit back, contact the LTB (Landlord and Tenant Board). </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-24 07:15:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Settle down, ok? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-24 07:11:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> ok </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Been too busy lately, so only have had time to log in at 1am PST during weekdays. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-24 04:00:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> But I haven't been able to find any real good fights.

A couple of months ago, I could find a good fight at all times of the day.

Any idea what happened to the late night population? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-24 03:56:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I remember when the game came out in 2004.

I was still a kid.

The starter zones and Ironforge were packed full.

The game had this aura about it that made it a journey and exciting. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-24 02:08:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What a train wreck.

One of those things that just consistently gets worse and worse. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-24 01:54:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Wants to face them like a man. 

Proceeds to walk out after being asked questions. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-24 01:46:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Then the burden of proof is on you to figure out what is regular defects from aging and lapses of maintenance versus the seller failing to disclose any known issues with the home prior to selling.

If you can figure it out on your own I would follow it up with a property lawyer to see if it's worth pursuing for compensation. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-24 01:30:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Nearly every U.S. state has laws requiring sellers to advise buyers of certain defects in the property, typically by filling out a standard disclosure form before the sale is completed. (This responsibility remains even if you bought the house "as is.") The standard form usually asks the seller to state whether the property has certain features (like appliances, a roof, a foundation, systems for electricity, water, and heating, and more) and then rate or describe their condition. Some states' disclosure laws are more comprehensive than others, and if a feature isn't on the list, the seller may not be required to speak up. Also, the seller isn't usually required to scout out problems. But if there's clearly a place where the seller should have stated a problem but denied it, your job is to try to figure out whether the seller in fact knew about the problem. For example, if the seller patched over or hid problem areas, or if the neighbors have told you about the seller's efforts to deal with a problem, the evidence is on your side. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-24 01:20:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If you weren't charge you won't have a criminal record.

To be fair, two bottles of vodka is way too much alcohol for a single person.

You're lucky you didn't do anything worse than just pass out. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-24 01:16:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Do not listen to police officers when it comes to what the District Attorney is pursuing.

1) You're on the right track. As I don't know the details, I can't circumscribe particular questions except to notify the lawyer to do what he needs to do to get the best outcome possible.

2) No, stick to one lawyer. Check his reviews beforehand, if he seems reliable and decent, then shopping for lawyers is a huge drain on your emotional and mental energy and should be avoided if possible.

3) It depends on too many variables. Ask your lawyer the best case scenario, then ask him the worst case scenario. Then expect something in the middle. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-24 01:12:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This.

Be concise, provide all pertinent information, and keep your cool.

These types of institutions have huge cracks in the floor, and are usually willing to assist you if you have all the relevant documentation and evidence to back up your claim. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-24 01:09:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Do not listen to any advice on here.

Go get a lawyer who specializes in elder law and powers of attorney. Listen to what they have to say, and go from there.

Your situation is so convoluted and ridiculous that no one over the internet will be able to understand the presiding legal issues you currently are and will encounter with the banks and any other entities. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-24 00:56:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> In Canada, for instance:

If your SO and yourself are both 17 years old.

If you two make a sex tape depicting yourselves having sex.

Hold onto that sex tape for 1-3 years.

And then the video later surfaces in your possession.

You are illegally in possession of child pornography, and can be federally prosecuted.

Child pornography laws in Canada, and from my understanding in the US have a tendency to be overarching at times. What I'm getting at, is find a good criminal lawyer, and get this settled. Do not try to figure it out yourself as Child Pornography laws are inherently complicated and won't make sense to a layman.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-24 00:47:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Actually if a police officer fails to utilize due diligence on a plethora of matters it can reflect poorly on him as its considered a miscarriage of justice. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-23 00:59:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> While statutory rape is applicable to strict liability in most states,I don't know whether transmission of material harmful to a minor would be. 

The reason I say this is largely due to how communication and chat infrastructures on the Internet work. If you're in an adult chat room and a minor pretending to be an adult comes into the chat room. Then how are you liable? Especially if you explicitly ask them their age and they reply with age of consent.

Are we all required to: request picture identification before interacting with people on the Internet? 

Like I stated in my original comment. If this had entered the physical world, then yes it becomes more complicated, which would include strict liability.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Farmer John? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-22 20:54:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-22 17:14:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> https://youtu.be/ew0h3xnwyR4?t=18s </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-22 16:59:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This.

Really important aspect is to keep any records where she states that she was 18. Screenshots of her profile depicting her age as 18, as well as any logs from text chat.

If she claims to be 18, and you have no other means of attaining her age, then typically you aren't liable if she turns out to be under 18. That is if this maintains a *distanced* relationship, this advice will hold water. If you had actually met her in real life, then it gets much more complicated. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [REQUEST] Post a sticky for remedies to the "sending a dick pic" to a random stranger, who then happens: </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-22 16:37:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-22 16:31:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You have no legal recourse as this hasn't developed into a pattern.

Outside of being annoyed, and being roped into a a bizarre situation, you yourself have not been harmed.

If I were you, go down to your local police station, ask to talk to an officer, and figure out any future options if this nonsense persists.

If it stops, continue with your life, and be glad you're separated from this crazy lady. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-22 16:29:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> We once had a liaison cop at our high school who was easily 6'7, built like a greek god, and had one of those intimidating stares.

While he was posted at our high school we had almost no fights, in fact I would say most shenanigans were at an all time low. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-22 16:21:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> No such thing as buyers remorse/cooling off when dealing with Canadian leases.

I'm Canadian and have had to deal with this prior as well.

You can come to a compromise with your landlord and hope out of good will they will rescind the lease without prejudice.

If not, then you're stuck with it. Learn from this though, before signing contracts; not only fully understand the contract, but how that contract will affect you in the future. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-22 16:06:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Cut all contact. It's probably a scam.

Then wait it out. Either move on with your life and learn from this scam (aka don't send dick pics to random people, lol), or if the police come knocking:

Don't divulge any information to them. 

Immediately get a lawyer, and listen exactly to what they say. Then do what they say to the T.

That is your best recourse. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-22 15:55:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This.

As sad as it is, you're on the hook for the medical bills. The only recourse would be to sue your mother for diverting those funds.

As swalsh stated, your obvious option is to declare bankruptcy as I'm sure $100k in debt is way over your head. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-22 14:46:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Get a lawyer.

Do what the lawyer tells you.

Remember to take this serious as the FBI is involved. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-22 14:33:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Do not involve the police immediately.

Try to find him and rectify the situation between the two of you.

If you feel even after his explanation that his intent was malicious and a breach of privacy, go to your higher ups and report the incident.

Don't let the guy get to you. You don't need to get into a physical altercation, because that may be what he's trying to goad you into. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Why does the media constantly, but subtly attack Bernie Sanders? Clearly fear. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-21 17:38:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> ELI5:Why did the bankers rally against FDR, even though FDR promoted using banks to deposit money? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-21 16:25:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> How much would it cost Donald Trump per year to operate his private Boeing 757? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-21 12:04:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Which Youtube ad did you most recently watch the entirety of? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-18 19:39:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> During nature documentaries, when the predator chases the prey, do you guys cheer for the predator or the prey? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-18 19:12:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> ELI5:How do they make CPU processors smaller (65 nm to 40 nm)? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-18 15:41:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> After doing so, the processor is capable of what the bigger one was, yet its smaller, cheaper, and more energy efficient. How? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Remote play is easily one of the best features ever. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-18 15:22:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Bring your laptop anywhere you end up going for summer vacation and bam, as long as you have your PS4 controller and a USB-micro USB cable you can continue to demolish people in BF4, Planetside 2, etc etc.

I love it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Do you think the psychological effect on your enemies of seeing an M1 Abrams roll up as support is better than it's actual combat effect? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-15 02:59:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Trying to imagine myself in an enemy position watching as a line of 3-4 M1 Abrams provides support to infantry troops clamping down on my position.

Wondering if I would run for my life, or stay and fight knowing they have tank support, even if I had the tactical advantage in location. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> ELI5: What obstacles do we need to beat to finally start making quantum computers? What is a qubit? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-14 00:46:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Can I safely use a 100w LED Light Bulb in a 60w slot? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-13 19:23:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's a ceiling light fixture with a bowl on the bottom covering the light bulbs, and the sides are not completely enclosed.

3 light bulbs go into each fixture, and they say 60 watt Max on each slot.

I put 3 - Phillips 100w / 1600 lumen LED light bulbs into the fixture.

Is this safe? Taking into consideration heat safety and wattage safety.

Thanks in advance for any input or advice. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What are modern day tank crews taught? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-11 22:02:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> 1) When they engage a target, are they taught to move towards the target and fire, or are they taught to be stationary and engage the target from a distance?

2) When being shot at and hit (non lethal, non mobility kill), are they taught to move, or to stay stationary and acquire the target that shot at them?


Do these differ between each Nation? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What's the point of utilizing tanks if technology like the M109 Paladin exist? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-06 11:07:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Wouldn't the M109 Paladin (With Excalibur rounds) negate any tactical advantage a modern tank would have on the modern battlefield?

https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=BDLQ-SICd90

To clarify, wouldn't the M109 Paladin quickly and easily eliminate your tanks (from a safe distance) if you were an opposing force attacking the US? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Reza Aslan Fox Interview. One of the worst Fox Interviews ever. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-05 08:00:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Best PS4 commercial/Advertisement? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-03 23:14:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> PS3 had this:

https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=QOdowE7I3_E

Pretty sure everyone remembers this commercial.

Which one defines PS4? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> I'm thinking about buying a PC mouse. How much should I spend on it? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-03 21:49:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The power of "ok". </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-01 20:04:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Can you help me build a boat? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-30 20:39:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> How do you remove contacts on the new Paypal website layout? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-28 10:47:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I don't see invoice settings or address book. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Do you think ARM will eventually replace x86? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-28 04:51:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Anybody else "Recent Activity" and "What's New", not updating since Wednesday? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-27 23:28:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> My Date and Time is set to update automatically, so thats not it.

Wondering if anyone else is encountering this? Not a big deal, just something I've noticed. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Anyone else love the Glassy Sky song from Tokyo Ghoul Anime? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-24 03:33:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> March Edition: The Picking Up and Putting Down Thread. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-21 18:24:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> How this works is what games do you plan on picking up and playing in March? 

Subsequently, as you get a new game(s), your free time gets taken by those new games, therefore which games do you then plan on putting down, and stop playing to free up time?

For me, I'm possibly picking up and playing Darksouls 3 and Fallout 4: Automatron DLC.

I'm putting down in exchange, Warthunder, Battlefield 4, and Planetside 2. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Your favourite F2P game on the PS4 PSN? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-21 04:34:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Planetside 2 for me.

Surprised Sony doesn't advertise it more on the PSN. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> These PS4.5 or PS4K rumours are a joke. Why do people pay any credence to them? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-20 21:38:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The fact that people play into these almost clickbait'ish articles from IGN and Kotaku is astounding.

Why would Sony create new hardware, slightly over 2 years since the PS4 release, they would:

A) Alienate their already 44 million PS4 customers

B) Fragment their current line up of games, and thus hurt their licensing profits since people would need to adopt the new hardware to purchase the PS4.5 games.

C) Go against their prospected 5-6 year cycle most developers have already advocated as Sony's plan.

D) Waste resources into a .5 (half tier upgrade), when they could instead invest in accessories that are compatible with the 44 million PS4 units.

Kotaku and IGN do this crap all the time.

They see the new "hardware unit box" that comes with the Playstation VR, which gives the PS4 more processing power to accommodate the Playstation VR's more demanding hardware requirements, and twist it into some bull story about some new PS4.

Had they instead said:

"Sony may plan to release a newer PS4 with the Playstation VR's hardware acceleration incorporated internally within the console itself. But essentially, regular non VR games, the units will be identical to previous PS4 units in capability."

This would make more sense.

I absolutely despise Kotaku's rumour mill, and how IGN will broadcast over and over and over the same garbage to fill slow news day voids. "Anonymous Developers" is a catchphrase Kotaku has invented.

Your guys thoughts? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What classification would Arima be in comparison to a ghoul? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-18 17:14:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> SSS or SSSS? Will there even be SSSS Ghouls in the future?

He kept the real one eyed owl on the defensive with exceptional ease.

He kind of puts a bottleneck on the story, as any Ghoul right now can't compare to him. So will the ghouls band together to take him on? Or will a ghoul rise up and exceed Arima in power? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Sovereign Citizen being dumb. Cop teaches him a lawful lesson. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-18 16:19:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> How do guys like Leonardo DiCaprio(Most of his movies, even when he was young), Mel Gibson (Braveheart), Marlon Brando, and Bruno Ganz have such captivating presence on the big screen? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-09 07:21:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What sets them apart? 

Is it something you can learn to do, or is it just "natural"? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> "It ripped my tow hook off" </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-29 07:23:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Alki David farts on microphone at red carpet event. Hands it back to interviewer. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-18 00:39:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What the hell happened? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-12 18:36:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Med was easily one of the best online games back in the late 90s. So many people on we had 1-2 forms constantly fighting in low/mid/high levelling zones on a daily basis.

Vibrant gods, contributors who would claw at Vryces front door to make zones and content. A cool system for Mudslinger contributions to earn donation items. Just all together a vibrant and active community, and though I hated the no cursing or trolling rules, I guess now that I'm older and have been exposed to other MMO communities like WoW (actually just WoW, Diablo 2/3), I have an appreciation for that cleaner old school Med community. 

I played from 97/98 to 99/00. Came back in late late 2015.

Now it's just like a dead horse. 

Where's the new content? Gear? New players. I log in and see 32 people, half of which are in BL's from guys who played in the late 90's. Where's the new people?

Also from what I've read, Vryce went a little cuckoo, he used to be a pretty reliable and chill guy, who would watch from afar but you knew he was there in the background making sure the game ran fluidly while the other people would contribute and put a diverse flavour to the game.

It's a shame too, Med NPK and CPK was absolutely the best shit ever conceived.

Albion online looks like it's mimicking a lot of Med's original NPK CPK zone segregation. So I guess some of Med's best features will live on in other games.

Here's hoping Vryce can turn this shit around, can't imagine an internet without Medievia. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Hooker gets ordered for Gross Gore live on Stream. Pimp then shows up for explanation afterwards. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-01 04:56:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Why was HEATFS so much better than HEAT? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-29 09:13:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> TV Host breaks snow globe, even after being warned it's heavy and awkward. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-29 07:38:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The Anniversary Bundles show coming soon? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-25 02:06:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm interested in the Heroic 6 month boost.

I started PS2 about 3 days ago, I noticed on the starter page, it scrolled "don't forget to pick up the anniversary bundle before it's gone"

The first day I started, I didn't notice the anniversary bundles even in the Bundles list. Today, they all of a sudden appeared, and have a "Coming Soon".

I'm wondering is this an error? Because when I go to buy it, it says "error".

My own research in the matter shows that the bundles (or specifically the 2nd anniversary bundle was available on Dec. 12 and 13th)

Thanks in advance for any clarification. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Gun safety thrown out the window. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-18 06:15:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Ted Nugent calls President Obama a "Subhuman Mongrel" </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-01 13:45:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Why don't terrorist organizations like ISIS, Al Qaeda, etc ever have old US tanks like M60's and it's later variants. Why is it always Russian tanks like T-54's/55's etc? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-01 13:01:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> When the US sold off it's older tank variants etc (M60's, M60A1-A3), including M1 Abram's, do they have some kind of decommission clause in the agreements that keep the countries it sells it's tanks to from reselling them to other countries/organizations, or going as far as forcing them to decommission the tanks after they use up their usefulness/upgrade to newer tanks? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> M60 vs the T-62? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-30 13:44:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Which tank comes out on top?

M60

https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/M60_Patton


T-62

https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/T-62 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [NG][Lvl 47][Mico]Looking for a bored high level to eat him fast [PW: gta555][PSN: subject323] </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-18 10:22:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thanks in advance. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What kind of damage would C4 do to a modern day tank? For example an M1A2 / M1A3? T-90's? Leopard 2? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-18 09:28:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Let's say we strapped some C4 to the front plate of an M1A2 / M1A3 Abrams, and set it off, would it blow a huge hole into the frontal Armour?

What about the side plates?

Underneath? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [NG][Lvl 37][RtVS]Looking for a bored high level to eat him fast [PW: gta555][PSN: subject323] </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-18 09:17:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [Normal Game][60][Hunter's Dream: I refused][subject323] PW: tt55yu SPOILERS </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-10 12:24:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Need help with Gerhman. 

Thanks in advance for the help. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> They need to get rid of trophies that force you to play the game 3 times, or alternatively save scum. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-07 11:50:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yharnam Sunrise, Childhood's Beginning, and Honouring Wishes is nonsense. It should have been a single trophy for beating the game. I have all the trophies except 2 of the 3 for beating the game. I'm halfway through the second trophy, but it really doesn't make sense for needing to beat the game 3 times differently. The trophies could have been put to better use.

At most, I'm hoping Darksouls 3 only has 2 game beating trophies.

Anyone else annoyed by this set up? Darksouls 2 has a single trophy for beating the game, I like that set up much better. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Call me crazy, but don't you think it's time the Cowboys get an actual real GM? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-07 05:21:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I get that Jerry wants to cut out the middleman, but I think it's time Jerry starts letting go of the reigns a bit and he can start by hiring an actual professional GM who actually knows what he's doing.

Been a Cowboys fan since the Aikman/Emmit Smith years, I was like 7 or 8 years old. It pains me to watch the Cowboys struggling when the problem is largely, in my opinion, Jerry Jones inability to put together a team who wants to show up to bleed and sweat for wins. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> PS4 Warthunder 1.26, am I hallucinating? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-06 05:58:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Any idea what is incorporated in this patch? I searched on google and it brings up nothing.

Thanks in advance for any input. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Is the Rakuyo OP? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-02 00:25:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I went 20 ish kills to 2 deaths last night invading people. I was shredding people in a single R1 chain. Not to mention taking on 3 guys at once with a 70% success rate. 

You could tell after I killed someone in under a second, they were looking at their TV screens wondering what the fuck I was using. 

I was only forced to switch to the pizza cutter to take on a group of 3 that refused to split up. 

Can anyone confirm the the Rakuyo is OP?

I'm also level 150 with 50/50 str/skill and almost 40 end. 50 Vit too. 

I'm just wondering because before this I never really invaded people before. It got so insane I had pairs of guys running away from me with no mobs around me to give them reason to run. 

Just a mediocre PvPers perspective on this. Have a good one. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What's the DLC equivalent to Ludwig's? 50 / 50 Quality build. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-11-28 00:19:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> For quality builds of 50/50 where are we going to get the most bang for our buck. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Is it just me, or since 1.07 Co-op seems to work really well. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-11-27 23:50:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The tweaks to Co op like seeing phantoms you within your level range etc, and finding people seems significantly more accessible and frequent now. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Guy shits himself street fighting, then refuses to get off the other guy. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-11-26 11:46:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> X Ambassadors, Jamie N Commons ft. Jay Z - Jungle (Extended Remix) [Rap / Remix] </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-11-25 05:51:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What kind of damage would a tank affixed rail gun (meaning a rail gun the size of a modern day tank barrel), do to a M1A3 Abrams, T-90, or Leopard 2? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-11-25 04:00:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What would a tank sized rail gun be equivalent to as far as modern day tank ammunitions? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The worst 30 seconds of this guys professional life. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-11-24 04:18:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Whats the next iteration of MBT's? Anything on the horizon that makes all current MBT's obsolete? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-11-23 22:47:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Are there any working prototypes that blow all modern day MBT's out of the water as far as firepower, amor, and mobility? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What would a modern day armoured platoon look like from each major nation? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-11-22 04:54:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Meaning, if lets say the US went up against Russia, or Great Britain, or Germany etc.

What would each nations armoured platoon look like? Just straight up Abrams vs Leopards or T-90's? Or would they pepper each platoon with support vehicles? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Road raging Redneck meets Karma. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-11-22 02:39:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Paula Deen, slurs/southern drawls something stupid, the awkwardness can be felt even over the clapping. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-11-15 14:45:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Why you teach your girlfriend gun safety before taking her out to shoot an AK. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-11-09 09:34:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Why Caucasians don't voice act Asian stereotypes in video games anymore. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-11-07 10:51:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> PS4 1.53 </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-11-06 01:24:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> PS4


Added Trophies

Added Internet Radio support

[b]Fixed freezes at start of tank battles[/b]

Use 'Display Area Settings' instead of a fixed 90% border

Fixed Customization interface (applying decals) when using gamepad




Did they actually fix freezes at the beginning of battle? It causes you to crash into team mates tanks, making them think you're a griefer. I'm hoping they actually fixed it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Don't let that be, your apprehension...Don't let not having the tools, be your trepidation. You see that business card? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-11-02 14:37:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Freeze crowd founder, Eric Leebow uses the ALS ice bucket challenge to promote Freezecrowd. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-11-02 14:15:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> He had two pairs of Claiborne's. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-10-31 03:08:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Str/Skill scaling for LHB. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-09-14 07:24:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> After doing some reading, I'm planning to go a quality ludwig str/skill build.

I'm wondering, if you go 30 str/25 skill, is that going to add ANY damage versus 25 str/25 skill? Or does it only take the scaling into account by the lowest common denominator, being 25 for skill?

Thanks in advance for clearing this up </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> With the release of Bloodborne and the change of style incorporated in this game, are you guys even excited for Dark Souls 3? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-09-13 13:36:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I just started playing Bloodborne this past week, and I honestly feel like this game is superior in almost every way to Dark Souls. Dark Souls 1 was easily one of my favourite games. The atmosphere, the play style, the fact you knew you were going to die. It was such a refreshing change in video gaming experiences I have previously played. At the time I had both Skyrim and Dark Souls on my table, I fired up both, and I ultimately got hooked on Dark Souls passing Skyrim for a later time. It has this way of drawing you in, especially when you see those ghosts of fellow real life players run by you in a sewer tunnel etc, and then disappear. 

Bloodborne has taken this to a new level, the atmosphere is significantly better. The way the world connects and feeds into itself like the circulatory system of a real human body, it just feels alive. The combat in Bloodborne also feels significantly more involved. Weapons and armour feel more accessible, and play style options feel limitless. 

I was excited for Dark Souls 3, but now after playing Bloodborne, I'm not really all that excited anymore. In fact I hope Bloodborne takes the flag ship spot that Dark Souls currently holds.

Anyone else in the same boat as myself? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> New Player, safe starting stats? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-09-12 11:11:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Is it usually a safe bet to soft cap (I assume 25 is soft cap) both Vitality and Endurance right out of the gate?

I'm planning to go strength character, I assume I then soft cap Strength? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Steven Seagal: Lawman. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-09-08 10:13:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Golf Announcer says people around the world want Tiger Woods Balls </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-08-28 21:49:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> One too many dick jokes. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-08-09 23:41:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Guy confronts police officer for sexually harassing him. In a Council Chambers dealing with a totally different issue. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-08-08 02:58:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Crazy Redneck stirred even crazier over incoming storm. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-16 07:03:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
