<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject4399</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-11-23 05:43:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Me too.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-11-23 01:25:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> ohhh ok. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-11-23 01:16:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> you mean deathchat? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-11-23 01:11:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> burn it with fire. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-11-23 01:10:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I dont understand. arent keys earned by winning matches? how is a person farming keys by being afk? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-11-22 05:26:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Most likely from far away.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-11-22 05:24:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Lol. Good one.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-11-21 17:28:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Why would treyarch even have it as an option? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-11-20 05:18:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Of course not. Gamers don't run.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-11-20 05:17:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> My character started dancing all of a sudden like those destiny people. Weird.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-11-20 05:06:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I wish my character could tell my teammates " stop fucking camping and get out there soldier! " </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-11-20 05:05:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah, i agree. I have an old nextel phone and i dropped it ONCE and now the PTT don't work. Now, I don't know where my homies at.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-11-20 05:04:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You cant. Gotta run thru every gun and attachment to find it.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-11-20 05:02:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah man. My game was smooth before the patch, now all of a sudden, it crashes every round. Absurd.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-11-20 05:01:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> None. We paid money for new ones. If you want nostalgia, i suggest you play the older cods. I'm personally tired of paying for newer cods only for them to keep remaking older ones.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-11-20 01:49:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Nerf isis.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-11-18 17:10:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Anytime.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-11-18 17:04:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Because, thing a ling a ling. School bell ring. Knife and fork a fight for dumpling.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-11-18 17:02:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Why would i wanna get u banned? I could care less about isis or terrorist in general or jesus or any other shitty gods for that matter. You can have anything as an emblem but u will get banned for texts like the N word, or  nude emblems. 
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-11-18 16:11:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You wont get banned. Rock that shit hard. No one will ever get banned for representing ANYTHING. People will only get banned for nudity, profanity or racial slurs like the N word.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-11-18 05:57:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Buy bucket.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-11-18 05:10:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Look at gameplays from youtube and determine yourself. Everybodys experience is different.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-11-16 18:18:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Or woman... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Choose your specialist combo. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-11-16 06:19:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If you had a chance to rearrange the specialist combo to make a new specialist character to work as 1, what would you rearrange and name it? I would take ruins overdrive ability with spectres ripper...running superfast slicing   dicing ?  I'd call him bladerunner.  Why the fuck not? Lol would be cool. What what you choose? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-11-16 06:06:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Blindeye maybe?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-11-16 04:42:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I hear you man, happens to me all the time. They definitely need to address this issue.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-11-15 23:04:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I play dom solo everyday. never have problems. I always get my streaks too. https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=menaSNcY6PM </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-11-15 19:25:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Return black ops 3 N play fall out 4.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Lingering red dots </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-11-15 19:24:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Anybody else notice that after you kill an enemy,  their red dot on the map lingers after they die? It makes me think i forgot someone else and when i turn around to go check, enemy from infront me kills me. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-11-14 18:13:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You're lucky i have a penis or else i probably couldve been.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-11-14 07:44:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Probably, but i don't. ;) don't play HC then.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-11-14 07:40:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Wow bro. You get bombing runs in black ops? Is that an easter egg? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-11-14 07:38:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That emblem tho.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-11-14 01:50:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Ill be one of your 5 friends. Send request. Psn is in flair.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-11-14 01:49:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Ill be one of your 5 friends. Send request. Psn is in flair.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-11-13 20:05:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Tdm. 75 score limit. Run with a full party. U will win everytime.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-11-13 17:41:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> No. Just my legs.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-11-13 08:39:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Probably my legs. Yep, my legs.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-11-12 23:27:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This is how i gain tons of XP while getting streaks faster on hardpoint or dom.  Throphy system to block names, ante up perk , combat focus to gain double xp, uav and counter uav with the wraith or raps. I get usually around 15k XP. Per match.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-11-12 23:22:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Launcher - ghost while camping.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-11-12 22:55:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Burn them all with fire.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-11-12 22:52:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Ive gotten about 3 epics, 4 legendary and about 7 rares. All from Commons.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-11-12 22:50:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> For them not to die instantly running past your hive pods, they must be jerks.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-11-12 22:48:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> My heart.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-11-12 22:46:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Dont worry about those guys. Those guys are jerks.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-11-12 21:20:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Time to kamehameha. Its refers to an abilty when goku ( a saiyan ) from planet vageta is at the mercy of usally ( freiza ) an known villain from planet freiza. He uses this ability to vanquish freiza.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-11-12 08:45:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> There is a way. Turn off the game. BOOM! You won't get burned.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-11-12 08:11:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I know what i can do, that wasnt my question.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-11-12 07:33:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Let it download. Close app after. Restart. Wait for main screen to change version number then u should be good to go   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Can we get a PS4DVR site where we can upload clips like the xbox one? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-11-12 07:04:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I know the xboxdvr isnt affiliated with Microsoft. Can someone make one? :) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-11-12 06:29:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Whats your address, ill bring some for you.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-11-12 02:48:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Dont.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-11-12 01:48:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Soulja...yuh jus affi pay ah little more fi di internet.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-11-12 01:24:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Damn? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-11-11 23:22:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Oh darn. No wonder im always lagging.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What happened to nuketown247? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-11-11 23:11:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I was off when the game came out and i played for a while and i loved the nuketown247 playlist. I havent played during my work week and now that im off, the playlist disappeared,  where'd it go? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> I use to fap from various porn sites. Now I only use r/gonewild. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-11-11 08:49:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Beta Version vs. Released Version ....My 2 cents. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-11-09 10:58:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> In my honest opinion, when I played the beta version, I had more fun than playing the released version. I'm not arguing that the version we have now isn't great, I'm saying the beta version was greater. They nerfed hellstorm and made it harder to get. I was getting trips and quads with that monster in the beta. At that time I was thinking, Wow they finally made the hellstorm more viable than bo2's version, then people that got killed by it, told treyarch it needed a nerf, not to mention up'd the score required to obtain it. Now, at most I get 2 kills from it  (if I'm lucky). Secondly, People that died by rejack, cried to treyarch and THAT got nerfed, now nomad is rendered useless, ( hive is still great, but people don't seem to wanna touch nomad). I used rejacked and still end up dying, No biggie, BECAUSE it can be countered by shooting the fucking smoke, but now that's gone. I mean, I remember Vahn said it wasn't suppose to keep your streaks anyways, So I guess it is what it is. Sparrow   gravity spikes are OP as fuck, I die from them all the time, but I don't care. why hasn't people cried about those? I use sparrow AND grav spikes all the time depending on game modes. I also, dislike the fact that they removed the holographic screen when to go to call in a strike. What I'm trying to say is, The only thing they should've fixed in the beta is the LAG/Connection issues (obviously) And minor Buffs to certain specialists Like the kinetic Armour (I know Active camo got a buff too). As far as the guns are concerned, They all seemed great, Nothing needed to be nerfed, not even the M8A7. You could've chosen ANY gun in the beta and do excellent.  Did you guy's had more fun in the beta or a better time with the current version? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Shoot first   die is BACK! @treyarch </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-11-08 08:23:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Seeing a lot of posts about this. People are reporting, including myself that we are loosing gunfights that we SHOULD'VE won. People are blaming their internet, some are blaming lag, i'm blaming broken camera angles. This isn't news. Broken camera angles has been there since bo2. Bdobbins spoke about this, they're videos about it on youtube and even thunder spoke about in his bo2 vids as well as his LATEST VID. You see the guy first, You shoot, You get instamelted and you're left scratching your head, thinking WTF just happened? when you look at the killcam, it shows the guy saw you first and your gun wasn't even up yet, right? Treyarch needs to address this issue. it's forcing people to play campy in a corner aiming down sight at a door. I read a post earlier of a guy posting about it and is ready to delete the game. It's not about getting better at the game that some people suggest, its the game itself that needs to be better. This problem has been around for a long time now and treyarch KNOWS about it. Have you guys encountered this? What do you guys do to counter this? Do you guys get pissed off when this happens to you? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Sneaky Sneaky Treyarch. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-11-08 06:13:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Sorry if the title seemed a bit clickbaitish, I couldn't think of a better one. Anyway, Before the bo3 beta, i posted some camo suggestions, it was alittle more than 2 months ago, which can be found here https://www.reddit.com/r/blackops3/comments/3gud2s/camo_suggestions/  ...Look at #5 in particular about the " kill counter " part. Now, I MAY be wrong because I haven't checked it yet...BUT, if you go check out the 2nd PRESTIGE for your weapon...it shows " Kill counter ". Hmm, Maybe i'm way ahead of my self. I'm not positive if its for matches only or just in overall in general ( which i assume ), But i'm glad they implemented this. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Crazy clip. Ruin on fire while using gravity spikes. Skip to 0:56 </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-11-08 01:03:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Ps4 - server queue. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-11-07 19:40:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> PS4 - How to install Nuk3town   Giant maps IF you preordered and don't see it. Ps store - library - BO3 - add-ons. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-11-06 08:20:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> This is for those of you that are curious about the patch 1.02 size. Its 2.6 gb. Ps4 </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-11-04 05:31:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Prestige 9 </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-11-04 04:09:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Nov 6th 12:01 am. Are you ready? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-10-31 17:35:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hello,  PS4 north america east coast ( NY ) player here, anxiously awaiting the drop of the game with only a few days to go, im off Thursday/friday....which means as soon as the game becomes available,  i'm hopping in straight to a domination match. If anyone else plays MP first, feel free to add me (ps4) [punannymagnet] during this week and we will party up on release and lay the smack down on MP. Hoping to meet some new awesome reddit players.Thanks for reading this post. Heres alittle something from beta.  https://youtu.be/Wp16FtUr6dY </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What if time travel exists in the future and people are traveling back and giving themselves winning lotto numbers and these are the same people that are winning the powerballs (currently). </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-10-25 16:36:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> it's definitely something I'D do. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Heatwave specialist ability. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-10-10 05:09:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I just seen gameplay of this abilty in use. Weird though, it says its stuns them for a few seconds , but to ME...it looks like ...wait for it....lag switch? ...lol it looked like everyone is frozen for a breif second then the player shits on everyone affected by the ability. THEY TOOK LAG SWITCHING AND TURNED IT INTO A SPECIALIST ABILITY. i'm gonna have fun with this ability. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Rejack. The new tac insert? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-10-09 06:28:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Okay, so since rejack doesn't longer keep you on your streak, what is the point of it still being in the game at all? I just read the the charlie intel " patch notes " from treyarch and they mentioned von said it wasnt even suppose to keep you on your streak. Okay, you run rejack, player kills you, they get rewarded with the kill, you rejack...loose your streak, rise up...player kills u again...gets rewarded again? I'm sorry, but i'm a bit confused as to what rejack was even suppose to do in the first place. It sounded like treyarch wanted to bring back the tac insert under a new name, because that's BASICALLY what rejack is now. I thought they would've decreased your scorestreak by half of what you had, which wouldve made more sense and rejack would still remain as viable. No one will use rejack now. Its now a useless ability. However, i could only think of one reason why i might run rejack,  nuclear medal. Getting that medal/playercard once and never using it again. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> I dont see the battlefront beta on the psn. Where can i find it? Help. [Ps4] </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-10-08 18:19:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Husbands of reddit, what is one thing your wife use to do that made you furious instantly BEFORE you married her and talked to her about it, but continues to do it AFTER you married her, but then just brush it off? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-10-06 06:05:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Since no one is gonna say anything..... </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-10-04 03:35:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I don't really like how the streaks and equipments are outlined in white. it looks weird. does anyone else have a problem with this? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Open World Mode </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-09-30 03:59:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Okay, Before people start down voting, here me out. I like zombies as much as the next guy. it's definitely a good alternative from multiplayer. But, as awesome as zombies is, on the next treyarch release, would you guys want another zombie mode or something new and fresh? I feel like after a while, zombies......(don't kill me) ...MIGHT...get boring? Zombies has been in WAW, BO1, bo2, and now bo3. Not sure if there will be a BO4 in cod2018, BUT lets stay they start a new series, wouldn't you wanna see something new besides zombies, i mean...keep zombies..its a fan favorite, but something else new to the table...who says it only has to be 4 MP maps each dlc? who says it has to be MP, CAMPAIGN, zombies/choas/surivival only? (i know aw had exo co-op as well). I feel like treyarch knows tons of people like zombies and will milk this to the very end. (i'm sure they will). You might want to ask me, well do i have any ideas for another mode besides zombies? I think I do. Why not have an open world mode? Where plays can meet and do various activities, mini missions,carnival games and unlock achievements/trophy's...i would love to use SPARROW and shoot some targets (archery)...and it'll take place in whatever country or city the CAMPAIGN is based in. bo3 example/ we can choose a specialist character and use our specialist abilities in the open world and fuck with people, i guess you might say kind of like GTA...but a mini version thats based in whatever city or country the story mode is based in. I strongly believe that the current gen consoles will be able to handle it. it's just an idea and i think we need to use the current gen consoles to it's full potential. introducing something FRESH to future cods. What do you guys think? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The number of redlight i hit is directly proportional to how bad i have to pee. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-09-27 21:02:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The fastest way to reach prestige master in black ops 3. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-09-26 19:31:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I was thinking about it and i thought to myself, how can i reach master prestige super fast? Well, this is how. Play moshpit. Moshpit has a combination of different game modes that earns for basicially everything. For example, itl put me in a killconfirmed match, which..without knowing ill probably earn xp for challenges , guns, camo. Same thing when it throws me in a domination match the next game, ill earn all those challenges for dom, hardpoint, uplink, tdm....without even realizing it. Now, before i enter mostpit, ill go in with overkill, 2 primaries, completely naked. No  perks or attachments. From what i know, you earn camos by playing without perks or attachments and using 2 primary at the same time makes these camo challenges quicker, plus u earn xp for those challenges as well.  I think that might be the fastest way to reach prestige master. Also, make use of these methods during double xp whenever available. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Stackable Killstreaks </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-09-25 05:47:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hello everyone. I know when myself, as well as other's are laying the smackdown on the emeny team, they earn their killstreaks. Sometimes, as they're in the momentum, they don't get a chance to use their streaks , the game overides killstreaks as you earn them. Now, i can see how this is fair, because if a guy can manage to earn his streaks ONCE, for example, reaper - ac130 - osprey gunner.....he can just sit in an isolated area the entire match as his streaks gets him his streaks again because of stacking. HOWEVER, to counter this, why not add a PERK to stack streaks, but throw it in a tier with ghosts or where it would seem impossible to get without "needing" certain other perks to obtain, if you catch my drift. Or consider adding stackable streaks as a specialist ability on future DLC specialist characters, in the same way combat focus ability adds extra points when you get kills/use streaks to earn extra points with kills. Only reason i thought about this is because, I usually backpack my teammates but sometimes its never enough, because as good as i am , time limit runs out and i loose a match because i needed like 3 more kills to get the WIN. If my first or second streaks were stacked, i couldve easily whip out my "wraith" and laid the smackdown for the W. You know how it is, when you're backpacking your team and you're waiting for your next set of streaks to get that few extra kills to carry your team but impossible because either time runs out, enemy gets there first ....if only your streaks stacked. Its just a thought guys. What do you think? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> If 2 indentical twin males sleep with a woman around the same time and she got knocked up, i wonder who the father would be because dna would prove both men are 99.9% </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-09-23 06:24:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Bad Boys 3 </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-09-16 01:35:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> does anyone have any idea when or if badboys 3 will be released? the franchise is awesome and i know lots of people enjoyed BB1 AND BB2. matrin and will make a great team and together, theyre hilarious. i know people are anxiously awaiting info for BB3. but i must ask, if they know their movies have done good in the past and they know people are awaiting BB3, why take so many years for BB3?  maybe there is an issue with the actors not getting paid what they want? i cant picture BB3 with anyone else besides martin and will. I feel like if they ever make BB3, jason statham will be in it. that dude is in all the good action movies. will, martin, jason statham, chow yun-fat, jet li would make an awesome BB3. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What if the most profound showerthought is in the mind of that iranian man, but he hasnt taken a shower in over 60 years. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-09-09 20:51:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> 07 camry stalls at idle. When rpm drops while making turns or i come to a complete stop, car shuts off. What could it be? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-09-08 17:05:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Redditor's of NY, will you be attending the labor day parade by eastern pkwy today? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-09-07 17:27:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Big up guyana. West indian labor day parade. 

http://imgur.com/a/yR6mi </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> I pee in the middle of the water in the toilet to assert my dominance at home. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-09-05 15:39:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Wealthy men are more likely to cheat on their partner than poor men, but the opposite is true for women. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-09-03 01:12:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> where do i post if i have a mens health question? its in particular to my penis. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-08-31 16:18:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> If someone asks me who will i be voting for, i can reply DEEZ NUTS without looking like an asshole. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-08-27 20:53:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> If you're thinking someday that someone might end up sleeping with your wife, don't worry, at some point in your life you'll be in a position where someones wife will want to sleep with you. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-08-27 05:58:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> if the next president is white , That means the entire country went black and successfully went back. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-08-25 22:51:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Offline Paintjobs feature </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-08-25 22:16:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> i've been thinking since we already have the beta downloaded, we can still access the paintjob option...wouldnt it be nice if we can still use paintjob and customize our guns and have it save offline, so when the game is released, itl be patched in and we'll be able to use them in game? I've spent more time on paintjob than i did playing the beta. In addition to this, when the game is released in November, will you guys be using paintjob MORE, or worrying about prestiging faster? Keep in mind that von said that theyre not fans of adding more prestiges. which means we have 1 year to reach prestige 10. but he also said that, theres something new coming to the prestige options, meaning theres a new way to leveling up more even after reaching master prestige. i'm guessing that has to do with Leveling up the specialist characters. but all that aside, I personally will hit the paintjob first and try to make something for all my guns before even touching multiplayer because, ive spent significant time on mutiplayer already and i know dilly YO...on which classes and specialists are OP, plus i know the spawns and the 4 maps that ive played on. the only new thing is, more maps but ive got 12 months for that. so yeah, i'll be spending more time in paintjob than playing mutilplayer on release. what are you guys gonna spend time doing on launch? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> People of reddit, what are some ways to utilize your phone to make some extra cash? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-08-25 17:03:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Are their apps u can download and watch a few vids and earn money? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> There are 2 kinds of people, those who who like to go out and party and those who like to stay home and both side thinks the other is a loser. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-08-23 01:45:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Netflix   Chill users of reddit, how old is your baby now? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-08-21 19:49:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Youre granted 5 mins of unrestricted internet in north korea. How do you utilize this? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-08-21 17:50:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [Nsfw] what was the lamest pick up line anyone ever used on you then got into your pants? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-08-21 17:00:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Guyana paintshop. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-08-21 05:15:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Searching for games..bo3beta </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-08-20 03:37:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Ugh. Its been an hour now. Still no games found. Wtf is the point. ..ugh. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Bought mw3 on release, Not a YTer , Finally got my first moab about 9months ago. was so happy, forgot to call it in, But i guess it wouldnt have mattered anyway. 720p. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-08-16 20:46:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> If people could read minds, and two people were reading each other's minds, wouldn't they just be reading their own minds? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-08-16 13:40:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Camo suggestions </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-08-13 14:35:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> if you had the option to choose camos, what would they be called and looked like?

mine are:

1. sapphire - similar to the diamond camo but with sapphire gemstones.

2. Matrix - animated matrix camo. i shouldn't have to explain this one, you all know what i mean here. 

3. Fireworks - Animated ( self explanatory ).

4. Night sky - Animated ...that displays how the stars look at night, that includes quasars, galaxies, shooting stars....ect. 

5. skull   Bones - Skull   bones design that looks really nice, but the best part of this camo would include your " kill " count , so that you wouldnt have to constantly pull up the scoreboard to check your kills. starts from the beginning of the match til the end. hence why its called skull   bones. ( death ).

6. Weaponized115 ( i know its coming back ) - but not just in green, but in like blue, red, hot pink, gold, purple...you get the idea.


what did you guys think of my camo ideas? submit your own. thanks. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [Serious] would they assign me a probation officer? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-08-09 21:09:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I might be getting 5yrs probation for refusing a breathalyzer test. would this mean i will be assigned a probation officer? or that means if i get ANY trouble with the law/violations..[whatever]....whilst still on probation that i will get arrested and sent to jail. i live in NY. i know for paroles, they are assigned a parole officer and they check-in every week or so. but i am uncertain about this probation situation. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Who do you think would play the ultimate batman? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-08-08 15:10:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Val kylmer was good. christian bale was good. michael keaton was ok , geroge clooney was ok... im not sure about ben affleck, but i think the role should've gone to either between, brad pitt or matt damon.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Shottas 3 </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-08-03 13:59:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> " shottas 2 " look ...meh. They should make a shottas 3 which stars movado and vybz kartel (look alike) leading up to kartels real arrest. about  the gaza vs gully war. whichever movie studio brings out that movie, They wil gross over a billion. any thoughts or insights? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> a man walks into a bar. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-17 17:47:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> a man walks into a bar and notices a sign on the wall from the owner that says " if you can make my horse laugh, you will get a free beer. the man asks the bartender to take him to the horse. a minute later the comes out and you could hear the horse laughing. the bartender asks the man " how did you make the horse laugh? " , the man replies " thats a secret. the man drinks his free beer and left. the next day, the same man walks into the bar and sees a different sign that says " if you can make my horse cry, you get a free drink ". the man accepted the challenge and went into the back where the horse was. a min later, the man came out and the bartender was surprised to hear the horse cry. as the bartender gives the man his free drink, curious and frustrated , he asks the man " you got to tell me how you did it, youve got to tell me how you made the horse laugh and now, cry ". the man replies " yesterday i told the horse my penis was bigger than his and today i showed him ". </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [POLL] After bo3, what would you want to see from IW next year? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-17 17:07:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> If you were given the choice to name your own elite variants for 3 guns , what would you name them? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-16 16:23:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> For me, i would choose:

Bal27 - Annihilator 

HBRa3 - H1N1

ASM1 - Six Feet Under </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> I wonder if anyone knows THAT ONE WEIRD TRICK TO GROW their PENIS BY 3 INCHES? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-14 13:24:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Question about servers bo3/cod </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-13 17:17:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I had a thought, i've always wondered why players from xbox and psn never meet up in the same game lobbies. Please don't bash me for asking this, As i don't know how any of this system works. From what i initially figured, [EXAMPLE] ..I thought xbox and ps worked as an ISP. LETS SAY , xbox is timewarner and PS is verizon...(isp)...they're both going to connect to the internet eventually. just different way of connection. but there is only one game/server that it connects to. so lets say bo3 or any cod for that matter...why arent both consoles meeting up in lobbies " treyarchs/activision/bo3 servers?" or im guessing itl be a system overload and activision has their own seperate game servers for xbox / psn users ALONE to handle the capacity of players? do you guys understand what im trying to ask? can someone with more knowledge of this please elaborate on this more. EXPLAIN LIKE IM FIVE. thanks. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The hype train. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-13 13:07:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Why do the people who constantly bash call of duty , is the same ones on the hype train every year.  You cod fanboys are nuts. As much as i am anticipating the release of black ops 3, i am on the hype bicycle. This way , my feelings arent hurt when the game disappoints me. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [BO3] - [NOSTALGIA - MAP PACK DLC] OR AS [Micro-DLC] </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-12 16:41:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> In the form of micro transaction, [excluding the 4 dlc]. Nostalgia map pack would include re-mastered maps from bo1-bo2 (not re-imagined like studio from bo2 as firing range from bo1). As a way to keep things fresh between DLC's. 
MY FAVS:

BO2:
- RAID
- SLUMS
- STANDOFF
- GRIND
- HIJACKED
- VERTIGO

BO1:
- Firing Range
- Summit
- jungle
- havana
- villa
- wmd
- NUKE (MOTHER FUCKING) TOWN

13 MAPS (MY PERSONAL PREFERENCE ABOVE) [OR 14] AS NOSTALGIA DLC $14.99 ( SEPARATE FROM SEASON PASS DLC'S )

2ND OPTION ( MANY WOULD PREFER )

EACH MAP [AS MICRO DLC ] $1.99 OR $2.99 EACH.


*** what do you guys think? would you want this? ** </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> ELI5: why do fat people have smaller penises? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-09 21:01:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> A Guyanese, Trinidadian   Jamaican </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-09 15:00:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> A Guyanese, Trinidadian   Jamaican went into the desert to look for hidden treasures. The guyanese brought food incase he got hungry. The jamaican brought water incase he got thirsty. The trinidadian brought a car door. The guyanese and jamaican were confused as to why this trini brought a car door and asked for an explanation. The trini replies " when i feel hot, i'm going to wind the window down ".  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> 2 Blonds go hiking </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-09 14:49:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> 2 Blonds go hiking. Knee deep in jungle, one blond says she has to take a shit, but forgot to walk with toilet paper. The other blond says, do you have a dollar? " yes " says the first blond. well use the dollar then, says the second blond. a few minutes later, the first blond comes out from a shurg of bush with shit all over her hands was well as her clothes. What happened, says the second blond? i thought you had a dollar to use? of course, says the other blond, but how was i suppose to use 3 quarters, 2 dimes and a nickel to wipe my ass without getting shit everywhere?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Fox should re-new MARRIED WITH CHILDREN. That show was the best show of the 90's and 100x times funnier than simpsons and family guy put together. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-09 13:55:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Fun Multilayer map idea " Flawless ". </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-09 13:21:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> When i use to watch chrissmoove back in the days, in one of his commentary, he had an idea for a map. he called it " Flawless ". when the game starts, (TDM/KC) , your team and the enemy team are facing each other, as soon as the timer counts down, START SPRAYING YOUR GUN LIKE A MOFO! trying not to die. Just to see who would go flawless. That sounds like a great idea for a map, because when the map comes up in rotation, you get nervous and anxious to be the one running to hide as quick as possible to avoid being killed to end up going flawless. of course, IF you die in the starting point, you wont respawn right there, you would respawn in the back/side of the map where most of your teammates are at just as regular modes. what do you guys think? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Do you ever wish you had a second chance to meet someone for the first time? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-09 03:28:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Medal idea/suggestion </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-06 23:06:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Im a big fans of medals. Sometimes when im bored , i check out my stats/medals just to see how many times ive earned a bloodthirsty or merciless medal. Ive seen challenge bonus for " top of the leaderboard 5-10 times " but i havent yet seen any medal give for being on top the leaderboard for any game modes. It would be cool to see how many times ive placed ontop the leaderboard. Basicially representing " most kills ". Dont you guys think that would be a cool idea? Everytime you get ontop the leaderboard, you get a medal representing it? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> JUST IMAGINE! [A NEW BREED OF COD] @TREYARCH @SHGAMES @InfinityWard </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-06 14:15:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Okay, I know this topic/suggestion has been talked about or mentioned already, but it didn't go anywhere.

What if all 3 studios (IW,TREYARCH   SH GAMES) worked on 1 cod, and have it be released every 3 years, instead of every year?

When a cod is released, its usually unfinished and it always hyped up to make sales quota and then 6 months into the life cycle of the game, its quickly forgotten by the " community " because the " new " COD info is being released/leaked and then, people get on THAT hype train. when the news of the new cod is released , the " community " starts to focus more on the new cods info. Then, when that game is released, its the same thing over and over. " they should've brought this back, this shouldve left this out, we wanted that gun/scorestreak/perk to return. a whole bunch of shit. but , what if....

what if all 3 studios worked on 1 cod. and they all work specifically on their strong points to make 1 exceptionally great cod that WOULD/WILL last for 3 years.

- IW is known for their excellent hit detection and sound mechanics, as well as killstreaks/maps/guns.

-treyarch is known for ZOMBIES, color details, maps, perks/guns.

- sh games is known for CO-OP, game modes, supplydrops, customizations, UI.

* movement mechanics should stay classic.

if all 3 studios worked on 1 cod, but specifically within their strong suites only, we wouldn't be complaining all the time. also, the game will constantly get patched/bug fixes and best of all, hackers wouldn't be all over that shit after 6 months. i say, season pass should be around $110 which should include 1 gun from previous cod, 1 re-mastered map, ( remains same, not re-visioned ), 5 new maps, 1 zombie map (total 6 maps) ( each studio get to design 2 maps). 

i think this idea will keep cod on the charts. i think people will get back into cod more. some people like treyarch more, and wouldnt purchase a iw or sh cod, and vice versa. if all 3studios worked on 1 game. people wouldnt hesitate to make a preorder.

what do you guys think?
[serious] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Lost connection to server/host. Cant find matches. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-05 04:23:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Ever since psn was down yesterday, ive managed to dl the dlc3 and im trying to look for games now and i cant seem to find a match or any match for that matter in regular playlists. It takes forever to find a match and when i think ive finally found one, i get an error. Lost connection to server/host. And im put back in a lobby continuously looking for a match. My connection is top notch. Now it says " communication to activision servers has been interrupted. Ugh. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> When psn suddenly goes offline for whatever reason or even xbox as well, so game companies get mad or reimbursed somehow because people arent playing/connecting to their games, such as gtav or cod/battlefield? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-03 21:21:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Do gaming companies *** </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Mutiplayer Maps [suggestion for bo3] </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-03 14:05:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> One thing i hated about all cod was being forced to play on maps i didnt like. I wish they would implement something like " map filters " giving us an option to choose which maps we want to show up. If they had this in Bo2. I wouldve definitely deselected DRONE AND OVERFLOW. i understand an option like this might have an impact on lobby match making as it would probably take longer depending if SBMM is as it is in Aw. HOWEVER, i don't think it might be an issue considering everyone knows all the bad/ugly maps and wouldn't vote for them anyway. SO, lobbies with all the great maps would show up all the time and wouldn't take long to find. do you guys think this is good idea? i know some of you will say " it will get boring after a while playing the same maps over and over ". no, if the game ships with about 12-13-14 maps, only about 2 maps at most PROBABLY wont be good. that leaves about 10 maps that will come up in rotation. i loved playing mw3, it was where i first started, if i had map filters, i'd play on dome, hardhat, mission, baakara, arkaden, seatown, village AND resistance, all day everyday. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [PS4][NA][AW] GOUNDWAR! lets go! </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-02 15:55:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> HEY, looking for some new friends to play some groundwar with, possibly with mics. i play everyday, but the time varies. i'm an OK player with a mic. i play groundwar becauses its fast paced and theres always someone to shoot every second. if you're interested, please send a friend request to "punannymagnet"   be sure to let me know you're from reddit. thanks for checking out the post. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> How is vybz kartel still making new music while in jail And is he ever going to be released from jail? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-29 17:29:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
