<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject3805</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-01-16 17:55:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> My life is a tragic comedy! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-01-16 06:40:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> My jimmies have indeed been rustled over your memory. I'm sorry for your loss. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-01-16 06:38:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I believe that you need to fix your formatting. Other than that, how creepy! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-01-16 06:37:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> When asked with the question, "Who ya gonna call", I would say "the ghostbusters".

You need to hire some new ghosthunters, or maybe bring in a priest. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-01-16 04:09:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> OMG NO DON'T WORRY NOT YET </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-01-15 22:15:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hey, Brewster is my friend!

Oh, and don't worry, I noticed that too. All will be explained. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-01-15 22:14:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> B-more reppin'! I'd hate to think that there's more of him. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-01-15 22:14:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Fruit...so nutritious and delicious...yet so evil. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-01-15 22:13:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Enjoy your years of therapy! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-01-15 22:13:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hey, he's my heterosexual life partner, so obviously he's a likeable bro (even if he tends to do stupid things sometimes...) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-01-15 22:12:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If we survive maybe we'll have our own TV show! Called "Creepy Capers" or something... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-01-15 22:12:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That's exactly why I asked her! But you'll find out why, and it's a very stupid reason. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-01-15 04:02:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I like to keep things exciting...

Just kidding, I didn't ask for any of this. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-01-15 04:01:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> thank </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-01-15 04:01:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Who's Ben? What's his story? I apologize if my own life experience if similar to his- Satan works in mysterious ways! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Yo, dude, do you have an adopted sister? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-01-15 00:25:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [Part 1](http://www.reddit.com/r/nosleep/comments/16edec/yo_dude_do_you_own_a_dog/)

*Frederick here. Wow! I really appreciate all of your guys support! I also really appreciate how many idiots there are on Reddit. Regardless, I figured that I owed you all more information. I realized in my last post that I threw you into the story a little late. Sorry about that. Luckily, Ive had another chance to write down some more background info. Once again, I apologize for any semantic errors.*


My name is Frederick Ellison. I was named after the great black abolitionist, orator, and thinker Frederick Douglass. I guess my mom expected another great black thinker, but all she got was a really nerdy, skinny kid who keeps solid grades and shares a love affair with Pokmon.


I had a pretty normal childhood, or so I thought. You know how you think somethings normal until someone else tells you differently? Well, I thought that everyone woke up in the middle of a cornfield on Friday nights, or sleepwalked to the basement door every Tuesday night at approximately 2:47am. Even when I would stay over at Brewsters house, despite the absence of a basement I would walk downstairs and just stare at a wall. Brewster found me once and took a few photos before making me a sandwich in an attempt to wake me up. Dont ask me how that wouldve helped.


Occasionally I would wake up and find humanoid shadows at the foot of my bed, staring at me with white pinprick eyes. I also happened to have a chronic bedwetting problem. No coloration.


These episodes stopped once I reached 14 and dropped religion, but the one constant that stayed was Brewster. Brewster Wellington III Sr. has been my friend since we accidentally exchanged saliva by teething on the same binky. We played sports together; I did his homework for him in French class; he punched a guy in the face for me. The correct term for our friendship is heterosexual life partners.


Consequently, it was Brewster who sent my current situation to shit.

____________
Yo, dude, garage sales! Brewster exclaimed, eyes wide at the number of garage sales in the small neighborhood. Ive heard that this street has some pretty sick deals.


If you say so


We puttered around a local Baltimore neighborhood in his souped-up Jetta. Despite Brewster having enough money to feed a small 3rd world country, he still pimped his ride like white trash a loud exhaust pipe, tinted windows, etcetera. I slumped low in my seat as Brewster turned up the volume on a piece of dubstep that couldve been mistaken for a dial tone.


I poked my head up to spy a neat-looking garage sale off to the right. Hey, Brewster, that one


NO, THIS ONE! Brewster screamed, jerking the wheel to the left. The car swerved into the driveway of an older brick house, and as I braced myself on the car door I noticed that there was only one table out in the open garage. The house looked empty, lights off and overgrown weeds choking the doorstep.


Brewster, theres one table and no ones there, I muttered.


It was calling to me, dude. He jumped out of the car. Come on! Well score some sweet deals.


I got out of the car just as Brewster was checking around the house and calling if anyone was home. He spotted me and came running with a huge grin, holding up an old Pokmon Blue game. Check it out, dude! Majorly old-school Pokmon game!


Whered you get that from?


The table!


I looked to the table in the open garage. It was completely empty. That Pokmon game must have been the only thing there, which was bizarre on its own level. I frowned at the empty table, noticing the strangeness of the situation. Brewster seemed to catch my uncertainty.


Hey, dude, you dont need to hang around, he said. You can wait in the car if you want and Ill just put the game back. This is weird.


I shrugged and got back in the car; Brewster returned a few minutes later and quickly pulled the car out of the driveway. We headed for my house for a night of watching reality TV, but as we drove closer and closer to my house I noticed Brewster beginning to perspire.


I furrowed my brow. You okay?


Just as we were about to pull into my driveway, Brewster gripped the wheel tighter and stared ahead. Uh, dude? He paused. I have a confession to make.


I quirked my eyebrow at him.


Uh, you know that Pokmon game that we just looked at?


*Yes*


WelluhI took it.


I turned to him as he pulled into my driveway. You stole it?


He parked and pulled the game out of his pocket. It looked so cool and no one was there and, I mean, you love Pokmon too!


Sure, but I dont steal shit!


His face fell. I just thought itd be cool.


I looked away. Whatever. Im not playing the game.


A few hours later I was playing the game, noticing the increasingly strange phenomenon not characteristic to Pokmon. All of the NPCs had blood spurting from their eyes and most of my Pokmon automatically named themselves DEATH or BEWARE. The main character was a girl, and her name was always Mildred.


You chose a weird-ass game to steal, I muttered to Brewster, but then noticed that he wasnt sitting next to me anymore.


I looked up to see him staring out the window. Yo, dudedo you have a dog?


Thats when shit hit the proverbial fan.

______________
As soon as the Naked Gray Thing ran away from the back door and Brewster stopped pissing himself with fear, we both looked at each other and screamed. We hit high octaves in horror.


*WHAT DO WE DO*? he shrieked.


I dont know. Calm down. I grabbed his shoulders. My mom keeps a shotgun in her closet. Grab that and come back downstairs.


He bit his lip, resembling a massive infant for a split second before running upstairs. I heard his footsteps banging above my head before they stopped abruptly. It didnt sound like he stopped to open the closet it was as if he was startled by something and froze in fear.


Brewster? I called hesitantly.


Uhdude? His voice was high with fear. Do you have an adopted Asian sister?


I frowned in confusion before busting it up the stairs, bursting into my moms room to see Brewster frozen in the middle of the room, staring out the window. My moms room has a small balcony, and on the balcony stood a small, thin Asian girl. She was about our age with straight black hair and a face that couldve killed someone. Her downy brows sharpened low over her dark eyes in a mask of rage. For some bizarre reason, she was holding a pineapple under her arm.


I stared at her for a moment. How could she have accessed the balcony? This was all too much to take in at once.


Are you lost? I shouted at her. Why do you have a pineapple?


She continued to stare.


And then she took a step forward.


Im not sure if it was her furious expression, the fact that a strange girl just appeared on my moms balcony, or the fact that a weird naked gray thing had just attacked us, but Brewster and I both rushed into the closet and jammed ourselves inside. I grabbed the shotgun wedged in the back and cocked it, aiming it at the closed doors of the closet.


Im scared, Brewster whimpered.


Shut up, I muttered. Its just a girl. With a pineapple.


I cracked the closet an inch to look outside.


Looking into the space was the girl.


My heart stopped and I fired the gun wildly, the base slamming into my shoulder as bullets riddled the room and smoke filled the air. Brewster screamed and jumped on me in fear, knocking the gun away. As the smoke cleared, the girl still stood before us, unharmed. She merely dropped the pineapple on the floor between us. We silenced immediately as her furious expression changed into a deep frown.


All right, you idiots, she said. Youre in trouble. Cut up this pineapple for me and well talk.


Oh, and the name is Mildred.


[Part 3](http://www.reddit.com/r/nosleep/comments/16uaoe/yo_dude_were_gonna_die/) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-01-12 14:22:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I AM SO VERY CONFUSED </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-01-12 07:10:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Oh, now that's not a very nice thing to say to someone who's being hunted down by an evil naked dog-man. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-01-12 06:40:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> http://www.youtube.com/watch?v=I8YQ6yI936A </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-01-12 06:24:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> WHAT? There are other people with this problem!?

Is there anyway I can get in contact with her?

...to ask her how she managed to afford 2 whole chickens a day!? Gosh, rich people and their money... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-01-12 06:21:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Well, I must lend my support to a fellow Baltimoron. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-01-12 06:19:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Oh, don't worry, that will be explained in the next part I write...if I ever get to...DUN DUN DUN

But seriously if I do survive I will upload. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-01-12 06:12:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'LL GET THE BLOWTORCH </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-01-12 06:12:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> My mom recently bought a mega pack of beef jerky from Sam's Club... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-01-12 06:11:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thank you! For my own sanity, I do like to have some humor, but hopefully I'll get a better balance going! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-01-12 06:08:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Har har! Baltimore: The City that Bleeds.

Sorry, I'm sure that didn't help you out at all. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-01-12 05:19:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Unfortunately, Baltimore has one of the highest murder and drug violence rates in the US, and that's what I was referring to. Now, if I lived in Baltimore county, they *might* have looked into it, but frankly my call was probably sandwiched between a murder and an accidental shooting. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-01-12 05:17:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Charm City! Why would you want to move, hon? Just kidding. You should probably watch out- I'm sure it was lurking around the houses for awhile. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-01-12 00:02:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Haha, sorry about the title! But thanks for following my story. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-01-11 23:42:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yes! Most definitely. This is just the first part of my story, it happened awhile go. I just wanted to set up the scene. You know, make it all pretty and whatnot. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-01-11 23:34:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Brewster still thinks it's a dog. Obviously, this is incorrect.

We actually managed to get in contact with 911 and reported it. Baltimore City does have better issues to deal with than a dog man hybrid, though. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-01-11 22:01:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thank you! I will most definitely be writing something else, that is, if I don't die anytime soon. Har har!

...I should probably take a break from the computer. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Yo, dude, do you own a dog? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-01-11 21:51:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Part 1


[Part 2](http://redd.it/16kxtb)


[Part 3](http://redd.it/16uaoe)


[Part 4](http://redd.it/1753qa)


[Part 5](http://redd.it/17gl5w)


[Part 6 (The End)](http://redd.it/17tobn)

*Hey, everyone. You can call me Frederick.*


*You know when you hear a word and then it follows you everywhere? Well, I picked up something paranormal one day and thats exactly what happened. Its a little more complicated than that, but Im trying to write a good story here, so bear with me. Or bare with me, if youre feeling frisky. Har har. I try to keep it light and lively even when Im being hunted down.*


*Now, Im not the best writer ever, Im actually more of a fanfiction guy (NOT lemon). Feel free to give me some tips, but lets be real here: Im dealing with the embodiment of pure evil and I dont have time to check my metaphors. Sorry about that. Maybe if I survive and dont come out of this completely bonkers, Ill review and revise. But, Im digressing. My story starts with my best friend, Brewster.*

_


 Yo, dude, Brewster said, looking out the glass doors at the back of my kitchen. He pushed back his baseball cap and scratched his head. Do you own a dog?


I looked up from my Pokmon game, frowning. It was about 2am and the neighborhood was quiet as death, but leave it to Brewster to find my empty backyard more interesting than a haunted Pokmon game. He was a textbook jock; a distressingly tan lax bro with muscles the size of Texas and a brain the size of a tube of chapstick. Somehow, we were friends. I paused the game to grab a fistful of popcorn. Hell no, my moms allergic. Its probably a stray.


It looks really sick, dude. Its creeping me out.


Just close the blinds.


I dont want to, he whined.


Jesus, we just found a Pokmon game where blood spurts out of characters eyes. You see strays every day!


I dont know, now its like foaming at the mouth He cringed. *Ughh*.


I rolled up from the couch, grumbling as I dropped the Pokmon game and walked up behind Brewster. He seemed terrified for someone who could probably snap any dog in half. Look, you moron, the I stopped as I looked out the door and into the darkness of my backyard, lit by a few garden lamps.


That was definitely not a dog.


That was definitely a naked gray bald man crouched in my backyard, drooling and staring at us.


My face screwed up in confusion. Again, leave it to Brewster to think that some poor homeless man was a dog. Aw, crap. Im calling the cops. Thats not a dog, thats a homeless guy. And hes probably mentally ill, its not his fault.


But he growled at me!


I was already dialing the Baltimore City Police Department, ready to explain that there was some naked guy in my backyard at 2am. The dispatcher clicked on the line.


*Baltimore City Police Department, state your emergency*, a calm female voice answered.


Good evening, uh, I live at 126 Woodbird Drive. I looked back to the glass doors; the homeless man was still firmly rooted on my property. Um, there appears to be a naked man in my backyard.


Static suddenly crackled to life in the background. *Could you give me your address, please*?


Frowning, I gave her my address again and waited for her to respond. Silence; except for static and an occasional pop. I thought that I had lost the call but there was still no dial tone.


Hello? Mam? HELLO, MAM? I shouted into the phone. THERE IS A NAKED PERSON IN MY YARD.


*Where are you going*?


What?


A loud pop echoed on the phone before the same tone repeated itself:
*Where are you going*?


Mam, are you on drugs? I asked, that being the only plausible explanation at the time.


*Come back*.


excuse me?


*Come back*.


Suddenly, out of nowhere, the thick smell of rotting meat clogged the air. Both Brewster and I gagged; he stuffed his sleeve over his nose and looked back at me fearfully. Why does it smell like hamburgers?


Hell if I know!


His voice turned fearful. Its the dog!


Brewster, *shut up*!


I turned my attention back to the phone, but the woman continued to repeat the same phrase over and over again.


*Come back*.


*Come back*.


*Come back*.


Can you connect me to the Baltimore county office? I asked politely.


The women was about to respond when Brewster let loose a high-pitched shriek; I whipped around to see the homeless mans face pressed against the glass door, snarling. I gaped at the visage and my eyes bugged. My mind struggled to process the face. That was definitely not a naked homeless man.


The thing had hollow, black eyes and a canine snout; its curled lips revealed dozens of stained fangs. A few gossamer hairs grew on its emaciated head; the rest of the body gray and taut, the spine stuck out on its back. At this point Brewster crumpled up on the ground, sobbing and repeatedly screaming MOMMM, as the thing brought a huge, bloodied claw up to the door.


I dropped the phone, the womans voice now only reduced to something that sounded like Latin, or Japanese, Im not really sure. The phone clattered on the counter as the Naked Gray Thing and I stared at one another, I shocked and horrified, it evidently enjoying scaring the crap out of two pathetic boys. After what seemed like hours, the things face crept into a huge grin and it paused to rasp two single words. Although the glass door muffled the sound, I heard the two words as clearly as if they were whispered in my ear:


*Frederick Ellison*.


Brewster stopped screaming and jerked back to look at me in horror as the thing shot off back into the darkness. I swallowed.


*Oh, shit.*


That was my name.

[Part 2](http://www.reddit.com/r/nosleep/comments/16kxtb/yo_dude_do_you_have_an_adopted_sister/)

__


*Okay, so maybe I use too many semicolons. So sue me.
Looking back, though, I suppose I threw you into the story too late. I got a little ahead of myself. Im sorry, obviously my jimmies are slightly rustled. Let me backtrack a little.* </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-01-11 17:33:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Shaun of the Dead! The bar scene.
http://www.youtube.com/watch?v=imsHXpEuxX0 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
