<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject3861</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-18 00:54:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If anything, they need to be calling him out on his BS even more than they already are. It's their job to give the truth, not to shut up to appease the masses. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-18 00:46:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> And with all the attention he's given to trivial personal disputes, it seems he needs to seriously get his priorities straight. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-18 00:39:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> He probably doesn't want to lose their passionate support for him. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-17 23:12:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That's true. I wouldn't want him to have to undergo lysis or anything. That would suck. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> My friend complained to me about how salty I always am. Should I be worried about becoming too hypertonic for my environment and having my cells shrivel up? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-17 21:26:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-17 21:18:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You get your grade marked down for that writing assignment. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-17 21:16:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Very rarely. It's commonly known that heartburn is caused by mini-fires that spontaneously start within your heart. However, fish live underwater, where it is difficult, though not impossible(as well demonstrated by a documentary I watched titled "SpongeBob"), to start a fire. The heartburn needs to be pretty intense, or else it will be quickly put out by the surrounding water.

Edit: SpongeBob fixed, I hope that makes you happy. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> If climate change is real, then why are the old Siberian gulags still ridiculously cold? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-17 02:20:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-17 02:16:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> People like to ask: if god created people, then who created god? The clear answer is dinosaurs. They existed millions of years before Earth, and roamed the universe as all-powerful beings. At some point, they got bored and decided to create god. God created the Earth from there, roughly 10,000 years ago, and the dinosaurs could care less, and have since transcended the physical world, and left behind their bodies on God's newly created planet, which eventually became fossils. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-17 02:11:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Your gravity must just be weaker than that of others around you, so the people who would be attracted to you are instead attracted to others. There is but one factor influencing this; mass. That's the key. The people with greater attractive forces are the ones with the most mass. To increase your attractiveness, you must increase your mass to levels higher than anyone around you. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-17 01:03:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Someone give this man a medal. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-16 21:21:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Nope. Definitely not racist to assume all black people know each other. Not racist at all. /s

Seriously, it was just extremely awkward all around. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-16 21:11:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It was really weird and awkward when Trump asked the reporter to organise the meeting with the CBC for him and assumed they were friends of hers for some reason. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-16 20:43:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It was ridiculous. Fox and friend is, for all intents and purposes, a right wing talk show, not real news. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-16 20:41:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I hope a reporter uses that exact headline he claimed the MSM would be using to describe the press conference. That would be funny. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-16 20:39:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Also, why the hell did he devote so much time to attack Hillary Clinton? You are president of the United States. You are not against Hillary anymore. She shouldn't matter to you anymore. He just can't let go. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-16 20:37:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Well, it's not really hard when you don't actually have to use facts, like at Breitbart. Still, I don't know if he could write well enough, even for them. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-16 20:34:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That was ridiculous. I can't wait to see all the different fact checks come out. I'm glad that one reporter called him out on his "biggest win since Reagan" lie. Well, at least he's taking questions from some less biased news sources now. Baby steps, I guess? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-16 12:37:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's literally almost 4 years out. If the general election polls were mistaken up to the very end, why should we care about a poll this far away from the election, without any campaigning having occurred? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-16 12:20:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah, they really are. But as long as they can yell "voter fraud" as an excuse, they'll be able to get ample support, unfortunately. They're claiming to tackle a problem that barely exists and taking away people's votes in the process. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-16 12:17:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Well this sucks. I'm nervous about these hate groups committing terrorist attacks themselves against Muslim communities, which they would probably justify as a sick form of "retaliation" for terrorist attacks by ISIS.

This is why we can't have nice things. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-16 11:49:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'll have you know that I have met many black atoms who are staunchly pro-matter. Stop perpetuating negative stereotypes. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-16 02:56:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I believe you are mistaken. To my knowledge, the first weeaboo president was Millard Filmore, who loved Japan so much, he sent warships there just to get them to open up their country to the US, and therefore allowing his fellow weeaboos greater access to everything Japanese than ever before. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-16 02:39:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> No, not range voting. That system benefits the candidates that no one has any strong opinion about or has even heard of, because no one knows them well enough to give a good score. Next thing you know, no one's first choice is president.

I much prefer instant runoff. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-16 02:35:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hello Samuel Ronan

As DNC Chair, would you make efforts to reform the Democratic primary system, especially regarding the issue of super delegates? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-15 23:33:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Well, they are usually wearing 3-D contacts, so you just can't tell. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Why do we still rotate with the Earth when we jump? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-15 23:02:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-15 22:57:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The wind is most likely jealous of your epic speedboat because it doesn't have one, so the wind is punching you in the face out of anger. Obviously, it's punches aren't always the strongest, since it's fists are in gaseous form. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-15 22:55:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This is why we need the Black Atoms are Matter movement to protest the unfair treatment of innocent black atoms. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-15 22:53:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> 1 horse, but it has to be alive. If it dies while you are eating it, you gain a fraction of 1 horsepower proportional to the fraction of the horse you ate. In practice, gaining one horse power takes a couple of horses, since they tend to die, and hence lose the remainder of their power, sometime in the middle of your meal. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Can hydroelectric dams produce clean energy if the water is dirty? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-15 22:42:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> I'm chairing a middle school MUN committee soon. Any good tips? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-15 02:42:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So, my high school MUN club organised a small middle school conference every year, and this year they've promoted me to chair since I've tended to perform better than most club members, despite having only been to 4 conferences (3 of which I won an award). I know the procedure and everything, but what are some tips on being as good a chair as possible? Keep in mind that the committee will be small and it's on globalisation. This will be many of the delegates' first conference. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-15 02:36:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Totally depends on the conference, and I've never been to that one, so I wouldn't know. Quite a few I have been to accepted late papers with no problem. A couple others were not so lenient. I'd try to get in contact with whoever you were supposed to turn it on to, and see if you can still submit it. It's worth a try. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-15 02:33:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Is anyone going to FIMUN at FIU this March? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-15 02:30:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Pfft, yeah right. Climate change isn't real. Because. It's cold. Where I am. At this particular moment. That's how this works, right?

More seriously, this really sucks. We can't afford to keep abusing fossil fuels in a way that heats the atmosphere. Soon enough, it will be too late to turn back, and that's not something anyone should be ok with. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-15 02:26:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm sorry to break it to him, but peace isn't happening without the two state solution. I don't think he understands how difficult this whole Israel-Palestine thing is. Saying you support peace but not the two state solution is just empty words. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-15 02:20:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Now, if only his problems weren't so god awful, this would be a good thing. Also, his approval rating is bad right now, and the cherry picking on specific attributes by the examiner is pretty bad reporting. 

http://www.gallup.com/poll/203198/presidential-approval-ratings-donald-trump.aspx </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-15 02:11:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Perhaps, but my thoughts are that they potentially could have begun making regular contact with native groups to make them exact tribute, which they already did with other small Asian states. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-15 02:09:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> In my honest opinion, she ought to resign. That just wasn't acceptable behaviour for a White House official. Sadly, I doubt anything that drastic will happen, and if anything, it just made Trump like her more. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What if Gran Colombia and La Plata had both stayed united </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-14 21:06:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So, if the Latin American countries of the time never fragmented into the countries we know today, how would it have effected the state of Latin America, and the world? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-14 20:39:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> All of Latin America split from Spain, and then a bunch of other smaller countries split from those countries. La Plata split into Argentina, Uruguay, Bolivia, and Paraguay. Gran Colombia split into Colombia, Venezuela, and Ecuador, and Panama split from Colombia later on. There have been quite a lot, that's just one example. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-14 12:23:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Well, I'd say he's probably the most controversial of the past century. 

http://www.gallup.com/poll/116677/presidential-approval-ratings-gallup-historical-statistics-trends.aspx

Presidential approval ratings are generally quite high towards the start of one's term, while Trump's is not.

http://www.cnn.com/2017/02/13/politics/donald-trump-approval-poll-low-gallup/

Of course the civil war being a thing kind of prevents him from being the most controversial ever, but you later specify post-Civil War. 1876 was also a big one, since the electoral vs popular vote totals were pretty mismatched and the issues surrounding the end of the Reconstruction. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-14 03:11:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Well, I would guess that if the American Revolution never happened, the colonists  would end up in a situation similar to Canada, with devolved autonomy by the mid 1800s. They might have even been incorporated into the same entity as the dominion of Canada, and the Eastern US and Canada fully independent as one country after WWII. Probably the Northwest as well, since Britain would likely still have been interested in that territory, and taken them easily without serious competition. Mexico might still have the SW US, assuming no conflict analogous to the Mexican-American War happened. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What if the Ming dynasty had discovered America </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-14 03:03:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Around the time of the Ming, they were sending around massive fleets at far as East Africa to exact tribute. So what if they would have looked to the east and found America before Columbus? Would it be feasible? How would that turn out? Would they establish colonies like Europe, or default to their historical tendencies to establish vassals/ tributary states? If they did establish colonies, how would they respond to dynastic changes, particularly the fall of the Ming? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-14 02:48:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Heh. I found that joke particularly funny, being from Florida.

To answer your question, the Normans of Northern France are different because they actually come from Scandinavian descent. The Vikings began raiding the area around 800 CE. In 911 CE, the Franks agreed to recognise the Dutchy of Normandy, lead by Rollo. Over time, the Scandinavians who lived there sort of integrated into the French population. As far as surnames go, having a Norman one as opposed to a French one means it probably come more from Scandinavia. Hope that helps. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> How did the Mongol empire maintain its massive size? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-14 02:34:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Besides the Mongols, it seems every other empire in the times when horseback was the quickest form of communication, that basically every other empire reached a limit and were unable to expand beyond, due to the hassle of keeping together such far flung territories. 

Yet the Mongols took most of Asia before splitting into fragments. The effect was delayed, and they somehow managed to keep them long enough to conquer the continent. I've heard a few explanations for this. The Mongols were incredible in the art of intimidation, so their ruthlessness might have deterred potential rebellions. I've also heard about the role their religious tolerance and general acceptance of other cultures(except Chinese culture) sort of kept it together. Yet it seems like both of those could apply to others. Many other central Asian empires were about as ruthless, and the Achaemenids were renowned for their religious tolerance and effective bureaucracy, something the Mongols, to my knowledge, were totally lacking in. 

So, what made Mongolia the exception as opposed to other groups with similar characteristics and/or superior governing structures? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
