<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject9504</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2009-09-20 01:26:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> the shade cast by trees, etc was/were bottomless canyons...the car had to keep up enough speed when on non-shaded pavement to jump over the canyons. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2009-09-09 20:50:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Take a deep breath.  You'll be fine. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2009-09-09 16:11:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You sound like you did [here](http://www.reddit.com/user/KellanStec) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2009-09-09 15:26:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> "Hi, I'm a bitter atheist and nothing upsets me more than some stupid bible-thumper.  So, since your thoughts are obviously MY business, I will post (and/or upvote) this totally hilarious pic.  I can barely stop LOLing long enough to submit this!  SHIT this is funny.  PEOPLE ARE GOING TO FUCKING LOVE THIS.  I am finally someone!"

Thats you.  Thats what you sound like. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2009-09-07 13:15:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I am an American....and I couldn't agree more...I want to UPvote the fuck out of this link... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2009-09-07 03:31:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Shit....I just read that it later became Ubuntu and was once called Lindows. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2009-09-07 03:30:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Linspire, anyone remember Linspire?  It was my first taste of what I believe was Linux, designed to look like Windows. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The reason there are so many Christians in the world... </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2009-09-05 02:13:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> God.

What did you expect to find?  Now, lets get this party started..... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2009-09-05 02:10:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Well played indeed...a formidable opponent.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2009-09-04 17:55:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Even with the psychological background tests and extensive application process its impossible to weed out all of the dangerous douchebags.  This officer needs to be an ex-officer ASAP..as does everyone involved..doctors, judge, magistrate...whoever... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2009-09-04 17:52:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I think you should upvote, upvote, upvote.  Maybe that isnt happening..everyone has to do their part.  I am not atheist, but I enjoy information...and some of the atheist posts are fascinating....and when they are, I upvote.  I know that sounds simple, but if you want it on the front vote it up.... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2009-09-03 01:16:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Ok, sorry to cut you short here just when you were getting your full wood on, but I have to call it quits.  I have been honest and open.  You have been a hypocrite from the get-go and continue to do so with your continuing flame war/trolling (which you accused me of).  

Jesus Christ I thought my beliefs were unreasonable.

Go ahead and respond, but be sure to use spell check AND have an adult look over your work.  I wont be reading your next post, but everyone else will.

Good day to you sir/madam.
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2009-09-03 01:05:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Wow.  Either you dont get it (which is a good possibility considering your spelling and grammar) or you refuse to get it.  Either of which is fine with me.  I will spend the rest of my time checking back and pointing  out your errors.

How could I (or anyone else) be expected to take your posts seriously when you dont know the difference between your and you're.

Holy shit there is no God.

Wait...wait.....wait....

JUST KIDDING!!!!...douchebag...

I am anxiously awaiting your barely legible response.  I printed out your last one and let my 4-year-old correct it with a red crayon.

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2009-09-02 20:56:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> ...not as long as I dont force these beliefs on others...and I agree that it doesnt add up.  It doesnt have to add up.

Nothing has changed here today.  I havent changed my beliefs and neither you yours.  I stand by everything I have said, as I am sure do you.  This thread seems spent...what a let down.

 



 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2009-09-02 20:09:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yes and no.  Its more complicated than that.  Of course I would fear the eminent judgment of God, but I dont have to fear it....because I already know that I am forgiven.

Your scenario doesnt work either...'hurt someone' is too general.  'Paid my debt to society' implies that I broke some sort of law.  Did I call someone a dick eater or did i punch someone in the mouth or did i murder someone?

If you are trying to pick apart my beliefs you are wasting your time.  I will be the first to tell you that my beliefs are not reasonable.  How can you pick apart a statement that I would defend with 'it just is.'  It cant be done.  

Notice a reversal of roles here.  I am not trying to convince you that your beliefs are wrong.  You can believe what you want as far as I am concerned.  I am the one forced to defend my beliefs......



 

  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2009-09-02 19:49:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Do you really have to ask that?...oh..and I will concede that you are right that I posted in /r/atheist.  I actually just responded to the post when it was on the front page and it didnt occur to me where it was located (stupid, I know).  I would not have knowingly trespassed....but now that I have, I am somewhat disappointed by the impression that a representative of a group who claims to be peaceful and easygoing has left on me....you are no different from those who you consider your polar opposite.

Anyway, to answer your question in the simplest way possible, I always ask for forgiveness when I do something that I feel goes against what I have been taught.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2009-09-02 19:25:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Also, I dont think the statement 'atheists are uniformily hated and dispised in every community' is correct at all' (and not just because uniformily and dispised are misspelled).  There are some hardcore, extremists who hate you, but the majority of Christians (at least the ones who I know) are like the majority of atheists: just want to be left alone.  I will use myself as an example.  I live a happy life and do whatever the fuck I want (I inserted the fuck in there as proof).  I am currently living in sin with a beautiful girl who is 4 years younger than me and I probably wont marry her.  I think being a Christian is what lets me do these things.  I dont have to be perfect.  I can fuck upand believe me, I fuck up.  The only difference is..and this is the part you hate for some reason, I ask forgiveness when I fuck up and I believe that some higher power grants me this forgiveness.  I dont push this on you and  I dont judge anyoneever.  I have gay friends.  I also have atheist friends, with whom I have had some awesome and fun conversations about our beliefs.  They didnt take it personally and neither should you.unless youre just one of those people who take everything personally (and it sounds like you are), in which case  you mention dicks so often that you must have one in your mouth.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2009-09-02 18:58:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> wow...great example of the understanding that atheists constantly whine for.  As far as not having 'this sort of community,' you are probably singled out, not because you are atheist, but because you are a douchebag, lol. 

I hope your day gets better.  I am going to wish like hell for heaven to be this 'candyland' that you speak of.  I've always had a sweet tooth! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2009-09-02 17:17:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Wow, 'eat dicks in hell' LOL.  What a let-down.  I expect so much more from someone who I presume is an intelligent member of the atheist community and the reddit community.  Please try again, but with more effort this time.  I will check back shortly.  
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2009-09-02 15:45:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Christian here....and I have noticed that reddit is like THE feel-good place for atheists to come out of the closet and get a nice pat on the back and some hot chocolate.

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2009-09-01 21:26:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> ..says the guy with 1" of viewable browser screen   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2009-08-29 17:33:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> that was awesome....without hesitation...the mustache...and Harvey wasnt surprised at all... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2009-08-29 17:25:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Wow...you should report immediately to the nearest payday loan store and prepare for a lifetime of being taken advantage of.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> REALLY reddit?....REALLY? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2009-08-29 17:14:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2009-08-29 17:08:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> She holds this kid to a higher standard because he is a 2nd-year law student....and he walks in and acts like he's totally ignorant to the entire legal process.  I dont even think she lost her temper.  She spoke to him appropriately according to the severity of his offense.  She was rightly appalled at his audacity. In a real court, where presumably this man hopes to practice one day, he would have easily been in contempt.  Its common sense, although you wouldnt know it from reading the comments here, that inside a courtroom the judge is God.  What he says goes.  If anyone thinks any different then you are in for a rude awakening one day.  I have been in court more times than I can count; you are expected to act and dress appropriately, with the utmost respect ever for the legal institution, whether you like it or not.  Judge Milan was right and the man was lucky that his only punishment was public humiliation. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2009-08-29 16:58:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> ..just watched it again and I keep thinking she is going to say "you do not sit here and say 'thats your opinion' like a BITCH...." </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2009-08-29 16:47:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> How embarrassing.  I am assuming that this disrespectful douche went back home and immediately dropped out of law school.  How could you show your face in class..to your professors, after publicly wiping your ass with the legal institution? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> attention reddit Atheists.... </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2009-08-28 23:31:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> ..please stop blubbering everytime someone mentions something that remotely sounds like Christianity or religion or Jesus.  Its totally ok, you may continue to believe what you want.  No one is going to take that away from you.  You're totally coming off as someone who feels as if they are barely holding on by a thread.  Its as if you have to snuff out all these tiny fires so that you dont involuntarily get sucked into the next doomsday cult.  The truth is, you are like gays and every other group who thinks they are special* - no one gives a shit about you or what you believe...oh, and no one is going to strap you to a table and shove a bible down your throat.  Use your free will and get on with your lives...enjoy yourselves...its ok.. 

*i omitted Christians because they rarely make the front page bitching about how the 'big bad atheists' are coming after them, although they arent excluded from groups who think they're special - they arent...and no one gives shit </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2009-08-28 23:16:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I dont buy into that for a second.  A book of words has never made me do anything.  There are too many sheeple running around out there waiting to be told what to do.  These people made the decision to let another human being die.  Maybe they were delusional and thought their particular book of words would save them, but they were obviously stupid or wrong or both.  The religion doesnt have the ability do anything.  

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2009-08-28 23:04:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Ultimately these people made the final decision to let this other person die.  A book of words has never made me kill anyone.  In the end its up to you, as a person with the abilityto kill or not kill, to exercise some common sense.  Please dont tell me that this isnt blatantly obvious. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2009-08-28 21:41:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> title should read 17-year-old killed by idiots.  Personifying religion so that you can further the atheist agenda is ridiculous.  Guns dont kill people.  Pills dont kill people.  Dumptrucks do not kill people.  People kill people.

Oh...and I do consider myself a Christian.  I try to go to Church every Sunday, but usually only make it in once per month.  I believe in God and Heaven.  

There are extremes on both sides....and extremes do not play well together.  I am just a regular guy who saw a blatant attempt ro skew the facts.  Thanks for your time. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The New GoDaddy Interface is SLOW and Just Plain Old Ridiculous...just saying </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2009-08-26 18:10:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2009-08-22 18:29:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I am a dog lover, but Spencer was obviously an awesome cat.  I am sorry for your loss. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2009-08-22 02:45:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Speaking of anal sex...I'm gay and I love to....fuck queers!
(I am not really gay...but its cool because my boyfriend is) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2009-08-14 21:37:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Afghanistan - We Make Sex Offenders.  Got a database just dieing to be filled up with sex offenders?  Here, have some of ours.

I gurarentee every one of those motherfuckers...on whatever board comes up with these backward-ass laws had a giant hardon when signing this into law.

"hmmmmm what else can we make them do?"

"we make them pole-strip and gangbang at age 15'

"fuck that, make it age 5"

"I like de way you think my afgan brother"

  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2009-08-09 20:58:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I am seriously fucking surprised that the insurance companies havent drummed up some bullshit reason to sue these 800 doctors, nurses, etc.

We should all Google Bomb 'piece of shit' to return the names of insurance companies.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2009-07-31 06:43:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Wow, the same pic I saw last month and the month before that and then twice in May and then in April...etc...........how many times has this made the front page?                                                           </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2009-07-27 01:50:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> un-fucking-believable.  I have never witnessed such pussism in my life.  You wouldn't have to worry about being traumatized by combat violence, because you would never make it home.  Here's what I recommend:  Tell your doctor what a pussy you are.  Get him to prescribe a testosterone supplement for you called Androgel.  Go home.  Strip naked.  Dump the entire contents of the Androgel into a saucepan.  Squat over saucepan, dipping your raisin sack into the gel.  Hold this position for 1 hour.  Repeat daily until you are no longer getting your ass kicked by girls.

You're welcome. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2009-07-23 19:40:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> incidentally, I just happen to have access to 4 live babies if anyone is interested.  Well, one of them is a toddler.  So 3 live babies and a toddler. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2009-07-19 05:58:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Imagine that.....the video has been taken down. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2009-07-18 16:03:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Because some people are actually desperate enough to be fooled into PAYING for info at EE...when its actually free.  I dont see a place in the world for EE like it is now.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2009-07-18 15:59:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If you are referring to the facts, as creationists see them, then there IS nothing new.  An event occurred long ago. There really are no new facts to 'come up with.' 

I realize that reddit is the main vehicle for your cause, and there would be no 'in your face!!' without it, but even the front page of the Scientology site changes from time to time.  You (and I dont mean you specifically) post the same 4-5 links/comics/whatever over and over as if you've discovered something new (and other atheists, I presume, upvote just for the in your face factor.  I am nearly certain that I can hear you screaming 'EUREKA' and IN YOUR FACE JESUS! from here.

It seems that atheism is the one constant rerun here, and while I have enjoyed the 4 atheism-related posts (for their humor and scientific value) I think the reddit community deserves something new.  

Diluting the front page of reddit with the same links over and over seems a little desperate.
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2009-07-18 14:48:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Whiny creationists have been plastering the front page of reddit with the same 3 pics/comic strips for the past 2000 years?   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2009-07-18 14:20:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> whiny atheist rerun...Dear Whiny Atheists, please come up with something new.  I know you have a chip on your shoulder and something to prove (or disprove), but please stop submitting the same 3 pics/cartoons every couple of months.  This is the internet.  There has to be something else out there. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2009-07-16 02:28:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Wow...a video of a trap reading from a script in an annoying Ron Burgandy voice does not add credibility to the pro atheist cause and is hardly what I would call owned. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2009-07-14 01:38:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If I could get my dick in my mouth I would never leave the house. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2009-07-14 01:35:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> wHAT?  That was some of my best work!  I canNOT believe your sarcasm!  Come ON..an EYE PATCH made of...you-know-what.... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Do I have to make a fake fucking account and upvote the hell out of myself just to get noticed around here? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2009-07-13 05:11:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Anything I post is always front-page worthy, yet I dont have a single comment/upvote/whatever....is there some special suckoff club that I need to join?....cause I'll do it... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2009-07-12 17:09:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Anything you can do?  Sure, shut the hell up and take your medicine.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2009-07-12 05:52:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Am I the only one who thinks 'manhole' is hilarious?   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2009-07-12 02:10:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Apparently they were bought out, but work on the project continued: http://www.nailbat.com/content/view/14/32/

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Does anyone else think that Hotline 1.8.5 was the pre-torrent file-sharing  sh*t?  </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2009-07-12 02:09:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2009-07-11 12:59:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Q: What does Helen Keller think about the the HK Simulator?

A: You would too if your name was ARGHUUUHHHHHUUUHH </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2009-07-04 06:33:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thank God.  Christians believe that without God, there would be no surgeon to operate, no craftsmen, engineers, etc to design and build tools of the trade, no professors to teach the doctors, etc, etc, etc. ..and they're correct.  With God, all things are possible.

Interesting how non-believers, who constantly complain that Christians dont mind their own business, are so upset over this woman thinking God.  I have read many posts, from non-believers, about Christians always stepping in uninvited and doing their 'Christian' thing, but here's an example of a non-believer overhearing a woman thinking God and then immediately running to tattle to the reddit communuty. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2009-06-28 13:42:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Its a Festivus MIRACLE! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2009-06-27 17:49:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I had to put my best friend down last summer.  Her name was Bob and she was a 17-year-old black lab..with cancer.  She and I grewup together and she was always there protecting me and just being a friend. I felt like I was tricking her when I asked her if she 'wanted to go for a ride' that day. Once in the vets office, he shaved her wrist, drew up a red liquid into a syringe, and injected it while I held her.  She was very calm except for one instant when she flinched and looked at me.  I continued to stroke her and tell her I loved her until she was gone.  I didnt think I would cry, but I did.  I carried her through the full waiting room in my arms in her favorite sleeping bag with tears silently streaking down my face.  Once home, I dug a hole in my back yard and buried her there.  There are flowers on her grave. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2009-06-23 17:01:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Future stripper.  I'd hit it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2009-06-11 06:29:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> ...but when I mention this 5 fucking days ago, no one gives a shit!!

http://www.reddit.com/r/reddit.com/comments/8q1gc/anyone_else_agree_that_godaddys_site_is/ </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2009-06-07 14:43:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Laporte didnt 'blow up' as the title incorrectly states.  Arrington is a douche and gets whats coming to him.

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Usually you have to pay extra for that... </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2009-06-07 01:17:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Anyone else agree that GoDaddy's site is specifically designed to 'trick' you into buying crap that you dont want or need? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2009-06-05 14:05:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2009-05-29 14:14:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Oh snap...here's another called The Left Shoe.... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2009-05-29 14:14:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I am sooooo awesome....I just made up another called The Beard.  Its a beard made of..... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Hey Reddit, I just  made up this awesome variation of the Dirty Sanchez.  Its called The Pirate and involves an eyepatch made of...well.....you know... </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2009-05-29 14:13:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2009-05-19 17:50:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> grinds'em    </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> hey reddit, you know what really grinds my gears?  When I click 'next image' and the entire page reloads with a different image instead of just the new image loading.....that grinds my gears </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2009-05-19 17:50:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2009-05-17 15:17:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm going to say Requiem for a Dream meets Center of the World (with peter sarsgaard)meets Wargames meets....tv shows Biggest Loser, not because I am fat though....the title just seems to fit.... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2009-05-17 15:09:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> wait a minute....what? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2009-05-15 00:47:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Fuck you very much. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> I already have unlimited internet, text, and pics on my plan.  Why does Sprint want me to pay $15 per line extra for the 'unlimited package' before I am allowed to upgrade.  Fuck you Sprint. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2009-05-15 00:47:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2009-05-11 16:35:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This is exactly Texas. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2009-05-10 17:01:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I-think.....hes-awesome......because.....his-name....its-the-opposite.....of-Christopher-Reeve    </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2009-05-07 00:44:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Free as in 'here, install our shitware first.'  No thanks.  How did this make it to the front page of reddit??? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> 20090506 Where is ThePirateBay?   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2009-05-06 21:33:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2009-05-01 00:51:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You, good sir, have a point. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Is it just a coincidence that the Prevx website is the first result returned when googling ALL recent crapware infections?...and of course they want you to purchase their software </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2009-04-30 17:33:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Did anyone else ever punch a hole in a floppy disk for the 1541 and use the other side? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2009-04-25 19:23:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2009-04-20 19:55:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> cho </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2009-04-08 03:39:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> what....oh...oh shit....awwwww shit </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> When I was growing up we ate the skin of the baked potatoe, just sayin </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2009-04-08 02:26:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2009-04-06 03:52:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Has anyone mentioned edubuntu?

http://www.edubuntu.com </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> bacon invasion </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2009-01-29 16:12:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2008-09-11 18:19:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> EE Blows.  I hate it when I am Googling a problem and accidentally click on a EE link.... pisses me off. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2008-09-05 15:20:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Awesome commercial.  If you dont get it then you know nothing about Seinfeld.  This is the perfect commercial.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Mummified Deer Pics </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2008-08-25 17:39:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2008-08-24 01:04:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> George Carlin (i think it was him) said, no one ever blames Jesus when they lose.  No one ever says 'we were doing fine until Jesus made me fumble.'  

Thats pretty funny.

But seriously, as a Christian I thank God everyday for everything.  Win.  Lose.  Thank you.  Thank you.  Thank you. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Beautiful Pic of My Best Friend Who Passed Away </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2008-08-04 18:01:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2008-07-30 15:32:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> hes back to continue the saga after a year-long break </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2008-07-22 12:44:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You think you're better than me? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2008-06-27 04:50:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Let me tonight declare in the clearest language and in the loudest voice as an esteemed scholar that I know that the United States government helped orchestrate the events of September 11, 2001 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> VT Professor publically claims Us Gov orchestrated 911 </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2008-06-27 04:50:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2008-01-10 16:57:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> CS Gas is a harmless 'less-lethal' weapon.  Blackwater employees have the right to defend themselves from perceived threats.  All US Servicemen and women have gas masks and they all know what "Gas! Gas! Gas!" means.

Why is this news? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2007-12-20 03:45:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> nice...at least he is honest...I guess </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Hilarious prison personal ad </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2007-12-20 03:45:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2007-12-20 03:28:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So you're a straight guy in prison trying to meet chicks with an online personal ad... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Very Unfortunate Placement of Prison Personal Ad Pic </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2007-12-20 03:28:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2007-11-24 03:04:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> 
Theres this old man who has lived alone in the mountains for years.  Well he gets tired of not getting laid so dusts off his clothes and goes to the nearest bar in the nearest town.  He sits at the bar and the bartender asks, Whatll it be?

The mountain replies, Ill have a bottle of whisky and the best woman youve got!

The bartender says, Well heres your whiskey sir, but um.we dont have any women.

No women? says the man, What the hell do you do for fun?

Well, says the bartender, Weve got that long haired cook in the back.

Oh hell no! says the mountain man I dont go for that shit!

So he takes his bottle and goes back into the mountains.  Time passes.  He decides to give town another try.  So he dusts off his clothes and goes to the nearest bar in the nearest town.

He sits at the bar and the bartender asks, Whatll it be?

The mountain replies, Ill have a bottle of whisky and the best woman youve got!

The bartender says, Well heres your whiskey sir, but um.we still dont have any women.

No women? says the man, What the hell do you do for fun now?

Well, says the bartender, Weve still got that long haired cook in the back.

Oh hell no! says the mountain man I dont go for that shit!

So the mountain man takes his whiskey and goes back into the mountains again.  And time passes.  And the mountain man is lonely.  So he goes back into town to the nearest bar.

He sits at the bar and the bartender asks, Whatll it be?

The mountain replies, Ill have a bottle of whisky and the best woman youve got!

The bartender says, Well heres your whiskey sir, but um.we still dont have any women.

No women? says the man, What the hell do you do for fun around here now?

Well, says the bartender, Weve got that long haired cook in the back.

Oh hell no! says the mountain man I dont go for that shit!

So the mountain man sits at the bar and drinks his whiskey and thinks.  He yells for the bartender to come over.  Yes says the bartender.  Suppose I was to do it with that long-haired cookhow many people would know?

Well says the bartender, About six people.

Holy shit says the mountain man six people, hows that?

Well says the bartender Me and you and him of course..and the three people it takes to hold him down because he dont go for that shit either.









 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2007-11-24 02:52:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> enter a comment here </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2007-09-25 13:52:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> a handfull of sites....thousands of pics </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> collection of indexed pics </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2007-09-25 13:51:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2007-08-29 12:54:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This is the oldest 'Best of' still available.  It is from August 2000 and is haliarious! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2007-08-29 12:54:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This is the oldest 'Best of' still available.  It is from August 2000 and is haliarious! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The very first 'Best of Craigslist' ever - very funny </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2007-08-29 12:52:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2007-05-09 12:05:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> After a long break in Australia...he's back...and promises a saga-post soon!  I thought he was dead. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Firefly is Back </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2007-05-09 12:04:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
