<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject5890</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-11 22:42:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I usually buy ELF blotting sheets but someone told me to just buy white tissue paper from the gift wrap section of the dollar store and cut it up. Is it really the same thing? It won't take off my makeup while blotting?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-11 22:22:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> ELF has one for $1 or $2. I don't wear eyeshadow but I have oily lids and it keeps my mascara from smudging. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-11 15:50:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thanks! Lol, that makes the nickname even better!  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-11 15:45:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I really like this CC cream but it is more full coverage than it sounds like you are looking for. I do set it with a loose powder because the finish is more dewy than I would like. But I like the staying power and the fact that it doesn't feel like a heavy foundation. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-11 15:27:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm new to this sub... Where did "Amnebet" come from?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-10 19:25:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> How many "Being" specials have there been so far? Barb, Butch, the Edwards, Deb, and now Matt. Were there any others?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-09 00:41:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You look just like her! I think you did a great job with the makeup and hair. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-09 00:36:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Audrey from Twin Peaks? :-) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-06 04:33:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> How are you applying your foundation? I used to be a fingers-only applier but after switching to dabbing it on with a damp sponge, my makeup goes on a lot smoother. 

Also, I use twice the amount of moisturizer I would normally use before I do my makeup. So on a non-makeup day, I use 1 pump. On makeup days, I use 2 and let it set while I dry my hair. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-06 04:22:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I use Cerave moisturizing lotion (just the regular formula) and it's pretty lightweight. I have sensitive skin and have not experienced a breakout from it. I like that it dries matte! It doesn't have SPF though but they also have a lotion for AM that has SPF 30. I've never used it though so I can't comment on it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-05 01:33:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That does sound terrifying! I'm definitely going to have to watch some videos before I attempt it. Thank you!  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-05 00:46:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Has anyone used Lash Boost from Rodan   Fields? It's really pricey but the results pictures have me coveting it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-05 00:37:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Darn, I thought I might have that one in my to-be-tried stash but it's the Full Fan Effect one (pink). I use a Shu Uemera curler which I sometimes carefully heat for a few seconds with a hair dryer.

I have been watching videos but I'm kind of overhauling my skincare and foundation/CC cream choices so I tend to get ADD and skip around. I'll definitely have to focus more on mascara videos. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-04 22:19:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thank you. I tried Clump Crusher a few months ago and even though I got the water resistant kind, my lashes drooped the second it went on. I wondered if maybe it wasn't quite as waterproof as other mascaras and that's why they had to call it water resistant?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-04 21:50:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thanks! Could you tell me more about the spoon technique? Do you just push them upwards with the rounded part?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Looking for a dupe of Maybelline One By One mascara </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-04 21:26:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> One By One was my HG mascara until it got discontinued a couple of years ago. I've been jumping around to different Maybelline formulas (this brand works the best for my lashes) but have yet to find a mascara + brush combo that even compares.

I'm looking for a dupe, preferably drugstore brand that has a waterproof version. I have the typical Asian lashes: straight, short, points down, hard to curl, sparse, light, blah. 

Right now I'm using Maybelline Lash Sensational (original pink tube) which is wet and goopy, despite being a few months old, but I can manage it decently by running an old One By One brush through it. I also use the Rocket one because I like that type of brush but I have to use like 5+ coats to get the coverage I want.

Hoping someone has a suggestion for me!  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-03 16:48:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Honestly, they've gotten away from walkers so much this season that it didn't even occur to me that Sasha would turn while in the casket. I knew she'd take the poison but I thought they'd open the casket up, Rick and co would see her dead and get mad, and there'd be fighting. I think I was as surprised as Negan when she popped out all walkerfied. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-03 16:46:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm pretty sure I saw Enid fighting in the battle.

Related question: when did Judith get to Hilltop? I seem to have spaced out and forgotten. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-03 04:52:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> She's fine (and full, lol)! She was on a chain next to the platform that Ezekiel, Rick, and Maggie were standing on at the end.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-06 22:07:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thanks! I figured they were already done since they're all so popular. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-06 21:57:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> These have probably already been done but I would love to take part in novelty socks and Doctor Who (I'm new to the show).

A Whedonverse one should be so shiny!! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Puzzle size for an Amazing Race event </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-02 02:05:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm running a scavenger hunt/Amazing Race type of event soon and I want to include activities for the teams to do so it's not just a foot race. How big of a jigsaw puzzle should I get? The teams will be about 4 adults on each. I'm thinking each activity should take about 10-15 minutes. 100 pieces? 200? Thanks!  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
