<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject2116</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-08 23:38:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's alright, it's a fairly fluid thing. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-08 23:38:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm glad you had fun. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-08 21:16:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> "Anglerfish typically have at least one long filament sprouting from the middle of their heads...This first spine protrudes above the fish's eyes and terminates in an irregular growth of flesh (the esca), and can move in all directions. Anglerfish can wiggle the esca to make it resemble a prey animal, which lures the anglerfish's prey close enough for the anglerfish to devour them whole." </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-08 19:47:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I suppose our son is technically the child of the mother and Alexander. He found her in a bar when her husband was on a business trip, and thought she was perfect for the task. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-08 18:57:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I did meet one once. I didn't like him. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The Anglerfish </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-08 18:22:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I am beautiful in ways men shouldn't be.

Pretty boy, lovely boy, with his flaxen curls framing a sweet face and big blue eyes with big black lashes. My mother, when she was in our run-down trailer and not at the bar, would say such looks were wasted on a boy and that she wished I was born a girl. I'm certain she wished I had never been born at all.

School was hellish from the start. Girls viewed me as a living doll to play dress-up with, and boys hated me because I made them confused. My third grade teacher once made a comment about my cherry red mouth, the gym coach complimented my porcelain skin. The computer teacher got fired after cornering me alone. I did not understand it  I wore run down charity store clothes, spent most of my time with my nose buried in a book, and barely brushed my hair. And yet, here was the whole school bearing down on me.

Puberty made it worse. All my classmates grew and stretched, flushed with hormones and lust. I grew some, yet no straggly hairs or bright red pimples popped on my china doll face. Instead, the star quarterback would torment me so he could grope at my long legs and graceful hips. My teachers would compliment my academic achievements and then mention that someone like me being so aloof was a shame. The theater teacher asked if I was "interested in boys" in hushed, hopeful whispers.

I was not gay or straight. I was Uninterested. Why would I waste time chasing after shallow and petty girls who were jealous of my appearance? Why would I let one of those testosterone-hopped jocks paw at my body and call me a faggot afterwards? Why would I want my fat, balding English teacher to bend me over for an easy A? They called me frigid, uptight, bitchy, rude, prudish. I wore it with pride all the way to the top of my class.

I left my little Midwest town for a college in the big city. I thought it would be easier there, full of beautiful people to blend into. Towards the end of November, my roommate tried to roofie my water bottle, and the double room became a single room very quickly. For sophomore year, I got a studio apartment on my own.

That fall quarter was beautiful, the trees like brilliant fire throughout campus, and I took a communications class required for my major. It was about giving presentations and speeches, and the school website said Professor O'Malley was to teach it  classmates had described him as a jolly old man, a little longwinded but excellent at teaching discourse and rhetoric.

I sat towards the front, my empty notebook neatly dated, and my classmates chattered all around me. I paid them no heed, eyes casted downwards, but I looked up when the door to the lecture hall opened right before class was to begin. The man who strode in was not Professor O'Malley.

He burnt white hot, reality dimming around his gravity. Everyone seemed so tarnished compared to him, dark-haired bronze-skinned Adonis among the gray and listless dead. Square-jawed and towering, his presence was so thick it was sweltering, smothering, suffocating. My classmates all gasped as his eyes swept across the class.

Adonis-among-the-dead stood at the front of the lecture hall and said, "Professor O'Malley had an unfortunate family emergency. I'm Professor Alexander Venus, and I'm taking over the class for the foreseeable future. Apologies to everyone who was hoping for good old John, he'll be back next quarter."

He spoke like rainwater, Adonis-among-the-dead, and no one seemed too broken up about Professor O'Malley being replaced by Professor Venus. His emerald gaze trawled through the suddenly eager students, before finally landing on me, sitting in the corner of the third row. It lingered there on my face, and Venus grinned with perfect teeth. For the first time in my life, my face grew hot.

Professor Venus looked away, then, and the TAs handed out the syllabus as he crooned out the class expectations like love poetry. Despite the crimson flush on my face, I wanted to ace this class like I aced all the others before, a deep-rooted desire to prove myself as more than just pretty flesh and skin. I would not be bested by an unexpected crush.

The first two weeks of class were shockingly normal, just Professor Venus talking about the basics of speaking. He wore designer, tailored clothing and Italian leather shoes, his car a flashy red BMW all the girls wanted inside of. There was no doubt he was a natural at this, his charisma a thing unto itself, and my dreams were plagued with green and bronze and hands and lips.

Two weeks of lecture, and we received our first assignment: an informative speech.

"Make it something you're passionate about," Professor Venus had purred. "Something that really makes your blood pump."

Based on those standards, most of the people in the class would've spoken about Professor Venus himself. A girl had found his Tinder profile and a boy his Grindr account, leading to frantic little pow-wows about what made Venus tick before class started. He didn't respond to either of their half-nude and borderline pornographic messages.

I wrote mine about the Amur leopard, *Panthera pardus orientalis.* There are only around sixty or seventy left in the wilds of southeastern Russian and northeastern China, due to poaching and deforestation. I gave what I thought was an impassioned speech about the dying species, and my peer reviews agreed with that thought. One girl cried over the leopards, but she was a bit sensitive.

Professor Venus just watched from the front, eyes never leaving me even as he took notes with a black fountain pen. While the peer reviews were given back immediately, the professor wouldn't give grades until all the speeches were concluded. I gave mine on the first day, and ended up being the last person in that lecture hall, besides Professor Venus himself.

I was placing my notebook in my bag when Venus stepped up behind me and said, "Dante."

I turned, blinking, and Venus was staring at me with calculation. I had professors and teachers and TAs hot to fuck me before, undressing me with their eyes as they imagined me bent over their desk, but Venus's gaze held none of that. It was simply...assessing.

"You could rule the world if you spoke with a bit more passion, Dante," he continued. He pronounced my name like a Florentine.

"What do you mean, Professor?" I asked. The thought of failure, of not being the best at something, gnawed at me like a hungry dog.

"Exuberance, joy, fascination, anger," Venus said with a laugh. "If you fluttered your eyelashes right, people would rip themselves apart for you."

I thought about his words all weekend, lingered on them as I stared at the shoes at the local department store. I needed nicer dress shoes for an internship interview, but even the discount rack made my bank account cry out. I pondered what luxuries I could give up  heating, warm water, coffee  when the man spoke beside me.

"Trouble picking out shoes?" he asked me. He wore a tailored blazer and had gray in his hair, wealth oozing from his pores. I thought about Professor Venus's words, and did not brush off the man out-of-hand like I would've before.

"No, it's just..." I said, looking at him between my lashes. The man touched the small of my back. "I have an interview for an internship and need new shoes, but..."

"College is so expensive these days," he said. I left that store with practically a new wardrobe, and all I had to do was let the man grunt above me as I laid sprawled on a California king mattress in his mansion. I left before dawn. When I came to class dressed in my new clothes, Professor Venus grinned at me.

I didn't think of it as a con or even prostitution, though people probably feel differently. Women seemed less inclined towards me, so instead I found men, wealthier the better, and let them give me things. In exchange, they'd beg for more of my attention. I didn't really care one way or another about the sex, but the *power* I held over these CEOs and lawyers and stockbrokers was indescribable. They would do anything for me, and I could get anything I wanted with a pout.

It was coming towards the end of the quarter and the long stretch of winter break when Professor Venus approached me again.

"I see that you took my advice to heart," Venus said. I knew he wasn't talking about speeches.

"Yes," I replied, and Venus smiled, fingers trailing across my shoulder.

"There's a bar I want to take you to," he said.

The fallout had we been caught doing this would've been immense; he was still my professor, I was underage. Yet there was no thought of consequences as Venus  *Alexander,* he crooned at me  escorted me into the high class bar on the expensive side of the city without a single person even mentioning my ID. Rules felt like things that happened to other people.

"You're a natural already," Alexander had whispered in my ear. "It's all the pity your father didn't teach you to hunt when you were younger."

"What do you mean?" I asked. I had not met my father. When I asked my mother about him, she spat on the ground.

"I'll show you," Alexander promised, and inclined his head towards a businessman watching us intently from a corner booth. Nice suit, nice watch, and lust in his eyes  exactly the kind I preferred, and it seemed Alexander did to.

Men are easily manipulated by their egos, and suddenly having two beautiful people make a beeline to you is quite the ego stroke indeed. It was easy to have him bring a car around to drive us to his lonely little penthouse, his wandering hands barely knowing who to touch.

It was Alexander who led us into the bedroom, peeled off the man's suit and pushed him on to the bed before stripping us both naked. He spooned up behind the man, arms around his chest and chin on his shoulder, and he said to me, "Watch, Dante."

Then his teeth sunk into the man's jugular.

I always thought that, if faced with a murder, I'd be disgusted and frightened like any human being would, even with my jacked-up sense of empathy. Yet as the blood splattered across me and dripped down Alexander's perfect teeth, I felt strangely...exhilarated. Alive. The blood was warm as it trickled down my pale skin, and my hands reached up to smear it across my white skin.

Alexander pulled out the man's throat with all the grace of a big cat, letting the body flop back down on to the bed. He looked triumphant, my Adonis-among-the-dead, and he pulled me into his arms as the man bled out on to his silk sheets.

"See, lovely?" he purred into my ear. "This is what you're meant to do."

We cleared out the apartment of valuables before we left, laughing and singing as the man's body cooled in the bedroom. That was the first of Alexander's many lessons.

Some of our kind specialize in a single gender, like I do, while others like Alexander can turn the head of anyone they want. None of us stick around longer than a handful of nights  extended exposure can lead to madness, and stalkers are a pain to dispose of. We get what we want and then leave with a kiss. How we propagate ourselves is simple.

Brood parasitism is a strategy where an animal, such as a cuckoo, tricks another into raising their offspring. It's easy to slip inside a stable little nest with a few kind words to an overworked and ignored wife, and leave all the hard work to her husband until the son starts coming into his abilities. Then we come back and take him to where he belongs.

I guess something went wrong with me, and that's why my father never came back for me. My mother must've hated me for being a constant reminder of her failed marriage. I wasn't taught to hunt in my adolescence, not allowed to bloom like Alexander did under his father's tutelage.

Alexander isn't going to let that happen to our son. He's five years old now, with dark curls and big green eyes, and I have his room painted and ready. He's currently with his mother and her husband out in some suburb, and whenever we drive by, we hear yelling. A teacher had recently been fired from his brand new elementary school. Clearly, she can't protect him.

We're coming for him tomorrow night. Our family is going to be complete. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
