<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject582</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-12-10 07:50:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The bad persistent cough. It can lead to emphysema.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Reefer Madness. Still up there in 2012 </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-12-08 05:32:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-12-06 22:38:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Rudeness </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> TIL Medical marijuana may help people quit tobacco </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-12-06 20:35:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-12-06 03:41:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Best advice yet </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-12-04 15:52:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I loled </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> UPS Reports Troubling Drop In Residents Answering Doors In Lingerie </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-12-04 02:32:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> "SANDY SPRINGS, GAIn what delivery personnel are calling an alarming nationwide trend, customers who answer the door wearing alluring lingerie and little else now account for less than 24 percent of the shipping business, a six-month investigation by UPS officials confirmed Monday. The latest numbers are, frankly, unacceptable, and a far cry from where the industry stood a decade ago, when the observed rate of middle-aged women receiving packages in titillating undergarments soared as high as 60 percent, UPS spokesperson Mark Dickens told reporters. Perhaps more upsetting is the fact that, of those still wearing carelessly fastened negligees or lace garter belts, a mere 12 percent are remarking on how very, very hot it is outside, inviting the deliverymen in for lemonade, and then conspicuously mentioning that their husbands are away at work and wont be back for a long time. This is a problem that must be rectified immediately. Despite the grim outlook for the home delivery service, a recent employee survey conducted by Time Warner Cable found that its repair technicians continued to report a steady bra-and-panties rate of 92 percent." </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-12-03 20:11:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Good luck, and make sure she knows you still love her. :) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-12-03 20:03:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Chances are you're only going to end up with a woman who also smokes. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-12-03 20:00:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I heard some fact that said guys naturally quite often fall for girls who are in relationships, while girls will tend to respect a man's relationship despite her feelings for him. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-12-03 19:58:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Make it clear you don't want to get back together, but tell her that. I think she would at least want to hear that. Maybe wait a few weeks. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-12-03 19:56:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Eyeliner at 12, and I only just started wearing concealer for under my eyes (I'm 18 now). That's it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-12-03 19:53:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm a natural ginger, and I know that I'm not attracted to other gingers or blondes. I can only think of one ginger I'm attracted to at all. All the gingers I know usually don't go for other gingers. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-12-03 19:50:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I would just think you need time before kids come in the picture, and that eventually you might change your mind. I wouldn't be mad, but a lot of women would if you backed out on your word like that. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-12-03 03:26:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> "you should find a way to do that."

That's basically what he's asking. -___- </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-11-30 05:46:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What is it? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-11-30 05:33:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> ^ Pretty much sums it up. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-11-29 21:37:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It takes time; I'm a "lost" freshman too, and I just started being able to narrow down my interests to sociology. Just pick classes that have to do with those areas. You'll know what sparks your mind down the road. :) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-11-29 20:25:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Don't beat around the bush about it, stupid small talk will make her nervous. And don't ask her a lot of other questions, just do it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-11-27 02:47:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That my birth triggered my mother's depression. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-11-26 22:02:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Welcome to America! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-11-26 21:50:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Always for the kief. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-11-26 17:51:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What a life </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-11-26 04:35:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Just dip it like fries and a good old shake! They're both amazing. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-11-26 03:20:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> A jar or pill bottle with a label. I use my prescription ones. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-11-26 03:19:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Cheetos and Raspberry sherbert. Judge me </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-11-26 03:15:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Keef* 

And you just answered your own question; if the keef is tokeable if dried out naturally, then wait a day and then smoke it. Should be fine. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-11-26 03:04:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Mom of the year </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-11-26 02:52:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I got this today too. Dank as hell, just as bad as skunk but different. It was an amazing chill but noticeable amazing. One blunt shared with a friend and I was good for a few hours.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-11-26 02:37:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's definitely your tolerance screwing with you. Give it a break for a few weeks at least. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-11-26 02:25:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Depending on the strain, I would say smoke a lot at one time or, if it's a really potent/good strain, smoke progressively during the day. The first option is always the safer bet. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-11-26 02:03:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Uggs. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-11-02 01:53:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> HAHAHAA I want to do this to someone because it keeps happening to me </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-10-29 00:58:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> 24/7* </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-10-23 02:07:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> not funny guys </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Newsradio 620 WTMJ reporting from scene of Temple Shooting  </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-08-05 20:56:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
