<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject8234</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-04-24 05:37:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> White Collar and House of Cards are probably my favorite shows ever next to sitcoms like Seinfeld and Frasier.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-04-24 05:31:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> My family is addicted to Breaking Bad.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-04-23 22:46:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Cruise- Florida Georgia Line

Ten Thousand Hours/Can't Hold Us- Macklemore

I Just Had Sex- Lonely Island feat. Akon

In Your Pussy- Afroman

One Day- Matisyahu

Charlie Brown- Coldplay

I Will Wait- Mumford and Sons

Anna Sun- Walk the Moon

Save Rock and Roll- Fall Out Boy

Kids- MGMT

We're from Barcelona- I'm from Barcelona

L-O-V-E- Nat King Cole

Mack the Knife- Bobby Darin

New York, New York- Frank Sinatra

My Way- Frank Sinatra 
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-04-22 07:08:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Here's what you'll be causing those who love you. 

I had to endure the suicide of a close family member two years ago. It was easily the most  difficult thing I've ever had to endure. Up until that point, I had contemplated suicide myself. After having someone else close to me do it first, I'm happy I never did. 

When a loved one commits suicide, a couple of things happen. 

First, the immediate shock sent me into a blind rage. My grandfather had shot himself in front of my grandmother, fifteen minutes after I had driven home from school to bring them both lunch. She begged him not to do it. He responded by blowing his brains across the room. 

After the shock subsided, pain set in. Not your average pain. This was different. I walked into the room where he did it and still, to this day, I feel a physical pain in my gut thinking about it. You wonder what you could have done to prevent it.. You ask questions, like why he did it, why didn't he explain, why didn't he let us know he was in pain, and, what now? The pain I endured after his suicide has lasted until today. He died two years ago and the pain is as real as it was then. I don't ever think it will go away. Those questions still persist and probably will still be there until I die. 

Then, during this intense psychological pain, the loved ones have to pick themselves up and pack away your things. This is perhaps the most painful part. The memories were too much for me to handle. It took me about a year to be able to look at his stuff again. Took me a year to visit his grave. 

After this, the family has to go through the funeral. This is another bad part. People send flowers, cards, food- it's all nice, but it doesn't help in the slightest. You put on a good face, tell everyone it's okay, and pretend like the pain is gone when it is really gnawing your soul into oblivion. 

For me, it took a solid year for me to cry about it, and to visit his grave. I look at pictures and still burst into tears, even though its been so long. He was my hero. Perhaps the most knowledgable, most loving and kindhearted man I will ever meet. He will never see my future wife or kids, meet his grandchildren, be able to see me graduate from college.. All because of his decision. I wonder if he would be proud of the path I am taking.. But most of all, I wonder why he killed himself when he was surrounded by people who loved him. 

I don't know you, and I don't know what you're going through. But please, do not commit suicide. You have people who love you. Not only that, but the pain you will cause others is a kind of pain that I have dealt with. It is the most painful experience someone could endure- the worst part is that the pain never leaves. The pain suicide causes is always fresh and ready to bear itself at a whim. 

Life has so much potential. You were put here for a reason. Find that reason and live it. Overcome your problems and show life that you're tougher than what it can throw at you. 

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-04-21 08:09:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Grower here. Good to know! Thought I was the only one who was a grower.. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-04-18 21:39:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Peaches. 

I was allergic as a child and outgrew it. Now I can't get enough of the damn things. Especially those Georgia peaches ;) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-04-18 06:00:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Conan O'Brian had a bit on him the other day, during a celebrity survey session. 

Question was- What is the first thing you look for in a car?

"Actor Steve Buschemi replied, "Eyeball room."" </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-04-18 05:57:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That explosion was unreal. Poor kid. Blew out the windows and their ears. Shitty day if you ask me.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-04-17 14:40:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Season 8 of 24. 

Spoiler Alert: When Renee gets killed, I was devastated. Jack had been after her for so long, and I was hoping that he would finally get her, but in the end, he never does. 

How I Met Your Mother- Pretty much all of the earlier seasons. Hilarious but somehow still somber- I could relate to Ted and his search for love so much. Later seasons haven't been as good but I'm happy with how things are turning out. 

Seinfeld- the Soup Nazi or the Butter Shave. 

Frasier- the entire series was fantastic. The series finale hit me hard.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-04-17 14:30:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Either the Soup Nazi or the Butter Shave for me. 

When Newman saw Kramer as a turkey dinner, I lost it.

Gets me every time.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-04-15 20:31:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm 20, never been in a real relationship. Never been kissed either. 

I've come close to being in relationships.. Seems like I always get the girls who tease but don't want any semblance of a relationship. Oh well. Bitches will be bitches. I'm willing to wait around for a nice girl who isn't going to cause me heartache and needless drama. I might be naive for believing there's such a thing as soul mates- but I do, and until I find mine, I'm willing to wait. 

I'm not too worried about it.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-04-14 01:00:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I've always loved Mjolnir Mix from Halo 3.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-04-12 02:23:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I wish it was socially acceptable to fling poop like monkeys.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-04-11 19:56:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> FUCK
you got me...... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-04-11 19:38:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Fuck.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-04-11 05:55:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Apparently my family comes from a rich history of freemasonry.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-04-11 05:37:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Discovered Redtube. Needless to say I have no soul anymore.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-04-11 05:35:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hoop earrings or girls wearing skate shoes. Dunno which I hate more.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-04-10 06:12:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I think we're missing a lot of possibilities here. I think Moltres wings, with a nice wing sauce over them, and a side of celery and carrots would put Buffalo Wild Wings out of business.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-04-10 06:08:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Fucking Whitney. I'd kill her Miltank in front of her, barbecue that shit up and offer her some.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-04-09 16:08:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Aren't there rumors Hitler sent out subs full of the artwork he stole? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-04-09 05:33:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I've considered this before but have been told it can be construed in ways other than the Indiana Jones look.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-04-09 05:23:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Ladies are people too!

I've noticed a trend in comments about this.. Never liked those kinds of terms anyhow. Glad you noticed! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-04-09 05:16:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It befuddles me how some people do not know how to articulate thoughts and ideas in modern English.. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-04-09 04:53:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I want to know where those sneaky bastards at Roanoke Island went off to..

Oh, and can someone tell me what the actual fuck happened to all that treasure Hitler stole from Europe? Cause if the world could get that back, that'd be great.. Fucking Nazis. Greedy assholes.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-04-09 03:17:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Upvote for being awesome. 

Also, I love the case that comes with them. Makes it easy to keep them untangled but yet still portable. I love mine.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-04-08 23:55:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Personally I've never tried an over the ear earbud that I liked. These X10's are some of the most comfortable I've ever had. I've never experienced any audio issues with them. They have a great response and cancel noise. Amazon usually had them priced anywhere from 90-100$. Well worth the price in my opinion. I'll have to check out your suggestion.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-04-08 22:28:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Probably Monoprice's studio headphones.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-04-08 05:36:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What kind of messed up porn have you been watching? You need some good, old fashioned American girl-on-girl action.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-04-08 05:33:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm not saying I hate anal or anything but she better have that clean enough to eat off of if I'm going anywhere near that  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-04-08 05:03:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Upvote for Seinfeld reference.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-04-07 16:46:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Exactly! 
Being a concert lighting technician, I use gaffers tape everywhere. A buddy I work with even made a wallet out of it. It's amazing.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-04-07 16:13:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I use gaffer's tape for all of my digit-reattaching needs.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-04-07 06:06:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Couldn't post so had to reply.. Sorry about that. 

Lost my grandfather to suicide two years ago. 

Lost my mentor of over ten years to cancer six months ago. 

Lost my uncle to cancer six months ago. 

Haven't told anyone this, but these are slowly eating away at me. I regret things I could've said or done. Every day and every night. It's like a living hell sometimes. Even though its been so long, the pain is like new every day. 

Not to mention, I'm a borderline atheist who comes from a family of staunch, bible thumping Christians called Seventh-Day Adventists. 

Can't tell anyone about any of this.. Mainly because I'm too proud. Glad I have Reddit though. Even if this gets buried in the deepest corners of Reddit, it feels good to talk about it. 

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-04-07 05:50:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> 20 year old virgin here too. 

Dude, don't do it. My grandfather killed himself two years ago. It is hands down the most painful thing I've ever had to go through. I run through the day he killed himself every day in my mind. Had I shown up earlier, I could've stopped him. Had I said something to him, been better to him, maybe it would've changed things.. It hurts so much, even now.  Two years later and it still hurts like it was yesterday. I was suicidal before his suicide- when I realized how much pain it could cause others, particularly my family. In retrospect, I'm glad I didn't. 

I was wrapped around this girls finger once. Slightest hint and I'd be enthralled. She led me on for years. Four to be exact. She destroyed me. That is the lowest I've ever been or ever will go. I finally realized, amidst the heavy rock music and depression, that I was worth more than that. 

Ever since, I've gained confidence in who I am and that slutty, controlling bitch can go fuck herself for all I care. I won't ever let that happen again. 


Long story short, women aren't everything. When you're meant to find a woman, you will buddy. Just gotta wait. Being single is better- no drama, no bullshit, nothing to worry about.  Plus, if you're wrapped around some woman's finger you might miss the one you're meant to find. 

 I know how it is. I've been there.  But you have to remember that there are people who love you and who wouldn't know what to do without you. Suicide is not the answer. If you get close again, make sure to talk to your friends about it. Let them know. See your doctor. You can get out of this. I did. I'm glad I let people in so I could.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-04-04 15:51:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> My buddy was struggling financially so I wired him a bunch of money to help him out. Secretly of course.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-04-03 00:59:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That porn photographer gig sounded promising.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-04-03 00:18:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> There is!

http://www.outblush.com/

Apparently made by the makers of Uncrate.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-04-02 23:53:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> www.uncrate.com is much better  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-04-02 23:48:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Where do I start...
Smoking, have tattoos, incessantly swear, flirt with other guys.

Other things that piss me off: 
Slang. Be classy. Show that you're going to college by speaking/texting intelligently and classily. Don't try to be "cool" and swear all the time and degrade other racial ethnicities/minorities. That's no bueno. 

A side note: have an opinion. Don't be one of those girls who will agree to whatever the guy suggests. Sometimes, we want to do what you like. You incessantly saying "whatever you want/like" isn't helping our cause and is really annoying. 

Also have an opinion on things like politics, religion, world issues. Even if you disagree with the guy, I personally like a girl who has an opinion different than mine and can back it up. Ignorance of these things isn't helping you any. 

Clothing wise, I hate skateboarding shoes/outfits. Also, hipster outfits. You're not impressing anyone. Big hoop earrings are fucking weird. Don't do it. 

Dress to impress. Sweats and no makeup is okay sometimes, but if you're trying to impress a guy, looking like you just rolled out of bed doesn't help your game any. I'm sure you ladies would appreciate a guy dressing nice to impress you- we appreciate the same. 

Oh, and for God's sake, don't freak out if a guy doesn't text back immediately. I've been with women before who incessantly text you, which is nice sometimes, but when you're at work/in class/at home beating the buffalo, it can get tedious. Have enough confidence to wait. Some guys aren't big into texting in the first place.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-04-02 23:33:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Bastille, Bombay Bicycle Club, the National, Arcade Fire, BlondFire, and Priory </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-04-02 21:52:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Regardless of what you may see on Swamp People, everyone in Louisiana does not have a Cajun accent. We have normal, civilized people there. The entire state is not a swamp. We have roads. However, what you see about the cuisine is 99% true. Road kill is okay to eat if you hit it yourself.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-04-02 21:03:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hi Charlie! Love your work. 

What advice would you give to an aspiring writer/journalist? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-04-02 05:56:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Beating the buffalo.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-04-02 05:55:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Napoleon Dynamite. Hands down. Seen it 10+ times and kills me every time.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-03-30 06:09:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Driving down the interstate. Look over, see two hot girls in a Suburban. They look over, smile, and wave. The driver is fully clothed and the passenger is buck ass naked. Looked like she was going to town on herself. 

Needless to say, I wrecked the car out of shock and ended up in months of PT. Just kidding. Almost wrecked though. 

TL;DR- two horny college age girls waved at me, one of them happened to be petting her cat  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-03-28 22:24:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Guy in my Sex Ed class was really innocent. We were discussing how females orgasm and he blurts out, "Girls can cum?!" Mind you, he was two years older than I was at the time. I responded, "Bro, you need to watch more porn."  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-03-27 15:25:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Met this cute girl at school. Told my buddy I was planning on asking her out. Literally fifteen minutes before I planned to do it, he asked her. She ended up going out with him for two years. Made up with the guy but still pisses me off.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-03-26 15:31:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Guy here. 

Had a good friend once tell me that her first lesbian experience was at one of these things. 

Not sure if she was bullshitting or not.. Sounds too good to be true to me  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-03-26 15:14:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Where do I sign up? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-03-25 03:02:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thank you for your discretion in not posting this.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-03-25 02:47:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> 'Murica.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-03-24 17:23:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> My mind=blown.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-03-24 17:21:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Who wants to smell like that when you can smell like grease, sawdust, and bacon? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-03-24 17:14:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Your man license has been revoked. Along with your license to grill, chill, and kill.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-03-24 17:13:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Naked cuddling  cuddling </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-03-24 17:09:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Especially in places with no dividers between urinals. I feel like an animal. That's how we do it in Murica.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-03-24 03:31:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> TIL the most found items are dildos, and women must masturbate more than they let on.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-03-24 03:13:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You were the hole in the latex  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-03-24 03:11:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Forget logic, right?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-03-23 15:23:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Doesn't matter had sex </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-03-23 05:51:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Scenario* </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-03-23 05:49:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I love the smell of curry and terrorism in the morning.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-03-22 06:06:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> My dad was stationed in Berlin in the Army when the wall came down. He brought home a piece. Coolest thing. It's almost like you can feel the history.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-03-22 01:46:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That all guys are douchebags. We aren't. There are nice guys out there. The women are just too stubborn to admit they want the douchebags until they're ready to settle down.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-03-21 14:42:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Upvote for being awesome.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-03-21 02:14:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm pretty much saying the general public doesn't. At least in my time in the field. People just don't understand how much time goes into a production, how much work it is, and then demand a miracle with little to no budget. If you're not willing to invest time into tech, you're going to get a shitty gig. Period.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-03-21 02:05:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm still in college but as a side job I do professional lighting for various events. Lighting referring to concert lighting, stuff you see at Maroon 5 concerts. Very obscure industry people know little to nothing about and have little respect or appreciation for.

I also do audio on the campus I attend. Good pay, people know more about it, but again, little respect or appreciation for the field.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-03-20 18:10:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Boobs make me happy.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-03-20 05:56:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The moment I heard my grandfather had committed suicide. It was a surreal moment, because not 3 hours prior I had skipped class to bring him lunch. I couldn't believe it. I knew then and there that I would remember that for years to come.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-03-20 05:53:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The obvious answer to this question would be Mila Kunis' vibrator.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-03-20 05:51:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> One Direction getting hit by a bus. In the words of Chris Rock, "Go Greyhound!" </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-03-20 05:48:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Morgan Freeman.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-03-20 05:48:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> take away the porn and outlaw masturbaition. we'd all be in jail. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-03-20 05:38:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Uncrate.com. So much cool shit to spend money that I don't have on.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-03-20 05:38:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> We stink bombed the janitor's office. In our defense, she was a real tightwad.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-03-20 02:05:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> 24, Monk, Numb3rs, Frasier, Cheers, and Seinfeld.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-03-19 22:03:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> "How did you know about my side job?!?!?" </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-03-19 21:55:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Twist: he was into the idea.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-03-19 21:54:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> She wants the D. Just not yours.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-03-19 21:51:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> "That's what your father used to say to me" </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-03-19 01:15:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Water with lemon juice. Seems simple but the lemon juice is really good for you and it makes plain water taste a lot better.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-03-19 01:13:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Music. If I find someone with my same tastes, I can talk with them for ages comparing and contrasting bands and songs.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-03-17 18:02:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Imagine you're in a sinkhole. There is no light, no visible way out, and darkness is closing in. That's what depression is like. 

I've struggled with it most of my life. Past few years have been happy though. 

My grandfather committed suicide a year ago. 

My mentor died of cancer two months ago. 

I have never contemplated suicide because of what my grandfather put me through. Needless to say, it is not something you can snap out of. It is a disease, and only a doctor can help. People's view of depression could not be more skewed. I'm happy I'm done with it. 

I live every day in constant battle with my depression. The threat of relapse hangs over my head daily. It is a daily struggle, one that I could not get through without my family and friends.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-03-17 17:51:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I actually used to have this nice-guy-itis and didn't know how to get rid of it. So my sophomore year of high school, I made up a creative way of asking this girl I liked to prom. I went to a Chinese restaurant and got a fortune cookie, heated it up, opened it, and left a note inside asking her to prom and letting her know who it was from. Resealed the package and paid off the office staff to put it in her locker for me. She turned me down, but it was a big boost to my self confidence. Do something risky and step out of your comfort zone. It helps a lot. Once you're out of your zone, you get used to being outside of it and that sets you up so you can start being more confident. 

    Number one rule- don't constantly text a girl. Chances are, if she doesn't text you first she probably isn't into you and constantly texting doesn't help. Also, let conversations breathe. If she doesn't respond right away, just wait. Apologizing for bothering her screams insecurity. 

TL;DR- asked a girl out and got self confidence.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-03-14 16:45:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Win-cest! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-03-09 19:08:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> As a Louisiana native, I find this to be extremely accurate.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-03-02 18:16:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> First off, stay away from Chauvet. They're notorious for breaking and not lasting long. A fairly cheap solution would be to get Luminair for iOS and hook your lights up via art net to Ethernet so you can control your lights via iOS. Luminair is incredibly easy to use. Try out controlbooth.com for a forum on lighting and sound. Those guys are awesome. I've been doing lighting for a while but I don't know a simple controller for that cheap. Maybe the guys at CB will have a suggestion. Best of luck.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-03-02 18:06:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Too bad beats are the absolute worst "high end" headphones you can buy.. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
