<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject6396</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Gigapixel photo of the mural at Huaca de la Luna, Peru </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-03 16:57:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [OS] Huaca de la Luna Plaza 1 Mural [21712x11244] </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-03 16:56:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Royal palace discovered in area believed to be birthplace of King Arthur </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-03 14:58:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> 3,500-year-old grave filled with exotic valuables found in Cyprus </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-03 14:56:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> 3,500-year-old grave filled with exotic valuables found in Cyprus </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-03 14:56:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Cahokia Mounds plans Archaeology Day </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-29 21:31:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Cahokia Mounds plans Archaeology Day </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-29 21:31:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Cahokia Mounds plans Archaeology Day </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-29 21:31:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Cahokia Mounds plans Archaeology Day </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-29 21:31:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Daniel Parada previews a page from Zotz #3, his alt-history comic on Mesoamerica </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-29 14:23:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Daniel Parada previews a page from Zotz #3, his alt-history comic on Mesoamerica </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-29 14:23:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Daniel Parada previews a page from Zotz #3, his alt-history comic on Mesoamerica </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-29 14:22:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> A Tapirape woman having her body painted </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-28 23:07:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Top archaeological finds-from-the-air list shows aerial technology is transforming understanding of the past </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-28 22:34:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> 17th-Century Cheese Found in Baltic Wreck </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-28 22:20:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> 17th-Century Cheese Found in Baltic Wreck </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-28 22:20:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Bioarchaeologist studies dental remains to explore the ancient people and culture of Oaxaca's Lower Ro Verde Valley </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-28 18:15:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Bioarchaeologist studies dental remains to explore the ancient people and culture of Oaxaca's Lower Ro Verde Valley </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-28 18:14:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Bioarchaeologist studies dental remains to explore the ancient people and culture of Oaxaca's Lower Ro Verde Valley </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-28 18:14:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Guy on a Maya vessel looks like he's wearing a clown hat </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-27 21:19:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Thug 4 lyfe </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-27 20:42:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> National security whistleblower lawyer Daniel Meyer alleges retaliation by Pentagon </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-27 19:14:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The AskHistorians Book Club - 3rd Discussion </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-27 12:56:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> As per our [announcement](https://www.reddit.com/r/AskHistorians/comments/4tquwc/askhistorians_book_club_3rd_reading_announcement/), this week we will be discussing the article submitted by /u/Uhm_yup. 

---

Tell us what you think!

What did you like? What did you dislike?

What did you not understand? What was explained really well?

Did you notice any problems or issues in the premise/methodology/sources/etc?

What would you like to know more about?

---

* Grau, Lester W. "Breaking Contact Without Leaving Chaos: The Soviet Withdrawal from Afghanistan." The Journal of Military Slavic Studies 20, no. 2 (2007): 235-261.

* www.dtic.mil/cgi-bin/GetTRDoc?AD=ADA470066

* There is a literature and a common perception that the Soviets were defeated and driven from Afghanistan. This is not true. When the Soviets left Afghanistan in 1989, they did so in a coordinated, deliberate, professional manner, leaving behind a functioning government, an improved military and an advisory and economic effort insuring the continued viability of the government. The withdrawal was based on a coordinated diplomatic, economic and military plan permitting Soviet forces to withdraw in good order and the Afghan government to survive. The Democratic Republic of Afghanistan (DRA) managed to hold on despite the collapse of the Soviet Union in 1991. Only then, with the loss of Soviet support and the increased efforts by the Mujahideen (holy warriors) and Pakistan, did the DRA slide toward defeat in April 1992. The Soviet effort to withdraw in good order was well executed and can serve as a model for other disengagements from similar nations. During the Soviet occupation of Afghanistan from 19791989, its occupation force, the 40th Army conducted 220 independent operations and over 400 combined operations of various scales. Many of these large-scale operations accomplished little, since this was primarily a tactical commanders' war. Some large-scale operations, such as the initial incursion into Afghanistan, Operation Magistral, which opened the highway to Khowst and the final withdrawal, were effective because the force employed was appropriate to the mission.

---

[Previous topics](https://www.reddit.com/r/AskHistorians/search?q=book+club sort=new restrict_sr=on) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Every series has a beach/pool episode </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-26 22:38:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> We Happy Few - Gameplay Trailer </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-26 21:13:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> West Mexico: Ritual and Identity exhibit opens at Gilcrease </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-26 02:18:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Has anyone gone to the West Mexico exhibit at the Gilcrease Museum? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-26 02:17:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If so, I'm just curious as to what people thought of it </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Descubren sistema de canales bajo el Templo de las Inscripciones de Palenque </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-25 22:51:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Mexico finds water tunnels under Pakal tomb in Palenque </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-25 22:46:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Mexico finds water tunnels under Pakal tomb in Palenque </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-25 22:46:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Extra Fingers and Toes Were Revered in Ancient Culture </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-25 19:10:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Ice Age Hunting Camp, Replete With Bird Bones and Tobacco, Found in Utah Desert </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-25 14:13:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Clinton campaign pushing lame conspiracy smear that we are Russian agents. Last time we were Mossad. Get it right. https://archive.is/4sg1J </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-25 00:24:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> New interim US DNC Chair Donna Brazile also implicated </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-25 00:04:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Bear's Den - Red Earth   Pouring Rain [Indie Rock] </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-24 00:47:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Bear's Den - Red Earth   Pouring Rain </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-24 00:46:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Bear's Den - Red Earth   Pouring Rain [Indie Rock] </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-24 00:46:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Researchers discover how rope was made 40,000 years ago </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-22 22:25:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Researchers discover how rope was made 40,000 years ago </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-22 22:25:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Huge statue suggests early rise for Buddhism </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-22 13:51:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Children's Doodles Found in Margins of Medieval Manuscript </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-22 13:49:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Children's Doodles Found in Margins of Medieval Manuscript </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-22 13:49:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> AskHistorians Book Club - 3rd Reading Announcement </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-20 14:17:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Based on the result of our submissions topic, /u/Uhm_yup's submission received the most votes. I will repost the information below. We have one week to read the article and next Wednesday we will come together to discuss what we read. Some things to keep in mind as you read:

- What did you like? What did you dislike?

- What did you not understand? What was explained really well?

- Did you notice any problems or issues in the premise/methodology/sources/etc?

- What would you like to know more about?

Obviously you do not have to answer any or some of these questions, but consider them as you read.

I would also like to thank everyone who submitted articles, but did not receive the most votes. All of the submissions were varied, interesting, and sounded worth reading. I hope that you will consider resubmitting them in a week and a half when we choose our next article/chapter.

If there are any issues, comments, questions, etc. please let me know in the comments below. Feedback is more than welcome and highly encouraged. Again, thank you all and have fun reading.

---

* Grau, Lester W. "Breaking Contact Without Leaving Chaos: The Soviet Withdrawal from Afghanistan." The Journal of Military Slavic Studies 20, no. 2 (2007): 235-261.

* www.dtic.mil/cgi-bin/GetTRDoc?AD=ADA470066

* There is a literature and a common perception that the Soviets were defeated and driven from Afghanistan. This is not true. When the Soviets left Afghanistan in 1989, they did so in a coordinated, deliberate, professional manner, leaving behind a functioning government, an improved military and an advisory and economic effort insuring the continued viability of the government. The withdrawal was based on a coordinated diplomatic, economic and military plan permitting Soviet forces to withdraw in good order and the Afghan government to survive. The Democratic Republic of Afghanistan (DRA) managed to hold on despite the collapse of the Soviet Union in 1991. Only then, with the loss of Soviet support and the increased efforts by the Mujahideen (holy warriors) and Pakistan, did the DRA slide toward defeat in April 1992. The Soviet effort to withdraw in good order was well executed and can serve as a model for other disengagements from similar nations. During the Soviet occupation of Afghanistan from 19791989, its occupation force, the 40th Army conducted 220 independent operations and over 400 combined operations of various scales. Many of these large-scale operations accomplished little, since this was primarily a tactical commanders' war. Some large-scale operations, such as the initial incursion into Afghanistan, Operation Magistral, which opened the highway to Khowst and the final withdrawal, were effective because the force employed was appropriate to the mission.

---

[Previous topics](https://www.reddit.com/r/AskHistorians/search?q=book+club sort=new restrict_sr=on) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Excavated tombs of Peru's Moche priestesses provide archaeologists with troves of artifacts, data </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-20 14:14:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [OS] The pyramid and circular sunken plaza at Bandurria, Peru. Dated to 3200 BC, during Peru's pre-Ceramic period. [4563x1596] </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-19 14:38:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Would Say Would Fall - a short documentary on reading the charred scrolls recovered from Herculaneum </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-18 21:45:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Reading the Unreadable </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-18 21:43:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Would Say Would Fall - a short documentary on reading the charred scrolls recovered from Herculaneum </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-18 21:43:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Reading the Unreadable </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-18 21:42:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> In societies that are lactose intolerant and do not ferment food like kimchi, how do people promote and maintain good gut bacteria? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-18 14:32:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The AskHistorians Book Club - Call for Submissions </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-17 17:51:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This topic is to ask for submissions for journal articles or book chapters from our community. ***Anyone can submit***, you do not need to have a flair. Please limit one submission per person. And please refrain from submitting entire books as our time frame does not allow it.

---

***Topic***

Any submission must be related to history. We have a wide variety of flaired users from fields such as archaeology to linguistics to medicine to music. Let's use it to our advantage. As long as the submission pertains to understanding the past, it is open for the book club. We are trying to broaden our horizons and understanding of the past and that must include seeing the past through a different lens. So do not frett if your submission comes from a medical journal, a music theory journal, or an edited volume by Mesoamerican archaeologists, it's all welcome. If it isn't, someone will kindly let you know. So if you want to submit something on Stonehenge, or changes in letter choice for recording indigenous languages during the colonial period, or advancements in medicine in the late 1700s, or experimental recreation of ancient music, go for it. 

***Article information***

Included in your submission must be the author or authors, the title of the work, the journal/book, year, etc. If using Google Scholar, there is an easy and handy Cite tool which gives a variety of options for citations. You can easily copy/paste that for your submission. My preference is MLA, but it will not be strictly enforced.

***Accessible***

Any journal article or book chapter must be accessible to the community, preferably through a link. The easiest way that Ive found to do this is to use Google Scholar. As Ive shown in [this example]( http://i.imgur.com/IeXcrPk.png), when searching for articles there is sometimes a link off to the right in which you can access the article or chapter for free. This is the link you must include in your submission, not a link to the journal page. I will be monitoring submissions to let anyone know if their links fail, but since I am based in the US my access could be biased. If anyone finds a broken link, please let me or the submitter know so that it can be fixed.

***Abstract/Summary***

Along with the link please include the abstract from the journal article or a written summary for the article/book chapter. This is to give us all an idea of what the article/chapter is about so that we can make a semi-informed vote.

***Voting***

Voting will run from now until Wednesday morning around 7am EST. Whichever submission has the most votes by that time will be chosen for us to read over the course of the following week.

---

Using the article from my Scholar example for our format example, the format should be as follows

 * Headrick, Annabeth. "The Street of the Dead It Really Was." Ancient Mesoamerica 10.01 (1999): 69-85.

 * https://media.smith.edu/media/ereserves/pdf_files/hillyer/f-j/headrick_street.pdf

 * The name Street of the Dead used to designate Teotihuacans main avenue originates from a Nahuatl notation on a sixteenth-century map. Though this story is often deemed apocryphal, I argue in this paper that oral tradition preserved conceptual information that may not be archaeologically recoverable. Support for this position comes from comparative cultural analysis of Mesoamerican mortuary bundles as they are expressed in ritual and iconography. Crucial to this argument are the well-known stone masks of Teotihuacan. A case is made that the masks originally served as the faces of oracular mortuary bundles. The likely existence of mortuary bundles at Teotihuacan generates organizational models for the city in which lineage emerges as a fundamental element and suggests new insight into status differentiation and the iconography of power at Teotihuacan. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What sorts of food did Old Copper Complex people around the Great Lakes eat? Were their spears just for hunting? What did they use their harpoons for? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-17 02:03:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> For reference

Spear point - http://i.imgur.com/1ioUoWO.jpg

Various spear points, fish hooks, and a few harpoons - https://s-media-cache-ak0.pinimg.com/736x/86/43/bd/8643bdf7adad2057027a1e6dadcccb81.jpg </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Native American copper necklace. Old Copper Complex. 4000 to 1000 BC. Taken in Copper Harbor, Michigan. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-17 01:49:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [OC] Copper necklace. Presumably Old Copper Complex. 4000 to 1000 BC. Taken in Copper Harbor, Michigan. [3120x4160] </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-17 01:22:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Rare Roman mosaic 'depicting Hercules' unearthed in Cyprus </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-15 22:37:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Rare Roman mosaic 'depicting Hercules' unearthed in Cyprus </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-15 22:37:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Rare Roman mosaic 'depicting Hercules' unearthed in Cyprus </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-15 22:37:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What Are Chastity Belts, Really? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-13 22:32:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What Are Chastity Belts, Really? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-13 22:30:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The AskHistorians Book Club discusses Charles Mann's article that became his bestselling book 1491 </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-13 15:33:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I just wanted to let you guys know that we'll be discussing Charles Mann's article today to Sunday if anyone wants to stop by, read the article, and discuss with us what you read. I'm sure anyone who is interested in Native American history, both pre- and post-Columbian would enjoy the article and discussion.

https://www.reddit.com/r/AskHistorians/comments/4smpye/the_askhistorians_book_club_2nd_discussion/ </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Holding hands for 5,000 years, a couple with mysterious jade rings and dagger </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-13 13:44:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The AskHistorians Book Club - 2nd Discussion </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-13 13:43:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> As per our [announcement](https://www.reddit.com/r/AskHistorians/comments/4ridaf/askhistorians_book_club_2nd_reading_announcement/), this week we will be discussing the article submitted by /u/Georgy_K_Zhukov. 

---

Tell us what you think!

What did you like? What did you dislike?

What did you not understand? What was explained really well?

Did you notice any problems or issues in the premise/methodology/sources/etc?

What would you like to know more about?

---


* Charles Mann's "1491" article from The Atlantic, which eventually would lead to the book of the same name

* http://www.theatlantic.com/magazine/archive/2002/03/1491/302445/

* "Before it became the New World, the Western Hemisphere was vastly more populous and sophisticated than has been thoughtan altogether more salubrious place to live at the time than, say, Europe. New evidence of both the extent of the population and its agricultural advancement leads to a remarkable conjecture: the Amazon rain forest may be largely a human artifact"

---

[Previous topics](https://www.reddit.com/r/AskHistorians/search?q=title%3A%22Book+Club%22 restrict_sr=on sort=relevance t=all) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Descubren ofrenda de sahumadores prehispnicos en Cuautitln </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-13 01:12:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> 23 More Wrecks Found at Greek Hotspot for Sunken Ships </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-13 01:11:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> 2100+ Greek and Latin graffiti as well as graffiti in Phoenician, Cypriot, Lycian, and Coptic were found in the Valley of the Kings. What do these graffiti inscriptions say? Have they illuminated Egyptology's understanding of the necropolis and Egyptian history? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-12 22:13:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The majority are at KV9 and the oldest ones date to 278 BC. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Homo erectus walked as we do </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-12 20:22:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Digs uncover buildings in Cyprus' 11,000 year-old village </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-12 18:08:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Digs uncover buildings in Cyprus' 11,000 year-old village </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-12 18:07:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Hidden angel mosaic at Bethlehem shrine sees the light </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-12 14:17:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> El Popol Vuh </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-11 21:35:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The Popol Vuh : Mayan Creation Myth. Animated Full Version </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-11 21:31:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Dawn of the Maya Documentary </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-11 21:11:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Rome workers unearth ancient baths and tombs </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-11 20:41:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Portrait mask. Olmec. Middle Formative period, 900600 B.C. Ro Pesquero area, Veracruz, Mexico </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-11 19:44:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [OS] Portrait mask. Olmec. Middle Formative period, 900600 B.C. Ro Pesquero area, Veracruz, Mexico [1336x1600] </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-11 19:42:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Hallan guacamaya momificada en un contexto arqueolgico de Chihuahua </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-11 17:57:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> 'Primitive Machine' Within Great Pyramid of Giza Reconstructed </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-11 17:51:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> 'Primitive Machine' Within Great Pyramid of Giza Reconstructed </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-11 17:49:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> 'Primitive Machine' Within Great Pyramid of Giza Reconstructed </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-11 17:49:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Massive open-access database on human cultures created </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-11 17:45:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Idris Elba Lives up to Gunslinger Name on The Dark Tower Set </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-11 17:44:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Roman shoe found in a well, Saalburg, 2000-years-old. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-10 16:43:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [OS] Roman shoe found in a well, Saalburg, 2000-years-old. [1024x687] </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-10 16:42:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Antibiotic resistance discovered in the guts of ancient Inca mummies </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-09 14:22:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Antibiotic resistance discovered in the guts of ancient mummies </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-09 13:41:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Antibiotic resistance discovered in the guts of ancient mummies </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-09 13:41:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Antibiotic resistance discovered in the guts of ancient mummies </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-09 13:40:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Can you see the 'ancient land sculptures' in these Google Earth images of Britain? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-08 21:07:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Skeleton with stone-encrusted teeth found in Mexico ancient ruins </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-08 17:29:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Cules son sus sitios arqueolgicos favoritos? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-08 15:36:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Skeleton with stone-encrusted teeth found in Mexico ancient ruins </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-08 15:32:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Skeleton with stone-encrusted teeth found in Mexico ancient ruins </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-08 15:31:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Skeleton with stone-encrusted teeth found in Mexico ancient ruins </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-08 15:31:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Skeleton with stone-encrusted teeth found in Mexico ancient ruins </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-08 15:30:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [OS] Burial of a woman at Teotihuacan with a jadeite tooth that was cemented or attached with fiber to her mandible. 350 to 450 AD. Mexico [361X540] </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-08 05:03:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Burial of a woman at Teotihuacan with a jadeite tooth that was cemented or attached with fiber to her mandible </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-08 05:01:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Estudian entierro de mujer de lite descubierta en Teotihuacan </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-08 01:13:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> New rock paintings found near Machu Picchu </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-07 00:25:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Prehistoric Tattoos Were Made with Volcanic Glass Tools </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-06 22:54:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Prehistoric Tattoos Were Made with Volcanic Glass Tools </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-06 22:53:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Ancient Brazilians occupied the same homes for centuries </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-06 22:52:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Cannibalism among late Neandertals in northern Europe </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-06 20:36:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Cannibalism among late Neandertals in northern Europe </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-06 20:36:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Bible Scenes Uncovered in Ruins of Ancient Synagogue </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-06 15:53:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> AskHistorians Book Club - 2nd Reading Announcement </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-06 15:05:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Based on the result of our submissions topic, /u/Georgy_K_Zhukov's submission received the most votes. I will repost the information below. We have one week to read the article and next Wednesday we will come together to discuss what we read. Some things to keep in mind as you read:

- What did you like? What did you dislike?

- What did you not understand? What was explained really well?

- Did you notice any problems or issues in the premise/methodology/sources/etc?

- What would you like to know more about?

Obviously you do not have to answer any or some of these questions, but consider them as you read.

I would also like to thank everyone who submitted articles, but did not receive the most votes. All of the submissions were varied, interesting, and sounded worth reading. I hope that you will consider resubmitting them in a week and a half when we choose our next article/chapter.

If there are any issues, comments, questions, etc. please let me know in the comments below. Feedback is more than welcome and highly encouraged. Again, thank you all and have fun reading.

---

* Charles Mann's "1491" article from The Atlantic, which eventually would lead to the book of the same name

* http://www.theatlantic.com/magazine/archive/2002/03/1491/302445/

* "Before it became the New World, the Western Hemisphere was vastly more populous and sophisticated than has been thoughtan altogether more salubrious place to live at the time than, say, Europe. New evidence of both the extent of the population and its agricultural advancement leads to a remarkable conjecture: the Amazon rain forest may be largely a human artifact"

---

* [Interest topic]( https://www.reddit.com/r/AskHistorians/comments/4nvm7y/bridging_the_gap_any_interest_in_starting_an/)

* [1st Call for Submissions]( https://www.reddit.com/r/AskHistorians/comments/4orpi0/the_askhistorians_book_club_call_for_submissions/)

* [1st Announcement](https://www.reddit.com/r/AskHistorians/comments/4paqmh/askhistorians_book_club_reading_announcement/)

* [1st Discussion](https://www.reddit.com/r/AskHistorians/comments/4qevw5/the_askhistorians_book_club_discussion_time/)

* [2nd Call for Submissions](https://www.reddit.com/r/AskHistorians/comments/4r1wgj/the_askhistorians_book_club_call_for_submissions/?sort=top) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> No one is an island: The history of human genetic ancestry in Madagascar </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-06 14:28:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> New picture emerges on human settlement of Madagascar </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-06 13:03:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The AskHistorians Book Club subreddit </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-05 19:26:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Reconstruction of 12,000 year old funeral feast brings ancient burial rituals to life </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-05 18:59:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Voyaging in prehistoric Polynesia </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-05 04:31:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Ron Howard tweets picture of Idris Elba in his gunslinger getup </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-05 04:29:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> CGI? Real model? A mix of both? What do you think the new series will use for their ship? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-04 13:55:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm hoping that they use a physical model as much as possible with limited CGI. I know CGI has made advances since Enterprise, but nothing really beats a physical object for me. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Golden statuette from the so-called Quimbaya Treasure, a collection of 200 golden objects (500-1000 AD) given to Spain as a gift by the Columbian government in 1893. Museo de amrica, Madrid, Spain </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-03 22:25:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [OS] Golden statuette from the so-called Quimbaya Treasure, a collection of 200 golden objects (500-1000 AD) given to Spain as a gift by the Columbian government in 1893. Museo de amrica, Madrid, Spain [2592x3888] </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-03 22:24:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The AskHistorians Book Club - Call for Submissions </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-03 14:53:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This topic is to ask for submissions for journal articles or book chapters from our community. ***Anyone can submit***, you do not need to have a flair. Please limit one submission per person. And please refrain from submitting entire books as our time frame does not allow it.

---

***Suggestions for this week***

Some users have made some suggestions regarding changes in format as we continue to develop the book club.

- Simpler format

Some have called for a simpler format when it comes to the title of the submission. The suggestion was just to have the title of the work and the author and leave out the journal or edited volume, year, page numbers, etc. Feedback on this would be appreciated and if anyone wants to try this out on their submission, please do.

- More general papers

The first paper was a rather niche subject, which I was fine with. But some people have expressed the desire for more general and accessible papers for now until we can build ourselves up to these more niche subjects. Perhaps for this round try and keep this in mind as you find something to submit. 

---

***Topic***

Any submission must be related to history. We have a wide variety of flaired users from fields such as archaeology to linguistics to medicine to music. Let's use it to our advantage. As long as the submission pertains to understanding the past, it is open for the book club. We are trying to broaden our horizons and understanding of the past and that must include seeing the past through a different lens. So do not frett if your submission comes from a medical journal, a music theory journal, or an edited volume by Mesoamerican archaeologists, it's all welcome. If it isn't, someone will kindly let you know. So if you want to submit something on Stonehenge, or changes in letter choice for recording indigenous languages during the colonial period, or advancements in medicine in the late 1700s, or experimental recreation of ancient music, go for it. 

***Article information***

Included in your submission must be the author or authors, the title of the work, the journal/book, year, etc. If using Google Scholar, there is an easy and handy Cite tool which gives a variety of options for citations. You can easily copy/paste that for your submission. My preference is MLA, but it will not be strictly enforced.

***Accessible***

Any journal article or book chapter must be accessible to the community, preferably through a link. The easiest way that Ive found to do this is to use Google Scholar. As Ive shown in [this example]( http://i.imgur.com/IeXcrPk.png), when searching for articles there is sometimes a link off to the right in which you can access the article or chapter for free. This is the link you must include in your submission, not a link to the journal page. I will be monitoring submissions to let anyone know if their links fail, but since I am based in the US my access could be biased. If anyone finds a broken link, please let me or the submitter know so that it can be fixed.

***Abstract/Summary***

Along with the link please include the abstract from the journal article or a written summary for the article/book chapter. This is to give us all an idea of what the article/chapter is about so that we can make a semi-informed vote.

***Voting***

Voting will run from now until Wednesday morning around 7am EST. Whichever submission has the most votes by that time will be chosen for us to read over the course of the following week.

---

Using the article from my Scholar example for our format example, the format should be as follows

 * Headrick, Annabeth. "The Street of the Dead It Really Was." Ancient Mesoamerica 10.01 (1999): 69-85.

 * https://media.smith.edu/media/ereserves/pdf_files/hillyer/f-j/headrick_street.pdf

 * The name Street of the Dead used to designate Teotihuacans main avenue originates from a Nahuatl notation on a sixteenth-century map. Though this story is often deemed apocryphal, I argue in this paper that oral tradition preserved conceptual information that may not be archaeologically recoverable. Support for this position comes from comparative cultural analysis of Mesoamerican mortuary bundles as they are expressed in ritual and iconography. Crucial to this argument are the well-known stone masks of Teotihuacan. A case is made that the masks originally served as the faces of oracular mortuary bundles. The likely existence of mortuary bundles at Teotihuacan generates organizational models for the city in which lineage emerges as a fundamental element and suggests new insight into status differentiation and the iconography of power at Teotihuacan.

---

* [Interest topic]( https://www.reddit.com/r/AskHistorians/comments/4nvm7y/bridging_the_gap_any_interest_in_starting_an/)

* [1st Call for Submissions]( https://www.reddit.com/r/AskHistorians/comments/4orpi0/the_askhistorians_book_club_call_for_submissions/)

* [1st Announcement](https://www.reddit.com/r/AskHistorians/comments/4paqmh/askhistorians_book_club_reading_announcement/)

* [1st Discussion](https://www.reddit.com/r/AskHistorians/comments/4qevw5/the_askhistorians_book_club_discussion_time/) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Exploran chinampas y canales de un barrio de la antigua Mxico-Tenochtitlan </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-02 02:16:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Carthage archaeologists dig up smart cooling system for chariot racers </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-01 15:17:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Amazing Things Weve Learned From 800 Ancient Skull Surgeries </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-30 18:51:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Last words: language of China's emperors in peril </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-30 14:37:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Wooden mask. Mixtec or Aztec. Postclassic period, A.D. 11001521. Mexico, Central or Southern Highlands </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-30 01:02:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [OS] Wooden mask. Mixtec or Aztec. Postclassic period, A.D. 11001521. Mexico, Central or Southern Highlands [1244x1600] </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-30 01:00:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Wooden treasures unearthed at Vindolanda </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-29 20:36:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The AskHistorians Book Club - Discussion Time </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-29 12:47:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> As per our [announcement](https://www.reddit.com/r/AskHistorians/comments/4paqmh/askhistorians_book_club_reading_announcement/), this week we will be discussing the article submitted by /u/Miles_Sine_Castrum. 

Tell us what you think!

What did you like? What did you dislike?

What did you not understand? What was explained really well?

Did you notice any problems or issues in the premise/methodology/sources/etc?

What would you like to know more about?

---

* Brown, Elizabeth A.R., 'The Tyranny of a Construct: Feudalism and Historians of Medieval Europe', The American Historical Review, vol. 79, no. 4 (Oct. 1974), pp. 1063-88.

* http://isites.harvard.edu/fs/docs/icb.topic1350026.files/Brown-Tyranny-of-a-Construct.pdf

* Peggy Brown's attack on the idea of feudalism is, as I said, a classic of medieval history, and remains important and controversial to this day. In this article, she tries to pull apart what historians mean by the world feudalism and how the concept has influenced how they interpret their sources. The end result is that she argues that feudalism is ultimately not a useful concept, that it confuses and obscures much more than it clarifies. Beyond the specific issue of feudalism, it raises lots of interesting issues about the uses of abstract concepts and models for the work of historians. Brown's work has been discussed before on AH, but I think this gives a unique chance for reader to engage with these kinds of big historiographical ideas and arguments first-hand.

---

* [Interest topic]( https://www.reddit.com/r/AskHistorians/comments/4nvm7y/bridging_the_gap_any_interest_in_starting_an/)

* [1st Call for Submissions]( https://www.reddit.com/r/AskHistorians/comments/4orpi0/the_askhistorians_book_club_call_for_submissions/) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Occupational markers and pathology of the castrato singer Gaspare Pacchierotti (17401821) </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-28 22:34:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> How Castration And Opera Changed The Skeleton Of 19th Century Singer Pacchierotti </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-28 22:30:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Ancient temple of Mexican Otomi Indians damaged </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-28 22:21:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Ancient temple of Mexican Otomi Indians damaged by assailants who allegedly said they were Jehovah's Witnesses </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-28 19:29:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Ancient temple of Mexican Otomi Indians damaged </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-28 19:28:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Ancient temple of Mexican Otomi Indians damaged </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-28 19:27:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Ancient temple of Mexican Otomi Indians damaged </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-28 19:27:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Roman mosaic unearthed in wheat field in Turkey's Krkkale </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-28 19:21:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> 18th Century Cheese Curd Fritters </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-28 17:00:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The Discovery of a Roman Gladiator School Brings the Famed Fighters Back to Life </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-27 21:52:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The Discovery of a Roman Gladiator School Brings the Famed Fighters Back to Life </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-27 21:52:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Unique Viking tomb contains remains of noble couple </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-27 20:38:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Cambodia says tests confirm Angkor boat 8 centuries old </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-27 20:37:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> 20 minutes into LOTR and chill and he gives you this look </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-27 20:35:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [OS] The ruins of Iaq Uyu on the Isla de la Luna in Lake Titicaca. Thought to be a burial place for royal Inca women. 1000 to 1500 AD [1600x1200] </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-27 17:09:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Ancient 'Deep Skull' from Borneo full of surprises </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-27 15:08:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Ancient 'Deep Skull' from Borneo full of surprises </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-27 15:08:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Did Atlantis Really Have Indoor Plumbing? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-27 03:51:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Anthropology students, professor finishing work at Cass settlement site </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-25 03:59:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Canaanites sacrificed animals from Egypt 5,000 years ago, archaeologists prove </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-24 23:08:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Skeletons, coins found in dig of ancient Pompeii shop </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-24 23:07:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Photos: Ancient Greek Inscriptions Revealed on Antikythera Mechanism </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-24 21:00:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Construction site near Kamloops uncovers proof of 'pre-contact Indigenous habitation' - British Columbia </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-24 14:29:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Construction site near Kamloops uncovers proof of 'pre-contact Indigenous habitation' - British Columbia </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-24 14:28:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Construction site near Kamloops uncovers proof of 'pre-contact Indigenous habitation' - British Columbia </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-24 14:28:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Campsite dating back 12,000 years unearthed by Route 8 - New Brunswick </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-24 02:11:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Were the Walls of Benin and Sungbo's Eredo in Nigeria constructed just for defense? Or were they a way to unify a diverse area into a single kingdom as the Wiki article says? Has anyone done any labor estimates on how many people and how much time it would take to build these massive earthworks? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-23 15:13:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Walls_of_Benin

https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Sungbo%27s_Eredo </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Emails: State Dept. Scrambled on Trouble on Clinton's Server </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-23 14:45:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Peek Inside Cat Mummies With New X-ray Images </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-22 19:57:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Peek Inside Cat Mummies With New X-ray Images </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-22 19:56:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Peek Inside Cat Mummies With New X-ray Images </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-22 19:56:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Human head effigy jar. Maya. Late Classic Period. A.D. 600850. Guatemala, Southern Highlands </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-22 16:38:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> AskHistorians Book Club - Reading Announcement </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-22 15:51:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Based on the result of our submissions topic, /u/Miles_Sine_Castrum's submission received the most votes. I will repost the information below. We have one week to read the article and next Wednesday we will come together to discuss what we read. Some things to keep in mind as you read:

- What did you like? What did you dislike?

- What did you not understand? What was explained really well?

- Did you notice any problems or issues in the premise/methodology/sources/etc?

- What would you like to know more about?

Obviously you do not have to answer any or some of these questions, but consider them as you read.

I would also like to thank everyone who submitted articles, but did not receive the most votes. All of the submissions were varied, interesting, and sounded worth reading. I hope that you will consider resubmitting them in a week and a half when we choose our next article/chapter.

If there are any issues, comments, questions, etc. please let me know in the comments below. Feedback is more than welcome and highly encouraged. Again, thank you all and have fun reading.

---

* Brown, Elizabeth A.R., 'The Tyranny of a Construct: Feudalism and Historians of Medieval Europe', The American Historical Review, vol. 79, no. 4 (Oct. 1974), pp. 1063-88.

* http://isites.harvard.edu/fs/docs/icb.topic1350026.files/Brown-Tyranny-of-a-Construct.pdf

* Peggy Brown's attack on the idea of feudalism is, as I said, a classic of medieval history, and remains important and controversial to this day. In this article, she tries to pull apart what historians mean by the world feudalism and how the concept has influenced how they interpret their sources. The end result is that she argues that feudalism is ultimately not a useful concept, that it confuses and obscures much more than it clarifies. Beyond the specific issue of feudalism, it raises lots of interesting issues about the uses of abstract concepts and models for the work of historians. Brown's work has been discussed before on AH, but I think this gives a unique chance for reader to engage with these kinds of big historiographical ideas and arguments first-hand.

---

* [Interest topic]( https://www.reddit.com/r/AskHistorians/comments/4nvm7y/bridging_the_gap_any_interest_in_starting_an/)

* [1st Call for Submissions]( https://www.reddit.com/r/AskHistorians/comments/4orpi0/the_askhistorians_book_club_call_for_submissions/) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [OS] Human head effigy jar. Maya. Late Classic Period. A.D. 600850. Guatemala, Southern Highlands [836x1024] </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-21 22:48:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Earliest Limb Transplant ID'd in Painting </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-21 20:17:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Researchers find Highland East Asian origin for prehistoric Himalayan populations </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-21 01:17:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Researchers find Highland East Asian origin for prehistoric Himalayan populations </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-21 00:14:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Gods and Monsters: Bulldozer Rips Into Ancient Sacred Site </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-20 15:27:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Take me out to the ballgame, two millennia ago </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-20 15:15:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Take me out to the ballgame, two millennia ago </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-20 15:15:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Take me out to the ballgame, two millennia ago </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-20 15:15:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Take me out to the ballgame, two millennia ago </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-20 15:15:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Take me out to the ballgame, two millennia ago </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-20 15:15:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Take me out to the ballgame, two millennia ago </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-20 15:14:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Great Pyramid of Giza Is Slightly Lopsided </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-20 14:16:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Great Pyramid of Giza Is Slightly Lopsided </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-20 14:13:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Great Pyramid of Giza Is Slightly Lopsided </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-20 14:13:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The AskHistorians Book Club - Call for Submissions </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-19 05:27:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [On Monday]( https://www.reddit.com/r/AskHistorians/comments/4nvm7y/bridging_the_gap_any_interest_in_starting_an/) I asked if there was any interest in an AskHistorians book club in which we all get together to read an academic journal article or book chapter from an edited volume and then discussed it. To my great surprise there was an overwhelming positive feedback to this idea. I hope the interest is still high as we take the next step forward by starting a trial run on our book club. As part of this trial we will be going with a two week format to start with (1st Sunday, submissions; 1st Wednesday, announcement; 2nd Wednesday, discussion; 2nd Sunday, submissions)

This topic is to ask for submissions for journal articles or book chapters from our community. ***Anyone can submit***, you do not need to have a flair. Please limit one submission per person. And please refrain from submitting entire books as our time frame does not allow it.

***Topic***

Any submission must be related to history. We have a wide variety of flaired users from fields such as archaeology to linguistics to medicine to music. Let's use it to our advantage. As long as the submission pertains to understanding the past, it is open for the book club. We are trying to broaden our horizons and understanding of the past and that must include seeing the past through a different lens. So do not frett if your submission comes from a medical journal, a music theory journal, or an edited volume by Mesoamerican archaeologists, it's all welcome. If it isn't, someone will kindly let you know. So if you want to submit something on Stonehenge, or changes in letter choice for recording indigenous languages during the colonial period, or advancements in medicine in the late 1700s, or experimental recreation of ancient music, go for it. 

***Article information***

Included in your submission must be the author or authors, the title of the work, the journal/book, year, etc. If using Google Scholar, there is an easy and handy Cite tool which gives a variety of options for citations. You can easily copy/paste that for your submission. My preference is MLA, but it will not be strictly enforced.

***Accessible***

Any journal article or book chapter must be accessible to the community, preferably through a link. The easiest way that Ive found to do this is to use Google Scholar. As Ive shown in [this example]( http://i.imgur.com/IeXcrPk.png), when searching for articles there is sometimes a link off to the right in which you can access the article or chapter for free. This is the link you must include in your submission, not a link to the journal page. I will be monitoring submissions to let anyone know if their links fail, but since I am based in the US my access could be biased. If anyone finds a broken link, please let me or the submitter know so that it can be fixed.

***Abstract/Summary***

Along with the link please include the abstract from the journal article or a written summary for the article/book chapter. This is to give us all an idea of what the article/chapter is about so that we can make a semi-informed vote.

***Voting***

Voting will run from now until Wednesday morning around 7am EST. Whichever submission has the most votes by that time will be chosen for us to read over the course of the following week.

---

Using the article from my Scholar example for our format example, the format should be as follows

 * Headrick, Annabeth. "The Street of the Dead It Really Was." Ancient Mesoamerica 10.01 (1999): 69-85.

 * https://media.smith.edu/media/ereserves/pdf_files/hillyer/f-j/headrick_street.pdf

 * The name Street of the Dead used to designate Teotihuacans main avenue originates from a Nahuatl notation on a sixteenth-century map. Though this story is often deemed apocryphal, I argue in this paper that oral tradition preserved conceptual information that may not be archaeologically recoverable. Support for this position comes from comparative cultural analysis of Mesoamerican mortuary bundles as they are expressed in ritual and iconography. Crucial to this argument are the well-known stone masks of Teotihuacan. A case is made that the masks originally served as the faces of oracular mortuary bundles. The likely existence of mortuary bundles at Teotihuacan generates organizational models for the city in which lineage emerges as a fundamental element and suggests new insight into status differentiation and the iconography of power at Teotihuacan.

---

Im not sure how mods want to handle comments, but lets treat this as we would any AskHistorians topic with comments focused on the topic and not making jokes or insulting anyone. Please be kind and be courteous. And lets take our first steps to a hopefully fruitful and informative new feature. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Figurine of mountain goat. Face gold-plated and also two attached curls on legs. One curl missing. Head made separate. Incised lines on side of body and leg incised on underside. Silver and sheet gold. Near Eastern, Iranian, Elamite. Proto-Elamite. 35002700 B.C. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-17 15:00:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Heave-Ho! Stonehenge Experiment May Show How Monument Was Built </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-17 14:57:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Rolls-Royce concept car, Vision Next 100 </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-17 01:59:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> D.A.R.E. to resist drugs [We Happy Few] </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-16 22:16:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [OS] Figurine of mountain goat. Face gold-plated and also two attached curls on legs. One curl missing. Head made separate. Incised lines on side of body and leg incised on underside. Silver and sheet gold. Near Eastern, Iranian, Elamite. Proto-Elamite. 35002700 B.C. [1600X1200] </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-16 21:18:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Ready to Monday </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-16 01:35:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Mysterious Earthen Mounds Discovered in Ancient Cambodian Cities </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-15 17:12:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> How a Utah county silenced Native American voters  and how Navajos are fighting back </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-15 13:19:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> How a Utah county silenced Native American voters  and how Navajos are fighting back </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-15 13:18:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> We Happy Few Gameplay - Xbox E3 2016 </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-14 16:14:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> 100 Silver Pieces Found in Roman-Era 'Hoard' in Scotland </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-14 14:33:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> 100 Silver Pieces Found in Roman-Era 'Hoard' in Scotland </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-14 14:33:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Monumental Ancient Naval Bases Discovered in Athens' Piraeus Harbor </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-13 20:59:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> x-post - Bridging The Gap: Any interest in starting an AskHistorians "book club"? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-13 18:44:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> https://www.reddit.com/r/AskHistorians/comments/4nvm7y/bridging_the_gap_any_interest_in_starting_an/

As another large history subreddit, with many users posting here and on /r/AskHistorians, I would greatly appreciate any ideas and feedback on my book club idea I hope to implement.

The gist is that I want to get together a reading group on a monthly or bi-monthly basis to read journal articles or book chapters from edited volumes in order to broaden our understanding and knowledge base. Most of the source recommendations here and on AskHistorians are books, which do always cover or adequately cover topics of research that journal articles or book chapters do.
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Ancient DNA analysis explains spread of domestic goats from fertile crescent into caucasus </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-13 18:02:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Archaeologists scan Reading garden for bones of King Henry I </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-13 17:14:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Bridging The Gap: Any interest in starting an AskHistorians "book club"? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-13 15:29:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I've been tossing this idea around in my head for awhile and decided last week to pitch it to my fellow flaired users. But now that I've gotten their input, I want your input because this idea ultimately rests upon you.

I would like to start a sort of book club on AskHistorians, but not focus on books. Our recommendations of books are put into our [Books and Resources list](https://www.reddit.com/r/AskHistorians/wiki/books) which anyone is free to look at, peruse, and read at their discretion. Instead, I would like to turn our focus on journal articles or book chapters from edited volumes. These are the sorts of resources that academics rely on, but sources in which we don't put into our list above. Articles and book chapters are advantages because they focus on aspects of research and topics of discussion that may not always be included or discusses in a book by a single or group of authors. These works may be dry, they may be technical, and they may just have a lot of jargon, but I feel like our community would still be able to come together and read one of these pieces, and have an intelligent discussion. AskHistorians users were invited this past year to the American Historical Association conference because of our methods to bridge the gap between academia and the public. So let's take this one step further. Let's try and attempt to broaden our horizons and knowledge about topics we might not normally seek out and read ourselves. Let's do this together.

This book club would work on a month long rotation. The first week, a topic will be posted calling for submissions. Anyone can submit an article or book chapter, but there are requirements. Said submission must be available online and open to anyone. The easiest way to do that, I've found, is by searching Google Scholar. Often, but not always, there are links to academic institutions or places like researchgate.net in which these articles and book chapters are free to read. See [this example](http://i.imgur.com/IeXcrPk.png). When you make a submission, you must provide the title, authors, journal (if applicable) and date. Your basic citation format, essentially. But you must also provide the link to the work and either the abstract of the article or a summary (that you may have to write) of the work if it lacks an abstract. 

Submissions need not be limited to just articles/chapters from history journals or edited volumes. As AskHistorians embraces multiple fields in order to understand the past, so shall the book club. Feel free to submit things from anthropology (archaeology, linguistics, ethnography, bio anthropology), art history, medical journals, etc. As long as it pertains to history it is open to for reading. There is also no time depth requirement on submissions. You don't need to submit something that came out in the last few years. If you've found something from the 1800s and think people will be interested in reading it, perhaps for the information or perhaps to discuss how dated the ideas are, feel free to submit that, too. Over the course of a week, the submission topic will be open to voting. At the end of that week, the submission with the highest amount of votes will be the chosen work to be read.

Some of my fellow flaired users raised concerns that we might fall into a rotation of the same topics or time periods and never move on to lesser talked about topics. For now, I say let the market decide on what we read. If it does become a problem, we could always implement a system in which once an article/chapter that covers one of our flaired areas gets read, we no longer will take submissions from that area until the rest of the flaired areas are covered. But that is an option for a later time depending on our initial success. Thoughts and feedback are particularly welcome on this area, as is the rest of the proposal.

Once we have our article/chapter to read, we have two weeks to read it ourselves. At the end of those two weeks a topic will be made for people to focus their discussion. Try to include what you liked about the article/chapter, what you didn't like, what you didn't understand, what you want to know more about, what were the problems in the methodology or premise, etc. As I said, this is a way to broaden our knowledge and an attempt to fill in some of those gaps we may be interested in filling. Hopefully we have a few flaired users around who can help to answer questions and point towards sources of further reading for those that are interested.

The discussion topic will be open for a week and following that week will be a new submissions topic. Hopefully with many new, exciting, and different submissions than the previous week.

Hopefully with this month long rotation there is enough time for people to read and participate. I understand our daily lives get in the way sometimes and we can't always make time for things like this if we had a much shorter time frame.

Comments below have wondered if we could use a shorter format. I proposed this:

 We certainly could shorten it from a month to two weeks. For example,

 Sunday: submission topic

 Wednesday: announcement topic

 2nd Wednesday: discussion topic

 2nd Sunday: new submission topic

 This gives people a week, including the weekend, to read the article/chapter as well as the following weekend to think of and search for new articles/chapters to submit.


Please, provide your input on this idea because ultimately this is for you rather than just me or my fellow flaired users. I want a system that works for you, that gets you interested in reading more, and wanting to come back for more information or to ask us questions. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Whistling Sling Bullets Were Roman Troops' Secret 'Terror Weapon' </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-13 14:26:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Whistling Sling Bullets Were Roman Troops' Secret 'Terror Weapon' </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-13 14:23:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Portrait head, stucco and paint. Uxmal, Mexico. Maya. 300900 AD </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-13 01:07:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Portrait head, stucco and paint. Uxmal, Mexico. Maya. 300900 AD </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-12 14:57:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [OS] Portrait head, stucco and paint. Uxmal, Mexico. Maya. 300900 AD [800x957] </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-12 14:54:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> West Mexico: Ritual and Identity - exhibit opens in two weeks </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-12 14:27:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
