<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject4900</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-21 10:17:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> GGG don't want to implement an AH because doing so will expose how rampant bots are....

Botting is far more rampant than the average player realizes, and I can only imagine that the addition of the Russian player base increased the numbers exponentially. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-17 05:28:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yep same here. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-15 23:03:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I don't know that I would be praising them for charging 10 bucks a month to do that though. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-14 19:02:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> http://imgur.com/gallery/91sn32Q </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-09 19:06:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> rroot also PM's noobs to try to sell them hosting kickassd while pretending to be offering "help"...only to try to sell hosting contracts in private chat rooms. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-09 19:04:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> People should probably also be aware that /u/rm-rroot PMs pretty much every "noob" on here trying to sell them packages on his hosting provider under the guise of offering "help" via rocketchat. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-27 21:07:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You guys are falling for GOP tactics 101.

Intentionally misusing a term in order to try and redefine it.

The more they can intentionally equate "voter suppression" to things that are OBVIOUSLY allowed, the less likely the public will be outraged in the future when legitimate instances do occur.

Whoever reported this article took the bait hook, line, and sinker. 

The result is that this will just be categorized by many as another example of the "media bias/dishonest media" based on the headline and the actual content of the article. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
