<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject1963</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-12 08:17:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Shhhhh no  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-12 07:54:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm a girl with two "female" first names and a "male" first name. My last name is a color. (One word first name, two one-word middles, and a color.) What does that make me?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-12 03:23:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yo if Sad Machine gets anywhere near my ear holes I will cry. Don't tease me with this.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-12 01:44:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Tbh the only way this could be better for me would be adding Porter but thaaaats probably not happening.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-12 01:42:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Outfit ideas - booty shorts and #thickthighsquad shirts  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-12 01:06:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> They have all kinds of stuff! Last year they had free mini deodorants, hair spray, Bobby pins, body spray, and I think hair ties? Stuff like that. If I remember correctly there are pictures somewhere with an idea of what they'd probably have this year. 

All those things plus mints and face wipes. Now I clearly remember the mints because they were wintergreen lifesavers and they were suuuuuper nice at, uh, certain parts of the night!  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-11 23:47:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This seriously made my day!  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-11 23:22:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm in Los Angeles and I've gotten an identical message. How weird.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-11 22:49:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I've gotten this exact message, as have my sister and my mom. Where are you located? Maybe they're just sending this to everyone in a region. I got so many spammy messages from care.com, even after I removed all info from my profile after finding a long term gig. So bizarre.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-11 20:06:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Basically my motto all week  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-11 19:57:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Girl, I am a total hourglass shape, plus some chubby legs. And I wear booty shorts like nobody's business. It's like nine trillion degrees even at night out there. Nobody is going to judge you! We're a great crowd. Focus on not sweating to death. My first year I was so self conscious but honestly once you get there you'll see. No reason to be worried! :) just get something good for the chub rub (I suggest body glide, I replied to a comment on here too) and you'll be golden. 

Personally I've got two pairs of booty shorts I'm wearing, and a bodysuit that's not suuuuper booty but certainly not something I'd wear in the real world. I'm comfortable, I feel cute, win win.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-11 19:53:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Another AMAZING product is Body Glide - you can pick it up on Amazon for pretty cheap. I haven't had chub rub issues for years because of that stuff.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-11 18:10:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I've had an insane migraine for the last ~48 hours and my kiddos were immediately confrontational this morning. My fianc has been out of the country for work for a few days and I forgot how to grocery shop and cook and clean by myself because I'm sorta lazy about those things at home. I didn't have dinner the past two nights until well after 9 and I didn't get more than 4 hours of sleep each night. These little boogers are driving me crazy, the oldest boy is purposefully pushing buttons. I'm pretty sure we're going to just go to a park after school today so I can set them free. I'm at the end of my rope right now.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-11 17:47:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This makes the whole show at least six times weirder. Now I have to rewatch the first season.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-11 07:05:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Fianc and I have lived together 4 years - and pretty much since the beginning have split things by percentages. We have about the same wage gap you do, slightly different. I make about 1/3 of what he makes, so we take all our bills and multiply them by that ratio to get our monthly contributions. 

We also figured out a weekly budget based on a normal spending week - groceries, gas, home supplies, restaurants, etc - and split that total number by our ratio again, so we're contributing a fair amount to monthly and weekly expenses. With whatever is left, we pay for our personal expenses and contribute to savings accounts. 

My fianc keeps saying he wants to write an app for couples budgeting following a similar model, but totally customizable. I keep showing him posts like this to prove there's at least somewhat of a market for it!  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-11 07:00:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I (25F) am a Full-time Nanny to three kids, currently studying to become a Psychiatrist! Fianc (27M) is a Software Engineer. This will be our third EDC!  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-10 21:07:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If you really can't access the registry/are worried about doubles, just ask the bride. I'm sure she'd be more than fine passing off the info, and once you purchase something from a registry, it shows that it's been purchased so she doesn't get doubles. 

If that doesn't work out? Buy her something small and physical (wine/etc) and then either a big gift card to wherever she has her registry (so she can buy the remaining things that nobody bought her) or give her a check. It's totally acceptable nowadays, especially from a casual relationship like work friends. And she can either use it for honeymoon stuff or wedding expenses.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-10 20:30:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Ugh, I'm so sorry. The parents really just have no clue sometimes. 

I started a prior gig in June. I had been working two nanny jobs because I was on contract with one family until Mid-June and the second family really wanted me to work for them, so I was splitting shifts. It was insane. It was almost an hour commute each way to the second job. They started asking me to do things that were NOT part of the initial agreement (doing the parents laundry, cleaning the entire house, etc) and I did my best to keep up while really only working for them ~6 hours a day and the other family another ~7 hours a day. The first family, at the end of the contract, ended things on a good note. We'd had problems here or there but we hugged, it was sad, etc. 

The very next week I was going to be able to focus full time on this second family. Instead they had me drive an hour+ to their home, where they had the kids, to fire me on the spot because I "just wasn't keeping up." They knew and encouraged me to finish out my previous commitment and had SEEMED super understanding about the double job thing. Nope. No warning. And then they had the guts to complain about how they'd have to take time off work, and this was so inconvenient to them, blah blah. It had been like four weeks. They had barely given me a chance. 

Some parents, no matter how nice they seem, are jerks. They see you as an employee and nothing else, and they'll squeeze you for your last minute if they can. 

You'll find something better. I certainly did. I'm so sorry this happened to you.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-10 01:04:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Seconded. I used to use this for waaaay back in the day when I did synchronized swimming. Shit holds everything. Just use a little and it is THICK, so be careful. But it kept heavy bits of fabric/rhinestones/entire other pieces of clothing together during a hardcore routine in the water.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-09 00:47:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I second this foundation! If you're used to a thinner foundation it can take a use or two for you to get used to the feeling, but I love it. I am an absolute oil slick and this is the ONLY foundation that stays on my face all day. I'm wearing it right now. I applied at 10 this morning, it's 6 hours later and it hasn't budged. My old foundations used to melt off like this within an hour or two. 

Also, don't skip the hydrating primer. The combo of the hydrating primer and the EL have been my HG. I tried the hangover primer with it once and my skin looked so. freaking. good. Este Lauder will give you a sample of Double Wear that's good for a few uses and shade match you if you go to their counter. 

My other thing was powder - i found that a brush wasn't properly integrating the powder into the foundation, so it tended to look weird on me. I switched to Laura Mercier pressed powder and I use a powder puff to press the powder into the skin. So much better and it looks so smooth. 
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-09 00:41:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Cover FX makes custom cover drops - you can get a shade that's closer to your tan skin, maybe even a little darker, and just adjust the number of drops as you get darker. It won't change the texture of your foundation too much and you can use them for a liquid bronzer when you get pale again in the fall. A few other brands make drops like that but Cover FX are the best formula IMO.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Nmom chooses today to tell us that she apparently almost died in a plane crash?? Then brings up a mortifying habit I had as a teen in front of the whole family. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-09 00:23:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So... My mom. 

My abuse was 85% emotional/psychological torture. 15% physical. I was kicked out and begged back multiple times. Moved out when I was 20 (am 25 now) to be with then boyfriend, now fianc, because A: he realized my home life was shitty and B: he'd never had a relationship before and we didn't want to leave the bedroom much. Heh. I went VLC for several months, then LC, and still limit contact to a point but mostly I just leave a conversation/situation if she starts going off about weird shit. 

My sister (22, GC) still lives with my mom. Today we got together for Mother's Day and had a little mini brunch - minimal effort. Bagels and fixings, champagne and orange juice. My grandma came too. She's a good deflector/redirector when it comes to my moms shit. 

My mom decided to choose today to tell us that, prior to my birth, while she was working for an airline and flying every other week to visit my dad on base, she missed a plane once and that plane crashed at the Denver Airport and everyone on it died. 

The quote to end this story? "So if it wasn't for me, you wouldn't even have been born!" 

Uh? Obviously? Then says that I better be glad every day that she missed that plane, and on and on... 

Then later we're talking about makeup. Pretty much nobody who knows me knows that, at 18, I was arrested and charged with petty theft. I was a bit of a klepto when I was a teenager, I'm not going to look too hard into the psychobabble of why. But I used to nick shit all the time. Target, mall, gas station food, whatever. I stole makeup from my mom all the time, but always gave it back. I used to get beat for it whenever it happened, but it was something I just couldn't stop. I obviously don't do it anymore but it really screwed up my life for a long time. So she's talking about her makeup and then she picks out some crusty, ten-year-old concealer thing that's missing half the parts, and says "oh look! That's one of the first things you ever stole from me. Remember how you used to do that? I can't believe how bad it got. You're terrible." 

My fianc knows what happened, I opened up to him about a year into the relationship. I only took so long because I was so fucking embarrassed. It's been five years. She just brought it up to shove it in my face after yapping about how excited and grateful I should be that she decided to randomly tell us this story about a plane that I don't fully believe. Yeah, makes me super happy. Love you too, mom. 

Happy fucking Mother's Day! I'm leaving early, having dinner with my fiancs mother who is still weird but better than mine, and then going home and getting trashed drunk and watching Game of Thrones. ~  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-08 22:33:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You have two options here, and neither of them having anything to do with making a decision about going or not going. 

1. You go, you keep a negative attitude and assume that this guy must be using or mistreating your sister, and your opinions won't be changed. You keep using the wrong "wrong" or "off" or bothered. Your sister sees this, she feels like you guys won't let her live her own life (which she clearly already feels) and things do not end well for your relationship with your sister. Realize that she may cut you out of her life indefinitely. 

2. You realize your sister is a grown ass woman who can make her own decisions. You let her know you love her and that you're glad she's happy. You keep up a good relationship with her, independent from your parents relationship with her. And you support her. As you should, because she is your sister and she's given you no reason to think anything is wrong with her. 

Go. Have dinner, maybe spend the night out there. See how normal it probably is. Is it about money? Probably at least a bit. But if this guy was just an insufferable asshole, she wouldn't be so happy. She has made a personal decision in her own life. Respect that.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> I miss you so much/I wish I'd never met you. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-08 06:41:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> He was my best friend. Then something more. Then something else. There was only ever one kiss - and I panicked and pulled away, and we laughed about it, but we still stripped down to our underwear and cuddled most nights for body heat in my freezing apartment, we still drank in my room and watched stupid shit on youtube, we still talked til dawn and opened up to each other about the darkest parts of us. Matt was the brightest part of my life for a very long time. As his personality disappeared, replaced by a frighteningly alpha-male personality splattered with contempt for anyone who didn't think he was funny, we fell apart. It happened over four years. Or maybe it happened faster than that, and I was just too blind to see it. 

We both started dating someone else. They broke up. I got engaged. He made up shit about how he thought my fiance was an asshole, so he didn't want to hang out with him/me anymore - my fiance is a shy, quiet engineer who respected my time with my friends enough to not need to be the center of attention. Maybe that's what Matt hated most. No matter how hard he tried, after I got together with Shane, Matt wasn't my number one anymore. Not after how he started treating me. Not after the things he said about me, about other women, about people he cared about. All for laughs on the internet. He was there the night I was sexually assaulted, the summer after high school. He broke down and told me he felt like it was his fault, like he failed to protect me. He cared so deeply about me and what I had been through. But his mind has been poisoned, one way or another. He dismissed an argument we had about it, just a few months ago, as "personal bullshit" and, even though we were in a debate with a bunch of other people specifically about sexual assault, told me what I was saying was irrelevant and that he wanted me to stop bringing it up because he didn't like it. Yeah, well, I don't like how your attitude has changed, and your friends sided with me, so fuck you. 

I wonder how often he thinks about me - I know he does, a mutual friend says they've talked about me quite a few times. I wonder how often he thinks about how we are now - distant, cold, bitter. And how often he thinks about those golden nights, up until dawn, talking about our dorky middle names or his alcoholic father or his mom's cooking or Korean horror movies or the people we went to high school with or our wildest dreams or anything, anything about what the future could have held for us. 

I miss him. I miss him like crazy. I want to message him and tell him to cut the crap. To hang out with me and quit the bullshit, to be my friend again. But I also want him to go to hell. I wish I'd never met him. I would give up every single one of our good moments to be able to still have the ability to trust a friend. He ruined that for me. 

What we had was chaotic at best. Years of on and off, romantic and friendly, caring and spiteful. I can't make friends anymore because I just expect them to break my heart. 

So, thanks, Matt. You are the worst thing that has ever happened to me. I know you've changed. You're not the man you used to be. And you broke me. Little by little, month by month, year by year, then all at once. And I couldn't stop missing you if I tried. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-07 07:04:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I get this problem when I work out/sweat after I shave, or if I just get more friction from clothes that day. skin can be a little dry after a shave, and then sweat can really irritate some people. It's literally like putting salt in a wound - tiny scratches on your legs that get salty sweat rubbed into them. Not fun. Make sure you're wearing super breathable materials and moisturizing well after showers!  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-07 05:08:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Now play the whole show backwards at 20x speed and you'll hear the lineup! Also maybe Satan. Actually you'll definitely hear Satan, he was hosting this shit and DIDNT DROP THE FUCKING LINEUP 

/cries  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-07 05:04:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Pasquale 

Why you gotta play with ma heart like this?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-06 23:51:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> As a fellow oil slick of a human I will totally vouch for Este Lauder Double Wear foundation. It's matte, but not too matte, and it is the ONLY foundation that doesn't have me looking like a greaseball by noon. And I've tried probably upwards of 65+ foundations. I use a hydrating primer and let it set in for a bit, and then the foundation last. 

I also agree with what other posters have said - moisturize, no matter what. Excess sebum can be a result of under-moisturized skin, because the skin tries to overcompensate. I started using a gentler cleanser, a good natural toner, and two heavy hydrators at night - a full on heavy duty night cream mixed with a beauty oil. I've noticed less oil and less breakouts since I started this. It seems counter-intuitive but sebum production is a weird, weird beast.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-06 01:38:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I used to be like this too - I got so into an intense highlight! But you really can adjust a look so much by toning down the highlight. I'd suggest bringing the darker color just a little higher up, and using a more neutral, blended highlight instead of the same bright color on the lid.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-06 01:32:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Murad Mattifier and Este Lauder Double Wear Stay in Place foundation. I usually use something a little more hydrating for a primer because if I go too matte, I can see the poor texture on my cheeks and forehead - no fault of EL, I just have awful texture I can't quite get rid of. EL DW has actually been my new HG foundation because it doesn't budge all day, even on my super oily nose and cheeks, which has never happened before.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-04 23:10:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If you need someone on standby for distraction/assistance/taking pictures, hit me up! My fianc and I are going alone for the first time and I'd love to help out! Where are you guys staying? Even if you're missing the Reddit meetup, I'm sure there are at least a few people who would be down to meet up earlier Friday/coordinate a time to cheer you on!  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-04 19:24:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I wore one from Little Black Diamond last year with no complaints. I wish I would have gotten one that was a little less conservative (I wore a style they don't have anymore: short sleeves, full back, scoop neck, good coverage on the bottoms.) it was comfortable but I was worried about being self conscious. The material was fairly breathable though and at one point I just poured water on myself to cool down lol. 

As for the bathroom issue.. I couldn't stomach the idea of being all nekkid in a porta potty either, but I used to swim competitively so I'm used to just pulling the crotch of a suit to the side to pee. As long as you're careful, which is easier when you're hovering anyway, you won't have a problem.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-04 00:48:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm also team bright pink lipstick - shade match as close as you can obviously. A shimmery, neutral eye with a bit of brown/bronze smokey magic thrown in wouldn't be bad. A neutral blush and subtle highlight. I'd also do liquid eyeliner and big lashes but that's if you're looking to go a little more dramatic.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-03 18:25:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I went through a similar sort of thing, but backwards. My fianc had been super good friends with this group of people since high school. When he and I first got together he was living with three of them, we all hung out at least once or twice a week, etc. Slowly, they started doing stuff without us. I always thought it was because they didn't like me, so I got kind of upset. I let it pass because I know he's an introvert and, like your situation, he seems to far prefer spending one-on-one time with me than with any group of multiple people. I figured maybe he was turning down invites for that reason, but then got a few messages over a few months asking why we'd been so busy and when could we hang out? We typically weren't THAT busy (though we both have divorced and remarried parents, so four sets of that did mean a lot of dinner plans).

Ends up this group of friends had been steadily devolving into a shitshow of petty, immature craplords who just made every outing about exclusivity and being assholes. The group had pretty much been split into two groups of people that hated each other and spent their nights talking shit about each other. They were all still friends, but the years had turned them into people who my fianc didn't want to hang out with anymore. He matured a bit faster than they did. He didn't want to hang out with them, so he told them we were busy with something else, a family thing, I had already made us plans, etc. His friends suddenly stopped asking and again I felt like it was my fault. Nope. He had just finally separated himself from them. And it was less about him using me as a scapegoat and more about the fact that he just didn't want to hang out with these people anymore, but he wasn't a confrontational person and didn't know how to break up with an entire group of friends like that. 

Don't go all ham and break up with him for this. Yeah, it's kind of shitty that he's using you as a scapegoat here, but he probably just didn't know another way. There's always the trope of the controlling girlfriend who steals her boyfriend away from his friends, and he may have felt like they'd just shrug it off and leave him alone if they finally came to that conclusion. Admit to snooping because you were curious about the cancelled plans. But confront him about why he's making you his scapegoat. Is it that he just doesn't want to hang out with these people anymore? If so, be okay with that and know that if you stop hanging out with these people, who gives a shit what they think about you? I highly doubt your boyfriend is telling his friends these things with the sole purpose of making them hate you. He's probably just trying to make a solid demarcation from that group of people. I was just as pissed as you are now during that initial stage of separation because I thought it was all my fault. It took a solid half dozen conversations for my fianc to come out with all the problems with this group and the reasons he was acting that way. I really do get the feeling that your boyfriend is doing something similar. He doesn't want them to think he's a dick, but he doesn't want to actually see them, either. 

My fianc and I don't see that old group of friends anymore. I don't care if they think I stole him away. In the long run we're going to have an awesome relationship and we won't have to waste time with people we don't like. We can spend that time making new friends who like both of us and who we like spending time with.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-03 01:33:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Sign me up! FH and I aren't getting married until next spring but I have more to lose than he does.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-03 01:30:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Best </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-01 04:03:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I've never done it, but my friend did one year. She added a little eyelash glue to the sticky side one night and let it get tacky before sticking them on. She never had a problem.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-30 04:07:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Duckling season at Disneyland is my favorite thing. Fun fact, last year around this same season I took my camera to Disneyland and took a bunch of pictures of them because, duh, look. at. them. And then the next week near my house this mother duck crossed the street but her ducklings couldn't make it over the barrier and were frantically running around this fairly busy street, so myself and another Good Samaritan got out and chased eight ducklings down and helped them over the lil grassy median and they found their mom at the other side, and that's MY duckling story! 

They're so cute I wanna cry  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-29 19:09:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Just got an email back! I checked out that website last night and had no idea that was setup like that! Austin is officially my hero. Also he apparently lives super close to me since his area code and the first three of his number are the same as mine. Lol. 

Thanks so much for your help! I'm feeling so much less anxious about this year now. Phew.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-29 18:05:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This sounds like something beyond your control. It can be difficult dealing with parents who have skewed ideas of parenting. 

Honestly? It sounds like a much bigger problem than her not playing with the neighborhood kids. Her parents making her put that much effort into her appearance and then chastising her for being proud of other accomplishments is bizarre, especially at her age. If it were me, I would call the school, explain who you are, and give them a brief rundown on what's happening and suggest they have a school counselor check up on her. Ask that they keep your name out of it. A counselor is much better equipped to handle something like this, and the parents obviously aren't going to initiate that, so you might need to before they cause some real psychological damage to this kid.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-29 17:59:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Try to do it faster! If she made, say, 200k last year in 30 days, try to do it in 25 or even 20. I've done that one, shortening my time to challenge myself a little more.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Depression/Embarrassing event made me lose all of my self-confidence. Cue the intimacy problems and crappy attitude. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-29 08:58:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hey, so, a little background. My fianc (28M) and I (25F) have been together almost four and a half years, living together for all of that. In that four years I've put on like 25 pounds. I'm not happy about it, but I've always been fairly comfortable with my body, especially in my relationship. I know he's attracted to me, so I must be attractive in his eyes. I clean up nice, but I am definitely a bit overweight. Think size 12ish. 

I'm a nanny full time, and one of the kids friends called me fat. Behind my back, when he thought I wasn't listening. I felt particularly grubby that day anyway (hot/windy day), plus the middle girl who is 7 agreed with the kid, and it just hit me in the gut.  I went home and cried and my fianc did his best to comfort me. 

Since then I've been a difficult person to deal with. I've lost all sense of self-confidence and I hate my body. I feel like this one stupid 9 year old kid finally said what I had been thinking for a while. I had gotten too big. I had put on too much weight. 

For the few weeks since then, fianc and I have been going to the gym, eating healthy, etc. Except I've been a total jerk. I'm crabby, I'm moody, I don't feel like I can wear anything without looking like a whale. I don't even want him to put his arm around me because I know he feels my fat. A few days ago we went to bed and he started making moves and I started crying again because I felt like he was doing it out of pity. Like he just wanted to make me feel better. I honestly do know that isn't the case but in the moment, when I'm feeling vulnerable, it feels that way. It's crushing. 

How do I get my mojo back with my guy? How can I let him know what all is going on and how this actually really upset me? I don't want to be like "hey we can't sleep together for a while because I'm moody." But that's pretty much how I'm feeling. I can't enjoy it. I feel like I've lost 100% of the confidence he's helped instill in me over the last four years. I want it back.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-29 06:30:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Sweet. Fianc and I are staying at the Monte Carlo so we'll be super close!  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Onederland isn't a huge accomplishment for me, but I'm there! </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-28 23:59:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> My HW was 203 - I always told myself I would never get over 200, then I did. Started about a week and a half ago, have been pretty good. CICO, 3-4 workouts a week, lots of walking, much healthier food choices. 

I had put my last 20 pounds on in the last 9 months or so. I started a new job and just got lazy. 

Weighed in this morning at 198.2. Yussssss. Just short of a 5lb loss. I will never go over 200 again. NEVER. 

5'8"/F/HW: 203.0/CW: 198.2/GW: 130ish 

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Anyone else having trouble contacting them for accessible options? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-28 21:27:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I've emailed three times. 

I got the correct email off a fellow redditor a few months ago. I started emailing in mid April. Have sent one a week since then, no reply. I usually carry a collapsible cane and I have pain meds I carry in case of emergency. I have a degenerative spinal condition that is super unpredictable and can really mess me up if I don't have a solid place to sit and relax my back/hips/shoulders. This is kind of a make or break thing here. I know there's plenty of time left but I really don't feel like placating myself by reminding myself that we have almost two months is a good idea, especially if something were to be not allowed when I finally get a response and I would need to find an alternate solution at the last minute. 

Has anyone here dealt with their accessible team in the past? What's it like? Did you run into any problems?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-28 21:09:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You still can't be as loud as you want - you'll be in a residential area with other houses around, and if you get the cops called on you, say goodbye to your Airbnb for the rest of the weekend. Vegas locals are going to be pretty pissy about the influx of visitors for the weekend, I wouldn't push it too hard.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-28 01:22:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hooks would be easiest/best in that situation. You'd have to sew in some pretty big snaps/a bunch of them for them to hold up, and they tend to be a bit more obvious. 

Good luck! You better post pictures so we can see how it turns out!  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> I'm getting help. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-28 01:19:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It took a long time for me to work up the courage to do this. When I was 9 I started exhibiting signs of an Anxiety Disorder, so my mom stuck me with a child psychiatrist who asked me to "draw how I was feeling" and then shared every single thing with my mom, who would pester me about everything that I said that she thought might make her look bad. I stopped psych shortly after because I just couldn't stand it. It didn't help anything. I yelled at my mom, told her this wasn't going to help if I couldn't talk about things that were actually bothering me. They medicated me on and off, but I stopped taking it when it started making me into a robot. (Paxil! Screwing with kids since forever.) 

I'm 25 now. Two and a half years ago I was diagnosed with a degenerative spinal condition and thus have serious chronic pain issues to contend with. I have also, through one-off counseling sessions and a few professional assessments, been diagnosed with Depression. I have self-harmed in the past but have been clean for a few months now. 

The year or two after my diagnosis, I couldn't afford to go back to a psychiatrist. Now that I'm technically disabled, I qualify for government insurance. They cover outpatient mental health care and medication. 

I am taking a first real step. I've been thinking about doing this for six years and I'm finally doing it.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-27 23:49:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's like you stole one of the major problems of my teen years! 

When I was in elementary/6/7th grade, my grandma would take my sisters out for clothes every school year and some Christmases. My grandma then retired and couldn't always afford to do so, so I got chastised for not making an effort. My mom was morbidly obese at the time and I feel like it was a "don't make the same mistakes I made" kind of thing. 

The makeup thing was always so bizarre. She encouraged me to start wearing makeup in 8th grade "if you want to", which was nice. Then she started wearing some too. She would buy herself hundreds of dollars of makeup then forbid me from having any, but comment on how "patchy and cheap" mine looked. It never did. She just needed one more thing to control. Ugh.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-27 22:29:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Seconded. Tell them what's going on and I bet they'll be a little more lenient.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What was your favorite non-music attraction last year? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-23 02:05:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> My guy and I pretty much ran from set to set, occasionally found a clear spot to sit, and that's that. We were with two other couples so we were always halfway through trying to meet up with people. This year it's just us and we realized we never do any of the cool stuff going around, even if we point it out the first day and swear we have to do it. We occasionally go on a ride other than the Ferris wheel, but we usually forget. 

What's a cool thing that happens every year or that happened once that you'll always remember? We're hoping to do plenty of cool little things throughout the weekend this time around! Also I'm just damn excited and need an IV line of EDC info D:  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Chub Rub? Thick thighs? No problem. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-22 23:05:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Posting this tip this year since I haven't seen it yet and it's a LIFESAVER! It seriously saved my weekend last year and everyone who has ever gotten that thigh chafing rash should check this out. 

There's a product called Body Glide - made for runners who chafe, but just as amazing for those of us who are bottom heavy/chafe easily. Seriously. Your inner thighs will thank you. I bought a tube on Amazon a few years ago, it lasts forever. I sometimes reapply midway through the night but it's a small sacrifice to pay for infinitely more comfort. It looks like your standard deodorant tube - twist up, plastic case. But whatever chubby baby angel tears they put in there are awesome. I think it cost me like seven bucks, and security never hassled me about it. Some people have said security asks, but all you have to say is that it prevents painful chafing and they won't stop you. 

Especially with all the sweating/walking around, this stuff is awesome. Less mess and better staying power than baby powder.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> New insurance making me start a whole new treatment plan, just got discharged from the hospital for severe pain. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-17 08:46:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Do they think I'm making this stuff up? I brought over all my records, all my results and labs and charts. I have pages of doctors notes and my notes and notebooks full of symptoms and meds and everything. Things that worked, things that didn't work. 

Before I lost my old insurance in June-ish of last year, I had a decent HMO, a fairly attentive team of doctors. I was easily prescribed Percocet for pain, my pain management clinic helped me try a ton of different options. 

Now I'm stuck on medi cal because I can't work. It's nice to not have to pay for most things, but reaaaally not cool that they're making me start my pain plan over. They told me today that they want to start my pain meds on Ibuprofen 800s. Ibuprofen. Ibuprofen. I told them it wouldn't work and the doctor looked at me like I was just looking to score opioids. Ugh. Next Doctor, please. 

The hospital wasn't bad. I can luckily visit the hospital I was seeing before, and if I go through the ER I don't get charged. They gave me some decent meds, let me lay around for a while, and sent me on my way. That ER is like 85% perfect and I had an awesome nurse today. 

But I'm so dreading this MONTHS LONG process of redeveloping a treatment plan because some jerk thinks he's king of the world and sooooo obviously knows my body and my condition better than my entire previous team - despite admitting he'd never even heard of my condition before. 

And my back hurts like hell. They gave me Valium for muscle pain which actually worked fairly well, but not enough to really release these muscle spasm things I've got going on.

Just... Ugh. This whole system is so screwed up.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Former scapegoat frustrated with nMom's treatment of former GC/current scapegoat sister. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-11 23:30:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Mekdiaodjwoskdjqkdnwkca okay don't criticize my crap format, on mobile and can't type as fast as I can think here 

I (25F) had a rough relationship with my nMom. Verbally, emotionally, and occasionally physically abusive. nMom is bipolar and has decided some time in the last decade and a half that the doesn't need to be medicated for whatever reason. Okay. Her choice. But. No. 

I was kicked out or willingly moved out 30+ times, starting at age 13. No matter what I did, it was wrong. She would trick me into thinking she was better, that she was getting help, that we could have a relationship again. Then I'd come home to shrieking and stuff thrown at my head and orders to clear out of the house before she burned all my stuff or fought me or whatever. K. There were so many times she threatened to never speak to me again or to cut off my phone or throw away/burn/donate all my belongings, but no matter how many times she relented and gave me a few hours to clean/pack up, I still felt fear every time. Fights always escalated to verbal abuse within 60 seconds. I moved out for the last time ~4.5 years ago to live with my now-fiance, even though we'd only been dating a few weeks, because I clued him in to my mom's bizarro behavior. She is sick. I know. And for someone with no N experience, he almost didn't believe me. That changed quickly, thank god. I was VLC for almost two years. Things were good. The less I saw of my mom, the more tolerable she was when I had to see her. 

My sister is 3 years younger than I am. She was always the GC - mommy's girl, her shopping buddy, her best friend. My mom never pulled that shit with her when we were younger. To be fair, I always had a bit of an attitude. My sister was a brown noser. Still is. But my sister is also one of the hardest working, genuine, loving people I know. Which is why I am having a hard time with my nMom turning the tables and ruining her relationship with her other kid. She knows that didn't go well the first time. She knows what it did to our family. Shit I can't talk about. 

To the point - my sister hadn't answered my calls in two or three days. Not highly unusual but she was due to come to my house one night and didn't, which IS actually unusual. I shoot my mom a text asking if something is going on with my sister, and she says it's too much to text, can I take a call? Yeah, sure, I can. Do I want to give my mother the opportunity to drone on for an hour? No. But she's at work. She can't get away with more than 10 minutes. So I let her call me, and she proceeds to - I shit you not - give me a total valley girl voice, like she's twirling her hair on the other end and rolling her eyes about the *injustice of it all*. And she goes on for her full ten minutes about how my sister didn't clean her room (she has previously told my sister she doesn't care if the room is clean. She charges my sister $600 a month for the room, she's paying rent; she can make a mess.) so she called my sister and threatened to throw "all her stupid shit away". Uh. And she says it with this stupid voice like I'm supposed to back her up and like I should be proud of her or something? I don't say a word. 

So then she says she called my sister that afternoon and my sister didn't pick up. My sister was at work. She works retail and can't bring her phone on the floor. She gives my mom her schedule every week because my mom demands it so that she knows where my sister is at all times. My 22-year-old, grown, responsible sister. But my mom then gleefully tells me that she told my sister's voicemail that if she didn't call her back by some arbitrary time - less than an hour from when she left the message - that she was going to cut off her phone service and lock her out of the house for the night. Same smug, self-satisfied, "aren't I good?" Tone. I cannot physically punch people through an iPhone. But if I could, I would have. 

I hate that all of this got dumped on my sister when I left. This shit happens and my mom doesn't realize she's killing her relationship with both of us - not that she's got much of one left with me. I can't. I just can't. 

Just that tone though. And she's started saying stupid shit lately like "you know how your sister is" and "well you would know, you were the same/worse than your sister at that age." Or shit like "now that you're grown up, you understand." And "I just want the best for you!" Uh. No. Me aging five years did not trigger any kind of magic rainbow "it's okay that my mom abused me for years!" Feeling. 

My dad was an enabler. He remarried and married an N. My mom hasn't technically married her boyfriend but he's an enabler just like my dad was. It's horrific. 

I am fiercely protective of my sister. I have backed her up too many times to count. But this is the final straw. Nowhere in that conversation does my mom mention money. She normally bitches if my sister is like two hours late with rent. They had a system - my sister directly transferred her rent for the month into my moms account. There was a record. Apparently the last two months, my mom has been making my sister give her cash. My sister has always pulled cash every week for various expenses, so her withdrawals for the last two months are way more than her rent. No clear record. When I texted my sister asking her about mom's weird behavior, she informed me that both of those months, my mom has insisted that my sister didn't pay her the full months rent last month. So twice, she has made my sister pay her 750 instead of 600. She has told my sister that if she doesn't pay the "new, fixed amount" she will no longer allow her into the house and her belongings will go in a dumpster, her car/phone will be taken away, her access to her debit card (shared) and her credit card (not shared, but secured with a loan from mom), etc. My mom is stealing money from my sister. And threatening to evict her. 

The last year had been almost okay between us. Again. Tolerable. But this just destroyed any progress she thought she had made. 

And to top it off, her brother - my uncle - is getting married in two days. We have a very small family. This will not be easy. Help.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Couples meet up? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-18 09:09:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> My fianc (28M) and I (25F) are attending this year - our third. We went in 2012 and last year. The first year we split a big condo with three friends. Last year we split with two other couples. This year we don't know anyone else going! I think it'll still be awesome (and less stress with meeting up/losing people we're supposed to drive home or whatever) but we're a little iffy about the whole long weekend alone. 

Is there any sort of meet up for couples? Or should I just hope cool people find me on here? Lol. We probably want to do a pool party or two, walk around the strip a bit, etc. maybe meet up with a couple at the event at some sets who listens to similar stuff. 

We're so out of the loop right now with EDM but our long time favorites are Dash Berlin, Tritonal, Seven Lions, Alesso, Zedd, Hardwell, Knife Party... We're sort of all over the place. Not super big bass heads but still exploring. 

Let me know if you're a couple going solo (duo?) or if you are just some cool, similarly-aged people who would be cool meeting up with some laid back, weird, nerdy 20-somethings! Or if you know how to meet up with said people.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> On the positive side, I haven't had a depressive episode in months. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-18 08:45:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> "I don't eat brunch!" </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-12 07:14:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Good ol' Shower Harvey, shunning things like facial expressions and actual things to do and brunch. 

"I can't eat Brunch, I'm on an all-carb diet. GOD Ashley, you're so stupid!"  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The parents did it. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-03 07:13:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I would love it if the whole thing was a conspiracy set up by the parents. Like parents are hella protective of their children. 

So the Wine Moms and Shouty Dads all like "hey THIS BITCH tortured our kids. Burn the witch."  

Ella and Byron rekindle their flame while scattering flower petals beside Charlotte's body after Ella called her there to "talk" post-Radley visit. 

Ashley steals the tape from the farm because the girls didn't watch enough of it to see that she carries another muddy pair of shoes through the lobby.

Pam thinking "normally Wayne would handle this shit but it's up to me now" 

Mr D "WHO PUT THESE PETALS ON MY SON/DAUGHTER" and then just storming off and disappearing for weeks 

Peter wondering how he's going to mention that this was def another of his illegitimate children. 

Veronica totally wine-blitzed and wondering how she's going to go from swinging a 9 iron to waking up early and having a round table with her election team 

Melissa making a cameo to remind them to wipe C's fingernails and place her a little more naturally. 

Obviously at least mostly a joke and idk where Emoji A fits into this but if IMK could come through for me on this one I would be eternally grateful, thx. 
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Happy birthday to me... </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-01 16:26:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Five years ago I was the party girl spending my birthday with dozens of people who wanted to celebrate with me. 

Four years ago I had just met my fianc and he made me breakfast in bed. 

Three years ago I went on a bar crawl with my closest friends that was nothing short of a mess. 

Two years ago I had a big family dinner and saw friends all week. 

One year ago I invited a bunch of "friends" to dinner and spent the whole night picking at my plate while everyone talked about shit they'd done without me and hadn't even invited me to. 

This year my own fianc almost forgot to say it this morning. None of my family has reached out to me. I have zero plans and nobody has had the intention of even meeting up for a drink. 

I'm 25 this year, so, happy birthday to me. 

Edit: I love you, Reddit. Thanks for cheering me up on my birthday. Thank you.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> "Ezra likes small women, so what?" </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-28 00:10:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Uh, yeah, Aria. "Small women." 

Ezra likes high school girls, not "small women". 

Anyone else simultaneously experience total laughter and disgust at the same time? Ezra is such a bizarre character. I like crazy boozy hobo Ezra even better.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> I didn't like Caleb before but now I do? Spoiler-ish. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-22 12:15:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> For whatever reason I never liked Caleb before 6B. Not like an intense dislike, I just didn't care for him at all. Not my type kinda deal. I wasn't a huge fan of he and Hannah's relationship because it just seemed so high school. Like yes, they dealt with a ton of other things that irl high school kids do not. But they constantly fought and they never seemed to really appreciate each other. I just thought they didn't mesh well. I love Hannah but I just didn't like Caleb at all. 

Then 6B. I dig the haircut, first off. Caleb's. But the Spencer thing? They had some obvious, albeit light-handed, chemistry in earlier seasons. I noticed it and was a fan only because I don't like Toby all that much either. Sue me. Never a Spoby or Haleb fan. Not exactly a huge fan of Ezria either because that guy gives me the creeps. Always intrigued by Spaleb. Spaaaaleeeebb. 

6B is actually the first time I've reaaaally given a shit about the ships. I watch the show because it IS a nine ring circus... But man. Spaleb. Someone else posted about all their arm touches. As friends. And the hugs. They always seemed a little physical. A little too similar. Tbh Spaleb is endgame. 

I can see Hannah breaking off her engagement because she still isn't 100% over Caleb, but less like trying to get back with Caleb and more realizing that she still has some moving on and growing up to do before she can settle down. 

I go saying this and IMK is going to go put all the boring high school relationships back together in six episodes or less. Watch. Ugh. 
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Peel-off lip tint! </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-13 23:27:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> My first thought was "what the ever-living f*ck" but after I watched a few videos, I'm intrigued. I'm not a huge matte lip fan but I've been wearing KVD Everlasting Liquid because it stays on so well (and I just got engaged, we smooch a lot!) so I'm wondering if this could be a cool alternative for when I want something... Else. Lots of people said they've put balms or glosses over them and they stay forever. 

Anyone here tried them? I'm ordering some on Friday (Berrisom) and I guess I'll just see how it goes, lol  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Autocorrect almost tipped my nMom off to the fact that I refer to her, at least on here, as nMom. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-07 20:26:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> My mom doesn't even really know what Reddit is, but still. I frequent this place. After learning, a few years ago, that my mothers bizarre behavior had a name, I post and read and respond here fairly often. 

So. 

Today I'm organizing a lunch with nMom, my future (possibly N) MIL, and my grandma. We're organizing my engagement party and getting Thai food. She mentions over texts that she's starving because she missed breakfast, except she then says she did have food this morning. Says something about thinking about curry. But what kind of curry? And I go to type in "Mmmm curry." Except it autocorrects to "nMom curry". I send it. Cool. I'm immediately thinking she's going to google nMom and blow up. 

To most people this would be an "oh shit" moment. Except. My moms last name is Curry. Literally. And I have very limited sense of humor. So when she replies back with "huh?" I just said "lol, Mom Curry." She lols, I lol, the toaster lols, I stare in terror at my screen, everything is great. 

Funny thing is, our "Curry" is only spelled that way because my grandpa's last name was spelled wrong on his birth certificate. Should have been Currie. So thanks, hick town nurse from 70-something years ago, for misspelling something that my grandpas parents didn't care to fix, because now I got to use it as an autocorrect fumble excuse that potentially saved me from death by my mother's screeching.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> In 365 days my life pulled a 180. I have never been happier or more excited about life than I am now. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-04 20:21:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So, a brief review of what life was like for me a year ago. A few years ago I was diagnosed with a rare, incurable, painful spinal condition. I was in the hospital once a month, in pain every other day. The way my condition works made it possible that I wouldn't be able to carry a child to term for fear of paralyzing myself. My family wasn't terribly supportive and my boyfriend was drawing away. I think he was feeling like he couldn't take care of me. I hated my job. I wasn't accomplishing anything I wanted to do, I felt like I was at a dead end. My depression and anxiety were at an all-time high. Holidays with my family sucked, everyone was mad at each other, I'd lost a lot of friends due to my inability to function normally. We were frustrated with living with other people. And to top it off, just after all of this, I very suddenly lost my medical insurance and wasn't able to care for myself in any way. All of this came to a peak on Christmas Eve last year. I was miserable. I usually looked forward to the holidays, but that day all I wanted to do was sleep. 

This year, things couldn't get much better. My symptoms are becoming more manageable, my depression is barely there anymore. I love my job! I'm a nanny to three AMAZING, intelligent, clever kids that I adore, the family appreciates me and the parents are great (and gave me a SIZABLE holiday bonus for a nanny!). My family still isn't all there but we're on the mend. I applied for state insurance and qualified for Medi-Cal, which means I can actually afford to take care of my mind and body again. So even if depression pops back up, I'll be prepared to handle it like I wasn't last year. Holidays were crazy but great. 

Probably best of all is this: on our four-year dating anniversary, in front of the Disneyland castle, my crazy-shy boyfriend proposed to me in front of like dozens of people! The ring is a beautiful setting I've always loved, and the diamond belonged to my late grandmother. We're getting married! In the forest! And because my symptoms are under control too, having babies down the road is totally possible. So my fiance - my best friend, my rock, my person - and I are getting our own place again, and everything is looking up. 

Just kind of on a cloud right now and thought I'd share! 

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> NMom and future nMIL had their first real meeting today. Nothing. Bad. Happened. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-31 11:31:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> My mother is severely and supremely delusional and narcissistic. After her divorce from my father four years ago (an N himself) she immediately dove into a new relationship and used it to "re-invent" herself. AKA revert to the stupid, drunken high school party girl she was when she met my dad. AKA used it as an excuse to pretend everything between us is a-okay because she's "better now" and a "whole new person". She was fairly emotionally and physically abusive during my upbringing. She likes to pretend it never happened. I was NC for a while but I don't live with her anymore and I got sick, so, contact was resumed. I just don't put up with her shit anymore. 

I started dating my amazing fianc about 4 years ago and have been living with him since like two weeks after that. He doesn't yet know I was practically homeless at the time (mom decided day by day whether or not I was allowed to live with her, I usually wasn't for whatever shitty reason, I slept in a lot of weird places) but that's another story. 

I met his mom. Nice enough at first. But time showed me her true colors. She's the same as my mom. Almost identical. Except she never had the violent tendencies, just the blaming and whining and whatever. Confirmed by my future Sis in law. She's just a falsely friendly person. She gets nasty and shuts people out pretty quick. She hasn't really done it to me because I think she knows if she tried, my fianc wouldn't let it slide. She wants to keep on his good side, he's the GC and he fixes her stuff all the time. 

We got engaged a little while ago. My mom, his mom, my grandmother (who knows all about my mom and helped me as much as as she could) and myself had our first lunch today to discuss engagement party stuff. I as ready for weird remarks, for sarcastic laughter, for attention stealing and eye rolls. I mostly stayed quiet except to put in my two cents about the party. They talked. And talked. And... 

Nothing bad happened. Not a single thing. They both played nice. Even when they had slightly conflicting opinions. There was hardly any one-upping or anything like that. I walked out strangely relieved. 

I'm not letting my guard down or anything. I know crazy can strike at any minute. But wow. Wow. Wooooww. That went a thousand times better than I could have ever expected. When I told my fianc it went well, his response was "Good. Wait. Really?" 

Yes. Really. Miracles do happen, I guess.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Any advice for Wedding planning with Ns involved? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-16 23:13:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Boyfriend is proposing to me this weekend, I'm 99% sure. If not, next week. Yay! A supportive, loving person in my life who sees how my parents are and doesn't force me to talk to them/give me the guilt about "they're family!". Seriously this guy is amazing. He's my best friend. I'm so freaking excited I can't sleep. 

Problem - my parents are both narcissists. His mom is, too. Our parents are all divorced and remarried, so we have eight parents. Three of them are Ns - my bio parents and his bio mom. All steps are great and his bio dad is great. 

My mom spent the entire day of my devastating medical diagnosis talking about how she had to move offices, and wasn't that terrible for her? And why couldn't I just let her talk about her problems "for once". My quotes. Her emphasis. She's a massive drama queen and can't let anything go. Everything is about her. She will have moments of clarity ("I can't let my experiences with your father cloud how happy you are in your relationship") but it doesn't last long. 

My dad is a habitual, compulsive liar. He's just a jerk, basically. And he acts like he's the king and we all have to come beg at his feet for anything. He once lent me money (a few hundred dollars) and insisted that I didn't pay him back. ("You're my kid! Of course I'll help you out. I don't want you to pay me back. Let me help.") he then pestered/verbally abused me in order to get money out of me when he got fired from his job. I wouldn't pay him (couldn't afford to if I tried). My boyfriend went behind my back and paid my dad off and told him to quit harassing me. (Totally annoyed that he went behind my back and gave into my dads shit, but I can't be mad at the guy for standing his ground against my dad, who is a pretty big guy.) his wife is an enabler, to the max, but she also has her moments of clarity. She basically thinks my dad is exactly the king he pretends to be and that he can do no wrong. 

My future MIL is a bit of an N. She guilts her kids into doing weird shit for her all the time - getting my SO to help her with tech stuff for a church she volunteers her accounting services to (she doesn't even go to church) and just generally guilting his sister. My SO was very much the GC and his sister the SG, though their mom wasn't nearly as bad as my mom from what I know. 

I've talked wedding stuff with my moms and my SO's mom a few times. Mostly, I get the feeling that I'm going to have to be firm, draw a few thousand lines, etc. I have been dreaming about my wedding since I was a kid, my SO likes all the things I like, etc. We're not doing traditional who-pays-what kind of things. Any set of parents can contribute whatever they want. Totally privately. We've had each set of parents express interest in helping, financially. We'll put in the rest. But for the most part, the decisions are ours. If someone insists on something minor, fine. I don't care as much about the wedding as I do about the life that comes after it, so whatever. 

I don't know if I want my father to walk me down the aisle. He hasn't been a sturdy presence in my life in years. I was thinking of having my sister walk me. It might hurt NDad's feelings but, you know what, if he wanted that place of honor in my wedding, he probably shouldn't have abandoned my sister and I after our parents divorce and moved hours away, refusing to drive out to see us and making us drive two hours each way to see him. 

Just feeling ridiculously excited but also... Dread. Lots of dread. Each parent on their own is enough. I'm not looking forward to having all eight of our parents in a room at the same time. More than once. I've already told both of my sets of parents that if they step out of line and do anything crazy/fight with each other/fight with me or my SO, they will not be attending my wedding. My SOs parents aren't such a big deal, they've been divorced like 20+ years. My parents have been divorced like 4 years and still hate each other. 

Help. Any experience/advice? 
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Just had a two hour phone conversation with one of my best and oldest friends. It may have saved my life. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-11-25 09:56:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I have been feeling really... Not great, for a while. Not suicidal or anything, but not like I wanted to be alive, either. I'm overwhelmed. To put it lightly. 

I've known this person since we were four or five years old. We've always been friends. Even when he moved across the country two years ago to be with his girlfriend, we still caught up and saw each other when we could. That girlfriend broke up with him, so he called me tonight to vent and just bounce ideas. 

But he just reminded me that I'm not alone, that we're very similar people and that we care about each other and are great friends. 

In a moment where I felt very alone, he unknowingly reminded me that I am not alone at all. 

Pick up the phone. See your "person" or any person you know you can just vent to, or even just talk about meaningless stuff with. Relate to someone for a bit. I hope it gives you as much relief as it's giving me right now.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Feeling good for the first time in months and I can't even enjoy it. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-11-21 08:19:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I feel like someone's going to turn a corner and yell at me for something I haven't done or did wrong, hit me, whatever. 

I haven't lived with either of my Nparents in five years but I still get that total, wind knocked out of me, paralyzing fear/"oh sh*t" nearly every time I relax. It was always my fault, even if it wasn't. When I was enjoying myself, it MUST have been at her expense. There must have been some thing I could do or admit to, to make them feel better about themselves. 

Not even a half hour of relaxing. Cool. Not.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> How do I tell my roommate that his sick girlfriend shouldn't be at our house? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-11-17 22:12:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> A little background - I (24F) live with my fiance (27M) in a four bedroom townhouse with our roommate (also 27M), who is my fiance's longtime friend. His girlfriend was living halfway across the country for the first year. It was understood that once she came back, she'd be over now and then. Not a problem. But she's loud, annoying (not a lot of our friends like her) and inconsiderate. That's almost besides the point, though. That's gotten better, after we talked once or ten times. 

But last week, he got back from an international trip. Understandably, she wanted to spend some time with him. Only when they showed up, she sounded like she was hacking up a lung. Seriously. She's very clearly very ill, I'm guessing with a nasty cold or the flu. She's been here (minus two days this weekend when he was out of town again) for nearly a week, now. So not only is she nearing the deadline for being here, (our lease and roommate agreement both state that we can't have guests longer than a week without getting permission from the landlord) she's been at the house (even during the day when he's at work, which is not cool) while she's spreading germs, using our kitchen and cooking tools/dishes, etc. 

If I worked any normal job where I could take sick days or just go to work sick, it wouldn't be so big of a deal. But I'm a nanny for a family of three kids. Going to work sick means that I get the kids sick. In order to keep three kids from getting sick, I would need to stay home from work - which requires that one of their parents stays home from work to watch the kids. So being sick not only causes me to miss work/lose money, it affects the family that I work for. 

I can't take it any more. A day or two, when he first came back? Maybe understandable. But when she's been here for a week, hardly leaving, and sick? That's not okay. She lives with her parents, she can stay there when she's sick like she usually does. It's not okay to risk getting us sick, and by association the kids and family I work with. 

How do I bring this up? It may seem petty or less of an issue than her being noisy, but sickness is a zero-tolerance thing for me. I can't afford to miss work or get the family sick. I hate having to talk to him about her over and over again, but just when it's been long enough that we haven't talked about it in a while, she comes back and pulls shit again. 

Problem - she knows a lot of us don't like her. I know she's beginning to think it's a personal thing. I'm sure she's nice enough when I don't have to listen to her screaming at 10:30 at night, but that's the only time I see her, so it's getting shitty. I don't want these continued talks to keep making her mad and keep making her act up just to piss us off (she and her boyfriend/our roommate are kind of assholes, but they're better than a lot of roomates). 

Help.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> I'm getting engaged very soon. I don't know if I want my dad to walk me down the aisle - but telling him that might make him sever contact with me for good. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-10-26 06:00:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Okay, a little backstory - my parents were married 24 years and, except for the last year or two, seemed absolutely blissful. They were the least likely candidates for divorce among my group of friends and our family friends, so their eventual deterioration and divorce was shocking, messy, and awful for my sister and I. They had definitely fought over the years, and I will readily admit I was a very difficult child, but he and my mother were verbally abusive for some time, something I didn't realize until their divorce was happening and the image of our perfect family was shattered - the good times no longer outshone the nights of screaming, shouting, my parents pitting my sister and I against each other and themselves.

I was always closer with my dad, he typically protected me from some of my mom's more explosive bouts of anger (read: uncontrolled bipolar disorder along with other issues, I suspect) so seeing the way he treated my mom (and later, my sister) during this divorce was a little like seeing your idol taking a shit in public - super disappointing and really gross. He started mildly abusing pain medication he'd gotten a while before for a wrist surgery, became explosively angry at the littlest things, and one time followed my sister in the car while she took a walk outside the apartment because he was convinced she was going "somewhere she wasn't supposed to". (This is still a bizarre, unexplained incident. He and my sister fought about it once but I didn't want to ask.

My dad remarried less than two years after his split with my mom, and his new family is eerily like our old one - two daughters, about the same age apart, my stepmom has similar mental health issues to my mother, they do all the same things, etc. My stepmom and I have talked, on occasion, about how my dad used to be, and she doesn't seem to believe me. I don't blame her, the honeymoon phase can be blinding. But it's a little bothersome. They live about an hour and a half away, two hours with traffic (and we live in LA, there's always traffic). But he NEVER drives out to visit us, it's always up to us to go visit him.

My mom was far from perfect too, they were toxic to each other in their last year or two. I moved out just a few weeks after they decided on divorce, moved in with my boyfriend (who I'd then only been dating a few weeks, but we carpooled to our jobs and he lived with roommates/on his own so he was totally okay with me staying there while my family blew up, he encouraged it). That was four years ago. We've been talking about getting married for a long time, but it's finally all coming to fruition. He's supportive, affectionate, the total strong but silent type.

The last four years have been terminally awkward. My dad makes up lies about my sister and I. He's basically turned all of our extended family against us - even though they all know he's a massive liar. He tells them we never try to contact him and that we've blocked him on social media, when really it was the other way around - I offered the olive branch, I always texted, called, etc. My stepmom would always be watching his phone, convinced he was talking to my mom. She wouldn't tell him we called, etc. He just stopped making an effort. I hadn't fought with him since the divorce, but a year ago he deleted and blocked me on Facebook out of nowhere, and he still claims to this day that he didn't do it and he doesn't know what happened, but when I tell him he's the only one who can re-add me, he never does. That was over a year ago.

I'm so torn. My dad and I were always so close, when we do see each other it's like nothing bad ever happened, but... below the surface, it bothers me. Every time I see him I'm reminded of his little lies, his desperate attempt to paint himself as the victim in that divorce and what happened after. He's busy with his new family. I get it. But I always pictured my dad walking me down the aisle.

I went out to his house yesterday with my soon-to-be-fiance (We've had an appointment, I tried on rings, I'm just waiting for him to surprise me). It was fine, but he didn't even make an effort to really talk to me. Bare minimum. I hadn't even thought about it until today, but after yesterday's frustrating visit, it suddenly hit me tonight while eating dinner. I don't know if I want my dad to walk me down the aisle. I don't feel like daddy's little girl anymore. I have had to go from dependent on and very close with my parents to being fairly independent/living with my fiance. I wouldn't consider having my mom walk me, either.

I honestly don't know what to do. I've been the only one making an effort, and if I tell him I don't want him to walk me down the aisle, it might be the final straw with him. The problem is, I love my stepsisters and I want them to be my bridesmaids. So I don't want my own father to be part of my wedding, but I want his new daughters to be in it. It's just tough. I honestly think he might cease contact with me if I exclude him. I know it's my day, but is there a way I can present it/change tradition in a way that doesn't seem anti-him, it just seems pro-something else?

I shouldn't be afraid of losing contact with him, because he's sort of obviously an asshole, but he's my dad and he's stubborn. I have a feeling that once he's gone, he'd be gone for good. He's fought with my sister for so long that he's never met his first grandchild, a boy, and the kid's two and a half now.

I considered having my sister walk me down the aisle. That's probably what I'm going to end up doing. Have any of you guys done this before? What was your alternative? I've considered walking alone, too, because I'm a grown ass woman and all that.

I think I just need advice on HOW to tell him, and maybe like ten internet hugs. Sorry if this was so long! I just don't have a ton of places to go for this kind of help. Thanks in advance for any advice.
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> I'm getting engaged very soon. I don't know if I want my dad to walk me down the aisle - but telling him that might make him sever contact with me for good. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-10-26 05:50:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Okay, a little backstory - my parents were married 24 years and, except for the last year or two, seemed absolutely blissful. They were the least likely candidates for divorce among my group of friends and our family friends, so their eventual deterioration and divorce was shocking, messy, and awful for my sister and I. They had definitely fought over the years, and I will readily admit I was a very difficult child, but he and my mother were verbally abusive for some time, something I didn't realize until their divorce was happening and the image of our perfect family was shattered - the good times no longer outshone the nights of screaming, shouting, my parents pitting my sister and I against each other and themselves. 

I was always closer with my dad, he typically protected me from some of my mom's more explosive bouts of anger (read: uncontrolled bipolar disorder along with other issues, I suspect) so seeing the way he treated my mom (and later, my sister) during this divorce was a little like seeing your idol taking a shit in public - super disappointing and really gross. He started mildly abusing pain medication he'd gotten a while before for a wrist surgery, became explosively angry at the littlest things, and one time followed my sister in the car while she took a walk outside the apartment because he was convinced she was going "somewhere she wasn't supposed to". (This is still a bizarre, unexplained incident. He and my sister fought about it once but I didn't want to ask. 

My dad remarried less than two years after his split with my mom, and his new family is eerily like our old one - two daughters, about the same age apart, my stepmom has similar mental health issues to my mother, they do all the same things, etc. My stepmom and I have talked, on occasion, about how my dad used to be, and she doesn't seem to believe me. I don't blame her, the honeymoon phase can be blinding. But it's a little bothersome. They live about an hour and a half away, two hours with traffic (and we live in LA, there's always traffic). But he NEVER drives out to visit us, it's always up to us to go visit him. 

My mom was far from perfect too, they were toxic to each other in their last year or two. I moved out just a few weeks after they decided on divorce, moved in with my boyfriend (who I'd then only been dating a few weeks, but we carpooled to our jobs and he lived with roommates/on his own so he was totally okay with me staying there while my family blew up, he encouraged it). That was four years ago. We've been talking about getting married for a long time, but it's finally all coming to fruition. He's supportive, affectionate, the total strong but silent type. 

The last four years have been terminally awkward. My dad makes up lies about my sister and I. He's basically turned all of our extended family against us - even though they all know he's a massive liar. He tells them we never try to contact him and that we've blocked him on social media, when really it was the other way around - I offered the olive branch, I always texted, called, etc. My stepmom would always be watching his phone, convinced he was talking to my mom. She wouldn't tell him we called, etc. He just stopped making an effort. I hadn't fought with him since the divorce, but a year ago he deleted and blocked me on Facebook out of nowhere, and he still claims to this day that he didn't do it and he doesn't know what happened, but when I tell him he's the only one who can re-add me, he never does. That was over a year ago. 

I'm so torn. My dad and I were always so close, when we do see each other it's like nothing bad ever happened, but... below the surface, it bothers me. Every time I see him I'm reminded of his little lies, his desperate attempt to paint himself as the victim in that divorce and what happened after. He's busy with his new family. I get it. But I always pictured my dad walking me down the aisle. 

I went out to his house yesterday with my soon-to-be-fiance (We've had an appointment, I tried on rings, I'm just waiting for him to surprise me). It was fine, but he didn't even make an effort to really talk to me. Bare minimum. I hadn't even thought about it until today, but after yesterday's frustrating visit, it suddenly hit me tonight while eating dinner. I don't know if I want my dad to walk me down the aisle. I don't feel like daddy's little girl anymore. I have had to go from dependent on and very close with my parents to being fairly independent/living with my fiance. I wouldn't consider having my mom walk me, either. 

I honestly don't know what to do. I've been the only one making an effort, and if I tell him I don't want him to walk me down the aisle, it might be the final straw with him. The problem is, I love my stepsisters and I want them to be my bridesmaids. So I don't want my own father to be part of my wedding, but I want his new daughters to be in it. It's just tough. I honestly think he might cease contact with me if I exclude him. I know it's my day, but is there a way I can present it/change tradition in a way that doesn't seem anti-him, it just seems pro-something else? 

I shouldn't be afraid of losing contact with him, because he's sort of obviously an asshole, but he's my dad and he's stubborn. I have a feeling that once he's gone, he'd be gone for good. He's fought with my sister for so long that he's never met his first grandchild, a boy, and the kid's two and a half now. 

I considered having my sister walk me down the aisle. That's probably what I'm going to end up doing. Have any of you guys done this before? What was your alternative? I've considered walking alone, too, because I'm a grown ass woman and all that. 

I think I just need advice on HOW to tell him, and maybe like ten internet hugs. Sorry if this was so long! I just don't have a ton of places to go for this kind of help. Thanks in advance for any advice.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> My spinal condition is literally making me stupider. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-10-08 11:21:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I've been having weird neurological symptoms on and off for 5 or so years. Two years I was diagnosed with a rare and untreatable spinal condition, as well as a herniation of the brain stem known as Chiari Malformation. My Chiari is minor but the other issue is bigger. 

Sufferers of both of these conditions have brain fog. Like, almost every person. To the point where some people can't work just because they can't focus long enough to drive. 

I was always a smart kid - top of my class sort of smart. Amazing test scores. I didn't stick with college though, my interest in education waned, and I now see that it matches up with my diagnosis. 

I've been writing for fun since I was a kid. A few years back I decided to get involved in a book writing challenge. But I've felt less and less able to perform. 

My vocabulary is not what it once was. I lose words or jumble up sentences fairly frequently. I have a lot of trouble verbalizing or writing or anything like that. I used to write beautifully, everyone told me so. Nobody tells me that anymore. 

Writing was my THING. My identity. I've lost it. And I just feel so dumb. When my fianc and I got together four years ago, I was still making witty banter and having deep theoretical conversations and whatnot. Now I can't keep focus long enough to watch a 20 minute TV show. Hell, I can't stay focused for four minutes. I've tried. 

I hate this. I hate feeling stupid. But there's nothing I can do about it.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Recently found out my dog died after a few years of not seeing her. Am having a minor crisis. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-10-08 11:03:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> We got my old dog - Sunshine - when I was 8. She was a blonde lab, German Shepard, ridgeback mix. Doofiest dog in the world - sliding down our wood-floored hallways, walking straight into glass doors, rolling around in dirt, the whole deal. The very first day we had her, we had just come from adopting her, we went to a friend's backyard BBQ and this dog, my beautiful stupid smiley dog, bolts through the back door and takes a flying leap right into the swimming pool. She'd been the smallest dog of three in a single crate when we found her, timid at best, but she'd warmed up to my family within minutes. That was 16 years ago, and she wasn't more than 6 months when we got her. 

5 or so years ago, my parents - who had always been the perfect couple, always so happy - went through a horribly messy divorce. We had to sell our old house, and we couldn't find a rental near us that would allow big dogs. We couldn't just give our dog away, so we spent weeks desperately asking family members and friends to hold on to her for a few weeks. Finally, a really close family friend - also fresh off a divorce - let us know that he was moving out to the desert, to a little house on a huge lot with lots of space for a dog to run around. And that he could use a friend out there. I will never be able to thank him enough for that. She was getting older already when they moved. 12, I think. Limping a bit. But he sent pictures every once in a while or told stories about her jumping into the car and wanting to go everywhere with him - something she could do in his tiny town that we hadn't been able to do for her in my city. 

I hadn't heard anything from him - or indirectly through my mom - for a year or two. I was secretly sort of glad. I knew she was getting on in years, and as long as I didn't hear it, I could pretend she was still laying in the shade, chasing a truck, or sticking her head out the window. 

A few weeks ago I went camping with my mom and some of our family. She chose a nice day at the beach to tell me that our Sunshine had died a little while back. I wanted to scream. I hated her a little bit in that moment, just because she had to be the one to tell me. I had known it was coming but I wasn't ready. I held it in. I almost felt like it wouldn't be too big of a deal. 

It hit me all at once tonight. Every single thing. How she'd lay on the warm wood floors just inside our glass back door. How she scattered food like crazy when she ate. She was a trouble maker, for damn sure, but she was our baby. How she'd bound up to the front door when she heard the car pull up, reaching her front paws up against this little metal bar on the door so that she could see us get out of the car through the glass panes in the door. Her dirty, ragged Sun and Moon collar. The smell of the dog shampoo we used to wash her with in the backyard, my sister and I struggling to clean this crazy, playful dog in the summer heat. 

I got up and sifted through the single box of pictures I have from my childhood, praying to whatever higher power that there was a picture of her. There was only one. 

We're camping. The picture is of me and my dad, standing behind this huge driftwood log while Sunshine stands on top of the log. She had this habit of looking right at the camera when she saw us doing it. She looks almost posed, her tail wagging. It broke my heart a little to see it, but if I didn't have a single picture of her I'd be devastated. 

I've been like totally sobbing for the last hour and a half and I'm just writing this because... I don't know. I know it's going to be too hard to talk about her in person for a while, to my fianc or anything. I feel like this is as close as she'll get to a eulogy. A doggie funeral. 

My last years spent with her, I was a lousy, grumpy teenager. I wanted her OUT of my room, quiet, out of my way. Funny how you always regret not spending time with people, once it's too late. I haven't had a pet since, and I keep itching to get a smaller dog or a cat, but I don't know if I can go through this again. 

I miss my dog, you guys, and I'm so fucking sad right now.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> I'm done living in a world where literally nobody cares about me. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-09-09 10:04:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> My family fell apart and nobody makes an effort anymore. My relationship is stagnant and stale and pretty much one sided now. My job is alright, but I'd still rather be doing anything else. I have struggled to lose weight for years. I hate the way I look, I'm not cool or funny or fun to be around anymore since I got a pretty serious diagnosis a few years ago. I've lost all my friends. I just don't do anything and I don't care anymore. 

I used to enjoy life. I did stupid stuff and partied a lot and met tons of people, but I enjoyed my life at that time. 

Lately I feel like there might be so much more for me out there, but where? I don't have the means to drop everything and go looking for this ideal life, as simple as it is in my head. 

So I'm stuck in one place, not a happy place, with no means to escape and no desire to do anything about it. 

I just don't care. And I'm tired of dragging everyone else around me down too. I don't enjoy anything anymore. Reading and writing used to be my respite and now I can't stand to do either of them. 

I don't know if I'm just venting or what. Just really unhappy with basically my entire life right now.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Any new or old MLs in the mix? My sister is a first year Co-ML for my region. And any questions for MLs? Regarding our sanity, maybe? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-09-03 22:36:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm Kate (Justkate), third year ML for Long Beach and Torrance :: California :: USA. What a doozy. 

For our area, we're a fairly spread out region. Not nearly as big as some regions obviously, comparatively tiny to regions that are entire countries, but a solid hour drive from west to east or north to south. We used to just be Long Beach, but when I applied it was actually to form a new region in the Torrance area, and they asked me to take over Long Beach as well. It's twice the area and literally 700% more people. Making it work. 

Last year though I had my sister as my lead minion - super helpful. This year she applied and now I have her as a Co-ML! I'm not sure I've ever heard of a sibling ML team before. I got her into it a couple years ago (this will be her third real NaNo, my ninth) and I have been pestering her to stick around since. Aww. 

Any questions about what we do? I know every region is different, but for the most part we handle the same things. I can also give you an idea as to how weird regions work things out, either really big or really small, and what kinds of crazy things we've heard or seen as MLs that you wouldn't expect. Coordinating novel writers is thrilling stuff, you know. 
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Had a huge fight with my SO last night and even though we made up, we brought up a lot of stuff that has me feeling really shitty. 8 mos. clean from self harm but the urge is strong. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-08-19 21:24:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I don't know how much I want to talk about. I just need to say something, anything, to let it be known to this sub or the Universe or whatever that I am barely holding on. 

We made up but some of the things that were said last night can NOT be unheard. 

He didn't say it and never would, but I know that I'm a fairly useless human being. I give him my all but I know, I KNOW it's not what he deserves. 

Just feeling so lost and so empty. But really actually sad, too, like just... I can't describe this by saying melancholy or morose or anything. Just so, so sad.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Who actually liked tonight's episode? Not a sarcastic question. It's far from what I wanted or expected but I'll be damned if Vanessa Ray didn't SLAY tonight. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-08-12 05:47:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> There's only so much an actor can do with a weird piece of writing. I feel like it's one of those situations where very very early on they said "we wAnt CeCe to be Transgendered Ali's brother!" But didn't keep that in mind during the rest of the show. (Side note: I did not intend to capitalize that A. My phone did it. My phone is also A. Or my phone is Tippi. Who knows??) 

To be fair, though, this show is hella complicated. We all know that. We analyze pictures of hands and legs and hoodies and veils. For an ABCF show, we've seen a lot of shit. They wanted that to happen from season one, they wanted CeCe to be Charlotte/Charles, they did a fairly good job of explaining it. There's only so much you can do on ABC family. Obviously it wasn't most people's number one choice - a lot of people expected her to just be Red Coat, after all - but for the writer's intentions, their long term game, they did okay. This is the equivalent of a C+ paper. It's not as awful as others I've seen, but I agree it's far from what it could have been. 

But Vanessa Ray. Let me tell you. She was raw as fuck and I have ten times more respect for her acting skills and her character after this episode. I always despised the idea of CeCe as A/RC/BW because I just didn't GET her. I didn't get why, when it seemed so obvious that Ali was trying to emulate CeCe, that CeCe kept chasing after Ali, too. That's what didn't make sense. And the transgender aspect, to some small degree, fixes that. Writing-wise, it was not amazing. Far from it.

BUT you have to be an awesome actress to be able to pull that off. To audition for a chic, breezy, attractive co-ed, and then to hear years later about the story they've been planning for your character? That's insane. She did an amazing job with what she was given. If she wasn't half as good as she was tonight, I wouldn't be coming back for 6B or anything else. Was it sloppy? Yep. What about this ABC family show about a bunch of high school kids and murder and a cyber stalker and an 11th and 12th grade that span multiple seasons is not sloppy? Be real here, guys - while this show has done some great things and has had some ridiculously funny/great writing and plotting at times, we've always known that there are plot holes galore. We've always known there are issues. But we keep on with it because number one, it's a great excuse to get drunk on Tuesdays, and number two, we've become invested in some way. I'm sticking around. I think they did just enough - not pandering to audiences and not something totally outlandish. 

So, there are dozens of hate threads out there. I guess I'm just hoping to have one that focuses on moving forward instead of quitting.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> I bought gummy bears to eat during the finale. After eating half of them, I look a little closer. Guys A sent me these gummies... </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-08-12 04:22:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Can't watch yet because none cable. Instead here's a picture of exactly how bored/excited I am. Complete with Gummy Bears, Chickpeas, "A" Wine, and Spencer's Stoner Beanie. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-08-12 02:34:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Having one of those days where one person says something sort of mean to me and suddenly I hate myself. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-08-11 11:42:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I fully admit to being a little bit harsh sometimes. Well, okay, less harsh and just, like, I don't care what people thing about me on the Internet because Internet. 

But I've been on the sub for a show I watch and someone said I come across as rude. I'm like okay, that wasn't my intention, but yeah I'm a little brash. Sure. I'm not going to kiss your ass. 

Then she goes on to say that if downvoting is a problem, it must be my fault, and seeing how my comments on that post were downvoted, obviously people agree with her... Etc etc. 

Look, I'm not perfect. I am not someone to apologize for my opinion, but none of my opinions were anything close to offensive and I've seen worse shit on that sub. But pseudo-teaming up against me on the Internet because I'm not all sparkles and rainbows is bullshit. I spent way too long agonizing over what people thought about me and obsessing over every word I said, letting social anxiety issues rule my life. Reddit, prior to this issue, has been my one respite. Now I get this crap and I feel awful and, like, am I really that bad? Is this girl just butthurt? I do have to try really hard not to come across harsh sometimes, it's a coping mechanism that I've developed after years of being trampled on and being nervous and I don't like it, but I far prefer it to never talking to anyone ever. 

So now I'm up at three in the morning upset because I've just been set back a few months/years of progress when it comes to letting myself have an opinion/debate. Because one person on the Internet said something. 

I just... UGH. 

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Having one of those days where someone said something kinda mean to me and it's bothering me more than it should. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-08-11 11:28:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Apothic put out a limited release Red blend. So now I not only get to yell awful things at my TV over regular A wine, I also get to cry over a second bottle of ~fancy~ A wine. Channeling my inner Drunk Moms tomorrow. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-08-11 03:22:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> I [24f] have been with my bf [27m] for almost four years. We've talked about marriage before, but now his mom is divorcing again and he's super hesitant. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-08-11 02:06:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> A little back story: my guy and I met four years ago, didn't start dating until a few months later. He's never had a girlfriend or even kissed a girl before me, whereas I had plenty of relationships before this that were usually really bad. My last ex was abusive. My bf and I have been living together pretty much since we started dating. 

Right around the time we got together, my parents went through a really messy divorce after 23ish years together. They had gone from perfectly happy to totally toxic to each other, plus both of them slowly descended into either drinking or narcotics and cheating. So there's that. I handled it fairly well because I was just tired of the fighting. 

My ex's parents divorced when he was a toddler. His mom is a little older, she's very Type A but also very "I can shop away my problems" and "in with the old, in with the new." She places extreme value on THINGS. She's also very very dramatic and tends to always play the victim. She can never ever admit that she's done wrong (she also very loudly proclaimed at dinner one night that when it comes to mental illness, you're either faking it or deserve to be locked up. She knows about my anxiety and depression, but probably doesn't remember because that's just how she is.) and it bothers me and also my boyfriend that she likes to guilt everyone into everything and act like she knows what's best for everyone. His dad is laid back, nerdy like my bf, and fairly quiet like my bf. Totally cool, not confrontational.  Obviously it did not last much longer than it took them to make two kids, my bf and his younger sister. 

Both of his parents remarried years later - his dad to someone very much like him, and his mom to an even older guy who does custom car stuff and is also really laid back. His mom and step dad have been having issues for years, but only really bad in the last year or two. 

Boyfriend and I have talked about marriage before. Within the first year of our relationship we had discussed it and knew that we were very serious about each other and that neither of us had any desire to ever date anyone else again. He's very close with my family while I'm slightly less close with his because I just don't see eye to eye with his mom on a lot of things. We've discussed where we'll eventually get married, he knows that my mom holds on to my grandma's old diamond that we're going to reset into a band I like. The whole deal. But over the last year he's been avoiding the topic, something that I really kinda took personally (I've never given him any reason to doubt our relationship) and something that seemed sort of out of left field. I didn't realize at the beginning of this year how bad his mom and stepdad were. I didn't know that they're only keeping it cordial in front of family. So now I sort of get the avoidance on the subject, but... 

His mom has made it official. She is moving out of the house she's lived in with bf's step-dad for twenty or so years. Don't get me wrong - I truly am sad for her and I can't imagine what she's going through. But at the same time, we all sort of saw this coming, at least in the last half a year, and as neither of them are willing to work on it, that's that. She told us last night at dinner that she's staying home from the annual camping trip (that we take on her birthday) so she can pack up and move. 

We're in the car on the way home and boyfriend blurts out "can you see why I'm hesitant to talk about marriage?" 

And yeah, to a certain degree, I can see. His mom is now twice divorced. My parents had a messy split. It hurts, when divorce happens. 

But how do I talk to him and make him realize that that's NOT US? That we are a VERY different couple (we're extremely communicative and insist on fixing our problems, we've had meetings to discuss our communication strategies and finances and how to better our relationship even when we're on 100% perfect terms) and that he can't let this instance, in which that one couple wasn't good for each other, completely tarnish his views on marriage? We've talked about getting married literally dozens of times before. I know it's hard for him to see his mom split. 

And the straw that's about to drop on the camel's back is this - I have a chronic illness. I'm disabled, not completely to the point of loss of mobility but I have many restrictions on what I can and cannot do. I have a lot of doctor's appointments that I can't even always get to. Due to my dad lying about losing his job (remember those narcotics I mentioned earlier? Yeah.) I just lost the great medical insurance I used to have. It was always our plan to get married before I was 26, because a: science says that couples who are together too long before getting married can have issues and b: that's when I stop getting covered under my parents insurance, so I could then use his. Also, we'll have been together 6 years, that's plenty of time. 

Now I'm worried he's going to throw things off and/or try and avoid marriage like the plague because of his mom's second divorce. I'm obviously a lot less concerned about the insurance than I am about the guy I want to spend my life with suddenly casting off the benefits to getting married.

How do I reassure him that our relationship has not changed? And how do I get him to disconnect his feelings over his moms divorce and marriage in general? I'm just worried that this guy that I see growing old with suddenly is convincing himself that he doesn't want the same things he used to and I don't know how to talk to him about this. Any advice appreciated.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Why are people ruling out the boyfriends? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-08-10 21:27:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I've seen so many lists where people just rule out Ezra, Toby and Caleb at the very least because... Why? One I saw claimed that they had been in a room with the girls when A was present. How are we sure that was A? We know there have been so many people in black hoodies and multiple people in red coats, so how can you possibly rule out three major characters who have been around for a considerable amount of time just because they were in the same room as a black hoodied figure? Tbh like 90% of Rosewood has been in the same room as someone with a sketchy costume, the boyfriends are not exceptions. 

(Also I'm ready for your downvotes, but, besides Mona and Caleb, who have we seen that has considerable hacking skills? So many A things revolve around deleted hard drives and wiped phones and changed records, so who the fuck is doing it? Someone on the A team has skills. People immediately rule out Caleb because they think he's ~dreamy~ and they don't want it to be him, but he's got the abilities, for sure.) 

These three have always just seemed sketchy as fuck in one way or another at one point or another. Idk. Im not saying I definitely think one of them is A obviously or that they're all canoodling with A, but I don't think that their involvement can be vetoed because of a scene or two with a black hoodie.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The clown? Here's a line from S04E03 that seemed like a throwaway at the time. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-08-08 01:19:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Guys don't forget that moms drinking wine and doing dumb stuff has happened before. Ella and Ashley get drunk and talk about a three-way. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-08-07 10:14:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Now that we only have one episode left, who do you want A/RC/BH/BV to be? Who do you actually think it is? And who would piss you off if they were actually included? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-08-05 07:35:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> There are so many theories out there, let's hear them all. 

I think Charles is involved but maybe not Uber A. I honestly think that assuming BH and A are the same person is a little... Boring? A has so many contacts and is in so many places at once, and besides having a team, I feel like this whole situation must have come out of two or more people, meeting and sharing their grudges against the girls/Ali in particular, and then pushing each other to go after revenge. 

WANT: I want it to be Toby/Jenna/Lucas/Mona/Melissa, in some order. I know this is not a popular theory, but again adding to the fact that there could be so many black hoodies out there, as has been proven to us previously, any of these people have motivation. Significant motivation. And in one way or another, they've all met - Toby and Jenna through their history and their betrayal and being used by the girls, Lucas being shafted by Hannah and being tormented for years, Mona and her old A game and Lucas helping then, and Melissa angry with Spencer for destroying both of her serious relationships and messing with her life, intentionally or not, etc. 

THINK: I think it's a mixture of people. I think Rhys is definitely involved, and I think that some kind of switch happened - either Alison/Bethany or Jason/Charles. We still haven't figured out the possible twin thing, so I assume that whoever has a twin involved, we're going to learn that one of them is involved. 

DO NOT WANT: If it ends up being any combo of Wren/any dead character (Garrett, Ian, Jessica, whatever) I'm going to be disappointed 

I'm currently re-watching most of the important episodes to work out concrete clues, but all I can see right now is that the whole thing with the older generation, NAT... It all feels so disconnected now. And none of that feels like significant motivation to trap and torture 7 girls. 

If this post seems a little rambling/random, just understand that I drank about as much wine as the liars moms did tonight. NO RAGRETS. 

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Okay, so there were plenty of answers this ep. Just not direct ones. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-08-05 07:07:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Obviously not the ones we were hoping for - did some of you honestly believe they would reveal A in an episode that wasn't the finale? Do you even TV? - but a number of things anyway. 

- A (or the BH she sees) is someone Ali knows, and it has to be someone she knows fairly well, because that face. 

- Kenneth has obvs been missing for a while - but where? Assuming nefarious causes, we have to also assume that this is someone who has a vendetta against K. Any thoughts? 

- From the preview anyway, we know the Liars have heard BH's story (I'm still not convinced that BH and Charles are even the same person, because why can't Charles have a hoodie-d lackey? Or why can't BH be A and Charles is his accomplice/teammate?) and that it is not a pleasant story. Even if they're just trying to talk him down from the ledge, they know that this person had a serious personal motivation. Whether or not it was actually justified will depend on what we see next week, but they all seem genuinely concerned when it seems BH is about to jump. Not disappointed that BH won't rot in hell, but... Upset? Sad? Who would they be that upset about? I believe the redemption story, while maybe not justifying everything that has happened to them, might have some slight moral grounding

We've been told to focus on the Why, more than the Who. I've seen so many totally crackpot theories from people who just match up half a dozen seemingly related "clues". But most of the majorly spouted theories don't have the substantial personal motivation that would be required to do these things. 

Or it could "just be Rosewood, lolz" which, just in this one case, I doubt.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Okay, I'm sort of lost. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-08-01 14:07:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I've only watched the series through once. I binge watched at night when I couldn't sleep. Before S5, I went back and tried to re-watch it all, but I'm... Easily distracted. 

I follow the story as far as current events go, and I remember 95% of earlier seasons, but I'm missing a few things. Like, it seems to be a pretty well-posted theory that Charles doesn't really suffer from any mental illness, that the reason he's locked up is because of... Something? Mrs D and something? But it doesn't sit right with me that an entire staff at a psychiatric hospital would all declare this boy insane with no reason. He clearly did some messed up shit when he was younger, but Ali mentions many times that the boy she remembers wasn't harmful or weird. I know that Rosewood is like 4% reality and 94% TV and 2% secret twins and ghosts but the back and forth seems to be confusing me. Can anyone explain what exactly is canon? 

Okay, and then as far as the old questions go - who's in the barrel, the Bethany thing, etc. I don't quite remember if Bethany was ever canonically related to the story or if it's all spec. And I don't remember how. 

Lastly, I keep seeing Wren and CeCe as suspects. I know CeCe's got her own motivations (the girl down the stairs, etc) but I don't remember what Wren's grudge might be. I remember him acting sketchy, but does that bump him up to being A, or does it just mean that at some point he might have been working with A? 

(Side note; I'm on a good amount of meds for a spinal condition/pain/migraines/etc so my memory is foggy on normal things. PLL has been tough for me for a while and hard to re-watch because tiny details don't stick.) 

So, if anyone either cares to answer questions or point me in the direction of a detailed, explanatory fan site, it would be much appreciated. Now I have a headache.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Not sure where to go from here. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-08 12:50:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> 24. Recently lost a pretty great job. Chronically ill with a degenerative spinal condition. Had a few months with very little pain, and now it's all flooding back. Making up for lost time. 

I have only briefly talked to a therapist about it, but in addition to depression and GAD, I most definitely have PTSD from the car accident that may have triggered my spinal condition. Every quick stop when someone else is driving is agony. My body starts to feel like... What are those orbs? The ones where you touch the glass? Google says they're plasma orbs. I feel like that. Except suddenly, someone puts both hands on the glass. It causes actual physical pain. I hate driving, but I hate being a passenger too. This happened November 2011. Has only gotten worse. 

Lost my job because I'm incapable of actually giving a shit. I just don't. I half ass everything because I just don't see the point of working my ass off in pain for a paycheck that will undoubtedly go solely to regular bills and medical. 

Pain has come back. What was once an "8" every day lowered down to a "3" for, actually, a good month or three. I have had very minor flares, but none lasting more than a day or so. It's slowly but surely creeping it's way back up to a constant 6/7. And the worst thing is, I had appointments - psych, Neurology, etc - but since I lost the job, I can't afford the copay. 

I'm extremely lucky to have been with my boyfriend for 3.5 years. He has offered to take the financial burden from me, going as far to say that even if I'm totally out of work, we can get by. I don't want him to have to do that, but I can't see myself struggling through a job search again. I would hate to even ask him for the copay for my appointments because it really isn't in budget. To top it off, he's emotionally just not there. He never has been. I know he loves me, but we've had a lot of issues, some related to my illness. He actually almost broke up with me once, told me he was unhappy, that I was a financial drain - come to find out that a lot of those exact thoughts were planted by a "friend" of his who wanted my boyfriend to be the pliant guy he could take advantage of. He would call my boyfriend and have him come over to help do repairs on his parents house, and then he'd leave him there to do all the work. None of our "friends" (I do that because none of them actually give a shit about me/us) liked this guy. Boyfriend got the picture and obviously we're still together. Things actually got better after that, but my boyfriend is an awful communicator who literally thinks that walking away from an argument or conversation will make it go away. We're working on it. So he's forthcoming with financial help, but emotionally distant. I want it the other way around, really. He's also a total workaholic, so we'll be watching a movie or with my family or whatever and I'll look over and he's remoting in to his computer and working. 

I have no real friends. Our friends all grew distant around the time I got sick, they hang out without us and don't bother to invite us, even though I've never turned down an invite because of my pain. I don't like to talk about it, either, so it's not like they don't want to hang out because I won't shut up about my problems. Boyfriends other friends recently stopped inviting him along too because apparently he turns down invites that I never knew about. And those friends blame me and my illness. I'm the bitch girlfriend who doesn't let him out of the house, right? Oh, except I invite people over all the time and push him to spend time with his friends because he doesn't make the effort. 

The friends I had before this relationship are all gone. One girl, my only real girl friend, I see her every year or so. My best childhood friend has been pretty great. He drunk texts me or just texts me randomly to say he's thinking of me and hopes I'm okay. I don't feel comfortable telling him that no, I am not okay, because he's the kind of person that would actually take an interest. He'd fly out here within days if I told him I needed him. I don't have feelings for him, never did, but his girlfriend is lucky to have a guy that is not only responsible, but fiercely loyal to his friends.

My parents are worthless when it comes to talking about this. I have a truly narcissistic mother who is too wrapped up in her own little world. She and my dad split four years ago, she cheated on him and then lied to my sister and I and said my dad cheated. We're not stupid. My mom magically had a boyfriend within weeks of separating from my dad, after 24 years of marriage. Anyway, she and her guy and my sister live in this big house near the beach, they always have people over, etc. She "forgets" to invite me, and reddit people have really helped me to realize that it's not about me, she's the problem. She doesn't want to invite me because despite what I'm going through, I love being social and talking to people. And often my illness comes up. She has a tendency to ignore my illness and turn everything back around to be about her and her oh-so-hard life. My sister has almost always been mommys girl, until she has recently started to come around. My sister is sometimes a pretty good support system. She was what the raised-by-narcissists community likes to call "fleas" from my mother. I'm sure you can get the picture. She's not bad.

My dad is worse. He put me on his insurance for work that he doesn't even have to pay for, and suddenly I should just do all the work in our relationship. He met a woman shortly after the divorce and they remarried. She has two daughters, a little younger than my sister and I, and they're pretty cool. But my stepmother is a little narcissistic too. And she gets a little paranoid, so she answers my dads phone and stuff, and I never get to just talk to him. I always was close with my dad until he got remarried, now his new family takes up his time. I spent two years being the only person to put effort into that relationship before I just stopped. It's up to him now. It's too emotionally draining for me to have to be the only person making an effort in my relationships. If I stopped trying to contact people and keep up with them - family, friends, anyone - I would just have no one. I already pretty much have no one. 

I was on the path to going back to therapy when I found out that my dad has been lying about not working. He works for the state through the union, so all his jobs are short contract. He swore he was going back to work in December. I now find out he hasn't worked since November. It's July. Which means that he could be removed from the list and I could lose insurance. He would rather lie to me and swear he's about to work than warn me. I only found out because he had to update his income in court for alimony and child support for my sister. So I could have potentially started therapy, only to show up just after I start trusting someone and get turned away for lack of insurance. I can't do that. 

I don't qualify for disability because I haven't earned enough "work credits".  I don't qualify for most kinds of aid because they require you to list the income of whoever is taking care of you, and my boyfriend makes okay money. There's no wiggle room - we live paycheck to paycheck just affording basics. They see that and say I'm fine and don't qualify. So I can't pay co-pays, can't see my doctors as often as I should be. I'm in pain, I'm depressed, I'm out of work. Repeat. 

Boyfriend offered to pay my copays. Said we can rearrange some bills and deposits, i need to take care of my health. Great. Again, he's making a financial offer in lieu of emotional support. 

I have a minor history of self harm. I don't feel the urge to lately, only because I don't actually want to feel anything. Not feeling things is probably what is best right now. 

TL;DR chronically ill 20-something with emotionally distant SO, shitty family, no friends, just lost my job, Depression/GAD/PTSD.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Help with Roommate/His Encroaching Girlfriend. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-08 05:54:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Alright, here's the story. 

My boyfriend and I have been together 3 1/2 years. Let's call him Sam. At the time, Sam was living with a few roommates, all friends, in a 4 bedroom townhouse that Sam's dad owns. I started staying over at his place from fairly early on, he'd drive me to work and we'd basically just come back and eat/sleep before the next day. He lived in the master suite and his roommates were all single dudes except one, whose girlfriend was across the country at school. Let's call him James and his girlfriend Carla. Carla would come into town and stay a few days at a time, mostly keep to herself. Not a big deal. Nobody ever voiced a problem with girls staying over and like I said, I kept to myself. I was very, very rarely there when Sam wasn't, I would go home to my parents place. Flash forward a few months, we all move out. 

Flash forward another year and a half, and the townhouse is available again. I'm out of work (I got a bad spinal diagnosis in our time away) so it makes sense for us to take on a roommate or two and save money. We reach out. James wants to move back in, as does our other friend Ian. At this point, Carla is still in school, so Sam and I are effectively living with two NEAT, QUIET professionals/bachelors. We provided all the furniture for common areas, all the dishes, etc. It goes pretty well for a while. Carla moves back about 8 months ago. A few months later, Ian decides to move back in with his parents. Not a problem. James, Sam, and I have a meeting where James is very clear that Carla does not want to live with him (traditional parents, money, etc. she works about an hour away and has her own place out there in addition to her room at her parents place, which is near to here). Okay, so the three of us resign for a month to month lease. 

Soon after, we sign a roommate agreement that goes over taking care of the common spaces, quiet hours, etc. One specific clause is that if a roommate has a potential guest that is staying more than 10 consecutive days, that tenant has to ask the landlord and some arrangement has to be made regarding bills and rent. 

Today is day 10. That might be fine if Carla still kept to herself, but she has not. Oh, dear god. 

She stomps up and down stairs, she never shuts up (and not only does she constantly yell, she puts on this false cutest stupid voice and it's annoying as hell). She brings her friends over in the middle of the day, she has a key and let's herself in whenever. She takes up the entire kitchen during the day (the entire pretty big kitchen) for hours at a time. She's here constantly. Like I said, ten days straight, and it's not like she goes away for a week after times like that - she's here probably 20-25 days out of the month. 

We tried having a discussion with him once, about her being over for a week straight and the change in bills, and he brushed us off and said it was a one time thing because she had some test for her internship thing. Okay, we let it slide, he knew it was an issue. It's only gotten worse since then. She's practically moved in. She has no regard for Sam and I, and she and James play stuff at loud volume, hoard dirty dishes, don't sweep or clean any of the common spaces, etc. She does her laundry here, monopolizing the machines for hours. She uses our cooking stuff (mixing bowls, pots, etc) to store huge batches of food in the fridge. We then can't cook with the things we need. Sam and I know we want our own place, and health-wise I'm finally at a place where I can start working again, but it's not happening any time soon, financially. James has made it clear that he won't move out until we do. He's also had multiple occasions where he basically throws parties at the house with no prior warning, sometimes Sam and I come home from a long day of errands and crap and just want to watch a movie in the living room, on our couch, on our tv, but we walk in to 15 people crowding our living room and either a booming movie or a bunch of people partying. Like, at least ask if it's cool. They're mostly mutual friends. We might have even liked to have join. But we don't get so much as a courtesy text. 

What do we say to him? We can't really just knock on his door and talk because she's always here. He's also fairly confrontational and we're worried he'll get super passive aggressive again; he tends to do that. But they're not being considerate of our space or the common spaces, and like, if she had a key for emergencies or was here once in a while, fine. But when she's making it so that I can't make my own meals everyday, it's too much. We would never have agreed to live with another couple. It's gotten to the point where I'm miserable living here, Sam hates it too. We're afraid of pissing off James because he and Sam were like best friends once, but this is insane. 

EDIT: TL;DR; my boyfriend and I's roommate was pretty cool, his girlfriend moved back, now they're an amalgam of annoying behaviors to the point of making us miserable.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Needed a place to store my ear headbands. Built one. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-06 03:46:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Question #2 - premier parking. Worth it? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-01 00:27:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Everyone knows the exit/entrance is a clusterfuck. Boyfriend and I are probably going VIP next year for various reasons, but what about premier parking? How much did it cost, how fast did you arrive/leave, etc. 

Saturday on the way out, we left at like 4. We literally didn't get back to our hotel until like 9. That's unacceptable for me. If premier is faster, we may end up going for that.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> VIP - Worth it? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-30 23:05:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hiiii friends. I was lucky enough to not get the withdrawals until this morning... But by this point the feels have accumulated and I am already planning next year. 

My question is really posed for anyone who did VIP this year. Was it worth it? A lot of people were complaining about the giant price hike this year, but from what I saw, it looks like they included a lot more stuff too. (I saw something about free drinks?) 

Just looking for a first-hand (or second, even) account of whether or not it was worth it. For me, it might be worth it for parking and entrance alone, everything else would just be bonus. My guy is sort of impatient and the parking situation getting out was just insane. We literally left the gates at 4:30 one morning and didn't get onto the freeway until almost 8. It sort of ruined the sunrise vibes for both of us. 

Sunday we did Valet, which was infinitely better, but for $60 extra for that, plus maybe faster entrance, plus places to sit (I'm disabled but when I contacted insomniac they wanted me to jump through a billion hurdles just to prove I needed a chair here and there)... It may be worth it. Boyfriend has a decent salaried job and I'm looking to hire into an okay job too, so while we don't have a ton of disposable income, we could definitely make it work if we thought it was worth it. 

Thanks in advance for all replies :) looking forward to next year already! 
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> NMIL and oblivious/enabler fiance. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-10 01:10:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> A little context - S (Fiance) and I have been together 3 1/2 years. We've talked about marriage a few zillion times, and while he hasn't proposed yet, we know we're on the way there. We're just both really financially nitpicky and want to make sure we can afford exactly what we want before he proposes and we get married. We've lived together for almost all of our relationship, mostly because I was escaping my own NMom and a pending divorce between my parents, plus S lives on his own and it just sort of worked out. 

In the beginning of our relationship, S's Mom (we'll call her N, fitting) was super super nice to me, like all the time. We got lunch a few times, we seemed to really get along. It didn't stay like that. It never does, in laws are interesting, but S is sort of a Momma's Boy to begin with, and he doesn't see the things she does. I mean, he SEES them, but he doesn't think her behavior is out of the norm. She was a little older when she had S and his sister. Married late, divorced while the kids were toddlers, remarried fairly shortly after. She's gone slowly weirder and weirder, in terms of her attitude towards me. Sometimes she's still super nice and almost overtly so, but other times she'll pick fun in a sort of stuck-up, holier-than-thou, condescending sort of way. She's fairly well off, she retired quite some time ago. She managed a bank for a long time, so she thinks she's the know-all, end-all when it comes to financial knowledge and what will work best for S and myself, even though our situation right now is not anything she's ever had to deal with (I have a serious chronic illness/pain syndrome, and though I manage to work and live around it, it's the bills and things that she acts like she can counsel us on). She gets uppity if we ever make a decision that she doesn't agree with. 

To add to it, she's got some very archaic opinions about mental illness. I suffer from depression and anxiety and 

But - here's the kicker. She finally did something that I DO NOT agree with at all, and S doesn't see what's wrong with it. She wants to build onto her house, for whatever reason. It's just her and her husband and on and off, S's sister, but it's a three bedroom place with plenty of room. Here's the thing - she initially intended this addition as a place for S and I to live. Full time. 

What? 

Does she think that between her condescending bullshit and the jokes and the second-guessing and the fact that S tends to not stand up for me when he needs to... I mean, does she honestly think that we would live with her? She knows we're going to get married, though she likes to avoid the subject like the plague. I just don't get it. Once I made it abundantly clear that under no circumstances would I feel comfortable living with his mom, S backed off. He's just off the opinion that it makes sense for multiple generations to live together, but he knows I'm a fairly private person and that I'm not at all interested in that sort of situation. 

However, she still needed S - and his sister - to put their names on the loan in order to get the loan, because she's retired and has no real income. So it's like, either way our credit is screwed, because even if she makes the payments like she's supposed to, which she might, that line of credit is going to count toward's S's credit score, and since I'm a nanny and get paid under the table... that's not going to look good when we go to buy a house or a car somewhere down the line. "Oh, but your name is on this loan for x amount of dollars" (I don't know the exact amount, but it's something like 250k). Just... 

bullshit. So mad. 

So now, even though S and I are good with money, we pay all our bills, we have a decent savings for people our age, etc... we're going to run into trouble when we go to get a car or house because his mom kept barreling through with a house addition she didn't need. 

And if it all gets finished and S tries to talk me into moving in with his mother/family, he can go live up there by himself. Ugh. He's an enabler, and he sort of sees it, but Mommy Knows Best, I guess. He's gotten better than he used to be (DO NOT get me started on the camping trips... I love camping but I would gladly never camp with them again) but he's not making much of an effort to change shit. I don't know.

UGH.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> NMom had been laying relatively low, until... </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-09 22:57:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Oh, god. 

I'm 23, F. My mom and I never had the best relationship growing up, obviously, she liked to kick me out of the house and tell me to never come back, and then come back to me days later, when friends and family asked where I was, crying and begging for me to come back because she "missed me", aka because she realized that people were not sympathizing with her. My parents split ~4 years ago, my dad wasn't a great guy to begin with (compulsive liar, vicodin addict, etc) but they were just toxic to each other. 

Since the split, my mom seems to have reverted back to the developmental stage where she was before she met my dad - 17, barefoot, lost on the beach. Not a good place for a mid-40's woman to be, but, she's been happier in the last few years and for a while, that seemed like enough. I moved out with my boyfriend around the time she and my dad split, so that was a nice departure too. She has definitely had her quips (minimizing my major Chronic Illness diagnosis and comparing it to the fact that she had to move offices, constantly telling me what to do and what's best for me despite the fact that she's horribly financially irresponsible, etc) but the last few years since I left and she and my dad split have been... not so bad. 

Ha. 

So we're all on a family vacation a few weekends ago, one we do every year and have done for the last few decades, since before I was born. There's a bar on the island that gives out these giant straw hats to anyone who orders these fairly strong drinks. It's a tourist bit, but one that I counted my way up to, heading into MY 21st birthday. Except my mom had promised to take me for years and never did. Instead, I went when I was 23, with my boyfriend, after giving up on that trip with my mom. Not super important, I wasn't looking for mommy bonding time, but she's a professional at making commitments and then bailing. 

So, my turn was gone. My sister, however, turned 21 this year and my mom made a huge deal about it, telling everyone it was "tradition" that when her girls turned 21, she'd take us for one and we'd bar hop and have a girls night with whoever else wanted to go. What? Yeah, there are two daughters. You bailed on one and went all out for the princess and lied to anyone within earshot even though I was, you know, RIGHT THERE and knew she was full of shit. 

So I ignore that and I'm like "you know what, she's been drinking, if she wants to attempt to feel good about our relationship I'll allow her to harbor under that delusion for a little bit." But then it gets weird. We're talking about eyes - my mom, my sister, my sister's son's adoptive mother, and myself. We're talking about eyes when my mom like points her finger right in my face and starts talking about how she's always been jealous of my eyes. They're not really anything special - green. There are two little brown flecks in each eye (which I recently found out are actually benign growths that could have potentially been cancerous. But that doesn't matter to mommy, who thinks they're "pretty"). But she was like aggressive about it. Okay. So I brush it off because A: It's weird and B: I don't want to feed into her shit right now, so that's that. 

Except it gets me thinking - about other times she's been weirdly jealous of me and has said it, fairly clearly, drunk or not. Things about my money (I have none, I'm a full time nanny, I'm just actually responsible with my money), my boyfriend (27, 6'3, more than a bit nerdy but fairly good looking), my things (like I said, I'm actually a pretty good saver), all of it. I don't know. 

I think the idea of anyone being jealous of me or my life is a joke on high magnitude, but it's starting to make me uncomfortable. Maybe that's been an issue with her all along? I don't know. Just figured that if I had an optimal sounding board, this was it. Maybe someone else has some experience like this and can make me feel a little less crazy? 


 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Just a small table flip moment for my nMom. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-14 01:34:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Okay, my boyfriend and I are Disneyland Passholders. We have been for years, before that I was a Passholder with my family, etc. My mom had one up until a year ago, when she stopped making payments. She has a habit of going shopping and blowing most of her spending money for a month and then claiming she's destitute and almost homeless and totally broke, yet she shows off new shoes every other week. Yeah, okay. 

So last week we're in the car talking about relationship stuff and how our significant others stress us out, and she's telling me how her boyfriend is stubborn, and I'm saying mine is too (side note: she's like "no Shane's a good guy, you don't know what you're talking about, my boyfriend is MUCH worse" and I'm just like yawn okay yeah yeah). I bring up this time at Disneyland a few months ago and she immediately sighs this huge dramatic sigh and when I stop to let her let out whatever it is she's going to guilt me about, she gestures for me to keep going, so I tell her about an argument and then it's done. I wait for her to respond or something and she just does another dramatic sigh and is like "I miss Disneyland, that's just one more thing I don't get to have in life." 

Uh, bitch, 'scuse me. I budget my money effectively after paying hundreds of dollars in ongoing medical bills so that I can pay fifty bucks a month to do something that makes me happy. You stopped making payments for no other reason than being addicted to spending money. You live in a giant two story house less than a mile from the beach, your boyfriend cooks and cleans for you every night, you're constantly shopping and buying new shit, you just took two vacations and are going on another one. But I mention Disneyland and all of a sudden, you have nothing? Because I have ONE thing that I'm proud to be able to do? Nope nope nope nope nope 

Then a few days later I'm laying on the floor at my nephews adoptive family's house. I have a spinal condition so I have fairly constant back pain but that day it was debilitating, laying on the floor and taking a pain pill are the only things that help. She scoots over to me on the floor and almost looks like she gives a shit about my pain, then starts talking about how she was destitute and couldn't put fuel in her car the other day so she got stuck at work for a whole thirty minutes, so I should just remember that I really have it easy. 

Fuck you fuck you fuck you fuck you fuck you  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Am currently laying on the floor in a side room at my uncle's while my family does the yearly Easter thing. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-05 01:50:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's not a huge deal holiday for us anyway but the fact that I'm laying on a hard floor with a backpack supporting my head and this feels better than sitting on the couch... Yeah. I'd go in there, but nobody here really gets the chronic pain thing, so I don't want to be some weirdo on the floor. I don't want to make a big deal out of it. Better to disappear and not have them worrying about me. I feel like such crap. My back is in awful amounts of pain and I stupidly forgot my meds today. Hips are killing me too. 

Waaaahhh. Just felt like getting that out.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> I just feel like absolute shit. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-12 19:50:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I've been depressed for as long as I can remember - even as early as Elementary school I've shown symptoms, and there's a huge percentage of depressed people in my family. I was fairly emotional during high school, like a lot of kids, but most of the time I still didn't feel like my head was really in it. I very nearly flunked out, but continuation school and my mom threatening to kick me out at 15 got me to finish. I dabbled in college courses, but never went back and I don't think I earned more than three units in something like three semesters. I had thought it would be a new beginning, something I could dive into, head first, but I hated it. I hated the people, the professors, the coursework. I had always wanted to be a writer, a novelist, but my passion for writing started to die off around that time. It's been a slow, shitty descent since then. 

I'm now newly 24, I've been in a serious relationship for a little over three years. I'd been in two awful ones before that, both abusive, so this guy is a breath of fresh air. He's really the only person that has made me feel truly, unconditionally loved. And that's why my depression is that much worse. His family has practically zero history of mental illness, and what is there gets swept under the rug. I've actually sat at a table, next to his mother (who doesn't know I'm depressed) while she made loud proclamations that people with mental illnesses shouldn't be allowed to own guns or have children. I've been steadily, secretly in total dislike for her since then. 

I just don't give a shit anymore. I don't. I have so many things to look forward to, I know that - my boyfriend and I are planning on buying a house by the end of the year, we're probably going to get married within a year or so. The few times over the last few years that I've felt real, in-your-face emotions, it's been with him. And yeah, sometimes that's anger, but mostly love. Mostly happy. But I'm so sick of the day in and day out. I've got a chronic spinal condition, it will never go away and I'm in near constant pain. It drives me crazy, knowing that I'll literally never again do anything without first thinking about my condition, about the needs of a stupid glitch in my spine above what I want to do. 

I self-harmed in December. I won't say much more than that about it, just that I didn't immediately regret it. Still sort of don't. I know it upset my boyfriend, and I think that's the reason I haven't done it again. I hadn't done it since high school, nine years before, and I don't plan on doing it again. It was just like a switch. I felt nothing, nothing, nothing, and then one morning I woke up and I felt everything all at once, a glimmer of happiness among waves of crushing sadness, white-hot anger, so bad I wanted to smash things, break things. That very afternoon, I was back to nothingness, or near-nothingness. You know how it is. Sometimes you feel little things throughout the day that almost make you feel like you're having a good day, until you look back on the week behind you and literally cared so less about it, in hindsight, that you can't remember a damn thing that happened. 

I know I need to go back to a psychiatrist, I know I should be medicated. But I procrastinate and I feel like, what, going and talking to someone and taking pills is going to magically fix me? And I'll be able to commit to things and feel normal? That's never going to happen, for me, so why bother? 

I just feel like I'm spending my life waiting to get better when that may never happen, and what then? I wake up in the morning and I can't wait to just go back to sleep, to pass the time. The monotony of daily life is stifling. I do look forward to weekends, to getting things done and deflating and just spending some time with my guy, but as soon as Sunday morning hits and I realize it's basically back to the work week again, I lose whatever grip on normalcy I might have had. 

I'm just so, so tired. Of everything.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Benefit x Birchbox Hostess with the Mostest prizes/haul </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-10-29 20:12:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> I am... not well. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-08-01 01:12:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I was told explicitly by my Neurologist and my PCP that when the pain got bad enough that my usual painkillers weren't working, to go to the ER. I started on Vicodin, 5mg, twice a day. Not helping, just made me high. Then Norco, 7.5, still just made me fuzzy, but did take away a little pain. They finally put me on Percocet (5mg, but "as needed" up to 4 a  day, 30 in a month). I'm in one hell of a lot of pain. I'd say my daily average is an 8, sometimes dipping down to a 5 for a little while. Now that my pain is consistently worse, I have even worse "spikes", usually at night. Usually when I go into the ER, they're super supportive. Consider my file "Flagged". My history shows degenerative spinal issues, extensive nerve damage, and explains that they're still testing because I have other, unexplained pain/sensory disturbances that don't mesh with my diagnoses. Anyway, they usually put me in a dark, quiet room and give me morphine, which helps. It literally takes 1-2mg of Morphine an hour to get me down to a 2, which sucks. 

But I wasn't able to work for a long time, so I couldn't pay my copays. I owed something like 800 to the hospital, it was getting sent to collections, and since my boyfriend is supporting us both, (and outright offered to pay my bills, bless his lil heart) it meant that we just paid what we can, when we can. It's... slightly better now. But I've been avoiding doctors, I've been avoiding pain management of any kind (I went a month without a pain pill because I constantly thought "there were be worse nights" and didn't want to pay the $40 copay monthly to see my PM team and then refill my prescription on top of that). I hate being a financial burden, but now I realize I've become an emotional burden. He hates seeing me in pain, I hate being in pain. I have pain that makes me literally tear my hair out, but I have been refusing to manage my pain, even after my boyfriend begs me to handle it. 

It's not cool. I have a new pain in my leg as well - usually they're shooting nerve pains from hip to knee and knee to ankle, but this is just a throbbing pain that feels like it's in my femur. Middle of my leg. I know I should get an MRI (I clearly have bad luck with health and need a new set of MRIs anyway) but I know that's going to cost $40 for the specialist visit, and $40 for the imaging center visit. 

I don't know what I'm looking for. Reassurance. Ways you've taught yourself to think of your own pain first. I just bury it and I'm not effectively taking care of myself and that's not good.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> NDad, LC. Calls to complain because... kind of a long one. [support] </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-08-01 00:35:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I was diagnosed with a degenerative spinal condition a little less than a year ago. I'm 23, but my body basically behaves like I'm 85 - bad joints, snaps, slipped discs, weak spine/back, loss of sensation, total numbness, partial paralysis that comes and goes, etc. Really fun stuff. 

Both of my parents are total Ns, always have been. My father is also the biggest liar I've ever met in my life. However, their narcissism somehow bonded them together for 23 years or so, until their messy divorce three years ago. My dad got remarried very soon after, my mother didn't. She's a whole different ball game, but I digress. 

In the year before my NDad got remarried, he was actually really supportive - this was all before I got sick. If I was short for rent, he would lend me money and tell me not to worry about repaying (with, of course, the tone that he was all but saving my life and if he didn't lend me $150, I'd be a homeless crank addict or something). But still, that counted for something, and there would be brief periods of time where he'd sit and talk to me without being a total dick. 

Then he got engaged to my Stepmom, who I have come to realize is just about as narcissistic as he is. It had been eight months since I'd needed help (due to ongoing doctor's appointments to try and figure out what's wrong with me, by the way. I'm not just an irresponsible spender, we spent months going to specialists trying to diagnose me) and I'd asked for sixty bucks to float for groceries until my long-time boyfriend got his next check. My dad agreed, and his wife... denied it. She said, directly in front of me, that parents shouldn't support their children in any way after they turn 18. (She says this while supporting her two daughters, of course.) And besides, they have to save up for the wedding, and every dollar counts. 

Okay, fine. Ramen it was. I started realizing that my Stepmom is both an enabler and a narcissist, a classic combo I was coming to realize would cause problems for them and for my dad and I, since it's that sort of behavior that split my parents up. She also is really weird about communication. Like, she answers my dad's phone and his texts, even when I address them to him (i.e. Hey Dad, just wondering what you guys are up to next weekend, we've got a free day and would like to see you and the girls. I get back: Hey girly! We're free Saturday! You should come out and BBQ with us!) Which, okay, fine. But I'm texting my dad to talk to my dad. And it's ALWAYS her responding unless I call him during the day while he's at work, and then he rarely answers. 

They get married, things seem fine. For a few months, it even seems like they care. Then I get my diagnosis. That day, she comes to pick me up because I didn't want to be home alone (it's a far drive, I was fairly surprised she did it) and I spend the day there until my boyfriend gets off work late and comes to get me. I'm in shock, sure, but I cry once or twice. But she's SOBBING. This woman who I've known for like a year and a half and who has been a little on the weird side is acting like this is her personal tragedy. 

A few weeks later I go back, we're watching some bridal show. My dad just got home from work and is sitting next to me, and I make an offhand comment about getting married before I end up in a wheelchair, which is highly likely for people with my condition. 

They EXPLODE. At first I thought the dog shit in her shoes, because she yelped so loudly. They chastised me for "condemning myself" and told me as long as I thought positive, everything "would be just fine, like now". Uh, okay. I understand she's fairly religious and spreads her mantra of positivity and prayer, but prayer isn't going to take my spinal issues away, and I'm just being realistic in saying I want to marry my guy while I can still dance with him. She starts throwing a fit about scaring her and scaring the girls, she's clutching at her chest, my dad chastises me about talking "like that". I've never been a sunshine and rainbows person to begin with, my dad knows I sort of tell it like it is or don't say anything at all. But all of the sudden, my illness and my life choice is a personal slight on them again. 

At this point, we're LC. My dad doesn't answer his phone, and she stops answering it for him. She stops answering half the time too, or she's really clipped and distant. Okay, fine. At one point, I ask for a loan - just $100 to keep my bills from going to collections and screwing up my credit. I tell him I've got a babysitting job coming up and I'll give him all $120 back in two weeks, I just need to cover this $100 ER copay. He sighs, and says he can't. They're having money troubles. It's been really hard. He's not making as much as he used to. This is all following the last time I saw him, about a month before this, in which he told me he got a promotion. That was probably a lie, the money troubles were also definitely a lie, because when I went out two weeks later, they had a brand new car in the driveway. He claims they paid it with my stepmoms tax refund, but she's not working, and even on unemployment, she wouldn't be getting THAT much in taxes back. He outright bought a car. Like, a $23,000 car. They don't pay rent, they live with her mother. But he couldn't float me $100 for two weeks. Oh, and two weeks later, they took a big vacation to Las Vegas for their anniversary. Posted pictures on Facebook. But, you know, they're broke! 

Things were just starting to be okay again (still LC, but we'd gone over there for Independence Day and only had one tiff) when I get a phone call from my dad, middle of a Tuesday. It's so out of the ordinary that I seriously think I'm dreaming and that my meds have finally dissolved my brain. Nope, I answer it and it's my dad, sounding tired. I ask him what's up, and he goes into this spiel about the hospital calling him about me. I am behind on payments (mostly because I couldn't work at the time, with three doctor's appointments a week and PT on top of that, and those copays alone ate up whatever was left from my boyfriend's income supporting the both of us). Because he's the "responsible party" on my insurance, they're nagging him. I ask how many times they've called. He says three times in the last two weeks. Oh, bother! 

I tell him I'll take care of it, I'll call them and tell them not to call him. His response? "You better, or I'm going to get on your ass about this. These phone calls are really stressing me out at work." Oh, I'm sorry. I lost it. Absolutely effing lost it. I told him, "Well, maybe collectors wouldn't be on both of our asses if I had a family member somewhere who could float me $100, but, you know, I guess they're all too busy buying new cars and taking expensive vacations to do something like that." I know he makes a lot of money. And he doesn't have to spend much. I started crying, which I rarely do, and I told him if he really wanted to get the calls to stop, he could have waited three days to buy his new effing car and he'd have made twenty bucks, to boot. I told him I was pissed that he lied to me, but even more pissed that he went from trying to help out despite being absent, to just being absent and being a dick about it. I stayed on the line, heavy breathing, and he just continued on with the conversation like nothing had happened. He said next time they called, he'd tell them to stop calling him. He asked how i was doing. I laid it on thick - I'm seeing two Neurosurgeons who probably won't operate on me because the surgery is super dangerous, I have eleven doctor's appointments in the next month and a half, I can't get upstairs without assistance, and oh, I have no support system because apparently my illness makes my family "uncomfortable" (my mom's words, not his, but still. Relevant.) Again, nothing. We said goodby and hung up. Oddest phone call of my life. 

I stared at the phone and was actually amazed. He wasted twenty whole minutes of his precious time, talking to me. I mean, it wasn't pleasant by any means, but it's twenty minutes. Dear Lord. Someone call a doctor. 

It really just blows my mind that a father can watch his daughter get sick, and distance himself and lie to her and become LESS helpful than before. The funny thing is, I'd love to blame it on my stepmom, but he's always been this way, and when I first got sick she was actually surprisingly, one of my best sources of emotional support. She'd pick me up from an hour and a half away and take me out to window shop or eat, or just hang out at the house with me. That stopped eventually, but still. 

My form of the condition is the least predictable. I could never have worsening of symptoms again, or I could die in my sleep from paralysis of my upper body, which would just stop my lungs from working. I could be paralyzed in three hours or slowly get better. But I've gotten slowly worse over the last ten months, and for the most part, if symptoms increase, they'll keep increasing. I had so many dreams for myself that I mourn the loss of. If this gets really bad, I won't be able to have kids, I won't be able to dress myself or read a book. Like, I need support. That is something I have come to accept, since I'm normally someone who HATES asking for help. I know sometimes I have to, but I despise it. But I need my dad right now. 

Okay, long post over. What the hell do I do? Is there a way to tell my dad to snap the hell out of it, that I don't care about the money, I just hate being lied to and pushed away when I most need someone? My dad and I used to be a lot closer, before he moved out to be with my stepmom. We got tattoos on my 19th birthday to piss off my mom, I was very much a daddy's girl growing up. He's changed. Even my chart-topping Nmom asks how I'm doing, 5% of the time that we talk. She and I had a very strained relationship when I was younger because I frequently called her out on her behavior, but I never saw it in my dad until I was maybe 19, 20, and moving out of the house for the first time. 

How do you deal with that? I haven't always seen him like this. It's like losing him, but he's just 80 miles away. Ugh. This is when I most need him to not be a jackass, to just call me and check in and, I don't know, treat me a fifth as well as he now treats his (younger) stepdaughters. Just... ugh. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Painful hand tremors? What? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-04-25 20:10:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I've had hand tremors before. I've had hand joint pain before. But I'm now venturing into a previously undiscovered (by me, at least) world of painful hand tremors. They hurt when they twitch. They sometimes just stop working correctly. I drop stuff constantly. But it HURTS. Every joint feels like it's on fire. Every tendon and nerve and muscle has electric-type pain. It hurts when they twitch, it hurts when they briefly stop twitching. And the twitching makes them hurt MORE. My joints in my hands feel like they're creaking. And I've got a prickly sensation from my wrists to fingertips whenever my hands move, but that could be any number of my chronic conditions. Meh. 

Just sort of venting and seeing what secrets you guys might have for hand pain. It's new, like this. This sucks.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Habitual quitter. What made you guys finally cut the crap and commit to losing it? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-04-11 20:49:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm 23. I've been a little "chubby" for most of my life, but was a pretty good/healthy weight until Junior year of high school. I just got lazy. I didn't want to walk the four blocks home from school. Throughout college, I was just too lazy to go to class. I started putting weight on, went from 5'5 135 lbs when I was around 16, to 160-ish when I was around 20. I've recently been diagnosed with Chronic Fatigue, in addition to a spinal condition, which explains some of that, and which has also put my weight over 190 at one point. I am 5'7 now, so a tad taller, but 190 is way over what I want to be. 

I have struggled with binge eating for a decade, but I think I'm finally recovering from that because I've gone from binging 2500+ calories every other day, to just finding a snack when I feel like I want to binge. While I have been eating healthier over the past few months, I slip up constantly. I bought a treadmill but can hardly ever convince myself to get on it. "Tomorrow" is my mantra. I've been convincing myself to put my fitness aside to deal with my back, but that's not really it, either. I don't know what it is. I don't stick to anything for more than a couple of weeks. I give in at the slightest sign of an unhealthy meal, and instead of getting back on track, I just give up. 

So, loseit, what has kept you on track? What tricks, systems, or motivators do you have that have kept you from slipping again and again? I'm hardly making progress. The fifteen or so pounds that I have lost, I've only lost since I've stopped binging, and now I've been hovering around the same weight for months.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> TW Wasn't technically raised by her, but my relatively new NStepmother is... interesting. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-04-09 14:13:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Mother is a wonderfully fantastical narcissist. I've spent the last two and a half years of NOT living with her, recovering from living with her, and even now when I see her, I'm constantly annoyed. My parents split just before I moved out, and it was hard on the whole family, but of course my mother made it about her. Now, it's agreed on by my sister and the rest of our family that it was for the best. Our parents were toxic together - my dad had anger issues that have since mostly resolved, mostly because my mother turned her N into being an explosive drama queen. 

My stepmom, however, is a different story. Don't get me wrong. I love her, she's family, and she is so much better for my dad than my mom was. She has two great daughters who complain about her just as much as any kids would. But... it has gone a step too far. I got a serious diagnosis back in September. Because my mom has a tendency to blow things up and make them about her, I talked to my dad first and immediately got picked up by my stepmom to go out to his house for the rest of the day, since I was highly upset and didn't trust myself to be home alone (history of mild self-harm, a few years clean and didn't want to relapse). She picked me up, asked plenty of thoughtful questions, and seemed to be really reassuring. The next day, my mom made a mess of things. So I started going out to my dad's more, and since my stepmom wasn't working, we spent a lot of time together, at which point her real feelings came out. 

Her family is pretty religious, old Argentinian and Mexican catholics. We've had plenty of family friends that have been the same, but most know to keep their religion separate from friendships. My stepmom doesn't necessarily have that problem, but she has a problem understanding that "faith" and "positive thoughts" are not going to heal me. I'm an atheist, and a firm believer in good science. When I got my diagnosis, the best thing for me to do was research. I would tell her little bits, not being too crazy with details. 

But my dad came home from work one week (he stays out at stateline four days a week, then comes home for three) and I was out there. My boyfriend hadn't come to pick me up yet, so I was watching a wedding show with my stepsisters. I had finally gotten to the point where I was making a "list" of things I wouldn't let my condition take away from me - mostly relationships and family, letting myself be happy, etc. But this was the first physical one. "I don't want to go down the aisle in a wheelchair." A lovely little FLEA I picked up from my childhood, sure, but a valid fear of mine - I have always dreamed of my wedding/marriage, and now that I've found the guy I'm 99% sure I'm going to spend my life with, I've already started sort of planning and my plan does not involved being limited with dress choices, venue choices, with not being able to have a first dance (or any dance)... you know. It IS a valid fear. 

But they both BLEW UP. Nstepmom started shouting that I shouldn't say those things, that they'll NEVER happen to me, that I just need to listen to her and have faith and stay positive... it's like, if they were upset by it, fine. It's a touchy subject and it was still pretty new. But to get angry at me for not having the same attitude/faith/whatever that they had... it still bothers me. 

She also, when my sister got pregnant months before that, tried to convince my sister to not put the baby up for adoption, despite my pleas to NOT DO THAT. My sister was only 19 when she gave birth, it was extremely hard on her to begin with because due to a hormonal issue, she had bleeding that seemed like periods, so she just thought she was putting on freshman college weight until she got bloodwork done at a routine doctor's appointment and they asked if she knew she was pregnant. She hadn't known then, and she was literally already 30 weeks pregnant. She just looked like she'd put on a little weight. She knew almost immediately that adoption was the only choice for her and found a wonderful family that helped her choose open adoption, so that we're all still a big part of the baby's life - except my dad and stepmom, since they so heavily pressured my sister to keep the baby that she's very LC with the both of them. She'll only see them if I'm there, now, and they still pressure her about seeing the baby. My stepmom, also, has lied about things she's said to my sister and I, to my father. She pressured my sister in private, and when my dad stopped within a few weeks, she didn't - but she told him she did. But then she'd text me, text my sister, call us, just wanting to "catch up" but in minutes she'd be crying, throwing a fit, begging us to change the decision. She still does this sometimes, and my nephew was born over nine months ago. 

Most of the time, she's fine. But she's extremely overbearing and self-righteous to a fault, when something doesn't go her way. She knows that it's this pressure from her, and her pressuring my father into talking about it, that is causing my sister to keep them from seeing the baby. She doesn't want that kind of drama with the adoptive family, who are wonderful to all of us because they know we support my sister's decision. 

It's just whack. She's normally pretty cool but other times, she can't get over the fact that I think differently from her sometimes. She still won't give up with my diagnosis, though it's been over half a year, and I'm just terrified of what will happen when things get worse and I have to explain that I'm in serious medical trouble. She's the kind of person that doesn't just 'pray for you', she holds unwanted candlelight vigils at hospital bedsides. I purposefully didn't tell my dad I was at the hospital a few weeks ago because I knew it would cause drama, despite the fact that my dad is the only one I wanted to call (besides my boyfriend, who was already there since he'd literally carried me to the car and then into the ER).  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [Trigger Warning] NMom spent the entire day of my dangerous medical diagnosis complaining about having to switch from one beautiful work office to another. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-04-09 13:42:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> To anyone else, this could be construed as a "coping tactic", but not if you knew my mother... 

She was always the victim, always storming off in an argument. My dad had anger issues when I was younger, but he never hit me - my mom did, and yet if my dad ever got angry at all, she'd make a huge scene and act like he was trying to attack her. On a road trip one time, she reached back, grabbed my hair, and pulled me from the back seat into the front, hitting me over and over again until my dad could pull the car over and make her get out for a while because she was getting too far. She snapped the seatbelt out of our Chevy van. I don't have to tell you how strong that is. It wasn't the only time she got that violent. 

She's always been like this. Prom dress shopping was all about what she wanted. She wanted me to be in Drill Team in high school because that's what she did. She always had stories about her parties and friends, and even when I got older, she'd ask me why I wasn't out on weekends and accuse me of turning away friends and being a "loner on purpose". Then she'd spend days praising how I wasn't drinking or getting into trouble. Repeat. She often had parties at my house for my friends, with jello shots or beer pong or whatever. Most of these started when I was 18, but birthday parties before that were always huge spectacles. Not that I'd complain, but it was like whenever she picked me up from a party, she had to observe, and mine had to be the best. She wanted to be Super Mom, not for me but so that she could prove something. When I moved out at 20, she acted like it was a personal affront to her despite the fact that she'd recently divorced my dad (who she cheated on, while telling my sister and I that HE had cheated on HER) and had quickly begun dating another man. He's great, I don't know how he puts up with her. She openly flirts with my boyfriend, praises him, and tells me I don't deserve him. UGH. More of that fun stuff. Now that I'm older and moved out and have a successful, loving relationship, it has almost gotten worse. 

I'm 23 now, and about six months ago I was diagnosed with a rare, unpredictable spinal condition. Because it's so rare, not a lot of research has been done on it. I'd been having pain and numbness and weakness and unbearable headaches for over a year, but I hadn't had insurance. Every time I complained about pain at her house, she would whine about any headache or toothache or fatigue she had and try and one-up me. You know the deal. So when I went to a Neurologist and things got serious, she got quiet for like two days. That's all. I got my diagnosis via phone and immediately went out to my dad's, because I knew he'd understand better (even though my stepmother is a bit of an Nstepmom, but more on that in another post) and he did. The next day I met my mom and grandma for lunch, and my grandma (who had just finished Chemo for breast cancer) was attentive, asked questions, offered help, the whole deal. My mom, on the other hand, never even asked how I was feeling. She listened, idly, as if it were small talk she wasn't interested in. She then spent an hour drawing a diagram of her new office, complaining about how she told her boss she didn't like the setup because she felt 'clustered' (which, duh, she slacks off at work constantly and hardly works, so she doesn't want to get caught doing it) , etc. She literally spent the rest of lunch talking about anything but my scary, life-changing diagnosis. At the end, she left early because she said she had a headache. 

I ignored it, I'm used to it. My grandma talked me down from the near-boiling rage (I'm used to it, I shouldn't have gotten angry, but that's a pretty big thing to ignore like that) and told me that was just how she was, she'd come around, etc. She sort of did - every month or two she'll ask how I'm feeling, but she does the same thing - turns the conversation back to her and her problems. Oh darn, she went to court with my dad and now he has to pay her more money. It was such a pain to go to court. Blah. 

She's... different now. I won't say better. Her boyfriend being so laid back (and usually not putting up with her shit - if  she gets crazy he just goes into the back house and plays guitar until she calms down) has been really good for her, I think. To date, the only serious acknowledgement she's had of my condition came four months ago. A family friend developed a spinal infection, she's in a coma. My mom went to see her in the hospital (yet didn't come to see her own daughter) and when I went over for dinner a week or two later, she burst into tears talking about how it really hit home for her because she saw what spinal issues can be like. She's never brought it up again.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Disabled Ex-Disneyland CM taking a first WDW trip with boyfriend and his family. Help? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-04-09 12:26:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I've had an AP for DL for years. Pretty much since I was a kid. I'm 23 now, my guy and I have been together two and a half years (actually, it'll be almost exactly two and a half years when we go) and we're going to Florida for a week at the end of May. Though we'll be staying in a house a few miles from WDW for the entirety of the trip, we may only be going to the parks for three days or so. I'd go every day, but we have things we'd be obligated to do with the family. 

SO. As someone who has been to DL and DCA literally at least four  hundred times in my life, what should I absolutely not miss at WDW? We'll be upgrading our Premium passes to Premier passes, so we'll have access to all the parks and we'll have a decent dining discount. I want to try to do at least one nice-ish dinner between the two of us, but I've read that reservations for a lot of places book up six months in advance, and since we're there in a month and a half, we don't really have that kind of time. 

What attractions are similar/the same as DL? What is close enough that we should skip? Which ones are different enough/interesting enough to warrant a visit? We'll probably do a day at Epcot, at least one Day at MK, and I want to do an afternoon or something at one of the other parks. Not sure which one is worth it! 

Since we'll likely be going throughout the week, I've read to end at MK, but I want to start there, even if it's just a half day there and then a half day at somewhere like HS or AK. Tips? 

And finally, FOOD. DL has hit and miss food everywhere you go - a killer flatbread here, a disgustingly dry meat stick there. Good turkey legs everywhere, but coffee that can be great or awful depending on where it comes from. Any places to avoid? Any places to absolutely not miss? 

Finally, because we're young and will want to have a little fun, a beer or two and a drink or two will probably be in order. Where are the best places for a fun drink or beer (preferably in park) that doesn't require sitting down and waiting forever? For example, at DCA I can get the same beer for the same price at Cove Bar and Bayside Brews, but Cove Bar can be a half-hour wait for a seat and then twenty minutes for a beer, where Bayside Brews has never taken longer than five minutes. Alternatively, the other beer stand not far from Bayside Brews often has horrendously long lines. 

So, general tips? A guide? I've read most of the online guides, but many of them seem to be dated or focus solely on family trips - while this is with family, I have no doubt that some of them will want to split off for periods of time, since the only kids under 18 are all under 3 and can do smaller rides while we do bigger stuff. 

This has been a marathon of a post, sorry, just eager to get better details so I can cement a plan in before we go. CM experience requires knowledge of a park so I don't absolutely drown in bad crowds or not great food. 

Also, I'm disabled - it wouldn't be clearly visible to the naked eye, but I have a spinal condition that prevents me from walking for more than twenty minutes without taking a break. I'm in a lot of pain throughout the day. I'm not sure if you guys updated your GWD routine, but the removal of the GAC passes has been hit or miss for us. What kind of system do you guys have over there? How many of the attractions, roughly, are accessible? I might rent a wheelchair, since I know I'm expecting pain as usual and I want to be able to have fun and not waste everyone's time. What do they cost, over there, and will they hassle me? I have a placard and some other information, but with DL it's hit and miss - some of them give you attitude unless you're really visibly impaired, which sucks and makes me feel worse. On a side note, I just got cleared to ride roller coasters again. I used to not even like them, but a year without them (pressure could have made it worse, we're at a point where we've figured out it won't, it'll just give me a little more pain) made me MISS THEM. I want to go on at least one big, crazy ride that I can only find at WDW or that is like DL, but different. 

I guess that's all! (I say as if it were short...)  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> "Outings" on camping trips. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-04-09 10:47:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I've been camping literally since I was a few weeks old, I've done all sorts of camping from extremely primitive backpacking (with a less-than full pack, only slightly on purpose) to RV camping and cabins (which I hardly consider camping at all - just my opinion!). I'm going to Hearst/San Simeon this weekend on the California coast, for those that don't know, it's about two miles from Hearst Castle. Beautiful site right near the beach, with a lovely little town to walk through and a great campsite, from what I remember from last time. 

Some people argue that camping should just take place within walking distance from your site - be it lake, hiking, whatever. Many also say that a short drive for hiking, lake, "typical" camping things is acceptable. But I've had people get outright uppity about going to other sorts of places whilst camping. I was planning on taking my boyfriend to Hearst Castle for a tour/walk around the groups while we were there, and maybe a winery one afternoon. I had someone ask me, "why bother camping?" 

Anyone else have opinions on this? Personally, camping is a method of lodging and an activity for me - I like the cooking, the relaxing, the unusual little cities and towns. I love trees. But does leaving for part of the day make it any less like 'camping' for you?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Eyeshadow probs. Everything ends up too "soft" looking for me. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-04-03 11:54:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I don't know what it is. I see similar looks with products I already own, I put them on my face... and everything just looks so much less... awesome. I'll admit that I usually don't use eye primer, but staying power isn't the problem, really, it's how the pigments are showing up/shaped as soon as I put them on. 

Here's my usual (eye) routine:

Moisturizer goes on all over my face, including eyes. 
Same with foundation. 
I do my brows, which I'm just starting to learn how to do.
I use some kind of "all over" color. For a while I was using a really pretty metallic taupe Sephora brand shadow. I'm not a big fan of matte shadows. 
Highlight - Moon Beam/light pink or white eyeshadow on top. 
Any combination of shadows from MAC, Urban Decay (Naked 2 Palette) and a few other palettes. Lately it's been something like YDK in the crease, the same highlighter from under my brow bone on the inner corners, and Blackout on the outer third of my lid. My lids are a little bit hooded, but not much, and I have high brow bones so there's plenty of lid above the crease. 

I'm pale as all get out, so colors SHOULD show up a little brighter/darker on me. But instead, everything just looks really... soft. I have tried changing up which brushes I use, but it doesn't seem to do much difference. Even if my makeup looks "dark" to my while I put it on, two minutes later I look in the mirror and it looks much less intense. I can't get an outer V darker shadow to save my life, it just sort of looks like it fades out entirely. I've started going from brown on the outer edges, to dark dark purple, and now to black, and still, it seems like my looks are all very natural. 

Maybe I'm just approaching this the wrong way? I'm not really sure. I don't like my makeup super dramatic or anything, but I can't get things to look defined or even close to that. It just all looks like I blended it over and over again so that certain spots are just vaguely lighter or darker than the rest of the lids. Maybe I'm not picking up enough shadow? Or maybe I just need to layer the shadow a little heavier once it's on? That makes a little more sense, since my base color can be pretty shimmery, so maybe the darker shadows aren't taking shape like they should because they blend too easily with the smooth shimmer shadow? Ugh. 

Heeeeeeelp  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Any MLs present? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-04-02 09:59:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I've been participating for eight years now (oh my god) and have won each time. I finally stepped up to become an ML last year (and basically was given an area 3x bigger/more populated than I expected, in a weird turn of events) and WOW. It's an experience, to say the least... some very good times, and some very very bad times. Wondering who else might have ML'd before, or who plans on doing it next year, to chat ML-dom and the perks and pitfalls. And also to wonder if any of you have had "issues" with another ML, as I got dragged into something this last year that made me want to quit the program altogether. 

If you have any questions, feel free to ask!  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Catching up all at once - my foray into two week's worth of intense feels (and my nightly sobfest when I realize I don't have the art skills I want) </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-03-31 23:11:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> A little history: I have no art history. None. I doodle in paper margins but I have no decent skill. I can't draw. The most artsy I get is designing a business card here and there, not including the logos that other, artsier people before me have designed. (Okay, I shouldn't say I have NO skill. I used to paint mugs for money. I wasn't great, but I wasn't the worst in the market, either. I just have trouble with painting things like PEOPLE.) 

About two (maybe three?) months ago I decided I needed to catch up on "that weird Night Vale thing" that I saw so, so many tumblr posts about. I did. Because I was on new pain meds, I was pretty loopy but also wide awake for entire nights. I would listen to three, four, five, or six episodes a night. I got caught up fairly quickly, and now waiting is TORTURE. It's like with any good TV show or anything - catching up is the best and worst thing you can do. 

However, the problem is that I have SO MANY IDEAS or I see so much inspiration for things I want to do. I just don't have the skills to even attempt these things. Someone posted on here about a Tarot deck, and I want to paint them so badly it hurts. Minor arcana and all. But I'm like "lol if I tried to paint people or anything that mattered, it would be a joke." 

My latest foray into trying to get all of my ideas of these people and places out, is creating them all via Sims. That's all I've got. I've seen some beautiful fan art. I'll make attempts to paint some WTNV things, but we'll see how that turns out. Meh.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> I'm chronically ill and struggling, hard. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-02-17 12:18:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I had been having strange, short-but-intensely-painful headaches for well over two years. I had no insurance. When I finally got covered again, I went into the ER with a splitting headache. Got a Neurologist referral, got MRIs done, got a diagnosis. I have a condition called Syringomyelia. Basically, it means that I have a fluid-filled cyst in my spinal cord (where fluid isn't supposed to go) and it creates a lot of pressure on all of those delicate nerves in my spine. It also interrupts cerebrospinal fluid (CSF) flow and that makes nasty things happen, to be short. Symptoms range from numbness and tingling, to muscle weakness and wasting, to headaches, chronic fatigue, etc. My entire list of symptoms, headaches, pains, numbness, tingling, nerve issues, etc, is much too long to type in here right now because if I did that my hand not literally would fall off and that's something I'm trying to prevent. There isn't any real "treatment" except for spinal surgery, and not everybody is a surgical candidate because it's a risky procedure, so even if you're getting worse, if you're not on the brink of paralysis or total life destruction (which is relative, of course) you probably won't get surgery. I probably won't. This could lead to paralysis, and because my condition is so under-researched, little is known about the progression. I could be just how I am for the rest of my life. I could wake up tomorrow completely paralyzed. It's a coin toss. 

Up until a few weeks ago, I was coping with this fairly well. My left arm has continued to get worse, but I was doing what I could. I finally got in to see my Neurologist again, and... bad news. 

Based on my symptoms (mostly debilitating nerve pain that shoots from my hips down to my ankles and feels like electric shocks to the bone, pulsating, for hours... gg legs), she thinks that there's at least one more syrinx somewhere lower in my spine. That, in my condition, is the equivalent of hearing that your first tumor is growing, and you also probably have a second one. I was prepared for something like this - we'd talked about it before and the idea then was to carefully monitor my symptoms and see what happened. Since the identifying symptoms got worse, she thinks there is probably another one. Joy. I was just getting the hang of one. Still, this isn't terribly bad news, it's a fairly common thing with this illness. The syrinx we DO know about for sure spans a little more than 5 vertebrae, and is about 3mm wide at the widest. That seems so tiny when you just see that, but remember that your spinal cord is about as big around as your pinky, and then you see that 3mm is kind of a lot of space. 

No, but then it got worse. My pain is not typical for my condition. Though many people with Syringomyelia do experience nerve pain in some cases, the TYPE of nerve pain I'm having is abnormal. I had an EMG done (basically they jab your nerves with needles and the results come out in waveforms that read out how well your nerves respond to electrical impulses. Hurts like a bitch. 0/10 do not recommend.) and my EMG results were abnormal, as well. My left side has responsiveness that is decreased by at least 60% on most tests. That explains the numbness and tingling, and also the weakness. It has gotten worse, though, in the two months since I've taken that test, so those results aren't so dependable. Now, though, we're doing a huge round of testing for a secondary condition. She's got a few ideas, all of them sound terrifying to me, and she said that while testing is normally for just ruling things out, it's highly likely that I have something and that I should prepare myself for changes. A few words were thrown around: Lupus, Fibromyalgia, Autoimmune Disorders, Rheumatoid Arthritis, to things like Degenerative Nerve Diseases (Alzheimer's, Parkinson's, spinal muscular atrophy). I'm reeling. It has only been six months since my first diagnosis and I'm having trouble accepting that another could be on the way and that my life will change even more. 

On top of all this is a bout of depression the likes of which I have never experienced. They say it's normal to mourn the loss of the future you had planned for yourself, and they're right. I've spent so much time saying goodbye to all of the things I wanted to do that I am no longer able to do. Hell, most days I'm barely awake for 12 or 14 hours, and during those hours I'm in pain. I am legally disabled. And that's about to get worse! But the reactions from my friends and family have not been helpful. 

About half of the time, people ask how I'm doing and listen and ask questions where needed. This is good, 10/10. 

Other times I've heard things like this: 

"I thought you were just lazy." 
"At least it's not Cancer!" 
"You can't be in that much pain." 
"You're too young to be that sick." 
(In response to Depression issues) "Just snap out of it."/"Just feel better." 
"I know what you're going through." (From totally healthy persons with one sick relative who assume they know everything about illness) 
"Are they sure it's ___________?" 
"Get a second opinion! You could be perfectly healthy!" 
(In response to my fears about disability/muscle wasting/paralysis) "Don't say that! That's not going to happen to you!" 
"You just need to stay positive and you'll be fine!" 

Stuff like this comes from my best friends. My parents. My step parents. My sister, my roommate, my boyfriend, everyone. One of my boyfriends friends had the nerve to tell me I "posted too much depressing stuff about being ill". Uh. Excuse me? Trust me, I get that staying positive is good. But stacking depression on top of a fairly new chronic illness and possibly another one is HARD. This is something that is changing the course of my life. (I'm writing this now at 3:00am because I'm in too much pain to sleep, the pain medication I have has been causing anxiety attacks so I'm not taking it, and my left arm is numb/dead/tingly, and trying to sleep on either side with that is laughable). This is something that threatens the very idea of simple things I have wanted in my life: walking down the aisle at my wedding, chasing my children around, swimming in the ocean, camping, everything. It's terrifying. The only person who 100% can sympathize with me is my grandmother, who just went into remission (discovered Breast Cancer at late stage 2B, closer to 3. Close save.) and my friend who has a nerve disorder, but hers is vastly different and we don't pretend to know what the other is going through. I just don't understand the lack of support from the people around me. Everyone was *so* supportive at first - texting, calling, offering to drive me to appointments, offering to bring me food. I turned it all down, I wasn't so bad then. But now that I actually need help, it's like I'm talking to a brick wall. On good days, I can get up and straighten up the house for an hour or so, then I'm tired and need a nap. On bad days, I can't get downstairs to eat. My boyfriend, who I live with, is starting to get it, but that's complicated - he was raised in a house that very much reinforced the stigmas surrounding mental health, his mother has the opinion that people with mental health issues shouldn't be allowed to own guns or have children, that sort of thing - and even then, it's like he forgets. It's pretty hard to get when I know I'm constantly complaining. He's normally pretty supportive, and I can understand he's frustrated, but since he can't see it through my eyes, he can't understand that when I say I'll run an errand or two the next day, sometimes I just can't get through getting dressed, driving 20-30 minutes to wherever I need to go, walking around a store, waiting in line, driving home, etc. That can total hours of activity that most people take for granted. I went grocery shopping a little over a month ago, and I tried carrying a basket. Laughable. It took me a week to recover. Of our two roommates, one is pretty supportive but doesn't talk much, so I know when I need to vent I can, but I don't like to burden him. The other one... he will listen, doesn't know how to respond, and then finds things that I like and tells me about them (ie I just discovered the WritingPrompts subreddit and I could cry I'm so happy) and like he just makes me laugh, which helps so much when it's clear that I'm just feeling like shit and that's what I need. 

I guess I'm just really finding out who is "there" for me and who isn't. But it's not helping that so many people offered support, and when it comes down to it there's really only a small handful of people I can count on, and even those people are... tricky. I looked for a support group in my area for people with my condition, but I can't find much. The one I found online is alright, but it's not the same. About two years ago I went through this big purge of people that were toxic in my life, it was hard but ultimately beneficial. I'm sad to find out that if I did something like that this time - cut out everyone who wasn't supportive or at least nice about it - I would have no one left. 

TL;DR I'm chronically ill and possibly have another condition and people suck. 

I'd like to say I'm just venting but I'm perfectly open for discussion and questions. Talking it out helps me, I think, and since I can't talk much about it with the people at home, I'm hoping people here will be better.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
