<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject7761</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-04 23:22:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I think the problem is the quality of the service depends on who you get. In my experience, the first person I saw was very by-the-book, and wanted to discharge me before I was actually better. The second person, however, was absolutely brilliant. She went absolutely out of her way to help me understand myself, and teach me techniques to manage my anxiety and OCD. 

I'm not sure to what extent it's a gendered issue. I've only experienced it from a woman's perspective, and I am aware there are issues across the board with the mental health services (or at least in the UK). Some people just don't understand mental illness, even in the mental health services! With that being said, I do think it's harder for men to 'come out' about mental health, since they perhaps just keep going and don't discuss their issues. I have noticed a few men's support groups opening up here and there, so that's promising.

I myself am going through a bad patch with panic attacks, and they are difficult to deal with. Have you done any cognitive behavioural therapy, as the techniques there can be very helpful? My advice is to keep going out as much as you can, putting yourself into situations that set off your attacks, so you can see that nothing happens to you. I know how hard that is through first hand experience, but it's the only way it will get better. Panic attacks feel awful, but those feelings are essentially normal and can't actually hurt you. I really wish you good luck in dealing with your panic attacks.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-04 21:56:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Perhaps listen to a classical radio station. Since I was a kid my mum always had a classical music station on, and that was how I got to know all the pieces, and find new ones I like. I find I'm still learning now who the different composers are/were and which pieces are by who. 

Perhaps also look into the specific genres or eras of classical music, and find the ones you like most. I personally enjoy piano and choral compositions the most, but there's plenty of other styles out there.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-04 21:43:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> All of these composers are relatively modern - composing in the last twenty five to thirty years or so. 

Ludovico Einaudi - I find his piano compositions the best. I Giorni was the piece of music that first got me hooked on classical music when I was 13. https://youtu.be/Uffjii1hXzU

Ryuuichi Sakamoto - Japanese film composer, very underrated 
https://youtu.be/LGs_vGt0MY8

Joe Hisaishi - Also a Japanese film composer, again very underrated, rarely hear him played on classical radio stations
https://youtu.be/J7or0noYfMA

Sir Karl Jenkins - Everything he composes is amazing, and he works in a variety of classical genres, some of his music is choral, some tribal, some instrumental. The Benedictus makes me tear up a bit. https://youtu.be/zc1Zoz-NUro

Morten Lauridsen - His choral composition, 'O Magnum Mysterium' got me interested in choral music. https://youtu.be/Q7ch7uottHU </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-02 23:30:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I love how they got such a 70s feel to the concert, really fits with the music. Watching performances from this concert on YouTube was the first time I was truly amazed by a live show. The Strokes are absolutely timeless. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-01 22:07:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The ending themes for 1 and 2 are absolutely breathtaking. They actually inspire me for making music outside the video game soundtrack genre. They're so nostalgic and moving. Whenever I listen to them, it's like I've gone back to when I was 12 and playing the series for the first time. 

I remember, back before I twigged that YouTube existed, I used to replay to certain points in the game to hear my favourite pieces from the soundtrack. Just like the game itself, the music clings to you and never quite lets go. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-23 22:02:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm a newer fan, but I didn't like Comedown Machine at first because it's so different to their earlier style, but One Way Trigger, Happy Ending and Tap Out are some of my absolute favourite Strokes songs now.  I think it's about enjoying it as work in and of itself and not comparing to their older style. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
