<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject2778</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-09-18 03:42:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If I'm alone in the house, it's any sort of loud enough noise to sound like a human might be making it. If I'm out on the street at night, it's anyone who stares at me for too long. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-09-17 14:02:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Brooks Was Here, from the Shawshank Redemption. It kills me when Brooks is speaking over it as well. [SPOILERS](http://www.youtube.com/watch?v=kotNxb2YApk) if you haven't seen it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-09-17 13:52:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Spot on! Thank you very much! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Horrified white rabbit </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-09-17 04:30:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's often posted in a sort of "DO NOT WANT" context, but I keep forgetting to save it. Anyone know what it's called or where to find a link to it? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-09-17 04:28:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Ah, slumming the student life at the moment for me. Cooked up a roast and now redditting before bed. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-09-17 04:26:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I fucking love a good seeded loaf. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-09-17 04:24:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Depends on the friend. Some friends, it's the quick one-armed over the shoulder hug, other friends it's super close and possibly verging on a bit gay. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-09-17 04:20:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Well, this is nice. How's your day going? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-09-17 04:18:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Paper. Plastic doesn't wipe quite as well, and tends to chafe. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-09-17 04:15:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah, spot me a KitKat while you're at it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-09-17 04:12:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm in the same boat as you, still not shaving and I'm 19 now. Comes with drawbacks, but at least I don't have to shave! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-09-17 04:10:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [Bullet](http://www.youtube.com/watch?v=ML27kyhRDcU feature=player_detailpage#t=21s) by Hollywood Undead. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-09-17 04:05:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Reading this title made [this](http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Buffalo_buffalo_Buffalo_buffalo_buffalo_buffalo_Buffalo_buffalo) spring to mind. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-09-17 03:54:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Playing WoW instead of studying harder for my AS levels. I had to work solidly for 4 months to drag my A-Level grades up to somewhere acceptable, and I've not got over that yet, even though I'm in University doing a course I enjoy. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-09-17 03:50:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Made me laugh like a kid :P </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-09-17 03:49:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's almost racist really. I doubt you'd ask for tips on how to ask a black guy out, so why separate gingers out? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-09-17 03:44:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I prefer to call out different things that rhyme, like Han #SOLO, #WOLOLO, or Marco #POLO. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-09-17 03:25:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Mine has to be Arrival of the Birds by Cinematic Orchestra. [This is a link](http://www.youtube.com/watch?v=7wgsZTv_1SA) to a video my sister did for her first year project, which is an animation of the poem "And Death shall have no Dominion". </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-09-17 02:43:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If I want to kick something, like a ball or a can on the street, I find myself getting the same sensation. If it's the wrong foot, or I misjudge it, my feet go a bit fizzy. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-09-12 23:02:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What cheese do you use to get a bear out of a tree?  
Camembert </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> I just realised the Amazon logo was an arrow pointing from A to Z. What simple things have taken you a long time to work out? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-09-04 12:46:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-08-20 15:34:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I remember that from a horrible histories book :P </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-07-30 16:50:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Even if it's WTF, doesn't mean you don't put death tags on it. "Gore and Porn are not by default WTF" </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-07-30 16:26:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Could you put a death warning on that please? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> A man was wandering, alone in a forest in rural China </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-07-27 12:07:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> He was getting weary from the long hours of constant walking, and was feeling very thirsty. He stopped to have a look around, and spotted a little shack in the forest. As he approached, an old man with a great long beard came out towards him, and bowed. "I see you are tired from walking, and you look hungry. I will allow you to stay at my house tonight, on the one condition that you do not screw my daughter. If you do, you shall have to face the 3 Chinese torture tests." The man nodded slowly, and gratefully entered the man's house. As he walked into the main room, he was struck by how amazingly beautiful the old man's daughter was. Thinking he would be able to at least be friendly, they sat together over dinner. She was flirty, and he reciprocated. The old man went off to bed, and a few minutes later, the man and his daughter went upstairs together for the night...
The following morning, the man awoke finding not the daughter astride him, but a large rock, and a staggering pain in his testicles. Wincing slightly from the pain, he struggled to sit up. Inscribed on the rock was a message: "Chinese Torture number 1: Wake up with 15kg rock on chest". As he had since recovered from his tiredness, and being a strong man, he hefted the rock with one almighty push out of the window. Watching it sail through the open gap, the rock turned slightly, revealing a second message: "Chinese Torture number 2: Left nut tied to rock". Thinking very quickly, the man jumped out of the window after the rock, and as he did so, read the final message on the bedstead: "Chinese Torture number 3: Right nut tied to bedpost". </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What cheese do you use to get a bear out of a tree? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-07-27 11:53:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Camembert! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-07-27 11:44:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Gonna go play Age of Empires...#WOLOLO </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-07-27 11:39:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> ...These go to eleven. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-07-27 11:37:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> No worries, just thought it might be something to get on a desktop. Looks nice. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-07-27 11:27:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Not strictly relevant, but what browser is that? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-07-26 18:44:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Kim Jong Un-tourage
FTFY </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-07-10 12:43:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What's Princess Diana's favourite band?
Radio Head. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-06-28 14:02:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Well, since you're addressing your reply to me, I can say that yes, I program often in OO, I'm studying Computer Games Programming at University at the moment. In doing so, I *need* linear algebra, as it concerns matrices and vectors, both of which I use extensively, and collision detection goes without saying. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-06-28 12:36:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Aaand the award for the most desperate neckbeard goes to... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-06-02 05:21:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> "In this day and age" was always "In this Dayen age". I asked my parents what a Dayen was, as in the phrase above. I remember puzzled looks and a few giggles as I was told it was in fact, "In this day and age". I also thought that the D in Disney was a bizarre character, or a quirky signature thing until I was about 14 ( same problem as someone else)

**tl;dr "In this Dayen age" Disney D.** </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
