<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject7521</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-15 08:30:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Wet brick </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-15 08:23:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Secret life of the American teenager. So stupid but I couldn't stop watching. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-15 08:21:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Totally agree! Loved that series. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-15 07:56:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hurts like heaven by Coldplay. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-14 01:18:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Make money like in the sims 4  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-11 05:46:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I fell over trying to pet my cat and the pain went from my rear all the way down to my foot </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-11 05:29:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm asexual and even if I wasn't I rarely leave the house. Single in the womb single 'til the tomb  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-11 04:38:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Spirited Away </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-11 04:31:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Stop talking so much, don't get Facebook, and do an extra year of high school </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-11 04:27:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Books, you can find ones that are in great condition for a fraction of the bookstore price  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-10 16:23:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Such a meowdel! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-09 06:01:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> In the 2nd semester of 12th grade I was taking a biology class but I dropped it after a couple days to take an online class. 

Well, a couple days later I was in the library during that class period and the same biology class I dropped came through to use the computer lab while I was sitting and checking something on my phone at one of the tables. Then a couple of minutes later the teacher came back to where I was sitting and he was so damn mad and he was said in a low angry voice, "so you would rather do this than sit and work?" And just to make him more angry I said yeah and then he just left. 

But then I kind of started tearing up because I was embarrassed at the fact that he caught me looking like I was a lazy ass because I'm not and I really had personal reasons that I won't go into for dropping that class and I was just mad at him for making me feel like a jerk because I wasn't...he didn't know shit yet he was judging me. 

Anyway, it was always awkward when I saw him in the halls after that. We never talked again after that and I feel like it was a loss to me because he was a nice guy and he was really helpful to me. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-09 05:37:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I have a cat named Oscar too but he's white and 2 yrs :) yours is so cute! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-09 05:35:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I have a crush on the only male nurse who works at the place where I get my chemo. Actually I'm just a sucker for anyone who's nice to me and I don't know why. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-09 05:18:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Pink rabbits by The National </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-01 00:03:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Me too, I deleted it cause I was mad.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-31 18:44:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I got fairy dust dusting powder, 2 shower gels, and a candy mountain. Stuff sold out soooo fast. I tried to buy a lot of stuff through the app but it kept asking for my address which i gave like 3 million times so I got nothing. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-29 02:49:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Big Bang theory is trash. Surprised it wasn't higher up here lol. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-21 07:14:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Telling someone who doesn't fucking want kids that they are being selfish or that they will when they're older.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
