<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject5070</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-06 00:07:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hirry up man! - I'm freezing.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-05 20:19:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hello dear stranger I am waiting in Yan Mayen right now, where are you? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-05 20:17:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I know that, does osteriech mean japan?? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-05 12:07:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What do you mean with Go to Dr. Osteriech for help? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-03 23:16:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> These are the best notinteresting posts, so melancholical and sugestive.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-03 23:14:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Plot Twist: Upvote </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-11-27 23:26:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I call it: "Leafs in the Soup." </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-11-21 12:27:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Someone upvoted this - Hello.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-11-21 07:04:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I live in germany we dont habe 10.000 refugees but 700.000 and wverything is normal.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-11-20 23:17:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Pretty normal tbh.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-11-20 23:16:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You have a friend. As do I.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-11-17 22:10:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The suicide rate in Greenland began to rise during the 70's so it is unlikely that its caused by harsh climate conditions. But many people in Greenland have an alcohol problem and suffer from a culture clash between western lifestyle and their traditions.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-11-15 11:01:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The dictionary I got should suffice, and a Kalaallisut to Danish dictionary is still quite useful since you could translate danish words easy into other languages. Thanks for your response.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-11-14 12:32:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> His question seems a bit silly. Millions of square meters? Why would he need that. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Jan Mayen is very cool, but this Sub is dead, right? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-11-09 18:15:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-11-08 22:09:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yes I've heard a bit about these little conflicts. We will see what happens!  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-11-08 20:04:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That makes sense. And i'm very happy to know that now, this is just something I couldn't have known. So thank you for the explanation. Now that you mention it the word settlement has really not the same meaning as village and I will mind my words better in the future. 

Btw: I've heard that Qaasuitsup might split into 3 smaller municipalities.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-11-08 10:48:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I never believed that I am a Special Snowflake, I just asked if you thought that I think so. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-11-08 08:28:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I would be really happy to get a response.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-11-07 22:35:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Ok, good to know. Sorry that I forgot to upvote, I thought you don't have to do that because there aren't many comments, but now I know that there is a Karma Counter. :) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-11-07 22:34:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I know what you mean, and I read everything you wrote, the main question of this post was just about the dictionray which got answered very fast. And I just thought that I could use this opportunity to ask something else as well. It is true that I'm not very prepared, but as I said, this question was just a "Bonus" as I can't do my trip to GL very soon. And I'm not quite sure what you meant with fantasy get off Sub, do you think I try to be a Special Sowflake because of loving Greenland? And I can understand that you don't like the word Settlement, but as a not native Speaker the only other possibility I can think of is village or town and I decided to use mainly the word settlement since thats how every inhabited place in Greenland is called in Wikipedia, tell me how I should call it and why (would be much appreciated). </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-11-07 21:26:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thanks, thats what I wanted to hear. Even though I would love to visit Tasiilaq, Nuuk and Nanortalik I believe its just to expensive.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-11-07 21:23:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I never knew about Lonely Planet so thank you for this tip. Secondly I've heard that GL will get a new Airline "Aluu Airlines", I wonder if flying gets easier and cheaper then. (But thats something I should Google and not ask here...) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-11-07 21:17:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yes other than going with a group its impossible to visit the park I guess, and with a group its damn expensive.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-11-07 21:15:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So I can only post things here if you want to travel to GL? I ask questions here becaise I'm interested in Greenland... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-11-07 13:01:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Why would you even know how long I'm planning on travelling to Greenland? I already know when I'll do it and to pass the time I try to learn some things abput GL.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-11-07 12:59:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thank you! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-11-07 12:58:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Many thanks. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Kalaallisut dictionary and travelling to Greenland. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-11-06 20:40:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So as you might have noticed I am currently the only one posting on this subreddit, so I try to combine questions.

First question: Is there anywhere in the Internet a useful KL dictionary? I know [this one](https://de.glosbe.com/kl/de/) but it isn't very big.

Second Question: I am planning on travelling to Greenland and I would be happy to get some tips of ppl, who have already done that. Did you fly or go by ship? Which Settlements did you visit? Do you have to go with a group if you want to go hiking? Did you visit the national park? How expensive was it.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-10-31 15:44:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> And it's again CAN'T_TRUST_HILLARY... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-10-31 15:04:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thanks.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-10-31 15:04:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I am going to read this asap. Thank you.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-10-31 07:57:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thanks! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> God and Kierkegaard. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-10-30 21:58:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> For me it doesn't matter what science says and proves and I am as open minded as you can get, but in the end I always come to God if I am anxious, I can't do anything about it wheter doubt it or not, I just fall into "Gods hands" when I'm in need. 

And is this what Kierkegaard said about religion? If anyone is familiar with his beliefs and could recommend me a book to understand him, I would be very happy.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-10-30 21:13:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Burningseries.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> I want to live until 2070 to see how utterly wrong Anno 2070 was. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-10-30 20:45:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-10-30 20:22:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Earth Sciences </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Why can't we color plankton white in order to stem or even stop climate warming? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-10-30 20:13:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-10-30 12:42:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Rilke! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [Misc] When is the Update? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-10-25 18:59:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Title.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-10-23 21:00:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Where do you live?
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-10-21 22:48:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Until now.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-10-19 22:15:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I would like to visit this forest.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-10-19 19:01:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So there are no trees indigenous? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-10-18 19:40:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Very interesting and helpful - thanks. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-10-18 19:39:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thanks for the comment, I was just wondering and you cleared it out. The Pohutukawa looks amazing!  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-10-18 19:33:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thanks for the quick response! I was just wondering about mosquitoes, because I thought it would be too cold for them. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> New-Zealandic trees. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-10-18 19:16:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Which trees are the most common one and how are they called? Are these trees similar to trees, which grow in europian regions or even the same? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Forests in Greenland. And Wasps. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-10-18 19:05:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I've heard that only in the southernmost regions of Greenland some trees manage to grow, but does a forest in Greenland exist?

I've also heard that mosquitoes in Greenland really exist (and a lot of them). Is that true? The same question goes for wasps, even though I haven't heard anything about Greenlandic wasps I would be interested if they exist. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-10-09 22:20:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thanks for uploading, this is very interesting! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-09-25 07:06:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> My age. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-09-22 19:21:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I dont know this show but it disgusts me. A bunch of idiots judging each other. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-09-20 22:25:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thats what i thought so thanks for making this clear, and I was going to buy the exact same book as the one in the link you sent me. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Anyone here? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-09-20 18:20:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I want to live in Svalbard. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-09-20 18:17:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I found a KL lesrning book in german so its fine. Thanks for your answer. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-09-20 11:33:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thanks, because someone said that you need the danish basics of grammar for kalaallisut grammar. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Learning Kalaallisut </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-09-20 09:48:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Aluu, if I want to learn kalaallisut do I habe to learn danish before? I'm a german native speaker.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-09-19 23:59:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Great  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-09-13 01:30:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It makes me melancholic. 
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
