<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject9743</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-06-04 23:33:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Aloe. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-06-04 20:40:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> There's not much for a part two. The three people who defended country music by calling people "emo faggots" and telling them to go kill themselves posted statuses of their own. Not much came of them. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Post a negative status about country music, all hell breaks loose. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-06-04 05:25:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-06-03 14:26:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> One Missed Call - Watch the Japanese version, American version sucks. A Tale of Two Sisters - More of a mindfuck movie, not all the scary. It is much better than it's American counterpart, The Uninvited. If you want some gore movies there's Grotesque, an awesome Japanese torture movie. I would also recommend Strange Circus, Battle Royale, Koma, Reunion, and Death Bell. (I love Asian horror, if you didn't notice.) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-06-03 14:10:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Cannibalism is a part of nature. The news is just focusing on these stories because they know people are interested in them. It's nothing new, people are fucked up and do fucked up things. This will die down, the media will stop covering it, and cannibalism will go back to the shadows. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-06-03 14:08:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> After downing 2 bottles of tylenol and having to get my stomach pumped. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-06-03 14:07:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I saw one that said "UKE." I'm not sure if it was referring to the ukelele or what the Japanese call the bottom position in a gay relationship. Either way, cool. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-06-03 14:05:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Sell the time machine. Shit would go for billions. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-06-03 14:00:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yes. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-06-03 13:54:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Bipolar disorder is harder to diagnose, if she is under 18 she cannot be legally diagnosed as bipolar. It can be suspected, but the DM-IV says it shouldn't be diagnosed at that time. Because of that, most teens showing bipolar tendencies are just written off as depressed. Bipolar is different from depression because the subject displays periods of depression, and manic episodes. If she is unusually sad for some time, and the next week she is unusually happy, it's safe to assume she is bipolar. That being said, it doesn't really matter what the diagnosis is. Self harm is dangerous and if she is not getting help then she should do so. She will not appreciate it, but that's because she is sick. When she begins to get better is when she will thank you. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-06-03 13:49:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Life is what you make of it. I've been depressed for 8 years now and have been on and off meds for that time. After a nasty suicide attempt and months in the hospital I found a place of refuge, a local haunt in my town. It's a place where I can socialize and work out my frustration in a positive way. I'm not telling you to go work at a haunt (unless you really want to,) I'm saying you need to go find your reason to live. My reason is to scare the shit out of people and make them piss themselves. I am now going to school and hoping to write horror films. I'm not always happy, but the passion I feel for this is keeping me going. I hope that you can find something just as important to you. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-06-03 13:42:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It essentially means that death is more painful than life. Why cause unnecessary pain when you can just live? Life gets better, despite constant obstacles and pessimism.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-06-03 13:39:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Wouldn't YOLO not apply here when talking about zombies? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-06-03 13:36:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Never tell them that they have no reason to be doing it, that hurts the most of all. Just tell them you're there for them, talk to them when they need it, be a shoulder to cry on, never judge them, and do little things to make them smile. In the end, it is their battle to face, but that doesn't mean you can't help them a little bit along the way. My favorite anti-suicide quote is the following:
Razors pain you;
Rivers are damp;
Acids stain you;
And drugs cause cramp.
Guns aren't lawful;
Nooses give;
Gas smells awful;
You might as well live. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-06-03 13:28:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> There's one movie that my current boyfriend showed me before we dated. My situation at the time was not the greatest and I was in and out of hospital and inpatient care. This movie just struck me. It's called Synecdoche, New York.
[Preview Here](http://youtu.be/XIizh6nYnTU) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-06-03 13:23:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Talk to him. He probably feels isolated and alone. Even if the cops said everything your father did was technically legal, the years of emotional and physical abuse have probably left him with some scars. The least you could do after choosing sides and ignoring him is reach out a helping hand. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-06-03 13:15:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It depends on what she likes, I suppose. For my boyfriend's last birthday I got him a couple of his favorite dishes from this weird restaurant he loves. I hate it, so we never go, but the least I could do was get him some baba ghanoush. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-06-03 13:07:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> According to the guy I was seeing, I wasn't "happy enough" for him.
I had just gotten out of the hospital for attempted suicide when I met him. The fuck? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-06-01 06:10:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Mr. Rogers had his car stolen from him while on the set of "Mr. Rogers Neighborhood." When the news announced that the car that had been stolen belonged to THE Mr. Rogers, the people who stole it returned it. (That's the only success story I know.) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-06-01 05:57:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> He's fine. The cut on his head is pretty much healed (this happened about 2 weeks ago) and we've fixed the door. His schoolmates asked him what happened, and he told them he got into a fight. I think the real story is much more interesting. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-06-01 05:56:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> He said it was similar to a roman numeral? I didn't really understand what he was trying to tell me. He claims that he didn't see it but he knew it was there. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-06-01 05:55:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I don't know. He said he didn't recognize it.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-05-31 10:49:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I hate saliva outside the mouth. It leaves this weird sensation when it's on my body and it gets cold and gross way too fast. I've never been able to understand why people like sloppy kisses or huge hickeys. The texture and temperature of saliva is something I cannot stand, I shudder at the thought of it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-05-31 10:33:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I don't want to retype the whole story, so here's a post I made the night it happened.

My brother started having night terrors when he was younger, they usually consisted of him crying and asking odd questions. After consoling him, everything was fine and he usually went back to sleep. He is now 16 and hasn't had a night terror in years, until tonight.

At around 1:30am I was asleep in bed but woke up to hear my brother screaming and run into the bathroom outside my room. He had not been feeling well earlier that evening so I assumed he was going to throw up in the toilet and be on his merry way. I then heard him run downstairs, it sounded like he was running into walls. My mother woke up and tried to console him, she asked him what was wrong and he replied, "I have to kill myself." At this point, I knew something was wrong so I got out of bed and went downstairs. I saw my mother in awe of the situation and my brother breathing heavily. He looked like he didn't know where he was or what was going on.

I went to him and tried to talk him down, he wasn't listening to me. He just kept insisting that he had to kill himself. Terrified, I asked my mother if we should wake him up with water before he did anything. She refused, and tried to pat his back to calm him down. This startled him, and he began to pick things up and throw them around the room. He lifted a couch at one point, but my mom pulled him away before he could flip it. He then went for a shoe-rack and threw it at me. After being hit, I grabbed my dog and ran upstairs to put him out of harms way.

When I returned from putting my dog in my room, I saw my brother run into our kitchen. There was a huge crash and the sound of broken glass, and then the lights went out. I heard one more time, "I have to kill myself," as my brother crawled towards me. He sat on the floor in silence. Apparently he woke up when he was on the floor, because he stopped freaking out. I asked him if he knew where he was, he said he did. I asked him if he was okay, he said he didn't know. My mother grabbed a flashlight and went into the darkened kitchen to find a hole in our back window with glass all over the floor. Judging by the blood on his forehead, my brother had slammed his head into the glass.

I told my mother we should call and ambulance and have him taken to the psych ward. She said she'd take him to the doctors tomorrow. My brother is now too scared to go back to sleep. He said that there was a number looming over him and the only way to get rid of it was to kill himself. He said there were no voices, no shadows, just a number he didn't know above him.

**tl;dr my little brother breaks windows with his head when he sleeps** </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-05-31 10:20:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> My SO is very into UFC. I get bored with it, but I turn it on for him. Although, we don't usually watch too much of it. I always ask too many questions and we wrestle. He knows all the stupid UFC moves so I end up looking like an ass and almost passing out. It's fun though! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-05-31 10:16:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I get migraines quite often, and I've learned to convince myself that they don't hurt. It only works some of the time, usually on my less severe migraines. I think it's more of me distracting myself from the pain rather than not feeling any pain at all. That being said, the mind can do amazing things. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-05-31 10:11:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> How many digits of pi do you know? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-05-31 10:07:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I wish it was "pidgeon" so I wouldn't read it as "pig eon." </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-05-31 10:04:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I want my first dance to be "I Want To Know Your Plans" or "A Walk Through Hell" by Say Anything. They're both cute and meaningful songs, but I don't know how to dance. Good luck! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-05-31 09:55:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I used to spell "pigeon" as "pidgeon." It sounds like there's a "d" in there. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-05-31 09:53:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Tell her how you feel. She has the power to end the engagement, and if you're there to support her and love her she can make it through. Even if she calls off the marriage you don't have to marry her immediately. You two can date casually or whatever. If her family feels bad about it, be a man and sit down and talk to them. If you are serious about her, tell them that you want to better your future for the two of you. In the end, you and her family both want the best for her. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-05-31 09:47:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Then you are fine. Even if the police do come looking for you, they won't have much evidence to go on. She probably won't even call the police, unless she wants to be viewed as a woman who hooks up with random men online. Also, the police have better things to do than go and get a warrant for a guy they don't know the name of to find a wallet. They'll probably recommend she cancel her credit card and be on their merry way. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-05-31 09:39:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Did you two just hook up or is there money involved? As long as the sex you two had was legal and consensual, you should either call the police and report her for harassment or just ignore it. If you didn't take her wallet (and if the sex was legal) she has nothing on you. She's probably just trying to scam you. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-05-30 09:21:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Why does it make you uncomfortable? Are they making weird eye contact with you? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-05-30 09:14:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The Song of Healing is a song from Legend of Zelda: Majora's Mask.
That is my favorite song in my favorite installation of my favorite video game series.
I also have a tattoo of it on my wrist for my 1 year anniversary of no self-harm. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-05-30 09:09:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> As a female who is usually attracted to men the same age as me or older, probably not. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-05-30 09:07:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I have had the same feelings with my current boyfriend. He had a past full of flings and one ended in a child being conceived. I don't hold any of it against him, because I love him. I realized that I was insecure because I was worried that I was not as good as the rest. All I know is that he chose me and we're happy. There's no reason that you should hold her past against her. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-05-30 09:01:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Angelica from the Rugrats. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-05-08 11:15:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Playing the Ocarina.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-05-08 11:12:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It depends on who is complimenting me.
If it is my family member, I usually just say thank you because I know that even if they were lying they would never admit it.
If it is a person I just met (especially a guy) I don't tend to believe them. They usually have no backing to their compliment, and most times they just want to get on my good side.
If it is a close friend, I take what they say to heart. I know these people wouldn't lie to me. They compliment me because they want to, not because they feel obligated to. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-05-08 11:06:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I am a female from the East Coast, and I have never tanned or duckfaced. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-05-08 10:54:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Does Yaoi count as porn? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Maxim the Yorkie at 4 months old </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-05-07 20:40:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
