<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject1334</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-11-08 07:34:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I don't know if this is what you're talking about or not but one time the leaders took a whole bunch of us to a field next to the church (side note: the field had a pavilion in the middle and a giant flagpole with a brick base also in this field. Probably not the safest spot for this "activity".) anyways, they threw us out there and blindfolded us. They put a CD player somewhere on the edge of the field and started playing one of Tommy Monson's talks really REALLY soft. They also drove a truck into this field and started blasting Taylor Swift or some other very worldly music as loud as it would go and we were supposed to "find our way to the prophet."  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-11-08 07:20:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's always been so frustrating to me that churches, the mormon church especially, can convince it's members that trials are a test of your faith and are making you stronger. A loving God isn't going to make your life shit "to test your faith" and "to make you stronger." Like my mom, a TBM, was diagnosed with breast cancer last year. (It was small and a double mastectomy made her cancer-free) Anyways, she said that at first she was a little puzzled because my brother had been on a mission for a few weeks and she thought you always received tons of blessings from your kid being on a mission, but then one day she says to me "I've realized that this was a blessing. I found the cancer before it had spread. The Lord was blessing me." She was actually convinced that her finding breast cancer was a blessing. WTF MOM. And then she was all "cancer was a blessing for us because it allowed us to see the hand of The Lord and increase our faith," through the whole thing. She got many priesthood blessings over this time and she thought they were so incredible because they would say things like "you will live to see your grandchildren" AFTER doctors had already told her that surgery would get rid of it no problem. WHAT THE ACTUAL FUCK MOM. It just baffles me how some people believe the things they do.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-11-07 18:39:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I think doing good would include not being racist, sexist, homophobic, and taking ten percent of peoples income for your own personal gain.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-11-07 18:35:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Richard Dawkins  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Does anybody know Joseph Smith's reasoning behind the Word of Wisdom? Did he even give any reasoning? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-11-07 15:38:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The Word of Wisdom has always been something that bothered me, even when I believed. As far as I know, coffee and tea in particular, have plenty of health benefits, and are actually decently good for you, so I never understood why we were commanded not  to drink them. I've always been taught that the word of wisdom is commandments that take care of our body, because "our bodies are temples, they're God's creation, and they're one of the greatest gifts he's given us." And so it's a terrible sin to misuse our bodies. But as I said before, coffee and tea are actually decently good for you. Also, it made more sense that God, as long as I was a good person (was kind, caring, compassionate, helped and served others, etc.), wasn't going to send me to hell because I drank coffee, I mean, come on, but as every good little mormon kid did/does, I just pushed all of this aside and ignored it. So now, I'm just curious if Joseph Smith every provided any explanation, at all, for the word of wisdom. 

Another thing that has nothing to do with this, but Reddit doesn't
let me post things close together, and it's just a small triumph that I thought you guys might be interested in hearing, so I'll just tack it on the end of this post. I got accepted into a university away from home. Better days are coming. 9 more months.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-11-07 15:27:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That's a dumb answer, IMO.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-11-07 08:32:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I have seminary before school. I have to drive from seminary to the school before school starts sometimes I am able to make it to my first class as the bell rings sometimes I'm not. Seminary is over at 6:50.am. I probably leave at 6:55 as soon as I can. School starts at 7:15. But with Walmart home office traffic on the route to school as well as a high school of 4,000 students things get pretty crowded. Plus it doesn't help that my parking spot is about a 3 minute walk to my class.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-11-07 07:28:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> 15 wins and a 3.97 ERA is not bad by any means either. I was even guilty of this before, but am starting to come around for Lynn and see how good of a pitcher he actually is. I think, honestly, Cardinal fans are a little spoiled when it comes to starting pitchers. Lynn did have the highest ERA of any Cardinal starter that had regular starts. However a 3.97 ERA isn't bad, especially for the number 4 rotation spot which Lynn seemed to occupy. I'm sure other teams would kill for a number four starter with those numbers. Anyways, as I was saying Cardinal fans are spoiled. If you look at what the Cardinals rotation ended up being for the last few months of the season this is what we get. Wainwright, Miller, Kelly, Lynn, Wacha. Wainwright, Kelly, and Wacha each had an ERA under 3.00. Miller had an ERA of 3.06. Lynn as I've stated before was 3.97. As well, Wainwright had 19W, Kelly 10W, Miller 15W, Wacha 4W (but many will point to his one loss and the fact that he started much later than the others), Lynn 15W So when we, as Cardinal fans, myself included look at these 5 starters, it's easy to be disappointed with Lynn. Oh he's just a run of the mill average to below average starter. When we just look at these 5. If you were to put it all into perspective and look around the league I think you would actually be impressed with Lynn. To reiterate what I said before 15W and a 3.97 ERA (I know there are more stats, I'm just citing those 2) really are pretty good numbers, maybe not for a staff ace, but really good numbers nonetheless. Especially from a number 4 starter. There are plenty of teams that would love Lynn type production. It's just easy to be disappointed by a 7 sitting amongst 9's. Ultimately Cardinal fans should be happy with Lynn's performance.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-11-07 06:36:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> And Merry Christmas ya filthy animal.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-11-07 06:34:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Before I start let me say this is not based on any fact at all whatsoever. This is just a thought I had. And now that I think about it, you probably questioned your bishop for this reason. At any point in history, from the beginning of time, it doesn't ever seem reasonable to write something down on gold (or other metal) plates. The time and effort it would take to chisel just one word would be ridiculous. Not to mention if you ever made a mistake. It just doesn't seem realistic to me. 
Also, on a side note, if anybody knows the answer to this question, please feel free to answer. Why would they have written the BOM on plates made out if such a valuable metal as Gold? Just doesn't seem plausible to me.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-11-07 06:27:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Another thing that pisses me off about seminary is that most days I'm barely making it to school on time (like bell rings as I walk through the classroom door), but some days I'm not making it on time to school. The whole situation just pisses me off.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-11-07 06:24:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Right, right. And I would definitely skip seminary if I could, but my parents do things like ask the seminary teacher if I was there. Then there's always in between seminary and school, but I barely make it to school on time as it is (sometimes I don't which pisses me off, but that's another rant for another day.)  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> I took Starbucks into seminary this morning. I could feel them judging me. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-11-07 06:10:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-11-07 00:31:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That is true. That would be a lot for a backup. Maybe the Cardinals can get something figured out and strike a trade sending him to a team that could use an upgrade at third, but isn't necessarily shopping for one? It wouldn't make the trade , but could maybe sway them in favor of it; put them over the top and get them to accept? Maybe I'm just crazy and hoping, that after all Freese has done for the Cardinals, he'll have a bigger impact than he actually will or can. Maybe I'm just crazy and all he is is a contract to shed.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-11-06 23:04:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> According to White Sox writers, the white sox have interest in Freese. Or at least should have interest in Freese. Would they be willing to open up one hole to fill another with a Freese for Ramirez straight swap? Or maybe send Lynn over too to make it more enticing for a club wanting to win sooner rather than spend years of rebuilding and then get a solid bench bat or two and maybe a prospect or two from them as well as Ramirez?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-11-06 22:48:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Besides the fact that Garcia has very, very little value on the trade market right now, Jaime Garcia is the only left handed pitcher capable of starting in the majors for the Cardinals at this point. Just like for spring training for the 2013 season, I'm gonna say Jaime Garcia has a guaranteed rotation spot.  He didn't have to compete against Lynn, Miller, and Rosenthal last year, and I don't expect him to have to compete this year. On a side note I would say Adam Wainwright is the only other guaranteed rotation spot. As it stands now (players could be traded) I think we'll see Lynn, Wacha, Miller, Martinez, and Kelly competing for three open spots with Lynn, Wacha, and Miller being the favorites.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-11-06 22:38:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I would definitely agree with this. I think Miller has A LOT of trade value. I also think The Cardinals would be dumb to trade him. I also think Lynn can commend decent trade value because as someone else commented "there are worse pitchers that have rotation spots" He's young, not too expensive talented and with the right circumstances could turn in to a solid 2 starter. I think this is a great time to move Lynn. Before maybe his contract gets higher and he gets older. He has great trade value and the Cardinals have younger pitchers ready to take the reins and blossom with a rotation spot. My vote goes to trade Lynn. I think Martinez's value is spearheaded by the fact that the 2014 could easily be his first season as a starter. I think a team thats on the cusp of finishing up rebuilding (a team like the Royals for example) would show some serious interest a guy like Martinez. I also agree that David Freese is not going to be worth much on the trade market. However I do think he could be a piece that could sway the other side into accepting a trade. I think it would be wise for the Cardinals to move him as his contract just keeps going up and Kolten Wong is ready to take 2B and Matt Carpenter can shift to 3B.  I also think Matt Adams has decent trade value, however, I think he's more valuable to the Cardinals than what they would get in return from trading him. Whether Allen Craig is at 1B and he provides a decent bat off the bench (an area of need for the Cardinals) or Allen Craig is in right and he adds power to a low-power lineup, I think he adds more value to the Cardinals than anything they would get in return for trading him. 
My prediction: Of the 5 players I listed (Miller, Lynn, Martinez, Adams, Freese) Miller, Martinez, and Adams will stay. Lynn and Freese will be sporting different colors come next spring. 
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What kind of trade value do you think David Freese, Lance Lynn, Carlos Martinez, Matt Adams, and Shelby Miller (who I really don't want them to trade) have? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-11-06 13:15:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-11-06 02:49:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This has always been big problem for me with all religion, but Mormonism especially. 
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-11-05 17:14:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I've always been the same way. I've seen all these people talking about how depressing it is and how you can't be happy not believing in a God and an afterlife, because without God life has no meaning, but I've always been just fine. Perfectly happy. Honestly, it's kind of better for me.  Now I don't have to be constantly worried about upsetting the invisible sky being and whether I'm going to hell or not. I echo the words "Life has meaning because it is finite. It has meaning because it doesn't go on forever. The Mona Lisa is worth $100 million+. Had Leonardo da Vinci painted many of them, it wouldn't be worth much, but because there is only one (amongst other reasons), it has an incredible value."  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> My TBM parents used Mormon 9:1-3 to try and convince me there is a God. I always found it ridiculous and dumb when TBM's pointed to this scripture in support of God's existence. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-11-05 16:45:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Mormon 9:1-3 
1 And now, I speak also concerning those who do not believe in Christ.

2 Behold, will ye believe in the day of your visitation--behold, when the Lord shall come, yea, even that great day when the earth shall be rolled together as a scroll, and the elements shall melt with fervent heat, yea, in that great day when ye shall be brought to stand before the Lamb of God--then will ye say that there is no God?

3 Then will ye longer deny the Christ, or can ye behold the Lamb of God? Do ye suppose that ye shall dwell with him under a consciousness of your guilt? Do ye suppose that ye could be happy to dwell with that holy Being, when your souls are racked with a consciousness of guilt that ye have ever abused his laws? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-10-31 14:16:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Here's the link to the full talk: 
http://www.lds.org/general-conference/2009/10/safety-for-the-soul?lang=eng

Just an all around ridiculous talk, in my opinion.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-10-31 06:41:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Just to add on, one that's up there on my list is Jeffrey R Holland, talking about the BOM, "No wicked man could have written it, and no righteous man would unless it were of God."  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What's the most ridiculous thing you've ever heard a GA say in conference? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-10-31 06:32:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Just curious.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Am I being irrational? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-10-28 22:38:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I first stopped believing in God. But I still maintained a mindset of "if any church is true, it's probably the mormons." Then as time went by I discovered all the problems and holes in Mormonism and I became genuinely pissed off. I was pissed off because of all the lies the church was feeding me over the years. Day by day, even when I think I've discovered them all, I keep finding new problems with the church and it just makes me so mad that I was lied to and manipulated over the years.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Question about Joseph Smith. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-10-27 17:04:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I've been thinking about this for a little while and I was wondering if any of you have any more knowledge that can confirm or even refute my suspicion. I'm just curious. Anyways, Joseph Smith was a convicted con man. So maybe the angry mob and the chasing the Mormons out of towns and what not had less to do with them being mormon and more to do with them being pissed at Joseph for conning everybody in town.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Question about the BOM </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-10-17 06:29:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> One thing that baffled me, even when I was a believer, was citing the bible in the BOM. I was always told that the bible and the BOM were happening at the same time. So how does Nephi (2nd Nephi) quote chapters of Isaiah? And how does Lehi quote revelations from the book god gives him when revelations hadn't even been written yet? If there actually is a logical answer I would love to hear it. It's just something I've been thinking about.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> TBM Mother wants me to repent with the bishop and gets mad at me for "disrespecting" the prophet. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-09-24 19:02:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> My TBM mom, after finding out some things I had done, and after I came out, she told me she wanted me to repent with the bishop because she doesn't know how to "get a change in behavior without repenting and God." So she basically told me she doesn't know how to be a parent. At least thats what I got from it. Also, back when I was like 12 or 13 and believed, I copied and pasted some pictures of the first presidency, off the internet. into a word document, put them in frames and put them around my room. Well, this weekend , after comimg out, I was cleaning out my room, so i took out the paper, through it away and gave my mom her frames back. Well, she got super pissed at me because I "disrespected" the prophet. Its hard living with mormon parents when you aren't mormon. I guess I'm really just looking for advice.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> TBM Dad wants to discuss the Book of Mormon. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-09-23 22:23:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> My TBM father, after I have come out, told me that he wants to talk about the Book of Mormon because he doesn't know how anyone can explain it if God isn't real and Joseph Smith wasn't a prophet. Help me out. I need the perfect ammunition.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-09-17 22:13:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You were exactly right. After a few days of just pure anger, I got my phone back as long as I don't look up anything "anti-mormon" or "anti-God" and still would think about and consider a mission, and they started letting me drive my car again if I would go to seminary.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-09-09 22:15:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I live in NW Arkansas. I was terrified too. That's why I hadn't up until this point, but my sister (who I had no idea was doubting) came out and they were getting suspicious of me and questioning me. So I finally just went with it. They just could not seem to understand that I HAD to lie to protect myself. When my brother told them, all it did was cause problems. They say it's only happening because I "lied" but them and I both know thats not true. They would have been like this regardless. I just hope your parents are more understanding and accepting.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-09-09 22:08:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> They required us to give them to them. Or punishments would be even more severe. Like losing everything for good, etc. 
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> I came out to my parents last night. Help. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-09-09 21:58:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I came out to my parents last night. So did my sister. Things did not go well. They took our phones and my car. Took our passwords for our phones, facebook, twitter, etc. Went through all of those things. We're basically grounded indefinitly. They're claiming that it has nothing to do with the beliefs, but that its because we "lied" and lived "secret lives". I'm 17 years old. I need helpon what I should do. It was even thrown out there of sending me to live with my grandparents. And they were even talking about pulling my sister out of dance (which is her life) because she "had to dance on a sunday a couple times and that must be a big reason why she doesn't believe and it's their jobs as parents to help their kids have their priorities straight." And when they found out I had been on r/exmormon and that I was going to introduce it to my sister they said furiously "And now you're going to show her an anti-mormon website!" so I said "It's a support group." and their response was "She's a 13 year old girl, she doesn't need a support group. And neither does a 17 year old boy." 
Please, help me out here, guys. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Closet exmormon attending EFY. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-06-12 09:11:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm attending EFY in Columbia, MO July 1-6 (anybody else?) 
Anyways, despite being atheist, I enjoy EFY, once you get passed the devotionals and what not, you can have a good time. I was wondering if anybody had some good questions I could ask my counselor or the people teaching the classes to either stump or troll them. This is how I make it through the devotionals, etc.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-05-05 08:38:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I definitely just felt "the spirit" while reading this post.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-05-02 04:57:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Oh my god. I am the exact same way.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> So I found this in the Doctrine and Covenants. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-04-13 19:25:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> D C 19:26 
"And again, I command thee that thou shalt not covet thine own property, but impart it freely to the printing of the Book of Mormon, which contains the truth and the word of God" 

Anybody but me see something wrong with that? 
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Did anyone else catch Uchtdorf say this during conference? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-04-09 06:04:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> He said, when talking about visiting Africa and all the poverty there is over there, "it deeply saddened me to see other LDS members living in such poverty." So does he not care about all the other people living in poverty? Was this a good catch or am I being ridiculous?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-03-31 20:55:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yes, we were (are) both guys.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Interesting story about a Mormon youth dance. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-03-31 20:39:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So I'm exmo, and once when I was at a church dance, one of my good friends (who isn't an exmo) and I were goofing off and doing this thing where we held each others hands and spun in a circle. Well, shortly after we started a leader came up to us, very serious, obviously angry and upset, and he says "Stop. It's not funny and it's not right. Do you understand me? It's not funny and it's not right." Just thought you other exmos might enjoy that.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Does anybody have a good question I can ask a dating panel at a fireside? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-03-24 21:39:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm going to a fireside tonight, and it's a dating panel. So they are wanting us to write down questions on a piece of paper to ask the people on the panel. I was wondering if you guys had any good questions to ask. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Lying </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-03-19 23:52:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I don't believe in God or follow mormon standards anymore, but my parents don't know that. So whenever there is a youth temple trip, I lie to my bishop so that I can attend. And I also still bless the sacrament and so on. Whenever I have an interview with my bishop, I lie and say I'm worthy. Is this bad? Should I feel bad about doing this? And also, my parents are making me put a bunch of money I get from working into saving for my mission. Money that I would rather have to do other things with. What should I do?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> I need some help in talking to my parents.  </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-02-19 21:38:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm 16 years old and I haven't believed in Mormonism for a little while now. My brother stopped believing when he was 14 and when he told our parents, all it did was cause problems. And for me if I told them, nothing would change. They would still make me go to church, seminary, mutual, etc. The only thing would be that it could cause problems between me and them as it did for my brother. So I figured I would just go along with things until I was out of the house. However, with the mission age being lowered to 18, I don't know how that would work out. I want to go to college and not on a mission, but they keep talking about me leaving as soon as I'm done with high school. I don't know what I should do since I was planning on not telling them I wasn't going until I was on my own. But with what they want me to do, I wouldn't get that opportunity. I need some help.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
