<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject8214</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Elon Musks Latest Prediction Is Simply Jaw-Dropping </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-13 13:19:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Leonardo DiCaprio Won More Than Just Best Actor at the 2016 Golden Globes: 5 Times He Ruled the Night </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-11 17:34:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Five things the U.S. stock market is worried about after last week's rout </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-11 15:44:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-11 13:25:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Elon Musk has really revolutionized our lives. Be it Tesla, Paypal, SolarCity or [Spacex] (http://www.profitconfidential.com/tag/spacex/) he is the one whose will power and urge to change human lives has made us proud. And ultimately this Tesla technology is going to be game changer for US citizens as it will save humans a hell lot of trouble and safe driving will be promoted </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Yuan to USD: This Could Hammer the Chinese Yuan 2016 </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-11 09:40:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Worst Stock Market Week </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-08 14:36:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This probably has been one of the worst weeks for the Global markets. How do you think will this week end for investors? On a high note or going further down? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-07 16:21:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Is there any possibility that VR games can affect a person mentally? Especially small kids...it is a very serious issue that kids tend to get involved in the things they experience on a regular basis...i knew a kid who used to be a part of a theatre group and she was playing the role of a daughter of a couple...in reality she was staying away from her father as her parents were divorced...she belonged to a very poor family...after some days of rehearsal she started feeling as if the couple were her real parents...she felt that all the situations in the play were real...she was so mentally disturbed that she cried and made life hell for the cast when they were going to replace the person playing the character of her father....any way my point is that this affects the minds of young boys and girls..is it in any way possible that such things can happen due to the oculus? any tests / precautions you guys have taken to avoid this? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Top 10 Ways to Invest after China Stock Market Crash 2016 </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-07 16:05:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hey guys as you all know the world markets are going berserk after the recent onslaught which has taken place in the China stock market. In the wake of such events I would like to ask you all what would be the 10 best ways to invest after this crash? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> China Yuan Devaluation Could Spark the Next Stock Market Crash </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-07 15:53:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-07 12:31:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This is pathetic...Its been the worst start for the global markets since 2000 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-07 12:30:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That is so over rated...and all the market hype isnt even worth it. China has become the centre of the world and indirectly they have controlled the global markets as of the present situation seems to me </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-07 12:06:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> China crash means much more to the world, Chinese Yuan also suffered a major setback as it sinked to a 5-year low. Oil prices are also suffering since 2015, now touching an 11-year low. Could this crash mean something for the US? http://www.profitconfidential.com/economy/heres-what-chinas-stock-market-crash-means-for-the-u-s/ </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> China Stock Market Crash Jan 2016 Explained: Why, What, How, Future </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-05 15:56:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-01 15:22:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Haha! I would really like to know who these 70% are...I best these might be from outer space or something.....I actually made a 6% overall profit in 2015..went down 24% as lost a good amount of money in Valeant...Ultimately all's well that ends well...2016 might just be the year of a market correction though...Check this out http://www.profitconfidential.com/stock-market/stock-market-correction-coming-in-2016/ </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-01 15:14:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It is also being said that US holds gold which is originally owned by other countries...how true is that? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> TIL United States has the Highest Gold Reserves in the world </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-31 12:32:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The Best Technology GIFs of 2015 </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-31 11:44:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Top tech stories of 2015 </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-31 06:26:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Some funny New Year's Resolution Quotes </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-31 06:08:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Martin Shkrelis KaloBios files for bankruptcy </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-30 17:47:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> 6 Awesome Things You Can Do On a Chromebook </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-30 15:14:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> BMO Analyst says crude oil could plunge another 50% </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-30 12:45:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The best NFL team right now is... </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-30 04:55:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Elon Musk trolling Volkswagen! </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-29 18:10:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> This is why Whisky ain't just a hard drink! </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-29 16:02:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> 2015 Might just have been the weirdest year till now </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-29 15:52:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Jim Rogers Says that the U.S. Dollar Is Not Sound </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-28 11:09:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> SpaceX CEO Elon Musk Drops the Hammer on Amazon Inc. CEO Jeff Bezos </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-24 12:12:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> 20 Startups To Watch In 2016 </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-24 11:02:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Donald Trump Calls Hillary Clinton's Loo Break "disgusting" </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-23 14:29:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Star Wars a Big Boost for Disney Stock </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-23 14:18:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-23 08:15:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah really...supposedly the government thinks he should start leading a good simple life....they don't understand a fucking rapist can't be normal! He is mentally ill and does not deserve to live in the society among normal ppl! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-23 04:24:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> He is already walking free...how shameful for such a developing country! And he has already recieved a sewing machine and 10K cash from the government...why the hell does he deserve all that? First of all he shouldnt be walking free....and second, he should be treated worse than a beggar....How can you let such a unworthy human even roam around freely like nothing has happened?? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The Federal Reserve hiked interest rates last week and the move completely changed the Canadian dollar forecast </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-23 04:02:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Guus Hiddink appointed as the new manager of Chelsea </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-20 06:39:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-19 10:55:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> extremely sry guys! my sincere apologies :( </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> ELI5 The Real Reason the Fed Raised Interest Rates? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-19 04:23:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> This Could Lead to a Canadian Dollar Collapse </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-18 09:55:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-17 18:26:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> the economy will never be ready </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Janet Yellen Is Committed to a Stronger Dollar </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-17 18:04:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The economic recovery has clearly come a long way, although it is not yet complete </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-17 14:33:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-16 17:01:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Stealing! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Get Ready for $20 Oil </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-16 16:59:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> 10 Observations From The New 'Batman v Superman' Trailer </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-16 12:24:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Is This Make or Break for Elon Musk? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-15 17:52:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Does This Spell the End for the Middle Class? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-14 18:32:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> 2016 Oscars?? These movies will surely make the cut </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-14 16:10:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-14 14:46:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Anything and everything which makes us happy is in itself, extremely satisfying for me! But moreover I would like to add spending time with my loved ones is most satisfying for me </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> One of the Worst Tattoos Ever!!! </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-14 14:32:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Worst Tattoo Ever! :/ </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-14 13:44:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Eight reasons why the UN climate conference in Paris led to historic deal uniting 195 countries </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-14 13:34:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Can Negative Interest Rates Save the Canadian Dollar? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-13 16:56:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-13 04:52:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The blue jay so called "patridge" seems to be lost in his hairy jungle! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> TIL 10 Facts about Pablo Escobar's wealth </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-13 04:48:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Tesla Motors is getting ready for a face-off with Alphabet Inc and it may be a winner-take-all kind of fight </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-10 17:35:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The Top 10 Biggest Video Games On YouTube In 2015 </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-10 15:54:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Mr. Trump...Why U open Ur Mouth? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-10 15:44:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> 6 Lesser Known Facts About Kendall Nicole Jenner </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-10 13:26:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-08 17:21:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> you should check this out for a clear understanding - http://www.elsevieradvantage.com/samplechapters/9780323034708/9780323034708.pdf </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Yen will become stronger than the US Dollar? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-08 15:58:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-08 15:54:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> ISIS terrorising the world is just shit....wish we had a game to kill ISIS terrorists and then get happy ending the ISIS if not for real..only virtually! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-07 19:16:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The true spirit of Christmas....Santa spreading smiles worldwide :) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Elon Musk would like to colonize Mars and save the Earth </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-07 15:33:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> RBA will have to cut rates again in 2016 lowering the value of the Aussie dollar </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-06 09:03:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-04 05:37:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> First of all, a dumb answer telling that there is only one way to access deep net shows ur talent. And yeah ur knowledge seems to be like...less than zero cos u think deep web can be accessed only using tor. And you are talking about my incorrect rambling? You are the one who referred to Tor when i was talking about hidden web services....lol </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-04 03:17:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Tor is a way to access deep net... tor isn't deep net. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-03 19:59:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Ever heard of deep net? It is a place where all such shady people loom around. These people can give to access to any person's bank accounts or credit / debit cards, leave alone the wifi hacking. They can hack into any system. You just have to name it. But this ain't safe at all...Please try and stay away from it...But a little knowledge is not at all harmful </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Little girls supporting Hillay Clinton for Presidency...but oopsss they can't vote! </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-03 19:54:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-03 18:20:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> However, Li-Fi may not be the go-to internet provider for most people due to its reliance on visible light. The technology website points out that visible light cannot travel through walls, giving Wi-Fi a significant advantage for most home and office consumers. Many people are also concerned with the potential cost of constantly running LED lights to provide a consistent stream of internet, making mass use unlikely.

The idea of Li-Fi was first introduced in 2011 by German Physicist Herald Haas during a TED talk. A year later, he founded a company named pureLiFi to focus on new advancements in the sector.

Deepak Solanki, CEO of Velmenni, said that the technology could be available within four years. "Currently, we have designed a smart-lighting solution for an industrial environment where the data communication is done through light, he said. We are also doing a pilot project with a private client where we are setting up a Li-Fi network to access the Internet in their office space." </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> This was Bill Gates' only transaction in Q3 2015 </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-03 18:06:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-03 16:22:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The light water reactor (LWR) is a type of thermal-neutron reactor that uses normal water, as opposed to heavy water, as both its coolant and neutron moderator  furthermore a solid form of fissile elements is used as fuel. Thermal-neutron reactors are the most common type of nuclear reactor, and light water reactors are the most common type of thermal-neutron reactor.

There are three varieties of light water reactors: the pressurized water reactor (PWR), the boiling water reactor (BWR), and (most designs of) the supercritical water reactor (SCWR).

The light water reactor produces heat by controlled nuclear fission. The reactor core consisting of fuel and control elements is enclosed by a water-filled steel pressure vessel. The heat generated by the fission heats the water which evaporates in the pressure vessel in a boiling water reactor but, in the pressurized water reactor, the steam evaporates in a steam generator of a secondary circuit. The steam energy is converted into rotary motion of the turbine to which a generator for the generation of electricity is connected. After flowing through the turbine, the steam condenses into water in the condenser and is recirculated to the pressure vessel or steam generator. The water required to cool the condenser is taken from a river and refed into the river in warmed condition or the heat is dissipated via a cooling tower into the atmosphere. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-03 16:19:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I follow Dwayne's instagram profile and he is a real Gym freak and a Dog-lover. He has certainly won hearts of his fans after this generous behaviour. We are proud of you Rock! We can smell what the Rock's cookin'! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-03 16:14:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> How are these tissues inserted in the human body? Are any special medical techniques or treatments used for insertion of tissues? And are there any side effects of the insertion ? If yes possibly what and how could they affect the human body? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Major news for Indians! Facebook's Internet.org service is now available throughout India </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-03 15:18:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-03 03:06:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Seems like she took No Shave November a bit too seriously! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> You gotta know these things about the Instagram King Dan Bilzerian </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-02 19:41:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Fed planning to hike interest rates in December....Things might get bad for the EUR/USD exchange rate </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-02 10:16:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-02 07:58:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This guy is in the legacy of Roberto Carlos~! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-01 18:05:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> With the name Quentin Tarantino Perfection is guaranteed! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Ariana Grande breaks hearts of millions of fans :( </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-01 18:01:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> 'Captain America: Civil War' trailer set a record with 61 million views in a single day </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-01 17:13:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Apple's All time record high Iphone sales in Q4 may indicate a major turn around for the company in a positive way </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-01 15:43:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-01 15:38:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> LEDs have a general life expectancy of 50 000 hrs. If you use your lights for 10 hours a day, this should be 13.7 yrs. If this is correct, then LEDs are definitely an investment, even the top of the range bulb would work out to cost 2.55GBP per year. Add that to the saving you would make on energy and youve got a very cost effective bulb!
However, there are times when, even high quality, LED products can last as little as a year. The problem with these can be attributed to a large number of things, here are a few main causes:
Heatsink
Designing a heatsink is a fine science. Some heatsinks do not have the correct amount of surface area, some do not take into consideration about the gaps between fins to enable air flow. Some have horizontal fins, when they are positioned vertically. The main design fault with the latter, being that heat rises. Rather than dispersing the heat away from the bulb, the heat coming from the lower fins heat the upper fins even more.
Capacitors
Most, standard, electronic capacitors are made from a plastic. These have an average life time of around 1 year, if used regularly. Capacitors are part of the circuit in every LED driver. Now a number of companies are making their capacitors from ceramics, giving them a much longer life expectancy.
Environment
LEDs are usually designed to work in our country, and in our climate. If they are used in a hot country, or enclosed area, the heat around them can easily surpass the heat they were designed to withstand, shortening their life time.
To get LEDs to their full potential, these factors, among other considerations, must be taken into account. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-01 15:30:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What makes HIV and AIDS different? basic difference between them?? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> 7 Reasons why Mark Zuckerberg is just a tiny bit beyond God-Like in Technology! </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-01 15:20:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-01 14:43:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The Dooms Day ain't far when nerds gonna marry computers! We are heading towards a very bad patch :/





 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-01 14:21:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> why else do you think some one will post such a link? a person who really wants to learn circuits can google himself or check out circuits on youtube. Don't need this thing buddy! Just a promotional tactic...m certainly down voting it </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Could December be the Game Changer for the stock market? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-01 13:13:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-01 12:36:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This dude's really getting some hate around the world from fans.......there have been young players always in this game....bt immaturity does'nt make up for such a mistake.....he better learn from it or else his career is drowned...LOL </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-01 08:19:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Why do the soldiers bow down to superman? Is it like some kinda takeover by superman? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Meanwhile in India.....alien invasion!!! Brace yourself warriors </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-01 08:03:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The other side of Pornstar Jenna Jameson </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-11-30 19:50:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-11-30 19:11:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> hahahahaha this ones really really hilarious! found something really funny after a long time!! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-11-30 17:58:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> 1. For one, he was the general who keeps on winning. And in any war effort, winning battles will always make you look good. And Napoleon won A-LOT! He pretty much goes undefeated up until Russia (Battle of Trafalgar doesn't count, caz Napoleon didn't direct that battle, which frankly I hope he did, and the loss in spain is the same situation, once Napoleon was in, they all got beat up). So he is the very definition of war hero up until the end of his military career. This is one of the main reason why he is the hero fo French, 

2. Secondly he was a revolutionary, and more importantly he isn't a pure revolutionary like the Jacobin, he does what he does to please the French people, and only the french people. For example he allows the nobles and the church state back in France after he was crowned emperor, but they have no power and right over the rest of the people. And this flies well with the French people who despite pushed out Church's, were still in heart Catholic. 

3. He was not only a hero to French, he was a hero to Italians, he was hero to Egyptians, and he was somewhat a hero to Poland. He freed the italians stats from Austria whom at the time ruled Italy with iron hand. Napoleon drove Austrians away and he ordered his soldiers not to plunder and pillage.which in itself is a heck lot better than Austrian army did. He eliminated the Holy Roman Empire and helped germanic states to built the Federation of the Ryen (I think that's how you spell it :P) allow them to have their own version of liberal and essentially made Germany. 

4. He was a hero to the government because during his time as general, his campaign kept government financially stable (somewhat, those guys really suck at economy). When royalists tried to overtook the french revolutionary government. Napoleon lead 6000 men, against 30000 I believe, and defended the government and drove away the royalist, essentially saved everyone on the council. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-11-30 17:52:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> cute dogs there! wish i could get a pet too :( </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> I thought Emma Watson just played an intelligent girl in Harry Potter. Reality is a bit different though...LOL :P </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-11-30 17:32:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-11-30 15:54:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> lol...u are a smart guy! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-11-30 15:19:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Focus shift for Tesla from electric motors to Rockets and Spacecrafts? how will the stock price get affected from this? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Scaring the shit outta Tesla eh? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-11-30 15:17:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> And this is some True ShitZ! Take a bow Leonardo </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-11-30 15:05:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Who has the last laugh in this Epic Twitter Battle? Jeff Bezos or Elon Musk...Elon Musk's mockery is just too damn funny! </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-11-30 14:43:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Exit Alert!!! Warning for the Foodies </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-11-27 14:21:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Best stocks to profit in December </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-11-26 17:16:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Youngest selfmade Billionaire arrested with corruption charges in Brazil! </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-11-26 17:02:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-11-26 16:48:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> WHat a story dude! Really inspirational....makes me feel proud about the citizens of our country who are working hard to achieve their goals in life! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The Federal Reserves easy money policies have helped the rich get richer. These policies have not helped the poor. This is the story about what the beggar in San Francisco Told Me! </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-09-18 17:54:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
