<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject3042</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Breaking news from a galaxy far, far away </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-26 14:41:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> I compiled these shot comparisons of BLADE RUNNER with modern sci-fi movies to show the strong visual impact of Ridley Scott's masterpiece </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-25 19:28:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Zombie movies would be much scarier if the make up looked like actual bloated, putrefied, and rotting corpses. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-16 22:11:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> ELI5: What are those transparent plastic cards with blurry lines they always show in movies when they show a lab sequencing DNA, how do those things represent genes and how are they created? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-13 22:22:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [VIDEO] Prvkrt v slovenskej histrii ide za mree lovek, ktor nm mal sli, ale rozkrdal verejn majetok </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-06 17:27:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> I know dozens of people who only use Windows and never even touched a Mac, but I don't know anyone who only uses Apple computers and never worked with Windows </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-22 22:53:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [Request] Looking for movies like The Mist, The Signal, I Origin or Coherence </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-19 20:33:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Volcanoes are like zits on the Earth's face </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-04 13:38:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> ELI5: Kauza s masrom </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-03 16:44:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Ahojte, prosm mte mi vysvetli tto najnoviu kauzu s masrom? Na zaiatku mi to plne uniklo

vaka! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Let's discuss Matt Damon's performance in The Martian from the perspective of it being nominated for an Oscar, meaning it was one of five best in the year (by implication) </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-27 02:07:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That scene where he operates on himself, that is why Matt Damon is nominated for an Oscar. In fact, the sequence starting when he wakes up after the accident and ending when he realizes he is fucked, that is a motherload of amazing acting. He perfectly conveys a near-future reality, where a scenario like this might happen. It would be the Apollo 13 of our time, but much worse. Damon is at the forefront of this reality, showing us a man stranded on a beautiful alien world and at the same time, thanks to the movie's moments of lightheartedness, showing us a man coping with this reality very well. He very effectively portrays the moments when Whatney's training kicks in, when he is at his most confident and efficient, to moments that are utterly human and show us his uncontrollable isolation and also optimism. To me it is an outstanding performance this year and also a bold new choice for the Academy, that is, to nominate an actor in a leading role from a sci-fi movie. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> ELI5: What would have been the response in the 1960s and 1970s to a similar crisis as seen in the movie The Martian, in our case where an Apollo astronaut would have been left stranded on the Moon under accidental circumstances? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-27 01:58:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Was there ever a contingency plan for when something might happen that would leave one, or both, men alone on the Moon? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Through his use of immaculate composition and long zoom shots, Stanley Kubrick created a perfect illusion of depth and perspective in Barry Lyndon. It's like a 3D movie without the glasses. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-26 16:22:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I wonder what he would have done with today's 3D technology. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> ELI5: Why do certain business, like supermarkets, cafes or branches of banks, leave the lights on at night when they are closed and empty? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-16 19:25:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I've always wondered about this and found it very confusing. Supermarkets do this very often and I always think they are open when I need one at night and of course they are closed and there is no one inside, not even a cleaning lady or whatever. What is the purpose of leaving the lights on inside? It seems like an awful waste of energy and also wouldn't it attract burglars since they can get a good look of what is inside (computers in banks, alcohol in shops, etc)? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Advertising agencies accumulate the most creative young minds to work on the least useful things imaginable </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-14 15:34:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It baffles me how much effort people put into making sure someone clicks on a banner instead of doing something at least a little bit valuable

Source: I work in an ad agency </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> I finally saw Risky Business (1983). Knowing nothing about it except the famous dance scene, I thought it would be a light 80s comedy... I was not expecting the porn version of Ferris Bueller's Day Off </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-11 13:43:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Risky Business surprised me on practically every level, from its music to its oddly shifting tone, story and R rating. Parents leave the main character alone for a week? Let's call some hookers! Damage dad's beloved car? Let's operate a high school sex ring! Doing it in every room of the house is not enough? Let's do it on a *real* train! 

What a weird amazing movie.

A 21 year-old Tom Cruise dressed in buttoned shirts looked nothing like a high school kid, but other than that I really enjoyed his performance. The famous dance scene was fun, but I was surprised by the rest of the movie and I think that scene is really out of place in it. I find it odd that this is the thing the movie is most remembered by (or associated with). </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Future archaeologists will discover Tupperware the same way we discover ancient pots and vases </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-06 23:09:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Are Chewbacca's eyes animatronic (or part of the mask in some way) or are they Peter Mayhew's eyes? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-01 15:56:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Since 1991's "Critters 3" (when he was only 17 and not a lead actor anyway) Leonardo DiCaprio has not been in a movie that has a sequel, is a sequel to another movie, or is part of a franchise in any way. Which other actors can claim this? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-31 14:35:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What a unique career this guy has. I really cannot even imagine him in a movie that has the number 2 attached to the title.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Custom handmade Finn and Jake I got for Christmas. My sister's colleague made these with no prior knowledge of the show after watching just one episode. Needless to say, she became a fan. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-28 15:45:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Is there no love for Jurassic Park 3? The set pieces, general entertainment value, and stand-alone originality should be enough to redeem it. [Spoilers for the movie] </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-28 15:10:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Over Christmas I realized that I have never seen Jurassic Park 3 properly from start to finish. I can't fathom why I didn't go see it when it came out in 2001, since I was the perfect age to enjoy it back then (I was 12) and over the years I only caught parts of it on TV. I've always been aware that it's considered the worst Jurassic Park sequel (I think that's still the case now when we have four JP movies) and that it has a low rating on imdb (5.9). But three days ago I gave it a shot, thinking that even if it's really that bad, at least I'll finally know why. And after three days I still find myself thinking about the movie and the more I do, the more I'm convinced Jurassic Park 3 deserves a second chance. I'm going to list the things I liked and leave out some of its problems as I'm sure they will be mentioned by nay-sayers in the comments. Let me just make it clear that i don't think JP3 is flawless by any means. I just think it's much much better than it is given credit for.

JP3 takes the Aliens route of being much more action packed and showing much more of the dinosaurs than its predecessors and basically becomes an action movie instead of an adventure movie (similarly to how Cameron switched genres from monster horror to action and showed us all those aliens instead of keeping them scary and in the dark). And why not? After two movies, the Spielbergian awe and wonder has faded and it would be pointless to try and recapture it (to imitate it, really) so instead JP3 goes all out. Unlike Jurassic World, this movie doesn't rely on nostalgia and apart from bringing back old characters (more on that later) it does its own thing. There is a new setting (well, the jungle looks the same, but at least it's a different island and we don't visit old locations) and a new dino kicks the T-Rex's ass instead of having it save the day again. Is this why JP3 has such a bad rep? Because it isn't JP enough?

I like the way they bring back Dr. Alan Grant. Having seen the dinosaurs up close and having rejected them as terrifying genetic mutants that are only a lab tech's facsimile of what a dino really was, he sticks tightly to his old school methods. He digs the dirt and dusts the bones. I think this makes perfect sense for the character. Later on the kid they went to save tells Grant he read both of his books, but liked the first one better because Grant "still liked dinosaurs when he wrote it." I loved that bit of characterization and I would be hard-pressed to pinpoint anything remotely as deep in Jurassic World. (Here I should add a little disclaimer: I might diss JW a bit in this post, but it's not meant to be a JW dissing post and I actually enjoyed JW a lot, for various different reasons.) It's also a neat touch that Grant didn't end up together with Ellie and that his inability to talk about anything else besides his work lead Ellie's child to label him The Dinosaur Man. Again, it's a nice bit of characterization. Grant is so engrossed in his work that he has no life outside of it and his only hope in life seems to be training his assistant Billy to continue with his work. Naturally, when another rich guy comes waving a big check under his nose to fund the work, Grant can't help it but accept. He has nothing else.

Another part of the movie that I enjoyed is the plot itself. It's a small scale rescue mission, as opposed to the big semi-military operation of The Lost World, which again reminded me of the Alien franchise (where the Weyland-Yutani company insists on capturing a xenomorph and bringing it home, which is, naturally, the worst idea ever). In fact, the movie comes to an abrupt end as soon as everyone is rescued, because that was what the movie was about. There is no attempt to set up a sequel and no unnecessary multiple endings. The drive of the story is not to go see or capture dinosaurs, but simply to rescue a stranded kid (who magically manages to survive on the island for a very long time, totally like Newt in Aliens) and that is an original idea within the confines of this franchise. Again, JP3 is doing its own thing, which I appreciate. In fact, the movie leads you to believe there is something bigger going on, when really there isn't. Mr. and Mrs. Kirby are just regular people looking for their kid and their hired mercenary is just some guy who is capable of looking tough for limited periods of time. Even Billy, when he steals the raptor eggs, is not doing so for some evil corporation, but simply because he wants more dinosaurs to study.

JP3's biggest problem is that it turns the dinosaurs into monsters where Spielberg depicted them as simply animals going about their animal business. Here we have intelligent raptors communicating with each other and setting up traps (it is mentioned that they might have been even more intelligent than primates) and even engaging in some weird Mexican stand off/hostage situation with the eggs. But even this weirdness can be explained off. JP3 is simply a movie presenting a theory. Grant goes out of his way to convince his peers that raptors had large brains and organs allowing them to communicate with sounds. I'm no paleontologist so who am I to disagree with this theory that Grant seems to have covered with fossils as evidence? And then it turns out he was right and the movie shows us what those smarter-than-we-previously-thought dinosaurs might be like. Why the hell not? In fact the set pieces in this movie were great and the dinosaur action mostly holds up very well. There are tons of practical effects and the CG (mostly) isn't shabby and the editing isn't all over the place and the camera isn't shaky. For example, the fight between the T-Rex and that other big dino that kicks its ass was great. I loved how it was staged under the jungle canopy, just two pissed off animals fighting over food (in this case our characters) and I think that scene really gave a good sense of how those prehistoric battles might have looked like. There are many thrills in this movie and unlike Hammond's park ride, in JP3 there is no danger of not seeing the money shots. And let's face it, when we go see the third Jurassic park movie, what we really want to see is the money shots, right? Was anyone expecting it to be Shakespeare? 

**TL;DR:** I enjoyed JP3 more than most people seem to have. I think it continues Grant's story nicely, I like the action and I appreciate the movie for doing its own thing instead of going for nostalgia or imitating Spielberg. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> A pressing Star Wars question that I haven't seen discussed much: Did Han ever make fun of Leia for kissing her brother? I bet that is something he would tease her about. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-25 23:09:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> If everyone in /r/EXPLAINLIKEIMFIVE sticks to the"search for answer first" rule, eventually all questions will be answered and there will be nothing new to ask. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-22 20:39:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> In which case, the subredit dies. So if you break that rule in ELI5 (and other similar asking subredits) and pose a question that was already answered a year or two ago, you participate in keeping the discussion alive. That says something about breaking the rules sometimes, or does it? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [Request] Looking for a visually pleasing movie with an interesting plot, preferably with a sci-fi twist to it. Can be old or knew, American or foreign, but not too mainstream. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-22 18:39:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm looking for something to watch and I want it to be well shot and designed and have an interesting plot. I have seen a lot of movies so please suggest less known films. Thank you in advance

EDIT: sorry for dumb typo in title </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> How/why have fauna and flora evolved as separate and vastly different life forms and was there ever a hybrid middle stage between plant and animal? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-22 14:15:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> "Rey's Theme" from the Star Wars: The Force Awakens soundtrack is proof that once again, John Williams' music is perfect </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-20 19:31:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> ELI5: Why was having two lines of soldiers standing still, facing each other and shooting rifles at each other without taking any cover whatsoever considered a good way to do battle? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-14 15:28:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> This is a home made can crusher </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-05 00:02:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The Chase sequence from Attack of the Clones (2002) is an expertly executed, tense 5 minute scene that is exciting to watch even with no context. Surely the best part of the whole prequel trilogy. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-04 23:51:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Blade Runner (1982) [OC] [1920x1200] </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-04 23:13:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> How much do the books we read define who we are? Could you guess what I'm like if I named four books that I like? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-11-27 00:13:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I was wondering how much one could infer about another person based on their favorite books. How accurate would it be and for what reasons? And of course I decided to test this on myself, so I hope you will help. The question I am posing is this:


What kind of a person would you guess that I am if you only know the titles of my favorite books: The New York Trilogy by Paul Auster, A Wild Sheep Chase by Haruki Murakami, All Quiet on the Western Front by Erich Maria Remarque, and The Sleepwalkers by Arthur Koestler? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Tom Hanks seems to have aged considerably in the last four years. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-11-22 10:32:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> This happened two years ago and I still don't know why my printer hates me (pic is potato quality) </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-11-20 19:50:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> When Morpheus says that no one can be told what the Matrix is, what does he really mean by that? Isn't he tricking people into disconnecting like a total a-hole? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-11-19 14:34:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So the quote goes like this: "Unfortunately, no one can be told what the Matrix is. You have to see it for yourself."

But why can't people simply be told? I sort of understand what Morpheus is going for here - seeing is believing. Why would you believe someone if they told you that the world is a digital simulation from a dystopian future ruled by robots? But that is beside point. He could tell you and whether you believe him or not is your problem. The thing that bugs me is that he won't tell you what the Matrix is until you disconnect from it, by which time it's kind of too late for you anyway. Morpheus is sort of an asshole, is he not?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> To help promote at least a basic understanding of the Solar System, I created this infographic with all the basic data and facts about the planets and other bodies that are our neighbors in the Cosmos. It can be printed and used for educational purposes. [OC] (large file) </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-11-17 16:09:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> This urinal in a bar I went to had a soccer goal for better aiming </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-11-16 18:29:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Gothenborg, Sweden, at sunset [4660x1080] </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-11-15 18:58:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Event Horizon [1997] </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-11-15 18:53:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Gladiator [2000] </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-10-17 18:25:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> This cord comes out of the wall from behind an electrical socket and is plugged right into the socket </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-10-17 18:23:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> TIL Johannes Kepler's father was a mercenary and his mother was accused of witchcraft and faced torture unless she confessed. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-10-14 11:07:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> I doodle scenes from famous movies when I'm bored at work. Here's the first batch. I bet you can guess all the movies. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-10-13 15:35:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> ELI5: Why is there no official action taken against Japanese whalers, instead leaving it to organizations like Sea Shepherd to deal with them? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-10-05 16:41:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> AFAIK whaling is forbidden and Japanese whalers pretend to be research ships in order to catch them. Sea Shepherd battles them and all of it is well documented, so why won't anyone do anything about it?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> After 16 years, FIGHT CLUB feels very out-dated but also very relevant [SPOILERS] </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-10-01 11:17:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yesterday, I had the opportunity to see **Fight Club** for the first time in the cinema with an audience. All my previous viewings (I think I saw it five times) were on TV/DVD and alone. It was a great experience, the audience enjoyed it very much, there was a lot of laughter and spontaneous cheering at the end. It is a movie I would definitely recommend seeing with a group of people on a big screen. It was also the first time I watched it in a couple of years (I can't even remember when exactly did I watch it the last time). And there were a couple of things I noticed about **Fight Club** that were surprising, enjoyable, but also disappointing.

In my formative high-school years I was a big fan of Chuck Palahniuk. I thought he was the coolest, smartest, most edgy writer out there and of course the movie blew me away with its cool, smart and edgy style. Nowadays it all feels very 90s to me. The voiceover narration in particular felt forced sometimes, with Edward Norton's dry voice delivering one-liners that no longer struck me as poignant commentary or intriguing observations. The lines felt like nothing but sentences that were once edgy paragraphs in a book we all grew out of. That post-modern, post-whatever nihilistic grit that the movie is drenched in felt like watching an old music video on MTV that no longer impresses with its stylized loathing of everything that is clean and popular. If I were to compare this movie to Fincher's later work, especially the cynical and satyrical **Gone Girl**, then **Fight Club** feels like the awkward rebellious teenager and **Gone Girl** is the adult that prefers not to think of its embarrassing former self.

**Spoiler** territory here, in case you haven't noticed the title. There is something about that famous twist that feels out-dated as well. I don't think I can properly put into words exactly what I mean about that, though. I think maybe audiences nowadays would see straight through it and realize much sooner that Edward Norton's narrator and Tyler Durden are the same person. Watching **Fight Club** with hindsight, the clues are so obvious and numerous that I can't decide what was Fincher going for with all that foreshadowing. Did he think his audience was too stupid and wouldn't notice them? Or did he think his audience was too clever and needed the clues to accept the absurdity of the twist? Which is the correct question to ask: "How could Norton be Durden?" or "How could Norton *not* be Durden?"

But don't think I dislike the movie. On the contrary. Somehow, despite my criticisms and negative observations, I think I never liked it more than I do now. I can't really explain it. Despite its out-dated style, which at best induces 90s nostalgia and at worst is cringe-worthy, **Fight Club** still feels very relevant. Its themes are still applicable, even more so than in 1999, and I long to know what Tyler Durden would do about our smartphone driven obsession with selfies, retweets and facebook likes. What of all the ridiculous fashions and trends, like hipsters, insta-filters, and everything being retro as if desperately trying to escape our modern times while at the same time fueling them with more and more ridiculous and abstract consumerism. I am Jack's evolved sense of style, but I'm also Jack's subconscious yearning for revolution.
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> I was at the National Gallery in Slovakia and noticed they use Star Wars wallpaper on one of the walls in a 19th century art exhibit </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-09-27 09:19:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Star Wars: Episode III - Revenge of the Sith [2005] </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-09-27 09:12:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Mad Max: Fury Road [2015] </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-09-24 18:21:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Star Wars: Episode II - Attack of the Clones [2002] </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-09-21 20:17:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> My former colleague just posted this stunning sunset in Bratislava </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-09-20 22:35:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Onsi Shalom - Night Tulip </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-09-13 22:00:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Onsi Shalom - Bahooni Came to Grifton [rock] </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-09-13 21:54:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Earth-Moon infographic I made inspired by the new picture from DISCOVR </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-08-09 22:01:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> I rewatched Indiana Jones and the Kingdom of the Crystal Skull and maybe you should too [SPOILERS, obviously] </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-19 20:47:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I don't think anyone truly loves Crystal Skull but I do think many people truly hate it. Back in '08 it was a big disappointment for me and I haven't watched it since. Until last night. And I was surprised to see that it's not actually half as bad as I remembered it to be. (But still not good, though.)

Unfortunately, the movies starts badly. Even the very first shot is anti-climactic and dumb. When you go see an Indiana Jones movie you expect the Paramount logo to seamlessly transform into the first shot of the film and Crystal Skull opts to do this in a totally irrelevant and childish fashion with a CG chipmunk. Then a brief, totally irrelevant car chase follows and abruptly ends when the plot of the movie finally kicks in. Indiana Jones is then betrayed by his long-time friend and war-time colleague Mac and this betrayal unfortunately feels irrelevant as well, because we have no emotional attachment to their relationship. We actually find out that they worked together for years *after* he betrays Indy. So automatically I just don't care. The following action sequence in the warehouse is pretty good, though, right up until that controversial moment when Indy survives the nuke in the fridge. Is it dumb and unbelievable? Yes, of course it is. Does it bother me? No, not really. First of all, Indy has survived some impossible shit before and it's not like these movies have any sort of realism attached to them. Second, more dumber things happen later in the movie, so by comparison the fridge is actually a neat gag. Those forced chipmunk jokes... that's another matter.

I like the setting of the movie and the fact that Indy is a war hero and former spy. It is exactly the sort of career I would expect him to have between WWII and 1954. After all, he hates Nazis. I also really like that he continued teaching, a role he probably secretly enjoys more than his macho adventurer nature allows him to admit. The McCarthy commie witch hunt commentary in the movie is a bit forced but forgivable and it helps to show just how much Indy lives to be a professor. I even really enjoyed the chase scene between Indy and Mutt on the chopper and the two commie agents in the car. Which brings me to another unpopular part of the movie. Mutt.

Think what you will of Shia LaBeouf. I personally don't care what actors do IRL when I watch a movie. That is why I'm able to enjoy Tom Cruise in pretty much anything despite the fact that he's a crazy Scientologist. And also why I still love Mel Gibson's movies. So putting his recent behavior aside, LaBeouf is actually pretty good in the movie, playing a good-guy greaser who's anxious to save his family and recruits Indy on his mission, for which he himself is quite ill equipped. They make a pretty good duo and the movie excellently treads that fine line between letting Mutt do some action stuff for which Indy is a bit old and at the same time not stealing Indy's spotlight or making him obsolete. I also really enjoyed their relationship before Indy finds out he is Mutt's father. Indy is just and older, experienced, world-weary but ultimately chilled out guy stuck with an eager kid and he just casually gives him some wisdom and talks to him the same way a cool estranged uncle might. It's a buddy movie and it kinda works. But after Indy finds out that he is Mutt's father, there are some dumb jokes ("finish school, young man") and they loose that casual buddy rapport, which is a shame.

Most of the really problematic parts are in the final act of the movie. The chase through the jungle is a good action sequence despite some dodgy effects and the ant scene is not nearly as bad as I remembered it, but I can see why some people dislike it. However, the way they survive a drop down three big waterfalls is completely ridiculous and of course there is Shia swinging on vines with a bunch of monkeys. I don't know how that shot made into the movie but it's really, really dumb. I think Crystal Skull would be dramatically less hated if they left out those ten seconds of footage. If I remember correctly, many people also dislike the alien angle. I'm completely ok with it and here's why: Indiana Jones is a universe where God is confirmed to exist and where ancient sorcery is still practiced. So why not aliens, too? I might not necessarily believe that aliens helped ancient South American civilizations, but it is an intriguing subject for fictionalized archaeology of the Indy variety and the finale in the temple is a good one.

So what is the verdict? I no longer have to pretend there are only three Indiana Jones movies. The fourth one is flawed but it's still very much possible to enjoy it. I think if they cut two or three minutes of stuff from the movie, it would turn out great. Which is something you can't say about Temple of Doom, my new least favorite Indy. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> I moved and organizing my books was naturally the first thing I did in the new rooom </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-27 16:25:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Gladiator [2000] </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-27 13:17:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Team - Drzim ti miesto (I'm saving you a seat) - one of the best rock songs to emerge from SLovakia </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-10 21:27:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Bad Karma Boy - Dunaj (a song about life and the Danube river from a cool Slovak band) </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-14 21:57:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> These statues from a Bulgarian monument built during communism look like something made by Dwarves from Lord of the Rings </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-03 17:31:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> ELI5: Non vlci - o o vlastne ide? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-03 17:26:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Prosm mte vysvetli o o ide s tmi Nonmi vlkmi a preo je okolo toho tak hal? Nieo mi uniklo? vaka </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> So boxing is popular, I guess? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-03 16:23:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Avengers wallpaper I made a while back - I think it's pretty relevant right about now [OC] (1920x1200) </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-26 12:03:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Exterminate All Rational Thought, digital, 800x800 </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-22 15:18:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Cynick obluda: o mm ja spolon so irokm? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-22 10:18:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Question about Professor X (and other telepaths): If he reads the mind of a foreigner who doesn't speak English, does he still understand the thoughts? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-14 21:19:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So I was wondering if Charles Xavier were to read a foreigner's mind if he would actually understand what they are thinking (and if so, then why). Not sure if this is the right place to ask but it seemed appropriate. Thanks! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Ako to bolo s Vhostavom? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-13 20:13:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> A good reason to be excited to see Avengers: Age of Ultron </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-12 00:03:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Eight hours of awesome chillout, electronic, and ambient music </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-11 23:28:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [Request] Movies about resistance movements during WWII </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-11 14:39:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I saw a couple of movies like [Max Manus](http://www.imdb.com/title/tt1029235/), [Soldier of Orange](http://www.imdb.com/title/tt0076734/), [Flame and Citron](http://www.imdb.com/title/tt0920458/) and [Black Book](http://www.imdb.com/title/tt0389557/) and I really liked all of them. I'm looking for more movies about resistance movements against the Nazis. Anything European, old or new, would be great. 

Thanks  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> ELI5: Why aren't all space exploration efforts systematically focused on one planet at a time, so that we learn everything about it and then move on to the next one? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-04 18:05:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Wouldn't it make more sense to thoroughly explore one object at a time instead of scattering probes and resources all over space and getting partial results from each? Why don't we just invest in missions to one celestial body until we learn as much as possible about it and then move on to the next one? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Does the Xenomorph from the Alien franchise breathe? Does it have a sense of smell? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-30 15:45:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I watched Aliens last night and I noticed something that never bothered me before. Newt's hiding place, where they first find her and Ripley crawls in to get here, is in a huge vent with constant airflow. So her scent must be all over the place and the Xenos could find her very easily. They might not be able to fit inside to get her, but they could circle the place so she would be trapped in the vent. I reckon either this is a mistake and should be taken with a grain of salt, or the Xenos have no sense of smell. Can you think of any scenes where they use smell or, on the other hand, where it is obvious that they have none? And do they even breathe (seeing as they can survive vacuum)? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Challenge this: Terminator 2 is James Cameron's best movie </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-27 23:34:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Do you agree or do you prefer Aliens, the first Terminator, or perhaps even The Abyss? If so, then in what way do you feel is your choice of movie better than T2? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Main square and marina in Piran, Slovenia [OC] [1553x1553] </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-24 09:23:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Going to Berlin for extended weekend May 8th-11th. Anything in particular I should see at that time? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-23 23:08:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I was wondering if you know of any interesting events during those dates? I assume there will be some sort of celebration or remembrance of the end of WWII on May 8? I wonder if there will be perhaps some traffic restrictions because of this, or perhaps some massive crowd gatherings or stuff like that.

It will be my first time in Berlin (in Germany, in fact) and I would like to make the most of it. I'm going with two other friends and all three of us like different things, so it would be really cool if you could also recommend some nice places or sights with universal appeal (so perhaps not museums and galleries). Thank you very much! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> ELI5: Why do people always want what they can't have, even if they know they can't have it and the desire only makes them feel miserable? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-20 09:07:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Is there a psychological or evolutionary predisposition to desire things we can't have, even if on a logical and intellectual level we know we can't ever have them? Why is it so? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [Request] Looking for a movie that has a subtle (possibly supernatural) mystery at the core of a normal, dramatic plot </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-16 19:21:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I recently watched the wonderful Peter Weir film **Picnic at Hanging Rock**, which is a period drama about a couple of girls who went missing - you've guessed it - during a picnic at Hanging Rock. 

At first glance, it's a normal costume piece that takes place in 1900 about bunch of school girls, but it actually has a slightly surreal plot with a big unexplained mystery with a supernatural twist to it. I really liked the combination and I'm looking for something similar. Thank you. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Ridley Scott's two best and most famous movies - Would you pick Alien and Blade Runner or not? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-11 21:57:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I admire several movies directed by Ridley Scott but still, my two most favorite movies of his, by far, are Alien and Blade Runner. I think they are the totally obvious choice. Having watched both movies many times and in various versions, I believe I'm pretty well versed in their many qualities and the few places where they lack. But I wonder, if other people had to pick two, would they omit one of them? Which one? Or would someone omit both in favor of other movies? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Blade Runner (1982) [OC] (1748x2480) </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-11 20:35:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Star Trek: First Contact (1996) [OC] [2480x3508] </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-07 02:28:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Super chilled out playlist of electronica, ambient and indie beats (currently over 80 songs, constantly updated) [Spotify] </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-04 22:17:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [Suggest] The Sicilian Clan (1969) - dramatic and thrilling French heist movie with a great cast (Jean Gabin, Lino Ventura   Alain Delon), great soundtrack (Ennio Morricone) and plenty of suspense to rival American movies of this sort </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-01 22:19:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The best photo I ever took in a museum. Vienna Natural History Museum, to be precise. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-01 00:52:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> I'm looking for a non-fiction book about sex in various cultures and time periods. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-28 12:20:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm interested in how sex was perceived in various cultures and in different eras, how people understood orgasms, what were some customs, positions or rituals associated with sex, etc. Basically I'm looking for a cultural anthropological history of sex. I'm also interested in neuroscience, so books about sex from this point of view are welcome as well. Any suggestions for books or even articles would be greatly appreciated. Thanks! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> TRUE LIES was on TV last night. Is there any love for this movie here? It has great action comedy moments, amazing stunts, and effects that really hold up. Also, Arnie's best acting? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-18 15:33:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I remember reading somewhere that James Cameron showed the movie to Kubrick and he was blown away by the effects. The movie really holds up in the technical department but the story itself is still pretty cool as well. It's a great action comedy that partially makes fun of its own ridiculousness and it's highly entertaining from start to finish. I'm not sure how popular this movie actually is, but I feel like it should be way more popular. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Chill playlist of relaxing electronica, ambient and downtempo music (constantly updated) [Spotify] </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-14 15:10:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Zero Dark Thirty [2012] </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-09 10:46:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> I made a concert poster for my friend's band. I would love to know what you think [Poster] </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-06 14:18:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [concert poster](http://i.imgur.com/G19YuFx.jpg)

I made this poster for my friend's rock band and I was wondering if you could give me some feedback. I made a couple for him before, they were sort of spacey and psychedelic. His only brief was to make him say "whoa that's cool" 

First time posting here, so looking forward to some responses. Thanks a bunch! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> If Kathryn Bigelow made a third movie about the Middle East, which topic would you like it to be about? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-01 01:55:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The Hurt Locker was concerned with IEDs, a tripplet of letters that became instantly recognizable during this post 9/11 conflict. Then Zero Dark Thirty of course was about the hunt for and assassination of Bin Laden. Now if she were to complete an unofficial trilogy with another movie in such a setting, which aspect of the war, which battle, which piece of news would be an interesting choice and which would you like to see filmed? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> ELI5: Of all species, human offspring have the longest period of childhood and dependability on their parents (or elders). How can this apparent vulnerability be a product of evolution? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-29 14:09:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> For many hears, human children are completely defenseless and dependable. This seems in contrast with evolution's tendency to favor the fittest and most likely to survive. How and why have we evolved like this? Also, is this long period of childhood and vulnerability a product of our social nature or is social nature a product of humans needing to take care of their children for a long time?

thanks </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Thought you guys might like these posters with lyrics from Time [OC] </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-28 18:48:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Zero Dark Thirty [2012] </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-26 21:13:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Butterflies (Carl Sagan Quote), Photoshop, 1920x1200 </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-25 18:46:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Thief [1981] </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-24 19:16:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> My boss was not pleased by my genius creation </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-22 14:18:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Is there any new scientific research on the causes or origins of deja vu? Why do some people hardly ever experience it while others experience it often, and is either a symptom of something? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-22 09:46:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> My top 15 sci-fi movies of the last ten years (2004-2014) </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-20 12:32:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This is my list of the 15 best sci-fi movies of the last ten years. It was going to be just a top 10, but there were so many good movies to choose from. I left out all comic book movies because I see them as a genre of their own. Each movie on the list is accompanied by a short explanation of why I chose it.

* **15. Another Earth (2011)** - I admire low budget sci-fi that adds more plot and real emotion instead of big effects and pomp. This movie has an interesting (albeit not wholly original) sci-fi concept and it explores its effect on two people.

* **14. Cloverfield (2008)** - As a thrilling ride evoking 9/11 horrors in combination with a classic monster attack on a big city, this movie makes great use of the found footage first person format. 

* **13. Mr. Nobody (2009)** - Jared Leto is great in this complicated and emotional sci-fi drama that tackles the classic "what if" concept in an interesting way.

* **12. Serenity (2005)** - Not only a gratification for fans of the TV show Firefly, but also a very well written space opera adventure that services all of its characters and brings some good action and twists.

* **11. TRON: Legacy (2010)** - This movie's script and acting are far from ideal, but it does a perfect job of taking the viewer to a whole new and wonderfully designed world, which coupled with a great soundtrack creates an audio-visual experience to be remembered. It was also influential with its costume design and overall look.

* **10. Star Trek (2009)** - Think what you will of the altered timeline, lens flares, or its awful sequel, but Star Trek is a fun time at the movies with great special effects and a perfect cast that breathes new life into a classic ensemble. 

* **9. Primer (2004)** - This low-budget creative *tour de force* from Shane Carruth, who stars, writes, produces, directs, edits, and composes the music, is a complicated time travel tale that is still discussed after ten years and baffles and intrigues its viewers.

* **8. District 9 (2009)** - Jump-starting the careers of its director and star, this movie provides an interesting take on the alien invasion story by making it a failure where the aliens are stranded and persecuted on Earth. Great action, effects and designs galore. 

* **7. Edge of Tomorrow (2014)** - A straight up sci-fi action movie acts as a combination of D Day with Starship Troopers and gives us a fresh take on the Groundhog Day concept of repeating the same day over and over. Also interesting for Tom Cruise playing a coward (initially) and Emily Blunt as a supreme badass female heroine. 

* **6. The Man from Earth (2007)** - Another low key, low-budget story that resembles a theater play and is without any visual effects or action, yet gives us a fascinating story of a man who doesn't age and who has been alive for 12 thousand years. 

* **5. Moon (2009)** - Combining ideas and visuals from Solaris, Blade Runner, 2001 and Alien, this movie still manages to be wholly original and unlike any movie that came out in 2009 or even in all of 21st century so far. A great one man show from Sam Rockwell and the story has mystery and a twist.

* **4. Inception (2010)** - Nolan brings a fascinating and literally mind-blowing sci-fi twist to the heist genre with his original movie. Filled with stellar actors, it is both a fan favorite and admired by critics. Its great visuals were awarded with Oscars for effects and cinematography.

* **3. Snowpiercer (2013)** - Joon-ho Bong's English-language debut is a traditional sci-fi story in that it uses its futuristic story and setting to comment on current society and its problems. Wonderfully stylized action and a great turn from Chris Evans make it a thrilling experience.

* **2. War of the Worlds (2005)** - Despite criticism for its abrupt and anti-climactic ending, as well as a sudden change of pace halfway through the story, this movie is a showcase of Spielberg's great sci-fi action sensibilities. Once again evoking 9/11 (and its resulting paranoia) it remains one of the most thrilling movies in this director's rich career and good modern adaptation of the most classic of sci-fi tales.

* **1. Looper (2012)** - Beautifully shot, perfectly acted and completely original, this sci-fi thriller shows Rian Johnson's immense talent and seals him as one of the best young filmmakers and a real hope for the future of genre movies. A misleading marketing campaign mostly sold the movie as a time-travel showdown between Bruce Willis and his younger self, but in reality it has a deeper story with some Terminator-esque vibes and also provides an interesting take on the super hero mythos through the character Sara and her powerful telekinetic son, who she hopes will become good with proper upbringing and not an evil overlord. Makes you think what would've happened if Superman wasn't brought up by the Kents.


(edited some formatting and typos) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> I spent Saturday re-arranging my books (and some dvds and memorabilia) and I thought I'd share the result [OC] [2212x3113] (xpost from r/bookporn) </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-18 17:28:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Looper [2012] (Spoiler) </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-18 17:11:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> I spent Saturday re-arranging my books (and some dvds and memorabilia) and I thought I'd share the result [OC] [2212x3113] </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-18 13:49:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> People keep criticizing J.J. Abrams for his use of lens flares but I watched LOOPER again and noticed Rian Johnson uses a lot of lens flares as well. Both are doing STAR WARS now. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-18 10:12:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> First of all, Looper - what a great movie. Simply unbelievable. But I was really surprised how many lens flares there are. Sometimes they are small but some times they get ridiculous. Why is Abrams the only one who is getting crap for their use? Is is it just because more people saw his movies than Looper?

I also find it interesting that both Abrams and Johnson are doing Star Wars now. I remember when Abrams was announced for Episode VII that people we worried he'll use those lens flares from Star Trek again. There were fan trailers and parodies for this all over the internet and people pre-judged his movie's aesthetic because flares were never a part of the previous Episodes. But not a single word about Johnson's use of lens flares at all.

EDIT: here are two examples http://imgur.com/a/ldbw8 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Michael Mann's new movie BLACKHAT is better than the sum of its parts </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-16 20:28:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Blackhat is not getting the best reviews and it's probably going to flop, but I just saw it and I believe it's not nearly that bad. I went in knowing it had bad reviews and during the start of the film I could see why. The beginning is not very good but once it gets going it only gets better, I think. There are some surprises and by the end I found myself liking the movie and genuinely rooting for the main character. Speaking of whom, people say Hemsworth is too much of a hunk to realistically play a hacker, and while that might be true, at least his character is not the stereotypical action hero. He's much closer to a normal guy. He actually doesn't do that much during action scenes and even prepares a big first aid kit before he confronts some bad guys, knowing he'll probably get hurt. That's the sort of thing you never see in a movie. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> John Wick [2014] </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-15 21:15:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> One of my bookshelves with a wooden statue my dad did when he was six. [OC] [3574x1949] </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-14 21:01:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> I tried to watch THE RAID but had to turn it off after 20 minutes. I'm sorry, but why all the hype for this movie? Will it get better later on? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-13 16:02:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I know people on reddit love The Raid, but before you drop the hate on me, please note that I'm sincerely trying to figure out what went wrong - I had hopes that I would love this movie too, but I just don't see it.

First of all, it looks cheap. Like crowd-funded-B-movie level of cheap. It had zero cinematic feeling to it, instead I got a home-made vibe from it, as if a group of friends put on some black sporting equipment and filmed themselves running around like SWAT. The completely obvious CG blood also took me out of the movie every single time. I'm not saying it's a bad thing to make a cheap movie and not everyone has massive budgets and Hollywood effects at their disposal. But I just couldn't take The Raid seriously.

The acting is as corny as it gets, though I'm perfectly willing to attribute this opinion to my own ignorance of Asian cinema in general and their acting sensibilities in particular. What did you guys think of the acting? Again, I only got that amateurish home-made vibe from it.

The script is, well... was there even a script? The opening is laughably expository to the point where a simple title card telling me the basic facts would probably be better than the scene in the van as they are riding to the building. And I found the rest largely unbelievable. Like when they are about to enter the gate but there's a guy who wants to deliver medicine to his wife and the whole team of armed men on an important and dangerous mission just stands around exposed while they argue with some civilian. Really? 

The action was ok, but I think I liked John Wick's action much more. As I said, I haven't even seen most of the movie because I was so disappointed that I turned it off. Will it get better? Is there going to be any actual story beyond the video-game scenario? Are there going to be any actual characters beyond the cliche evil cop boss and the cliche evil mafia boss?

Thank you for your helpful responses. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> I heard New Girl got really bad and then reinveted itself and became better - so is it worth getting into? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-06 22:31:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I watched a couple of episodes during the first season but then I stopped for some reason and I forgot all about the show. Later I heard that it got really bad and so I was happy that I didn't waste my time with it. Then I watched a few episodes on a very long and boring flight and they were from the third season and seemed ok. After that I read somewhere that the show changed and became great after going very much downhill. So could you please elaborate on what the show's problems were, how it changed, and whether I should pick it up again? Thanks!

EDIT: Just thought I'd let you know that thanks to your responses I picked up the show again and I'm enjoying it a lot. I sort of got into a binge-watching spiral yesterday, finished season 1 and got halfway through season 2. I'm really enjoying and but I noticed the sexual/emotional tension between Nick and Jess is ENORMOUS. I'm surprised it took the writers three seasons to put those characters together. Shame they didn't handle it well. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> I visited the Hobbiton movie set in December and I thought you might like some pictures. The attention to detail is stunning. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-05 19:18:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> North by Northwest (1959) </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-03 16:59:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The Wolf of Wall Street [2013] </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-03 10:35:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Great discussion of why Andy Warhol's Soup Cans are considered art and what is the meaning and value of modern art in general [7:08] </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-12-31 19:16:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> I made this timeline of events for the time travel movie Predestination (2014) </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-11-26 22:25:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Going to New Zealand next week. I'll be staying in Auckland for two and a half days before moving on further south. What should I see in the city? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-11-22 19:49:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I would be grateful for any recommendations whether it's museums, cool buildings, good food, places with a great view, etc. Thank you! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Surprisngly negative thoughts on Guardians of the Galaxy (2014) after watching it again this weekend </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-11-18 20:02:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I really enjoyed GotG in the cinema this summer and I was really looking forward to seeing it again. So I was very surprised when I watched it this weekend and noticed that it's not really that good. At all. 

I think a lot of this has to do with being blow away by the new world and characters initially when I first saw it. I have never read a comic book in my life and although I've been catching up on some Marvel stuff at least on wikipedia whenever a new movie comes out, I knew next to nothing about the Guardians. So seeing it for the first time at the cinema, suddenly I was in this awesome, colorful, fun world with weird and amusing characters and a pumping soundtrack and lots of jokes. But this novelty has since worn off and I started seeing the movie's major faults.

Villains are not the MCU's strongest suit and in this movie in particular the bad guy is there simply to be bad. Ronan was visually great but his motivations were underdeveloped. He wanted vengeance for something that happened god knows when off screen and he despised some sort of peace treaty that we only ever learned about from a character watching TV. In fact, practically every character's motivations for their actions were based on something that happened in the past and off screen. People hate Gamora because she's done bad things, but we never saw that. She betrays Ronan because she hates him for doing other bad things we didn't see. Drax wants to avenge a family we never met who died who knows when. Rocket apparently has some sort of painful Wolverine-being-experimented-on-esque past that is barely mentioned. And the movie goes out if its way to awkwardly set up Peter's alien father but it leads absolutely nowhere and I guess we'll have to wait for the sequel to find out anything relevant about it. 

The plot of the movie is also pretty thin. It's a very straightforward story about chasing the MacGuffin and I guess everybody in the movie has to make at least three deals with other people and get betrayed at least twice for the story to move forward. And all that to save (or destory, if you're looking at it from Ronan's perspective destroy) a city that's very pretty to look at but as an audience member I have absolutely no reason to care about Xandar at all. It's not even any of these characters' home (or is it? because the movie is vague on that part as well). I feel like GotG was a great way to launch a new franchise, because it's a simple and fun movie, but for the sequel they are going to have to come up with a much better story and give these characters more depth, otherwise it will just be a dumb movie with a talking racoon.

ETA: sorry for the typo in the title </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> If I can have my cake and eat it too, then the cake both exists and doesn't exist at the same time. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-11-17 02:05:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The cake is like Schroedinger's cat! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> If Daft Punk released an album of sampled and reworked Pink Floyd songs, would it be a success? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-11-17 02:00:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> First of all, I wonder if something like this happened, whether people would say they were brave for trying an album like that, or only that it was a stunt, an attempt to call attention to both themselves and Pink Floyd, who asked them to do it in the first place.

Second, I wonder if Daft Punk could pull off something like this and perhaps revolutionize how rock fans view electronic music.
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> I recently rewatched Iron Man (2008) and The Incredible Hulk (2008) and realized that in terms of quality, Phase Two is miles ahead of Phase One </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-11-06 13:44:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Between these two movies, the terrible thrid act of Captain America: The First Avenger, the mess that is Iron Man 2 and the forgettable Thor, I really marvel (heh) at the steep rise of quality in Avengers and afterwards Phase Two. What caused this improvement and do you think it will go on into an even better Phase Three? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Every time you look at a sunset, someone on the other side of the planet is looking at a sunrise </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-10-31 16:48:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> In retrospect, this is fairly obvious, but when I first realized it I was quite fascinated by this. It's a pretty comforting thought, to know that even as your day is coming to an end, someone else is just getting up and life continues on and on. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Could Jennifer Lawrence win an Oscar for The Hunger Games? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-10-29 22:06:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I can't even begin to imagine what that would do for the franchise and for her career. Her second Oscar for a tremendously popular genre sequel with still one movie to go? She would own the world. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> In light of Marvel's string of news and the success of the Avengers trailer, how happy must James Spader be right now? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-10-29 20:48:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> James Spader, man. He must be so excited. This movie is gonna rock, and its gonna rock thanks to him. He is about to explode as Ultron. I wonder what that must feel like, when you are a respected actor, but nowhere near stardom, and you know that overnight everyone would talk about you, learn about you and watch your previous work. Do you think he's looking forward to it? Or do you think he somehow regrets that his biggest break is a CG character in a comic book film? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The news that Patrick Stewart will play a white supremacist got me wondering: Has he ever played a villain? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-10-22 13:24:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> He seems like such a nice person and I cannot remember ever seeing him play an antagonist. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Could you please recommend some recent Scandinavian movies? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-10-15 10:24:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I recently enjoyed a number of movies from the Scandinavian region and I'm looking for more. I saw Kon-Tiki, Headhunters, Adam's Apples, Max Manus, Borgman, The Hunt. Any ideas for more? No Ingmar Bergman please, I saw those. Thanks </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Three Avengers widescreen wallpapers </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-10-05 18:32:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Suarez biting simulator </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-06-28 17:22:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Native American Space Chief </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-02-02 20:48:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> video of "The Philip Glass Ensemble - Pruit Igoe   Prophecies" with space shuttles, planets, stars and the Moon landing </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-02-02 19:45:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> 11 widescreen wallpapers from Battlestar Galactica that I made (S4 spoilers) </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-02-02 11:23:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
