<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject5443</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-07-20 01:18:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm sorry, but discussing methods of suicide is strictly forbidden on SW. We are more than happy to discuss why you are suicidal, but we can't give you advice on doing it. If you want to make another post telling us why you feel this way, we'd be happy to listen.
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-07-19 21:05:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm sorry, but discussing methods of suicide is strictly forbidden on SW.  We are more than happy to discuss why you are suicidal, but we can't give you advice on doing it.  If you want to make another post telling us why you feel this  way, we'd be happy to listen. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-07-17 00:09:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Listen, I'm sorry you are in so much pain.  And if you like to talk about that pain and find some understanding here, we can provide that.  But it is against the rules for people to discuss suicide methods here, I cannot allow your post.  Please understand, we want to help you, not to die but to live. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-07-15 20:03:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> How can you expect to be happy when you nurture hate within yourself?  Loving and being loved by others creates happiness and meaning in life, it's something you can practice.  It's up to you which road you walk down, choose carefully. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-07-12 01:27:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> call 911 and get yourself admitted to hospital.  They won't be able to get you there.  After that, you might need to leave town, but that's a lot better than dying.  You can start a new life, be a new person.  You're life's not over, take what chances you can. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-07-10 15:39:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> you could ask in /r/Assistance for help coming up with the money for meds.  What has been going on in your life? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-07-10 14:49:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm sorry we don't allow people to give out contact information on Sw, mostly for their own safety.  If you want make a post explaining what's wrong people will respond. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-07-08 16:09:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hey, maybe you could talk to your sisters and tell them how you feel?  In the meantime talk to us.  What's going on in your life right now?  What has led you to this point? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-07-03 03:19:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You are projects fearful, negative thoughts you have about yourself onto other people.  Realize they are not thinking what you fear, you're thinking it and you are in control of what you think.  You can change that by recognizing your internal fear is the source of the problem and it has nothing to do with anyone else, it's an irrational fear that you can let go off. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-07-03 02:13:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You can talk to me if you want, what do you think is at the root of your unhappiness? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-06-22 15:58:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Paul Rudd </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-06-21 14:05:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's against the rules to discuss methods of suicide here.  But if you want to talk about why you are suicidal, we're happy to listen. /r/SuicideWatch is just for that.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-06-21 02:07:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Paris, Texas. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-06-17 19:43:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I think it's understandable to hate yourself as a teenager, I did for a long time as well.  It is a way of rejecting a painful world.  Adolescence is difficult for almost everyone, everyone has insecurities about how they look and what others think of them.  Suicide can seem like a solution but it isn't.  growing to love appreciate yourself is the solution.  It sounds simple, but it isn't easy.  When I was a teenager I hated the my weight and the size of my nose.  I thought if they were different, I could get girls and be more popular and cool.  But I guarantee the guys and girls you see as the most popular have two or three things they hate about themselves and wish they could change.  Learning to accept yourself as you are is part of the journey of being human.  Try to view yourself with the same compassion and understanding you would give a close friend.  No-one is perfect, we don't demand it from others so we shouldn't from ourselves.  Try and appreciate your good points.  If feeling suicidal persists maybe see a counselor or a therapist.  In the meantime [here'](https://moodgym.anu.edu.au/welcome)s a website that introduces cognitive behaviour therapy, which helps you be aware of how you think about yourself. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-06-16 21:42:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [Fowler likes to party](http://img.thesun.co.uk/multimedia/archive/00174/SNS1362B_174328a.jpg) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-06-16 18:23:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Suicide ideation is a fantasy of escaping the pain and difficulties of life you are facing.  Feel welcome to post over in /r/SuicideWatch I'm a mod there, we can talk it out. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-06-15 23:41:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> but you never actually raped anyone? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-06-12 23:12:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm glad you couldn't do it, I couldn't either.  This can be the beginning of the rest of your life.  You can decide to fight your depression and do everything you can to put what's wrong with your life right, to grow and learn into a happier, more fulfilled human being. Get help, be willing to learn.  Adopt a trial and error approach to life, habits or action that prove destructive in the long term cut them out.  Things that have a positive effect for you do more of.  You are at the bottom now, but at the bottom you have something to build on, a new life. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-06-12 20:10:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm sorry for what has happened you, but we cannot condone revenge bullying.  As Ghandi said 'an eye for an eye leaves the whole world blind.'  If you want some emotional support or just to vent you are welcome, but any posting of someone elses information will lead to immediate removal. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-06-10 16:08:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Only A Game? by Eamon Dunphy is a dairy from a season in the old second division with Millwall, fascinating read. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-06-10 13:52:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Please consider making a post in /r/SuicideWatch but please don't discuss any methods, it's against the rules.  But there are good people there that will talk to you. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-06-08 21:35:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Why don't you take a chance and talk to us about your life, what harm can it possibly do? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-06-08 21:16:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> We can't fulfil your request, it's against what we're here for.  But if you want to talk about why you are feeling suicidal, we're here to listen, it's up to you. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-06-08 20:04:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Can you tell us why you feel such an urge to die? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-06-07 16:37:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> 
yeah, what happened Stephen Ireland? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-05-31 12:47:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> his new partner is one week from retirement. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-05-29 02:05:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> that wellspring of life lives deep within you.  You had to go to the edge to discover it, but it's always there deep within.  The one thing you need is to hold onto the hope that your life will get better and never let it go.  Hope will carry you through the darkest of places and eventually to the light. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-05-29 01:38:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> looking up the quote just now i found the next line - And that makes me happy. For it says that no matter how hard the world pushes against me, within me, theres something stronger  something better, pushing right back. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-05-29 01:36:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I've been there.  I too found that wellspring of life, that demand that I must live.  Later I read this quote which summed it up for me - In the depth of winter I finally learned that there was in me an invincible summer.

Albert Camus </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-05-28 18:42:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Props for quoting Chaucer in a football thread.  I wonder what Ovid would have made of the Bosman ruling? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-05-28 18:40:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Visions of David Brent </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-05-17 19:46:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Robbie Fowler </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-05-13 17:10:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm sorry, we don't allow discussions of suicide methods nere.  If you want to make a post telling us the reasons why you want to commit suicide, you're more than welcome.  But this post will have to be removed. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-05-13 14:32:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The Silence of the Lambs.  It's a very good book, but it's a great movie. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-05-13 14:09:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If it happened once it can happen again.  You've got to have hope.  But while you are waiting on the right girl to come along you can be working on improving your circumstances and yourself sense of self.  If you could do one thing each day to make you feel like you're making progress in life, that would give you a sense of purpose.  Is there anything you can think of to fulfil that role for you? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-05-13 13:45:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> what do you think might help? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-05-13 12:56:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Could you perhaps check yourself into a psych ward by telling them you are an immediate suicide risk?  There you could get some shelter and some counselling and perhaps medication.  It would give you a break.  Please try and take care of yourself and love yourself, it's okay to be different, everyone is in some way it's just more obvious for some. You have it very tough, but I believe there is always some hope.  Please keep trying, you are a precious person and we don't want to lose you. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-05-12 21:00:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This is a question iI thought long and hard about.  The breakthrough for me was when I read the advice 'try to view yourself with compassion.'  It's easy to always be self critical and see your faults, but if you can learn to see yourself with the same compassion and understanding you would give to a dear friend you can begin to love yourself.  Nobody else is perfect, so why should you expect you to be? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-05-11 10:23:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Why do you think you deserve to feel this way? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-05-10 15:15:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> if needs be you can check yourself in A E and tell them you are an immediate suicide risk, they should take care off you for a while.  It may take the pressure off. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-05-10 03:45:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> okay, I understand.  But could you ask your therapist to move your next one forward as it's an emergency? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-05-10 03:42:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> well, i think you are in crises now and need to be seeing someone at least once a week if possible.  Can you arrange that? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-05-10 03:12:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> can you get some counselling? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-05-10 02:52:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's never too late to change your mind.  I know you are overwhelmed with grief at the loss of your boyfriend, but you will recover in time, please don't give up. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-05-09 00:06:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That is true, but Vincent is calling for the free market system to be destroyed, I'm wondering what would be a realistic alternative? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-05-08 20:30:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What is the alternative to the free market ethos? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-04-28 11:08:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's pretty disappointing for a pixar film, it's just pretty good, kind of average.  They are usually so great.  Also Billy Connolly's voice is so recognizable as the father you can't stop picturing him. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-04-22 15:31:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You have recovered from depression before, you can do so again.  Don't let a temporary feeling kill you, you are worth much more than that.  Have you seen any therapist about your illness?  It can be treated.  Imagine in the future there is a time you will thank the stars you didn't give in now and die, you can get to that point, but you must hold on through the darkness and believe it's going to get better. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-04-22 00:57:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> just say the first thing that comes to mind. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-04-22 00:34:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Do you want to talk to us about it? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-04-20 18:11:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Latro Of the Mist by Gene Wolfe for something different.  It's about an amnesiac soldier in ancient Greece who can see and converse with the Greek gods. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-04-20 16:55:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I suggest you write a letter to your sister, perhaps that way you can get through to her and begin to repair your relationship.  When this happened you were and had endured a massive trauma in losing your father, you were to young to know how deal with it and perhaps you took your grief and anger out on your sister.  You've got a second chance, your sister is still alive.  I think you and your sister should seek counselling to deal with your grief and confusion.  Writing that letter is a good place to start rebuilding your lives.  I'm sorry all this happened you, it's very hard,but it's not too late to make things right. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-04-20 02:45:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> CNN reporting police car left, police applauded, someone asked is it him and police replied yes. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-04-17 23:13:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I suggest you see a psychiatrist, this is beyond our knowledge to help with.  Good luck! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-04-15 19:45:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> so drone wars are good? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-04-15 19:40:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I feel Cheyenne is a character who got frozen in the role of the rebel when was 15 and was rejected by his father.  The whole film is his journey to come to terms with his dad.  The message of him appearing as a normal adult at the end is, I think, the completion of his quest to first understand and then forgive his father, thus freeing him from the role his father had inadvertently cast him.  He has finally become an adult.  Just my theory. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-04-15 01:50:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I forgot to mention protest is being criminalized and police are being militarized. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-04-15 01:17:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It looks promising.  I'll hope for the best after the massive disappointment that was 'On The Road.' </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-04-15 00:56:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I find it a cause for the despair that almost all the answers to this question refer to the size of the economy as the key indicator of America's health as a nation.  It is symptomatic of what has happened under neo-liberalism that has grown since the time of Regan. This in itself is a sign of it's decline, the markets are our gods now, we must sacrifice the future of our children to appease them. 

Morally America has declined.  Habeus corpus is now optional, people are assumed guilty. Once the totem of human rights, America has become a nation that tortures prisoners, prisoners who are not convicted of any crime.  

The media and public discourse have declined to infantile levels of name calling and arguments that by rights, should make an adult blush to make.  

America has failed to lead the world in the greatest challenge facing the world, climate change.  Science is not regarded as the unbiased harbringer of truth anymore, if the facts don't suit, they are distorted and dismissed.

Education is poor, an uneducated populace is easier to control and easier to fool.

Corporations are people, legally.  But far more powerful people than anyone else.  Almost no-one gets elected unless they are corporation funded, meaning politicians must serve their paymasters first and the people second.

America has the highest prison population in the world.  The land of the free?  Really?

Unions are broken and marginalized, people have very little power aside from their vote, but then can only vote for corporate approved candiates.  The media is almost run by the corporations.

Socialism for banks, too big to fail, too big to jail.  One law for the rich, one for everyone else.

America will spend endless money on wars and almost nothing on the poor, it's the definition of anti christian values.  Most Hardcore American Christian's support this.

America kills by drones.  People are murdered by remote control, including high numbers of civilians and no-one cares.  Imagine if another country was killing Americans in the US using drones, how would you feel about that?

America supports Israel unreservedly, no matter how badly they abuse the human rights of Palestinians.  

Congress is brazenly defying the will of the American people.

America is a great country and I hope it can find it's way, I am not anti American, but I believe you must face your problems in order to conquer them. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-04-14 11:10:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I love to hate Nurse Ratchet from One flew over the cuckoo's nest. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-04-12 01:07:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I've noticed with Torres lately, his pace seems to have returned.  He's running faster than I've him in years. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-04-10 18:51:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Boom In the shot! The ultimate! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-04-07 21:25:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The opening scene in 'Fear and loathing in Las Vegas' was hilarious to me.  It was so good the rest of the movie couldn't quite live up to it. 'Should I tell him about the bats?' </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-04-07 18:58:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Fascinating read about a fascinating person. Usually 'writing tips' articles disappoint me but this one was inspiring, thanks for sharing.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-04-07 01:28:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Kill a bear! 

Don't kill a bear..... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-04-06 22:58:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I really love Cat's Cradle by Vonnegut.  Mainly for the invented religion Bokonism. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-04-04 15:03:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I agree you may have some form of OCD.  It is treatable with medication and tryto practise meditation, you can reach somwhere deeper than these thoughts and find some peace.
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-03-26 12:46:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> All thr characters did was moan and complain and give out to each other the entire movie.  They were like super rich spoilt brats. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-03-21 23:19:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> r/suicidewatch </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-03-21 23:18:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> R/suicidewatch </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-03-19 19:40:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Amazing prose! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-03-12 02:59:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> you don't get to judge whether someone else's pain is worthy of being posted.  If you don't feel you can add something positive to the post, just ignore it and move on.  Everybody else's pain is as real to them as yours is to you. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-03-12 02:54:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> tough love isn't okay, full stop.  You don't get to get your kicks beating up on vulnerable people, whether you think it might be good for them or not.  It might make you feel good but certainly doesn't make the OP will any better, which is what we are trying to achieve here.  If you don't like the rules, don't post here. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-03-12 01:44:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I removed this comment, mainly because the last line is tough love (not allowed) and borders on abusive.  Please read the guidelines for tips on how best to engage with depressive people. Thanks. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-03-12 01:36:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If you knew how many times someone messages us saying they've been pming someone who has now told them they are going to commit suicide and then goes offline, you would reconsider.  Such instances are very disturbing for a well meaning helper, if it happens on an open thread, people don't feel all the responsibility for someone's life is on them. Do you understand? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-03-12 00:47:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's up to the OP to decide who to reply to, sometimes they go offline soon after there post and sometimes that can be frustrating for people trying to help but there isn't really anything we can do about that. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-03-12 00:46:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> We always try to encourage OPs to seek professional medical help.  It is up to the doctors then to decide if they need medication. You can suggest medication may help but obviously we can recommend any particular medication as we are not qualified. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-03-10 15:38:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Kerry is the bright one who pretends to be thick to be popular.  Class Clown with a roguish smile. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-03-10 02:12:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If you were happy before you can be happy again, it is still within you waiting for it's oppourtunity to blossom.  Joy is the natural state of humanity, look at a baby to see it.  This is a terrible times for you, but you can get through, it's amazing what we can survive if we just hang in there.  Hold onto the hope that you will live to see a better time, and you will. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-03-09 15:02:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hey, what happened? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-03-07 13:43:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Everyone else is wearing a mask too, everybody suffers in this life, you are not the only one. Change is guaranteed in life, if you want to the change to be positive you have to push it and try and direct it yourself.  Persistence is key to character, you've got to keep trying. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-03-07 01:53:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It is a key lesson in life to learn to cope with disappointment.  Everybody encounters it many times in their lives, and it is how you respond that defines how well you thrive in life.  Many people don't get what they want or what they first wanted, or have to find another way of getting what they want.  You need to readjust your approach or your goals and try again.  Right now you are hedgehogging, curled up in a ball and hoping the problem will go away.  It's a natural reaction but it doesn't help.  You've got reassess and begin to move forward again.  You can still achieve a wonderful life, it won't be exactly as you first expected, it never is, life is full of twists turns and surprises, but it is worth carrying on, there is a worthwhile life out there in the future for you, you need to believe in that. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-03-07 01:08:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I know the pain of that kind of depression and thinking, I've been there.  I want you to know you are not the worthless person you feel you are, that's the depression driving your thoughts.  You are worthwhile and loved, you are a good person and I'm sure you mater to all the people you've helped in your life.  Maybe you need to get some help in learning to appreciate yourself and raise yourself esteem, you deserve to feel better about yourself.  Keep the faith you can get through this and emerge a stronger person. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-03-07 01:02:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> There is a will to live deep within us, we don't understand how important our life can be or what our place often is, but inside we know we must live.  Trust your life matters, suicide will only weaken the light in the world, there is so much you can yet contribute.  I'm really sorry you feel so low, do you want to talk about it a little? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-03-06 09:51:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You may surprise yourself with competence, all things you haven't tried, you could be good at so many.  Have a little faith in yourself, you can grow.  There comes a time when everyone has to face up to life, I escaped through drinking, but once you do, after a while, you'll wonder what you were so afraid of.  It's really not that hard. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-03-06 02:30:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You have a fantasy of a life with this girl which allows you to escape the difficulties of your life.  But perhaps the fantasy is only adding to your problems, too much escape into fantasy can allow us to neglect the real issues that need to be faced in our life.  Taking steps to dealing with the real issues you have to deal with and try and let go of the fantasy.  It will be hard at first but when you begin to make progress on the things that really matter, you will feel empowered and emboldened and your real life will begin to improve. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-03-05 20:22:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The Wind Up Bird Chronicle by Haruki Murakami as an adult.

The Catcher In The Rye by JD Salinger as a teenager. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-03-05 18:03:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I read an interview where Laurence Fishbourne said he turned down the role of Jules to star in a friend's art project instead, so I doubt the first 'fact.' </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-03-05 15:57:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It sounds to me like leftovers from the table of Jimmy's greatness. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-03-01 02:28:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> They'll just raise their salaries.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-02-27 20:36:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> oops, just saw that! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-02-25 14:33:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> A true gentle man. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-02-25 06:17:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Discussion on methods of suicide is banned on SW, so this post has to be removed.  If you want to talk about what is making you feel this way, you are welcome to make another post. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-02-24 02:04:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Getting professional help is always the best way to go when you are feeling suicidal.  You nee help, it is available so please reach out and take it.  I know some nights can be harder than others to get through, but please hold on, tomorrow will come.  Help is available, find out if you can get a recommendation from your doctor for a therapist.  There are also support groups and hotlines which are free.  In the meantime you can talk to us, it can help to just vent and let out.  We are here for you and we care, even if we don't know you, you life is as important as anyone else's and has unknown potential for goodness. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-02-24 01:28:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Tell us what's going on? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-02-24 01:28:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> We won't play games like this. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-02-23 02:53:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> There's always a second chance in life, no matter how many times or how badly you fuck up.  There is hope, you just got to believe in it and hang on it.  Try again, believe in yourself again, you can change things, it takes time but you can do it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-02-23 02:15:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It is normal to feel apathy when experiencing depression, which you almost certainly are.  Have you sought any professional help for this?   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-02-23 02:01:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> what happened? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-02-23 01:43:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> because your life is important. Not just now but in the future.  You have no idea how your life can affect others for the better, you can make a difference in the world, a positive difference.  If you die you'll will make the world a worse place to be.  You need to have faith that you are here for a good reason and your life can turn out well if you stick at it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-02-22 19:14:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Have you told your therapist that your situation is worsening?  There is hope for you, you've got to believe that.  Feeling like a burden is common for depressed people, but it is always an exaggerating guilt feeling.  The true burden would be the feeling of loss and confusion you would leave your family with if you committed suicide.  You have beauty and life in you, you deserve to let it shine.  Have you tried meditation?  It can help you grow positive feelings within you and let go of negative ones.  I really suggest you talk to your psychiatrist and family again.  They need to know how troubled you feel, you are loved, don't doubt it, and people do want to help. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-02-22 15:50:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Asking for advice on suicide methods is banned here.  You are welcome to make a post telling us your story on how you got to this point in your life, we would like to hear. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-02-21 16:15:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> All anyone needs to know about Georgoe Galloway - [pussy](http://youtu.be/6v9IXwFb_cg) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-02-19 23:39:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Also Gypsies </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-02-18 14:36:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Vanishing point _ [kowalski](http://youtu.be/0xBzYsE4y1k) Primal Scream </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-02-18 03:37:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> just thought it was an interesting story, man. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-02-17 23:04:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> maybe it was a fan? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-02-17 22:35:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hey I'm a mod, we don't allow pm invitations because they can be hazardous to users.  You can make a post describing your situation and invite replies or we can talk if you want privacy. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-02-16 15:43:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> V for Vendetta.  Critics hated it but everyone I know loves it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-02-14 19:19:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> well, i think it's important that the people who are helping you listen to you.  Somethings work better for some than others.  Ultimately they're the experts but you are in charge.  Have you tried ancillary treatments like meditation and exercise to augment you're treatment? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-02-14 15:07:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> thanks </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-02-14 12:07:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Please read [this](http://www.reddit.com/r/SuicideWatch/comments/xgrba/from_the_suicidewatch_mod_team_if_youre_here_to/) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-02-13 01:51:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> By changing yourself you change the world because you are a part of it.  Apathy and cynicism arise from thinking one person cannot make a difference, but it is this idea that is the biggest obstacle to people creating change.  'You must be the change you want to see in the world' - Gandhi.   

Would your suicide change the world?  Yes and for the worse. Suicide spread out pain and trauma through families and communities.  Not only that but we would lose all the positive things you could have done in your life.  It could be just you loving some people.  Love sustains us all, and is reason enough to keep going.  The more love and care and kindness you put into the world the better it will be.

A smile can save a life. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-02-12 20:12:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> no worries. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-02-12 17:08:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Also horsemeat jokes have already gotten old. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-02-12 14:41:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Only his later stuff </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-02-12 00:53:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> wow, explains everything </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-02-11 23:40:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> really? have you a link? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-02-11 18:24:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The rest is buried somewhere and we gotta find it. Now I hear there's this map.... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-02-11 18:21:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Second rate? Name a better singer! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-02-11 18:16:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Jack Nicholson can play the 'Jack' character but he can also act a character part eg. About Schmidt. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-02-11 18:15:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> there's the bond Sean Connery and the bald post bond Sean Connery. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-02-11 18:13:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I think it was Orson Welles </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-02-11 18:13:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You get this with a lot of leading men though, I mean Cary Grant was always Cary Grant. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-02-11 13:18:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Just proves David Moyes is a genius who deserves a top job. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-02-11 12:41:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Obama for Pope! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-02-10 22:04:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What people end up discussing is what is the easiest and most painless way to go.  It can encourage people to do it, which is the opposite of what we are trying to achieve here. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-02-10 14:48:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> no problem, I'm in Ireland so it's early.  Drop a line any time you feel like talking, it's no problem </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-02-10 11:40:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Well, I think eliciting sympathy from someone is akind of quick way to feel someone's love.  I used do it as well when I was a teenager.  It is understandable you did that because you needed to feel love so badly, when your parent was so critical and seemingly unloving.  Your mother probably isn't conscious of how negative she is or how badly it affects you.  I think you are a conscientious person who cares very much what their loved ones think of them and are frightened of earning disapproval from Krista when that already all you get from the other most important person in your life, your mother.  But you feel guiltly for exaggerating.  I think you are being too hard on yourself, we all make mistakes and we need to learn to forgive ourselves if are to be able to cope with life.  Try to view what you did from a compassionate understanding standpoint.  You were young and very vulnerable, you did it with no malice or desire to hurt and anyone, you did it purely out of a desire to be loved.  It is completely understandable.  You have learned from this, that ist is a destructive thing to do even if you didn't mean any harm, so I'm sure you won't do anything like it again.  Give yourself credit for having lived and learned, that's all any of us can do. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-02-10 10:38:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Well, you don't necessarily have to tell anyone straight off the bat that you are suicidal.  You can just say you are finding really difficult to cope with life right now and feel you need some help.  I think people can understand that.  Tell what do you think has lead to you to this point in you're life where you feeling this way? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-02-10 10:17:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I think you could benefit from talking to your sister.  There is help available to us, but it takes courage sometimes to reach out.  DOn't feel guilty about it, it is likely there will come a time when you feel strong and she feels week and you will able to return the favour.  Is there any counselling available to you in your school or in your area?  Counselling can be very helpful.  Would your parents be willing to pay if you explained you needed someone to talk to?  How is your relationship with them?  

Anyway, it's nice to meet you, Christina, I'm John. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-02-10 09:50:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> No, I've been moderator for maybe 5 years now, I used to leave messages on threads all the the time but there are so many posts now as the community as grown and I guess I became a little exhausted from trying to reply as much I could. So now I mostly check the spam filter and also remove comments from trolls.  I like helping people, though, and I'm reasonably good at it.  So fire away, I'm happy to listen. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-02-10 09:04:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thanks, appreciate it, I've freed it now. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-02-10 09:00:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I have it removed.  But there are different subs such /r/offmychest and that might provide the kind of group you are looking.  And, if you want someone to talk to about overcoming depression, I'm here for you, I mean it, I've been through it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-02-10 08:47:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> /r/depression is probably the place to go to. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-02-10 08:45:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It got caught in the spam filter, happens a lot I'm afraid.  I'm sorry, but we don't allow discussion of suicide methods on our sub, it's safe or healthy for the other users. If you could amend your post and remove the talk of how you plan to die and talk instead about why you want to commit suicide then we would be happy to have it on the page. Again apologies and I'm sorry for what you're going through, but there is hope, it's never too late to change your mind as long as you're alive. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-02-10 08:43:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm sorry, but we don't allow discussion of suicide methods on our sub, it's safe or healthy for the other users.  If you could amend your post and remove the talk of how you plan to die then we would be happy to have it on the page.  Again apologies and I'm sorry for what you're going through, but there is hope, it's never too late to change your mind as long as you're alive. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-02-10 08:33:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hey, we really discourage people from solicting pms here, they can find themselves under to much pressure to save a person all on their own.  The best way to contribute to the group that is sw is to leave helpful comments on others threads.  If you need someone to talk to about what you are going through, you can talk to me.  Anytime. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-02-07 02:40:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hi, mod here, I salute your good intentions, but we don't allow people to solicit private messages on Sw. The reason being that people quickly get in over their head and have no back up to assist them.  At least once a week we get a message from someone who has been trying to counsel someone privately and that person has threatened to commit suicide and gone offline.  This is very distressing for the person who was just trying to be of help.   The right way to help to engage people on the threads, offer supportive and encouraging comments.  The onus will not be all on you.  I hope you understand, I need to keep this post off the sub, for your sake. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-02-06 03:22:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> /r/rapecounseling may help you. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-02-06 03:20:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Despite chronic depression and constant suicidal thoughts when it came down to doing it I found there was this unbreakable will to live within me.  It reminds me of this quote from Albert Camus - in the very depths of winter I found there lay within me an invincible summer.  I struggled against depression for a long time, but it's been worth the struggle, I have become strong, stronger than I ever thought I could be.  I've found new life and happiness, I made it by fighting my way through.  You can do it too, anyone can do it, depression is a part of your mind, you are the master of your mind, it is not yours.  You can learn, but you must fight for your life.  Never give up, never surrender. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-02-06 03:10:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hi, I'm a mod over at /r/SuicideWatch you're welcome to come over here and talk things out.  It's a supportive community with people who will listen to your story. It could help you, please give us a chance. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-02-05 23:28:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I also love Hannibal Lecter's destruction of Clarence Starling's ego in [Silence of the Lambs](http://youtu.be/pXJx5mORmMI) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-02-05 22:35:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Harry Dean Stanton in the booth at the end of [Paris, Texas](http://youtu.be/CDfekAmb_xs) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-02-05 21:28:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Home is where the heart is.  It is really for any single person to decide where they consider home.  If it's Ireland, then you're welcome.  Other people's opinion's are just other people's opinion's/ </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-02-04 00:31:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Call 911 immediately and get help.  There is hope for you, just get help now and when you come back we can talk about things more.  Make the call. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-01-30 01:51:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> high on life, baby! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-01-30 01:36:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Jon Hamm would be an awesome James Bond if he could do the accent.

I think there's a surprising resemblance between Adam Sandler and Bob Dylan (see esp. the wedding singer)


Seth Rogan could play a young Bill Clinton.


 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-01-30 01:27:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Jim Jones is normal to you??? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-01-30 01:25:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> wow...just wow! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-01-30 01:01:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I have an aversion to anyone playing Jesus who has blue eyes. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-01-29 21:45:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Pity, I liked them when they were accessible and catchy. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-01-29 16:39:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> These posts aren't allowed because frequently someone finds themselves taking full responsibility for someone else who is suicidal, it becomes too much to bear very quickly. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-01-28 20:54:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Remember now, shoulders back, tits out, that's what the boys like! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-01-28 01:15:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [Julia](http://www.imdb.com/title/tt0903627/) starring Tilda Swinton, I've never net anyone who's even heard of it, it's brilliant.

[Delicatessen](http://www.imdb.com/title/tt0101700/?ref_=sr_2) french movie by the guy who went on to make Amelie, weird and wonderful.

[The Killing of a Chinese Bookie](http://www.imdb.com/title/tt0074749/?ref_=sr_1) thriller cum character portrait by John Cassettes, the father of American Indie cinema

[Over the Edge](http://www.imdb.com/title/tt0079688/?ref_=sr_1) Early expample of 'punk' cinema, Matt dillon's first film

[Dig!](http://www.imdb.com/title/tt0388888/?ref_=fn_al_tt_4) documentary following two bands in the nineties, most rock'n'roll film ever </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-01-27 15:16:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm glad you're okay, id you ever want to talk about things, make aa post here. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-01-27 03:05:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I don't know the drug but you better call 911 and go to the hospital.  We can talk about things when you get back, right now it's important you stay alive, you don't know what life has in store, what's shitty now could be great down the road. Get help! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-01-27 00:14:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Better call an ambulance.  When you come back we can talk about this, but please don't post pictures like that to this sub, it's not good for others to see. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-01-26 02:11:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> How many will the stadium hold? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-01-25 17:52:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> what is the problem? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-01-25 16:58:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Why do you think you are irreparable?  Times change, people heal and move on. Your life isn't over, who knows where you'll be and how you'll feel at 26, at 36?  Get yourself the help you need, don't give up, you can fix yourself. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-01-25 02:27:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> given the Catholic church is campaigning strongly against x-case legislation here, i think it does. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-01-24 02:45:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> and give yourself time, it takes time to heal. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-01-24 02:16:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> /r/SuicideWatch is a sub where you can get some support if you want to post there. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-01-23 22:35:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I think a break from the real world could be good for you, i think it's a good idea to go back to the hospital where you may at least get some care and support and be out of the stressful home situation for a while.  Now is a time for you to focus on getting yourself better, your marriage and relationship with your parent will need to take a backseat to that for a while.  It's okay to concentrate on looking after you for a while, you desperately need care, from yourself most of all.  Practicing meditation will give you a new coping mechanism which should help you.  Take care of you for now. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-01-22 02:53:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> funny people is great too. He can act, it's just he doesn't bother 90% of the time. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-01-21 02:53:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hi I'm a mod over in /r/suicidewatch, it's a supportive community for people who are feeling suicidal, please feel welcome to come over and make a post. It might help to talk about things a little.
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-01-21 02:50:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hi I'm a mod over in /r/suicidewatch, it's a supportive community for people who are feeling suicidal, please feel welcome to come over and make a post.  It might help to talk about things a little. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-01-20 01:47:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I think you should go to the nearest hospital and tell them you are an immediate suicide risk.  You need proper help immediately, please get some. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-01-19 22:26:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hi, discussion of suicide methods is prohibited on SW, it's on the sidebar.  If you want to discuss why you are thinking of suicide you are welcome to make another post.  But no methods, please. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-01-19 20:50:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hey Kylechief, I'm a mod over in /r/SuicideWatch, it's a supportive community for people who are feeling suicidal, please come over and make a post we can talk things over, it might help you. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-01-19 13:25:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Joey Barton has read a book! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-01-19 00:38:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> lovely girl. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-01-15 03:31:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> please read the sidebar. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-01-14 20:09:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I reckon he's really a ginger! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-01-14 18:33:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Well, you know it can take a lot of work to heal from a frightening childhood, a good counselor will help you on the way through it.  It most have been very destabilizing as a young boy to experience this. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-01-14 10:28:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> There is no doubt such a traumatic experience would have left a deep mark on you.  It was how your dad coped when the pressure was too much, so now you cope in a similar way.  I think your mom was right to get you away from a drunk with a gun, it was a dangerous situation and she was trying to protect you.  I think maybe you should get some counselling to help you overcome experiences and learn new ways to cope. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-01-13 23:20:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Slim Pickens [death](http://youtu.be/hFxwq33rVAs) in Pat Garrett and Billy the kid, to the strains of Bob Dylan. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-01-05 15:26:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It seems suicide is an escape fantasy for you when you feel under stress or pressure.  The next time you find yourself having suicidal thoughts remind yourself of that, it is just a reaction to stress, you don't really want to die, you just feel pressured.  Remember that the situation will pass and tell yourself that you can handle it, as you always have before.  Don't beat yourself up, you are not really that suicidal, it's just a coping mechanism you develop when you were younger.  Try and develop new coping mechanisms to replace it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-01-03 02:08:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> /r/SuicideWatch  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-01-03 01:56:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The 31-year-old is rumoured to only want a new rolling 12-month contract with Real but has been offered a two-year deal which has left him in a state of indecision.

What? must be the first time ever. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-01-03 01:41:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It was on the news this evening.  Look at what you have done, reddit! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-01-02 01:50:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> an interesting take on that i read is that it is really a history of violence in cinema, from cowboys at the beginning through gangsters and on to martial arts.  Made me look at it in a new way. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-01-02 01:46:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I honestly think a lot of people were unconsciously homophobic -'oh it's just gay cowboys.'  They couldn't see past the gay thing to see it for the beautiful romantic love story it was. To me it's like Romeo and Juliet, a great love between two people kept apart by the constraints of society which inevitably ends in tragedy. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-01-02 01:43:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I liked it in general but I didn't like how the villain's 'superpower' is computer 'magic.'  You can do ANYTHING with computers in films, it's a cheat. Also for all his genius, his rock solid, super encrypted code was absurdly easy to break. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-01-01 18:35:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I am going to buy this book! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-12-31 18:19:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I feel for struggling clubs though,  you only have a month to bring in players who might save you from relegation.  Prices and wages are inflated because of the time pressure and false scarcity the window induces, panic buys are common. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-12-31 16:34:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I can understand banning transfers in the final two months of the season, it wouldn't be fair if struggling teams had their best players picked off, but otherwise at the start of the season why not? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-12-31 16:10:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I miss the old days when a transfer could happen at any point in a season.  I don't really see why we should have transfer windows in the first place, why not all the time? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-12-29 18:32:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Bord Failte must love it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-12-29 17:20:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I remember the look in Cech's eyes between the penalties, they were like high powered lasers. I thought there's no way that man is going to lose. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-12-29 01:18:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Have to mention Steve Staunton for his nightmare reign in the Republic of Ireland.  Couldn't manage his way through a set of traffic lights. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-12-29 01:16:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Warnock is a horrible prick, always blaming everyone but himself. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-12-29 01:14:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> West Ham sacked Harry Redknap after finishing fifth in the league and put him in.  A season after that they were relegated and sold off the best crop of young players in a generation.  West Ham are the most self destructive club I know. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-12-29 00:04:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm sorry you suffered such a traumatic, hurt thing, clearly it is still having a major affect on you.  I have no personal experience of this, but I think you need to get counselling/therapy straight away.  There is a sub calle /r/rapecounseling which may be able to help you better than I can. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-12-28 23:58:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> There is now someone making dummy accounts with a slight variation on our mod's names in order to troll users.  Please be wary of this.  Report to the moderators and do not reply to the troll, it feeds there hate to know they have upset someone.  They are very sick people, we must be strong and refuse to let them harm us.  We will do everything we can to stop this and close the accounts, but because of the nature of reddit, it is hard to fight this kind of trolling. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-12-23 17:25:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> But who can forgive the pope? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-12-23 16:40:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You won't find that person, they don't exist.  My story isn't a cliche, it's real life and it happens to a lot of people just like you. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-12-23 13:31:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I used do the same thing for years. Now I'm an alcoholic.  I found the alcohol helped me cope while i was drinking but my symptoms were much worse the next morning.  So then I would take xanax till i could start drinking again.   Every day mental health got a little bit worse.  In the end it was terrible and I found I was addicted to alcohol.  Since I gave up I found the process reverse and every day I got a little bit better.  Be careful, it's is a dangerous road you are going down.

I would reconsider therapy, I've had some terrible psychiatrist who didn't help at all, but also some good ones that did.  I'm now with a counsellor who is really helpful.  Don't give up on it, there are good and bad shrinks out there.  Also meditation and exercise is very helpful.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
