<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject1722</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-15 02:09:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Doesn't he care about those people swimming for their lives down in Louisiana, where's Kanye when you need him? Maybe this will help them next century! He's brilliant! Hey, did you catch his summer '16 playlist that dropped last week? He's so cool! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The 15 most provocative Trump magazine and tabloid covers </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-14 23:05:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Hezbollah Leader Echoes Trump That Obama, Clinton Founded ISIS </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-14 22:28:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-14 17:33:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Whatever you do, don't call them "thugs" or "home grown terrorist"! Like Stephanie Rollins Blake said, {nations mayor} "we have to give them their space"! Mean while we have a murder a day in Baltimore, and who knows how many in Chicago! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-14 17:20:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Do you prefer kittens or fire breathing dragons? Hypothetically speaking of course! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-14 17:10:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Wow, Cuomo's come to Allah moment! :) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-14 16:49:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Same reason it was acceptable to burn effigies of GW! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-14 16:39:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Not to mention the silverware Hilary "allegedly" stole off Air Force One! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-14 16:27:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Said the former Chief of Staff! https://en.m.wikipedia.org/wiki/Leon_Panetta </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> America's Addiction To Mercenaries </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-14 16:22:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-14 16:00:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> We should all be so lucky! "We're not worthy"! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-14 15:47:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> "You can't argue with a man with a shotgun"! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-14 15:26:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's a vast left wing conspiracy! Another popular one. For some reason it's acceptable the second you hear of some wacko white dude going on a rampage to say "see, look", when it's some other ethnicity, we have to look at how said person was ridiculed, and the environment in which he grew up. I'm confused! Please educate me redditor's!  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Great Lakes No Help For A Struggling Trump On The Road To 270 </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-14 15:15:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> No-tipping policies at US restaurants prompt delight  and disaster | Life and style </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-14 14:49:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-14 14:17:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Let me preface my preceding comment for the itchy trigger fingers, all is fair in love and war as far as the blame game! Some are quick to make a blanket statement against Islam, not differentiating between the different sects. Just like people want to make blanket statements on Christianity after some spawn of satan priest gets caught molesting! You have Branch Davidians across all faith's!  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-14 13:56:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> All is fair in love and war I suppose! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-13 16:55:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> For sure there is safety in numbers! If you want comment karma, and you know what's good for ya! Celebrate diversity, and difference of opinion as long as it's our's!   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-13 05:38:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Rectify!  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-13 05:28:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What an beautiful song! Synced leads sound amazing! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-13 02:19:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> As sure as the Sun does rise! If we had know then..... Baby steps, Progress not perfection, that won't happen until we're gone! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-13 00:48:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Did he have the missing emails?








 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Records Sought For Clinton Foundation Donor Placed On Intel Board </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-13 00:38:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-12 16:59:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> US politics? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Elizabeth Trudeau Defends Clinton Foundation </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-12 16:19:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Clinton State Department Aide Helped Clinton Foundation </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-12 15:45:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-12 06:24:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> White America would have been more appropriate! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-12 06:18:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yes it took a team of hipster interns to make him as cool musically as possible, glad you enjoyed! More Kool-Aid anyone?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-12 06:15:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You have got to be freakin' kidding! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-11 23:09:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Not a Trump fan at all, just trying to figure things! I never was any good at math, but even I can see every time I question the status quo, like minded/closed minded people get bent! Maybe I should post about how cool Obama's playlist is! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-11 22:58:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Just wondering between Hilary mentioning Bobby Kennedy, saying she shouldn't get out of the race because he was shot in june, when we have the potentially at the time first black president. Then old Joe here, wow! I Guess Trump should be arrested huh? Double standard much? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> La Dispute - A letter (with lyrics) [emo] </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-11 21:07:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> La Dispute - A Broken Jar Lyrics [emo] </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-11 21:04:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Hsker D - "Real World" [post-harcore] </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-11 20:52:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The Evens - Cache Is Empty [indie rock] </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-11 20:43:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Superchunk - Precision Auto [indie rock] </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-11 20:32:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Mudhoney - If I Think [Grunge] </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-11 20:21:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Fugazi - Cassavetes [post hardcore] </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-11 20:11:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Syria conflict: Footage shows 'chlorine attack' aftermath - BBC News </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-11 19:59:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Jeff Buckley - Forget Her [alt rock] </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-11 19:47:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Nancy Pelosi: DNC Hack Is " Electronic Watergate" </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-11 19:36:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Military Reports Skewed Too Positive On ISIS Fight </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-11 19:18:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Taliban Conflict: Thousands Flee As Fighting Threatens Helmand </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-11 19:03:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-11 18:21:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I didn't know they were hostages, I thought the Iranian Navy rescued them? So confusing! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Talk Of An Assassination Limbaugh Recalls What Hilary Said In '08 Race </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-11 18:19:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-11 14:57:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> "Fry Him Like Bacon" </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-11 06:17:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Stevie Ray Vaughan, "Life By The Drop" [MTV Unplugged] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-11 05:35:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Timing was just a coincidence I suppose! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Obama displayed high level of deception when questioned on 400 million Iran payment </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-11 04:34:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-11 03:56:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You pick a lost cause you sure do commit, I'll give you that! Take care, I'm moving on, never intended to go here with you. It was a light hearted thread, hope tomorrow is a better day for you! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-11 03:52:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'd take a day at a meeting thinking about getting high over getting high thinking about how am I going to get to a movie! Keep coming back, more will be revealed! Maybe you haven't had enough pain yet. I had my first kid when I was your age and swore I would be a good father and put that shit down! Couldn't help myself, I had no discipline from an early age, shit got rough and I got to running, lost everything my kid is 16 now and is tired of hoping I get my shit together! He's hurt, rightfully so, he hates me and that hurts! I guess what I'm trying to say is I'm 38 now tired and lonely, I should have long been dead, do you think you will have that kind of luck? Do you want to have a lack luster life if you are lucky enough to not die you may end up in prison, you ever been to prison? Keep fucking around!! Get it now while you can, time flies I was 22 yesterday I swear.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-11 03:30:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Well it's been quite some time seeing how my children have long out grown The SpongeBob, so yeah it was borderline 10 years ago I can only imagine! Do think it was intended to be tongue n cheek, I hope you're not this impatient/aggressive with your children! Are you new to parenting or something? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-11 03:19:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Don't have to like it, but i found myself wanting to know exactly what my kid's were watching and ended up getting hooked, plus it was a way to interact with the kid's. Not sure why you would join the thread, but you are definitely entitled to your opinion! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-11 03:16:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Great Song! What a tearjerker, as can be said of most of Peter's music. Going through it right now and this has always been a song I derive strength from to press on through the valley! Right on time, thank you!  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-11 03:10:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Well said! Seems like depending on agenda, the few detractor's get more attention!  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-11 03:06:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> No kid's huh? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-11 03:02:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So I don't walk around banging on my chest "I really like my some Vag!" So conversely why do some feel like they have to cram there sexual preference down other's throat's (pun intended)! To preface my question, I have come across some of the most genuine, kind hearted homosexuals you would ever meet! They never felt the need to explain to me what they like to do in private nor did I them, all was well!0 I will say I do think it odd for someone to dress like a female to try to attack, I guess straight men? Not talking about legitimate trans-gender.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-11 02:50:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You can't eat that many, "why"? They'll go straight to your hips! Ha </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-11 02:22:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The one where SpongeBob has to clear his mind of everything but fine dining, which he does literally. Latter when someone ask his name there's this big production of two guys in an office inside SpongeBob's mind going through files and flipping out 'cause they can't find anything on a name! Quite the metaphor.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-11 01:01:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Lord knows there's no way a supreme being could speak different dialects to different people over many centuries, or through music, art, your neighbor! Religion is good for nothing but wars and in fighting. I would wager that if there was or is a God/Allah/Buddha that he or they would probably just want us to treat each other with respect/dignity, be kind, compassionate, tolerant. If people are so sure of their beliefs, why would you be threatened by someone else's beliefs? If anything it should only confirm what we know, since we/they know it all! Tolerance  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-11 00:24:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Why has it taken this long for true followers to suggest something like this? Better late than never I suppose!  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-10 20:48:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I suppose it's for a just in case scenario, so if there was some sort of breakdown of the electronic system, they would have the hard copy backup to count manually, which presents it's own set of problems as. It was done in pen, so at least no hanging chads to deal with!:) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-10 20:37:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So it's only a crime/illegal if you get caught? And you put a lot of faith in our gov. if you think they know the exact number of people here illegally! Wait, am I allowed to say illegally? Maybe sojourner would be more proper. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-10 20:21:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> How much? The suspense is killing me! Of course all the people here illegally are accounted for, that's like if we make more gun laws or just stricter laws in general, it'll somehow keep the people who already aren't not following the existing somehow get in line! That's what makes them criminals/illegal.    </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-10 19:20:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> How much do they then cost tax payers, in hospital ER visits, police and fire, school not only in money but english speaking children having to twiddle their thumbs while teacher's make sure Lupe understands what was tought (language barrier). I'm all for people wanting a better life for themselves and their family, but there is a right and wrong way to go about it! Hilary will say anything, do anything to get elected, as evident in this half truth!  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-10 16:09:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Don't be too hard on yourself, it's ok to have those feelings you just don't have to act on them! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-10 16:02:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's not a popularity contest! Music is subjective in the ears of the listener! You don't have to like it to appreciate it or the simple fact that someone else my!  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-10 15:50:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> In Maryland during the primary's, the ballots were done on paper then when you're through you place the ballot in a scanner it's uploaded' then you personally place the ballot in a locked box so there's a hard copy! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-10 06:49:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Damn, impressive! you were not even close! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-10 06:47:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Drag 'em on over! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-10 06:22:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> All about it now a day's! Google Play Music for me which includes commercial free YouTube Red! Two years going strong and I haven't look back. There's a slight learning curve, take your time and enjoy! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-10 05:23:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What happened to all those shovel ready stimulus jobs we were sold on 7 or so years ago? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-10 05:14:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Here's mine in tablet mode.http://imgur.com/a/6EfCg </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-10 04:04:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Sounds kinda like the way political polls are done! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-10 00:14:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Good thing he's never read the Constitution, or that could really be misconstrued! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-09 23:45:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> http://imgur.com/a/frldX This is where I'm talking about. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-09 23:29:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Try actually using the settings icon in the cortana ui and make sure your region ie. dialect is blank or should say choose one. She will assume you're in the default area you selected during setup. Hope that helps or at least get's you going in the right direction! Good Luck.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-09 23:05:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Right, you had to vote for Obama if you didn't want to be called a racist (does your conscious bother you? tell the truth!) now we have to vote for Billary unless you're threatened by women! It's all fun and games 'till someone's feelings get hurt!   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-09 22:47:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Kool-Aid anyone? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-09 21:40:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I passed! Sweet.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-09 21:15:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Must be the same branch of the FBI Hilary gets her info from! :) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-09 20:52:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Seems to be fashionable to do just that these days! Yet certain elements can say whatever they want about an opposing viewpoint, but don't dare disagree with the masses.       </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-09 19:53:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> No that can't be more trustworthy than our goverment! BTW I have some beachfront property you may be interested in! :) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> EL VY - Return to the Moon (Political Song for Didi Bloome to Sing, with... [Rock] </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-09 19:49:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-09 19:40:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> When did we start trusting every last thing our Gov. tells us? Certainly you don't believe everthing CNN reports! I must just be ill informed. My apologies! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-09 19:30:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Say's who? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-09 19:03:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Right, and the economy and jobs market are booming! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-09 18:58:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This has to be some sort of racist right wing conspiracy! What are you going to tell me next, Michael Jackson slept with little boys? Or that you shouldn't let your son become an altar boy? What's this world coming to when you can't even enjoy a Jello-Pudding Pop! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-09 02:58:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What happens when the shit goes down? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-08 15:45:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Didn't Derek Zoolander open an academy just for that affliction?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-08 15:42:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Strange Bedfellows for sure! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-08 14:49:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Out now, Give A Glimpse Of What Yer Not! Thought the Pile up was some obscure hidden track or something! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-08 14:25:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thought this was going to be old school Dinosaur Jr 
since Dinosaur was their original name. What a rip!
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-08 06:59:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> There is an option in settings/start menu to add things to the left side! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-08 02:56:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I think edge is just slow.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-08 02:49:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Soup, Blind Melon! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-08 01:55:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm using ABP on edge and chrome works great! You can put the badges on the banner and watch it roll! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-08 01:51:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Turn Cortana down, turn off Cortana everywhere! Including lock screen. 
My  RAM is actually down since 1607 chrome is event closed save drive. I shut down a lot of extension's as well! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-08 01:40:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Actually there are more features and more fluid IMO on edge! Picture quality is better as well! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-08 01:39:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Chrome can only do Netflix in 720p, MS edge does full 1080p! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-08 01:29:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Then another 1,278 in Japan! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-08 01:25:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Or a wanna be! Blood's say nephew! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-08 01:24:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Means he's affiliated. Crip! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-07 19:43:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> 12 yrs and was amazing until the wreckage caught up! I was trying to make up for wrongs to someone who had based their existence on the  premise that I was the devil. Made it a roll coaster 3 yrs and now have not spoken (save birthdays) for over a year now! People change! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-07 14:54:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It was for me as well, just started working properly on 8/6! Pretty cool when it works.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-07 14:50:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I personally like it better on the taskbar! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-07 14:48:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I wish she would disappear automatically after dialogue! And you could verbally ask for help in edge not just right click access! Other than that we get along just fine.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-07 14:35:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Anything of 40oz To Freedom, Sublime! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-07 02:11:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Ha, he said balls! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-07 02:09:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Quite a conspiracy, right up there with the framing of MJ! Smh. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-07 02:01:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Green Mind will always be the one for me, this album is definitely growing on me! The Barlow tracks aren't bad at all. They came through B-More last year and I wasn't able to go so I'm a little jealous! J is and has always been they're heart and soul IMO! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-07 01:40:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Doesn't change the fact! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-07 01:36:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Scott Weiland played with them for a bit if you get chance check it out! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-07 01:30:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> "if I can't be my own, I'd feel better dead" </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-06 22:06:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Blur had a self titled album that had sort of a yellow cover, came out in '97.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-06 20:31:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> should be the 2016 Olympic theme song! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Iron and Wine - Boy with a Coin [OFFICIAL VIDEO] [indie rock] </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-06 19:05:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-06 18:34:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Pretty vague! Need a song, lyric something. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Dinosaur Jr - 'Give A Glimpse Of What Yer Not' Review </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-06 17:55:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-21 12:11:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Steers and queers! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-19 04:39:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> And access to your clipboard,a dedicated # pad and space bar cursor control! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-14 20:36:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Google Play Music!  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-14 14:48:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Good for you Nolan, don't sell yourself short weed eating is the skill position, some yards the same size  have more trimming some have less. Good luck!  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-14 14:45:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The yard is to ocean as boat is to mower </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-14 14:39:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's a visual app, I believe it does cast to the regular chrome cast! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-14 14:37:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Would be great if it synced with play music!  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-30 18:38:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Just confirmation  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-29 15:13:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> No love for the galaxy alpha apparently  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-29 15:07:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Apple could have helped and maybe been able to keep the fbi from having unfettered access. Instead the tried to play the marketing strategy and it seems as though it backfired.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-27 15:53:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> People and options inside said contacts thread  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-27 15:43:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Is this functionality going to be for all OEM stock camera apps or just the Google camera?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-28 16:48:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> They wanted the character to represent current events more closely I imagine. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-28 14:59:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hope they implement it for Google now cards soon too! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-27 20:22:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Noticed an issue this morning when a fully charged battery dipped to 50% overnight. I was using nova with a Google app widget, I've charged my phone 3 times already at 3 pm. The phone was hot to the touch as well. Google app updated 3 time's in the past 2 days. Unfortunately I went back to the Google now launcher. G-850a </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-20 18:53:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If I wanted an iPhone! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
