<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject5255</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Do Home Remedies really work? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-11 09:11:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Do Home Remedies actually work? Home Remedies for everything... </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-11 08:48:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-09 13:27:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> yung mga kupal kong kaibigan yung mahilig mangasar xd </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-09 12:40:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Why are people downvoting me?
I came here to ask for help not to spread wrong information of stuff like that </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Mga Magandang Pangasar o Comebacks </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-09 12:37:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Para hindi puro seryoso ang reddit...


Ano kaya mga magandang pangasar o mga comebacks, palagi ako talo doon eh =P


Panglaban sa mga "Edi Wow" o "Kuwento mo sa pagong" </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-09 12:30:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> how do I change it? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-07 06:21:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Allowing citizens to kill Criminals...

What could possibly go wrong?... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-06 12:00:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> why not </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Can I use tapwater instead of Distilled Water? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-06 09:50:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-04 16:41:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm not from from the states

And it says It can't be shipped where I'm from... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-04 16:37:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Dang...
Thanks anyway...

Last Question

You know how can I get lye? =P

I tried looking online but it's way too expensive. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-04 16:20:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> look man I can't find lye for jacksh*t

I just wanna do one for practice

I don't care if its already 70% complete of the whole process of soapmaking

I just wanna know if it's gonna have any defect on it... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-04 16:10:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> yeah but I'm gonna mix Lye with half of that stuff anyway?

It's like buying Lard
instead of rendering fats by yourself

Is it not? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Can I use this (photo) as a Substitute for Lye in Soap Making </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-04 15:45:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So I want to make Soap and all I need is LYE 

but I can't find a place that sells 100% pure lye 

Then I found this 
Soap Chips 

http://imgur.com/a/mz2aX
photo of back
http://i.imgur.com/Y5SOrmE.jpg 


The ingredients are 

Sodium Hydroxide (lye) 

Refined Coconut Oil 

Purified Water 

It's obviously not 100% lye but half of the ingredients 
here already used for soap making... 

And it doesn't have aluminum that 
ruins the lye 

Will it still work though? 
Need response from an expert at Soap Making
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-02 15:28:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> let's just say his famous with the "kids".... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-02 15:19:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> srsly? ever heard of the tv show Jackass? or at least the movies? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-02 13:32:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's an interview with Steve-o
the context is anything "Steve-o" related...
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Steve-O Podcast Interview </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-02 05:59:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Try to guess all 4 of them.. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-29 15:43:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-29 15:39:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I think we're done with shaky cam man...


Just always remember dude, Less is more...
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Hilarious Tom Cruise Impression </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-29 11:07:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What Role can Steve Buscemi play in the DCU if he was casted... </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-29 10:26:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What role you wanna see him in...
http://img05.deviantart.net/d006/i/2015/079/b/b/the_joker__2015_by_chinook23-d8lt0q1.jpg

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Picture of Quentin Tarantino, Robert Rodriguez, Frank Darabont and Scott Spiegel.... </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-29 10:16:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Lex Luthor could have just framed Batman </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-22 11:59:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  just realized Lex could have framed Batman. He could have gave Superman a legit reason to fight batman, make him think Batman kidnapped her or better yet, make him think Batman killed her. That way they're both fueled by hatred and both realized that they made mistakes. It also would have been impactful if superman thought his mom was dead, so that Batman can see that he shares the same pain of having dead parents. This would have humanized both of them and gave them a concrete reason to team up </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Tom Cruise Impersonator Rallies the Sales Force at a Pharma Conference </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-22 04:09:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-21 01:22:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> " Douche" hahaha... You guys are the most ingorant fanbase I have ever seen.

It's like feeding vegetables to a child man....


one simple critique and you guys think I'm a DC hater, wow, so you guys hate Chris Stuckmann now?  Oh yeah you do cuz he said Suicide Squad was a mess (even tho he said he enjoyed some of it)

I can somewhat relate to him, cuz I liked suicide squad, up until the 3rd Act where DC fucked it up...


I'ma just take my Man of Steel Blu-ray and leave....  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-20 13:58:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> like their writers could write any better...

Anyway it's just common sense tho,
It baffles me how much DC keeps making horrible decisions... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-20 13:42:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> i don't know...

cuz it affects them?????? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-20 12:51:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Real or not it makes a good point... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-20 10:25:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> https://media.giphy.com/media/3o7TKDkSPpPwnJArGo/giphy.gif </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Re: An Open Letter to Warner Bros </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-20 10:11:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> How To Do A Tom Cruise Impression </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-12 12:59:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Tom Cruise Impersonator, Videos of him Acting Like Tom Cruise </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-12 12:44:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-12 05:31:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> How about the other way around, Movies that reference Pulp Fiction </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> SAW-ENTOLOGY with not tom cruise </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-11 14:12:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Tom Cruise Impersonator Auditions for Twilight! </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-11 01:56:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Tom Cruise Impersonator Auditions for Twilight Funny </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-08 15:54:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-07 17:44:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm not confused I just forgot to add something
DC Animated and DC Cinematic is both DC anyway so gives a f

I just mentioned The Killing Joke because it's a part of Dc that's getting panned by critics </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-07 17:42:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> if WB owns DC
then WB is DC

It's easier to simplify it that way

and alot of people do it </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-07 17:34:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Oh god please don't tell me people are fighting over a helmet </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-07 17:05:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> lol Sorry if I sound whiny,

Sometimes I get too passionate and express it too much on typing =P </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-07 16:41:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Well we got to admit the DC films do got some heavy flaws...


But yeah man Rotten Tomatoes Critics are too fucking rough on DC movies man....
Way too rough than necessary..

There's only like a few reviews that's fair. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-07 16:32:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I love you </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-07 16:29:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> lol I didn't say it was Bad..
I just said it was a mix-bag

meaning there were good parts
lol </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-07 16:28:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The critics just got Man of Steel wrong man...
That movie was awesome tho </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-07 16:21:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That's a good point.
On the Avengers thing.

But DC is doing some really bad decision on their films storywise,
have you notice that their mindset acts like a typical bad Michael Bay type production

where they think like 

"oh people like action, there's gotta be a big action set piece at the end, it's gonna make us alot of money"
or 

"oh we gonna cut this movie short, it's too long, oh if we cut this movie, it's gonna make us alot of money"

You know stuff like that?
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-07 16:20:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Dude shut up

Don't call me the troll when you're the one who's throwing insult,
I haven't thrown a single insult at you...


I love DC but I'm brave enough to admit that they got some heavy flaws.. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-07 16:03:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> dude read the whole thing...

I want DC to succeed

That's why I'm making suggestions!
 but they need to get their shit together

just saying..... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> DC Needs to get their Shit together </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-07 15:56:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I have a couple of  points I want to address about DC right now.

1) I've lot faith in DC, that's 3 strikes in a row. BVS, The killing Joke, and Suicide Squad.

Suicide Squad for me is a mixed bag, but it could have been great if they didn't fucked some things up!



DC really has no idea what they are doing! 

Do you guys really think Justice League is gonna be good? No! It's gonna be shit, there's no faith anymore. It's the same shit (Oh maybe the next movie is gonna be the good one, or maybe the next one, or the next one) and it always ends up just awful.


DC keeps making the excuse "Oh we made it for the fans, it's for the fans" 

DC is not giving you fans any justice if they keep giving us shitty movies.

And stop lying saying that the movie is good because deep down inside you know that its not a good movie,

Just stop lying, wanna know why?
 Because how will DC learn? If the fans express their real feeling towards their movies maybe they will start getting their shit together.

2) And don't blame the critics, but hey Rotten Tomatoes can sometimes go a little bit rough (and Ghostbusters a 70% seriously?) but back on topic. Maybe you should side with them so DC will actually learn and get their shit together.

Anyone else like the DC executives operated like a Michael Bay production or just any bad executive studios who has a stupid mindset of, "oh people like action, people like popular music, we gotta do this" I think that's what it is.
Anybody else feel that?


They need to stop rushing this DCEU. I get it, they are rushing because they want to keep up with Marvel. But here's the thing,

WHY?
Marvel ain't going nowhere. You think they are gonna stop making movies after Infinity War? No! Of Course not!
I know we all want to have Marvel vs DC 
but there's no competition if DC is shit.
They need to get people who know what their doing.


I've watch a Suicide Review that explain what's DC is doing wrong
https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=nsyNWktNYHA
Go watch somewhere in the middle on the rant about DC

My Suggestions for DC 

- get some people who knows good storytelling, character development and obviously the comics
- rewrite Justice League, 
because it's safe to assume that its gonna be garbage, 
maybe push it back to 2018 (Hey you've pushed BVS from 2015 to 2016, and we've managed to wait so yeah)

Push Justice back to 2018,
Make an Aquaman movie first,

-Make a Cyborg movie, or a flash movie

before we get to Justice League..


That's my suggestion.

Listen DC, I fucking love you, I fucking loved Man of Steel, I honestly think that is a good movie.

Ben Affleck is fucking awesome as Batman, and so is Henry Cavill and even Gal Gadot.
Anyway that's all I have to say, I really wanna hear you guys' opinion on this..
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Tom Cruise Impersonator Auditions for Twilight </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-07 13:35:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Funny Tom Cruise Impersonator </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-07 12:08:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Funny Tom Cruise Impersonator, and whole channel of it </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-07 11:37:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-06 14:28:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> F*ck totally forgot about them....

I guess that's happen when you get writers block

Anyway thanks for this, it really did help me out.. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Happy Wheels Glitch/Bug Involving Groups </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-06 14:16:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Anyone else having this problem...
There's a bug everything you group two groups together.

-Especially when you're working on a detailed level
 filled with alot of art. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> How to Make a killer as main protagonist likeable.. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-06 02:32:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> How can I make my main protagonist be liked by the audience if he kills people..
He's a low rent hitman, but he doesn't just kill on the jobs, he kills people who just mess with him...
Basically he's stone cold serial killer, but how do I make him likeable? Is it even possible? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-26 11:12:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Lol this was fun coming up with names...

Jules - Ice Cube

Vince - John Cusack

Mia - Krysten Ritter

Butch - Jason Statham

Marcellus - Terry Crews

Mr Wolf - Jeff Bridges



Bonus ones

Jimmy - Will Forte

The Gimp - Tom Hanks

Marvin - Kevin Hart </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> A Bitter Falling out? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-12 06:23:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> How do you tell a cat that you don't have food? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-31 03:38:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-23 16:24:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This is all opinionated man...

Even the school thing is just an opinion, I was just exaggerating. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Movies that has bigger story behind the plot?? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-23 15:02:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Theory: Esmeralda Villalobos comtemplating on Killing. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-21 11:57:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You guys know the theory that everybody in Pulp Fiction is a criminal.

I think the cab driver is no exception.

At first, the scene might seem like random chitchat but I think tarantino got something else in mind...

or I meant Esmeralda got something in mind... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> "I'm Honest about being Dishonest" </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-15 04:22:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I remember having a conversation about a guy who keeps lying...

He said something like


"I'm honest about being dishonest"

atleast he's telling the truth that he sometimes lies.

This quote just hits me like what do you guys think about it XD </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Cow Chop Fan Art lol </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-07 14:59:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Was Uma Thurman's twitching intentional? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-01 17:21:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Anybody notice in the Jack Rabbit Slims scene, 
Uma was kinda twitching in the entire conversation, 
it's very subtle but you can notice it.. 

Was that intentional? 
Because of the whole "Drug addict" 
thing with her character 
if so great acting.. 

or was she cold or something? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-01 03:35:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I think killing off one of the biggest Superhero ever is darker </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-31 09:46:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Read my post..
I reinvented Lex's plan

https://www.reddit.com/r/dawnofjustice/comments/4cp1j4/how_bvs_should_have_ended_atleast_for_me/ </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> How BVS Should Have Ended (Atleast for ME) </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-31 09:39:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> **Spoilers**

Need to be fix

-Doomsday

-The Death of Supeman

-A better reason to fight

1. Doomsday

Instead of Doomsday use Superman, make him evil.
With Red Kryptonite
and Have Batman and Wonderwoman fight him

so it's still called fucking BATMAN v SUPERMAN *w/ wonderwoman

Lex Luthor's plan was stupid,
Instead of trying to make Doomsday,
instead he was making a way to make Superman evil,
with red Kryptonite,

Luthor's Plan should have been:

Make superman evil, make him kill people,

Lex luthor saves the day by defeating Superman

with Kryptonite,

 so people will love Lex and Hate Sups


IT WOULD HAVE BEEN SO MUCH MORE SENSE!



2. The Death of Superman.

Superman shouldn't have died, it was too way early to kill him off!

Superman was evil. Batman and Wonder Woman managed to make him good again. People now hates Superman even more.
He leaves Earth, becomes an exile..

So Justice League will be about finding Superman, instead of bringing him back to life....

*Think about it.


3. The Fight.

Make them WANT to fight each other, not with some hostages..
It would have been so much better to see them willingly to fight each other... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
