<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject2315</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-09 03:00:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Parents are both blonde, children are both brunette. Poor Dad.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-09 02:49:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Are Shia even actually Muslim tho? 

Ha! J/K... sort of.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-09 02:36:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hm. I'm an American revert expat living in the KSA. Since I am a woman and married, I mostly pray at home, obviously. However, I have been to many a masjid. From California to New York and several states in between. Most of them have been absolutely one dimensional in regard to ethnicity, race,  and the like. So, my experience with western masjids hasn't been that of witnessing great diversity. 

Here in the Kingdom, however, just walking through Tamimi's I see brothers and sisters from every part of Allah's great, big creation. Westerners of every color, Asians from the southeast to the pacific islands, Africans, and of course Arabs. This is also true for the masjids I've had the chance to attend. 

So, idk, bro.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-09 02:19:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Alhamdulilaah!  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-09 02:16:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Salamulaykum Wa Rahmatullahi Wa Barakatuh. 

Plucking the eyebrows is not permissible in Islam. It is called Al Namas. 

Abd-Allaah ibn Masood (radi Allah Tala Anhu) said: "I heard the Messenger of Allaah (Sallallahu Alayhi Wasallam) say: Allaah has cursed the woman who does tattoos and the one who has them done, the woman who plucks eyebrows (al-naamisah) and the one who has it done (al-mutanammisah), and the one who files her teeth for the purpose of beauty, altering the creation of Allaah. 

(al-Bukhaari, 5931; Muslim, 2125) 



However, in Fatwa al-Lajnah al-Daaimah, it is stated:

There is no sin on a woman if she removes hair on her upper lip, thighs, calves and arms. This is not part of the tanammus (plucking) that is forbidden.

(Fatwa al-Lajnah al-Daaimah, 5/194, 195) 

The Committee was asked:

What is the Islamic ruling on plucking the hair between the eyebrows?

They replied:

It is permissible to pluck it, because it is not part of the eyebrows.

(Fatwa al-Lajnah al-Daaimah, 5/197) 

Of course, Allah knows best, but I hope this helps!  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-09 01:50:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Agreed. In our Deen, Allah SWT isn't male or female. Allah is not human and Allah's human creations do not resemble Him other than having attributes like Him. That is, eyes with which to see and ears with which to hear, etc. But in Islam, we don't believe Allah is some human looking male with a big, white beard looking over us. That is an egotistical and patriarchal Christian way of thought, of which we do not subscribe to. 

Allah is infinite and Allah created everything; time, space, heaven, earth, male, female, jinn, animals, sun, moon, stars, etc. Therefore, he could never be likened to humans. Human beings are finite, and Allah is beyond our comprehension.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-08 18:37:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Unamused by humans  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-08 18:36:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hahaha! When you accidentally open your front-facing camera...  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-08 18:32:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm sorry that your little one is no longer in her earthly form. I lost my dog a year ago; I know how much it hurts. May you find peace and relief from the pain.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-08 18:27:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Lol @ the sleeping human photobomb :-) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-08 18:25:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Those bad boys are growing wild! So cute!  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-08 18:12:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Alhamdulilaah, I'm a black woman, I'm safe. Sry whities and black men!  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-02 02:19:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This is amazing  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-01 04:15:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Gorgeous  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
