<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject2699</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Iowa governor dumps on idea of Rep. Steve King running for Senate </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-04-29 22:29:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Authorities take children of Idaho medical marijuana advocates, cite presence of pot in household, plan to return kids in 30 days. Mother of 4 boys used marijuana for multiple sclerosis. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-04-29 21:07:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-04-29 21:00:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Here's more on the details. Marijuana advocates and other legal experts in the state are calling the proposal unconstitutional.

http://www.huffingtonpost.com/2013/04/29/amendment-64-repeal-uncon_n_3179384.html </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Reinforcements arrive at Guantanamo to force 'humane' treatment onto hunger-striking detainees (who have reportedly lost the will to live after years of confinement without charges) </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-04-29 20:16:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-04-29 20:04:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's sketchy, but technically they would be the ones deciding if it's voted out. The measure to repeal would be wrapped into a ballot amendment that would be couched on approving more taxes. The way I understand it is it would set up the following scenario: 

a.) Vote for higher taxes and in so doing, keep marijuana legal.

Or b.) Reject higher taxes (which voters generally like doing) and in so doing, support the repeal of legal marijuana. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> After Being Approved By 55 Percent Of Voters, Colorado Lawmakers Consider Measure To Repeal Legal Marijuana If Voters Don't Approve More Taxes </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-04-29 19:39:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Mark Sanford gives voters his personal cell phone number...What could go wrong? This. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-04-25 19:49:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Police dogs in Washington begin new marijuana-free drug sniffing courses. Removing pot from their repertoire is a little harder. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-04-25 19:47:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-04-25 05:02:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> They are. And that's not even close to a reason to target them with violence. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Jeb Bushs moderate views on immigration reform molded by deportation of housekeeper: Another politician only able to see middle ground after being personally affected by political circumstances? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-04-24 23:25:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Former Romney intern charged with sexual extortion also dressed up as Ellis the Elephant for Gingrich campaign: "Turns out, there really was junk in that trunk." </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-04-24 19:29:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Anthony Weiner suggests more details could emerge from past sex scandal amid run for NYC mayor </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-04-24 19:28:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Obama drug czar admits "you can't arrest your way out of" the nation's drug problem </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-04-24 19:26:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-04-24 06:23:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What's wrong with this is that in Tennessee, every day is already traditional marriage day. There is no marriage equality and I suspect that such a development is a long ways off. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-04-24 06:19:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Alternate headline: "Glenn Beck Glenn Becks" </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> "Each of us put our hand on the Bible and swore to uphold the Constitution. We did not place our hands on the Constitution and swear to uphold the Bible." -- PA Democrat on anti-abortion bill. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-04-24 05:57:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Vermont marijuana decriminalization bill stalls: Opponents worry about being able to tax drug dealers, ignore cost of enforcement </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-04-24 00:06:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Does Eric Holder Have A 4/20 Surprise Coming For Washington And Colorado? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-04-20 00:40:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-04-19 19:46:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Won't somebody PLEASE! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Republican Urges Holder To Decide On Marijuana Legalization Because 'Children Are Dying' </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-04-19 19:35:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-04-16 18:06:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Can we say for sure that Steve King didn't have something to do with this bombing yet? Just asking. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-04-11 00:32:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Is he reporting from beyond the wall? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> 'Next Generation Science Standards' Urges States To Adopt Curriculums That Emphasize Climate Change   Evolution </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-04-10 21:46:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Obama Budget Contains One Final 'Screw You' To Mitt Romney And His Millions </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-04-10 16:26:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Democratic Senator Warns Congress May Take Action On Video Game Companies Over Violent Games </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-04-04 23:25:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> 35 co-sponsors jump on bill to legalize, tax marijuana in Maine, as it looks to become first state to legalize through legislation  </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-03-27 20:57:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-03-08 23:31:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The letter actually doesn't rule out targeting of U.S. citizens INSIDE the country, so long as they pose an "imminent threat" to others. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-02-22 06:26:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I thought this at first too, but mainly because I assumed these were North Korean kids that had been separated from their parents at age 4 and forced to perfect this strange ritual to perform for Dear Leader. That wouldn't be funny. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Pentagon Creating New 'Distinguished Warfare Medal' For Drone Pilots Who Operate From Afar </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-02-13 20:09:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Politicians flash guns to prove they're hard-asses, claim rappers who do the same are promoting unhealthy gun culture. Ironic much? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-02-12 00:22:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Joe Biden floats support for "smart gun" technology,  which prohibits anybody but the owner of a firearm to fire it </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-01-11 22:36:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-01-08 23:22:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Scary, but before we freak out too much, let's remember that whoever got picked had to be a Republican (so statistically likely to be a creationist no matter what), and that out of the potential choices, it seems like the scientific/health research community doesn't sound too down on Kingston.

http://news.sciencemag.org/scienceinsider/2013/01/new-head-of-nih-appropriations-p.html </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> In an underreported story from last night, "Charles Darwin" lost to Republican who called evolution a "lie from the pit of hell" </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-11-07 21:22:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Long lines, suppression, voting and ballot issues reported at polling places: Liveblogging our embarrassing electoral system at work  </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-11-06 18:53:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> So, You're Thinking Of Not Voting In This Election... </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-11-06 00:21:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-11-05 18:15:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Except, not. You've been Onion-ized. That source is bunk. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-11-02 21:34:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I wasn't arguing that it should be acceptable that it's primitive. In fact, the opposite. Touch screen sensitivity and calibration issues shouldn't be that hard to rectify. Just as it shouldn't be that hard to count, keep track of and issue absentee ballots. But computers apparently break, and humans are apparently idiots, so looks like we're stuck hearing stories like this, simply presented in a biased fashion by Fox News.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-11-02 20:47:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> To be completely fair, this is happening to people attempting to vote both ways, primarily because the technology is primitive and the people who run elections, usually administrators not volunteer poll workers, are exceedingly incompetent. It's kinda rare that you see human error excused because people are so eager to cry conspiracy. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Anti-Obama anonymous text bomb spreads misinformation, charges recipients for messages </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-10-31 04:37:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-10-25 22:53:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Did Obama's birth certificate list his birth weight at 25 pounds? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-10-24 15:34:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> But but but...they went on Facebook and said they did it. Why didn't the president mention the group's tweets and 4square check-ins at the consulate in his Rose Garden address? LIAR! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-10-23 21:43:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> MOAR BOATS! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-10-18 19:40:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Mitt Romney is so unpredictable and pliable that he *might* be better than Obama when it comes to marijuana crackdowns? That alone would be a dumb reason to endorse Romney, but take this statement from his campaign into account and it's even more idiotic.

"Governor Romney has a long record of opposing the use of marijuana for any reason. He opposes legalizing drugs, including marijuana for medicinal purposes. He will fully enforce the nations drug laws, and he will oppose any attempts at legalization."

http://www.huffingtonpost.com/2012/10/02/mitt-romney-marijuana_n_1931995.html </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-10-15 20:34:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Looks like Freeman should have done the Gangnam Style dance. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-09-26 17:33:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> He's right, but only if they haven't gotten laid in a really long time... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The Most Iconic White House Photos Of Obama's First Term (So Far) </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-08-24 21:06:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-08-22 22:46:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> In 2010. When the Tea Party was actually relevant. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-08-17 17:28:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Welp, looks like there's a shitty new Resident Evil movie coming out. The movie studio thanks you for the free promotion! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-08-08 23:49:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> A lot of the good songs from this album are sampled on Kid Cudi's "A Kid Named Cudi" mixtape. Now you realize why that album was so good, not to mention a few good samples from OutKast and Band of Horses, etc. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Connecticut Repeals Death Penalty </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-04-25 22:27:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Mitch McConnell To Constituent: Marijuana Leads To Death </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-03-14 16:36:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Democratic lawmakers offer bill to repeal indefinite detention section of NDAA </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-03-08 19:25:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Obama to reelection campaign: Release the Biden </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-03-07 05:59:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Marijuana activists hoping they've finally found a Senate candidate to be their champion </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-03-06 21:54:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Obama scolds GOP candidates for 'casualness' in talking about war with Iran </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-03-06 21:21:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> AOL pulls advertising from Rush Limbaugh's radio program </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-03-05 18:05:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Delaware City Council Passes Resolution Urging 'Personhood' Rights For Sperm </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-03-02 21:46:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Obama Calls Sandra Fluke After Rush Limbaugh's 'Slut' Comments </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-03-02 19:48:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Allen West To Obama: Quit Bragging About Killing Osama Bin Laden </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-03-02 17:26:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Senators offer Obama a license to strike Iran. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-02-29 20:58:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Supreme Court looks poised to grant corporate immunity, rule that corporation can't be held accountable in federal courts for international human rights violations. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-02-28 19:04:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> WikiLeaks suspect Bradley Manning charged with 22 counts, including "aiding the enemy," faces potential life in prison </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-02-23 20:43:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Civil libertarian "hero" Russ Feingold is "pleased" U.S.-born cleric Anwar al-Awlaki was killed in a drone attack </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-02-22 16:28:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Russ Feingold: Electing A GOP Candidate Would Be A 'Threat To Our Country' </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-02-21 15:31:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
