<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject4585</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-22 03:48:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I may be incorrect but if I remember correctly, the manga and 1999 version claim that mito won gon in a court case. Even if ging didn't really try that hard to win it, he still didn't just drop him off with her. She fought for him  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-22 00:15:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Here's a list of all who made it to the final phase. Hisoka,    Illumi.   Bodoro.  Pokkle.        Killua.   Gon.    Leorio.     Kurapika.   Hanzo.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> HXH Exam Power Scales </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-22 00:09:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> There's a lot of speculation about power scaling in hunter X hunter due to nens potential. But we rarely go back to before nen. I want a ranking of those who were in the Hunter exam. Hisoka and illumi could use nen but we're only looking at physical skill and power. Of the people who made it to the final part of the exam, who do you think are the strongest and who's over who? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-21 13:44:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I don't know why but I feel like you aren't allowed 500 Ft from a school. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-21 13:41:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Being born perfect and having an assload of acne are different buddy. Well maybe I shouldn't expect an autistic teenager to know that. Hell, you can't even write a sentence right. "I'm more than human being" that sounds like some shit my 3 year old would say.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Future Devil Fruits </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-19 18:48:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I know this question is asked a lot but I always feel like these are some of the most fun posts. What devil fruit, that hasn't been used in the manga, do you want to see in later arcs. What devil fruits do you think would be interesting to the future plots. New devil fruit ideas! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-19 03:39:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> How is it possible that someone doesn't understand this is pure satire? Even if you believe in white privilege and its harm on society you should still understand this a satire. It is a joke that questions your beliefs. Maybe you can defend your beliefs and debate like educated humans instead of being an asshole trying to make a mockery of anything that goes against their belief.  Don't be a child and make sarcastic remarks back, be an adult and fight for your belief with honor.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-19 03:27:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> They basically said them self that this didn't prove anything by stating " brain as a whole instead of pointing out individual structures and features,". This is basically a nice way of saying "other variables? Nope they don't matter or inhibit our results.  What this one little feature is different between men and women? Doesn't matter because it isn't the whole brain" it's almost impossible to get a scan of an entire brain (instead of one part) that correctly shows everything needed to claim what these people claim.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-19 01:21:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> One of the restrictions could be that this can only be used in order to save another's life and when you use this ability your body is paralyzed ( or something similar) for a certain amount of time. It's a last resort finisher. Once you use it, you're out of the fight </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-19 01:15:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I got manipulator and mine would be similar to a space manipulation. It would be called Switch. Basically if My nens touched something in 6 minutes max then I can switch it with something else of equal size. If I had multiple throwing knives and threw them at a foe, my nen would touch the air that the throwing knife touched. So if he dodged the knife I could just switch it with the air and then it's in front of my enemy again. If I want to switch a person I would have to touch them and then be touching rubble or something similar to switch. It's a strategic ability best used when in a team. I have to say switch every time I switch something, I must be using GYO at all time in order to see what my nen touched and I have to know the name of what I'm switching. Thoughts? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The strongest marine group? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-17 19:29:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm using this as a poll. I'm trying to see which group the one piece fandom thinks is the strongest. These are all groups affiliated with the world government. The groups are the old timers(Garp and Sengoku), the admirals(fuji,kizaru, akainu, etc) the CP0(Unknown) or the goresei. This is individual power, the amount of people in the group don't matter. Which do you personally believe is the strongest? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-17 04:19:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> She looks like John travolta in pulp fiction </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-16 04:45:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Have your parents come out and declared you're the biggest failure since the bush presidency? If not, just look in their eyes when they graze over you. You'll see a wince of regret when the only ring they see on you is that ugly ass one on your fave.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-16 04:42:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I thought you were some fat ugly feminist until I saw the fedora on your jacket. At that point I realized you were a guy who's never succeeded at anything except jerking off to your 12 year old sisters friends </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-15 04:01:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Can we keep this fanbase clean of the BS and drama of other fanbases and only showcase this beautiful stuff. Fans supporting other fans and being changed for the better by the content creators. Funhaus is currently too pure for this internet world </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-14 22:24:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You look like a mixture of an incest baby  and a giraffe.  once you get your autism figured out get a neck reduction </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-14 22:14:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Damn Bellatrix from hairy potter got old. I feel like no one loves you and anyone who even acknowledges you are those who use you for their own gain. Whoevers taking the pic just wants to watch people fuck you up and that damn cats only on you so you'll get off your ass and feed it  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Some kid let me post him. Show him the mistake he made </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-14 22:04:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-12 21:47:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> People hate when anything change, some of my favorite Dwight and Jim moments are in the last two seasons. Micheal was the main focus for a long time so him leaving makes less cringe style comedy he brings to the table. But his absence completely creates chances for other characters to interact in ways we've never before seen. Sure if you're not emotionally connected with the characters you can quit. But the development in those final seasons are beautiful and the show feels unfinished without it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Preferences </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-12 20:03:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-08 04:09:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That was the issue I was having. I was hoping some of the people here could give ideas I'm not thinking about. I'm not a fan of minecraft but if that's the only choice I'd be fine with another minecraft series as long as it's as interesting as some of their older minecraft series </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Want a new long running series? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-08 03:59:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The creatures, in recent memory, haven't done a full on team lets play. They've had many in the past such as treetopia and the likes. I may only be speaking for myself here but I would enjoy another lets play long running type series with almost all the creatures if not all of them. If y'all could think of something they could do for this genre of video what would it be. What would y'all like for 2016 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Slow loading </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-08 03:34:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I had this game and was pretty far and well off last year but that ipad broke and I never redownloaded until now. I redownloaded it onto my phone but this loading time is unbelievable. Is there any way to speed it up? It's stuck at 50% for about 20 minutes. Please help  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-07 21:37:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If you had to choose one office member as a representative to fight an AH member, who would represent you in battle? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-07 05:34:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That makes a lot of sense dude. When I think of it, the way you explained the business model is a lot better than I was thinking with their being a difference and separation between the staff and creatures. I like that idea of everyone being equal  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-07 04:46:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> He's moving back to the UK and he has major issue with the fanbase. Well more like the fanbase with him, I like him. But if he somehow stayed apart of the creatures he would be similar to how spoon or ze were. Almost non existent  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Is a new creature possible? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-07 04:34:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So we all know Seamus is gone, dex is angry and leaving, and Kevin is also gone. Also who knows if spoon and ze are anything close to real creatures. But is it possible we can get a new creature with so many of our newer, and one old, members leaving. Someone who won't cause drama. Any suggestions </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-04 19:22:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Caesar is the next straw hat and I doubt he will be stronger than he already is. People like usopp and nami will never be vice admiral level. Oda has said that its in there character to be weak. Franky or brook are probably going to be only slightly vice admiral level. Look at smoker, nami or usopp can never be that strong. It would be game breaking to their character </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-04 16:05:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Definitely the paw fruit.  I can go on vacation easily, just touch some annoying kid and send him to China. So many possibilities  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
