<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject2779</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-16 11:36:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> My own one.

My ex was ontop, and she was wearing a mimmi mouse shirt and the ears on the shirt fit perfectly with her breasts and I noticed so I... for some reason went "hoho, plutooo" in the voice of mickey mouse... We laughed the rest of the day just by making funny disney references.
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What's your most awkward/funny sexual experience? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-16 11:24:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> As the topic suggests, write about your awkward/funny sexual experiences.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-16 10:09:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> And the B stands for Bus... so I guess I could just ride it to work? Man, the things technology does these days! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-15 10:26:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I eyed over this comment and read "Cremated" and quickly came to realise I should stop watching supernatural.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-15 10:04:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You're amazing. Didn't know about this. Wanna have kids? 3 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-14 15:30:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> A wild domain has appeared!  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-14 08:23:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thanks for the advice, I'll look into it when I have one of the less stressfull days!  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-14 08:19:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Did you have say that??? *gags*.. I'm just telling myself it's food.. just to.. you know... get a peace of mind. *Pukes* </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-14 08:16:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I would've done that... only that it was a 50 minute drive to the customer, so I decided not to.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-13 19:55:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I should've.. now that you mention it.
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-13 19:32:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Well, my company no longer have any private customers. Mainly office customer where shoes are allowed inside. :)
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-13 19:21:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Well... The hallway was clean and so the horror didn't start until i got inside.. and i felt it'd be a bad thing to be like.. "Hey.. I'm just gonna grab my shoes. I went home after work and threw away my socks, cleaned my clothes twice and showered about 5 hours. 
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Trial for the Trainee </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-13 16:29:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> TL;DR Co-workers sent me out into the most disgusting house ever. 

Before I got hired by my company they wanted me to go along as a trainee for a while, this meant i did all the boring jobs and the stuff noone else wanted to do. I didn't mind, amazing co-workers and funny stories every day, anyway, onto the story.

My company want to get rid of all private customers and only have other companies as customers but one day an older lady, lets call her $PrivCust, calls in and wants help. 
Normally she'd get denied but my co-worker knew who she was and thought it'd be fun to send me out on the worse mission ever, they never told me this how ever. 
I gladly accepted as this was the first mission for me where i were alone in the field. 
I drove the car where the GPS wanted me to.. far out into the forest and it felt weird that someone would live there.. I finnally came to the gps location.

A Old house and $PrivCust was on the doorstep waiting for me and as I walk through the door I get swarmed by 5 dogs.. Didn't bother me really, as soon as i took my shoes of i felt something under my feet... Dog food.. I noticed there were 3 cats and 2 birds. The animal food stuck to my socks as i walked after $PrivCust to take a look at the computer. 

The stench was incredible luckily I hadn't eaten anything so there was nothing to come back up. 

FINNALY reached the computer and it was a laptop that had something we call "Police virus" basicly locks the computer down and you can't use it. I Ask for a place to sit while I work. $PrivCust just points towards a desk filled with paper and... animal food. I place the laptop on top of it all, open the lid and notice that the safety plastic is still on the screen... Filled with dog food.
 
After a lot of work in safemode i realise this would take all day to fix so I just decide to let her reinstallation of the computer would be easier. And $PrivCust agrees and I start the reinstallation.. realiseing how slow the HDD is... it took 3 hours to reinstall win 7 x64... I sat in that stench, i begun getting really hungry, for 3 hours. 
$PrivCust offered me some food, I usually accept but I didn't trust her not to poision me. 

After the installation was complete I helped her with additional software and then there was wifi... ohgodwhy.jpg .. I asked to see the router to fetch the password. It was in the kitchen. I got up and started walking, feeling that food under my feet all the way, get to the kitchen and i see the router. I grab it to pick it up when I quickly realise it's glued to the desk in some way. I use my manly muscles and pull it up eventually.. and realise that the router was glued with a mix of sugar and syrup of sorts...

I looked at the password, sorted it on her PC, just said "It's working now, have a good day" ran to the door, got my shoes and ran out to the car.

When I got back to the company everyone was waiting for me, hand sanitizer at the ready. 

A day I will never forget.

Edit: Fixing typos. Tell me if i missed something else. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-10 13:33:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Lawn-enforcement. 

Hold that door for me please.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-08 16:19:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> How in ... do you get a girl to text you about those sorta stuff!?!? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-08 16:12:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah... 'bout that... Same here </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What were your first encounter with your partner? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-08 14:46:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> How did you find your partner or what's the first thing you remember doing with them that made you realise you were in love?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
