<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject3775</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> How are leap seconds introduced and added into Internet Time Services? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-30 18:46:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Date/Time controls on various OS's have logic built in for properly calculating when the extra day is introduced on the calendar, and for moving forward/setting back the clock an hour for daylight savings time. However, Leap Seconds are not predicted by an algorithm. Instead they are periodically declared as the Earth's rotation is detected as slowing or speeding up due to different factors.  How are these changes introduced into the master time servers for the internet? Some computers get a time feed directly from GPS satellites. Is there a separate update to the GPS satellites to broadcast the leap second updated time?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> At the end of the hunt, the trophy pic! </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-29 21:05:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> How long does it take to run a DNA match? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-23 21:03:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Who radicalized the terrorist Dylann Roof? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-22 16:14:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> When young people in western countries with an Islamic family background attempt terrorism or head to the middle east to participate in violent jihad, law enforcement and the press asked the question "How did these youths become radicalized?". Often it is found there was indeed an instigator either in the community or on the internet who recruited and cultivated them into their violent acts. In some cases these instigators have been arrested or killed in drone strikes. Dylann Roof's family has disavowed his apparently racially motivated violent act. Who then radicalized Roof? Should the FBI call in a drone strike to take out the manipulator(s) who egged him on? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Arizona City Sues FAA Asking For Nanny State Noise Protection </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-02 15:09:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Would an near lightspeed asteroid passing thru the solar system exert exceptional gravitational effects due to its increased relativistic mass? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-20 15:58:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What are valid justifications for an officer drawing a weapon? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-27 17:07:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> At a recent family gathering, a somewhat distant cousin showed up in his new sheriff's uniform. He's only recently hired in his first law enforcement job and is currently doing highway/traffic patrols. We live in the south and based on past conversations, I know he is highly prejudiced toward blacks.  In conversation he mentioned in his new job, he's yet to work a shift where he hasn't drawn his gun at least one time. While genuine fear for their lives is usually cited as the rationale in police shootings, drawing one's weapon as a precaution on a daily basis seems excessive. It also seems as if it could be viewed as threatening behavior that could trigger a violent response where one would not otherwise occur. Do police officers generally have to report they've drawn their weapons and/or provide a rationale for having done so in their reporting? Should such frequent drawing of one's weapon be considered a sign of excessive fearfulness that suggests someone is not right for the job? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> TV Station: Global warming getting serious, killing people in their homes </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-07 15:40:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Does the pressure at the bottom of a glacier transform the ice into new ice phase? --e.g. Ice II, Ice V, or Ice VI? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-27 14:01:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Recently took a guided trip out on to a glacier in Iceland. The guide indicated the ice had to be at least 50m thick in order for it to be classified as a glacier. That thickness is required before the ice at the bottom becomes plastic enough to begin flowing, part of the definition of a glacier.  Got me to wondering whether the plasticity is the result of a phase change in the ice. From the [ice phase diagram](http://www.uwgb.edu/dutchs/Graphics-Geol/ROCKMIN/MetPhaseDiagrams/IcePhase.gif)? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Are there Tacmars on the backs of signs leading to the Homan Square black site in Chicago? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-26 21:08:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> One the persistent post 9/11 conspiracy theories is that the government has setup secret detention facilities all around the country, and there are [secret marking on the backs of road signs called Tactical Markings](https://usahitman.com/secret-military-codes-hidden-road-signs/) called  "Tacmars" that encode directions to these sites. Since the guardian has now exposed a "blacksite" like detention facility in Chicago, has anyone seen any Tacmars leading to the area? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> How far does the L1 libration point get shifted by the Moon's movement around the Earth? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-10 16:51:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> TIL - A museum in Iceland has casts of the 15 erect penises of the Icelandic National Handball team, sculpted in silver to commemorate their 2008 silver medal in the Beijing Olympic Games. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-06 20:50:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Bloomberg wants paternalistic state to protect corporations from their own incompetence </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-12-22 00:29:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Science article in "the register" fails to use the word "boffins!" </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-12-20 03:29:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Since when does "Fiery" mean lots of gunshots? USA Today wants us to believe they burned to death? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-12-15 18:46:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> TIL Unattended chocolates have a half-life of 51 minutes in hospital wards </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-12-10 21:21:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What exactly is done onboard a rocket when it receives a destruct command? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-10-31 13:23:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Rick Scott fears "Fan Death" </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-10-16 14:24:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> MSL Curiosity has begun imaging the approaching Coment A1 Siding Spring </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-10-15 21:54:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Inaudible sounds can still hurt you </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-10-01 03:24:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Who paid CNN to make Gaddafi the face of Climate Change? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-09-23 14:28:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Study of censorship in china reveals government's deepest fear: collective action for any cause </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-09-10 21:56:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Are plant fruits zygotes, combining the characteristics of both the female and male (pollinating) plants? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-09-08 19:20:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Having a discussion with a friend, he asserted a mild pepper plant grown in close proximity to a hot pepper would have greater "heat" from the pollen of the nearby hot plants. My inclination would be to think any traits passed on by the pollinating plant wouldn't show up until seeds of the cross were grown into a new plant that flowered and grew fruit --ie the seeds are the zygotes of the two parents, but the fruit itself only has the characteristic of the female parent plant (yeah I know both plants both male and female, I'm using "female" in the sense  of the plant growing the fruit). Which is the correct view? Are the genes of the pollinating plant expressed in the fruit? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What is the black dome on the front of the Su-27 fighter cockpit? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-08-29 19:01:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Looking at the [pictures of the chinese Su-27](http://globalaviationreport.files.wordpress.com/2014/08/su-27.jpg?w=521)  that intercepted the US P-8 plane off the Chinese coast recently, got to wondering about what appears to be a sensor dome of some sort right in front of the cockpit. On an ABC news video displaying the photo, it appeared to have a greenish cast. Anybody have any idea what that component does on the jet. Here's another [photo](http://www.milavia.net/aircraft/su-27/gallery/su-27_28.htm) from an aircraft reference site. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> How has the Napa Quake altered stresses on the San Andreas fault? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-08-25 16:55:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> When an earthquake fault lets go in one area, the slippage relieves stress on the fault locally. However, in doing so it can have the effect of increasing the relative strain on other areas along the fault. How has the Napa Quake changed the stresses on the San Andreas fault? Have higher stress areas been moved closer to or further away from the heavily urbanized areas of the Bay Area? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Can eating cancerous tissue from other animals cause cancer in humans? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-08-22 20:29:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Who pays the taxes to support all the public sector jobs in the Harry Potter magical world? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-07-08 21:43:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> With the exception of a few small pubs and shops, all the jobs in the magical world seem to be public sector. From the highly respect Auror job that Harry hope so much to obtain down the driver of the night bus, all the jobs seem to be working for government agencies of one kind or another. Where is the tax base to support such a huge public sector burden? A butterbeer or many flavoured jelly bean must cost a fortune with all the VAT added on </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> War from Space: Falluja is burning today </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-06-16 14:36:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> New laser instrument can remotely sense alcohol vapor released my motorists' breath inside cars </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-06-09 18:57:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Study finds women who talk "Valley-Speak" (Vocal Fry) may have more difficulty getting jobs compared to those who don't. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-05-29 17:00:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What do the ideograms on this blood chit say? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-05-27 23:14:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Astronomers discover star likely birthed in the same stellar nursery as the Sun </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-05-14 21:10:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The term "Muggle" was originally 1940's british slang for someone who smoked pot </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-05-14 14:59:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> How can NASA stabilize the Mars Sample Return rocket? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-05-13 17:50:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Study contradicts theories of stellar formation in dust clouds. Clouds populate from the outside in rather than reverse. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-05-13 16:23:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> SF Marines Recruiting Poster; Great War of the Californias, USA, 2001. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-05-07 21:49:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Work Promotes Confidence, USA, 1936 </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-05-07 19:27:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Let us unite to Americanize America, USA, 1916 </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-05-07 19:12:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Poster promoting forest conservation, USA 1938 </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-05-06 18:42:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Scientists watch high-temperature superconductivity emerge out of magnetism </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-05-01 21:57:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> How does a saint become the "Patron Saint of fill in the blank?" </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-04-28 13:37:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> With the Catholic Church declaring two new saints this past weekend, got to wondering whether the church also names the subgroup or situation that they are to patronize? How long does it take for patronhood to be bestowed upon a saint?
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> They just don't make biking outfits like that anymore </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-03-21 14:33:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Want to find where MH370 went? Look for contrails </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-03-20 21:30:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Since the debris spotted in the Southern Ocean seem to be latest, best clue indicating the plane flew down the southern corridor, there's still some legwork that can be done to help find the plane. For debris to be down there, the plane must have followed a track down there. Jet aircraft contrails are often visible in satellite images. For example, here's an [image from the EOS satellite MODIOS] (https://earthdata.nasa.gov/labs/worldview/?switch=geographic products=baselayers,MODIS_Terra_SurfaceReflectance_Bands143,MODIS_Terra_CorrectedReflectance_TrueColor~overlays,sedac_bound time=2014-03-08 map=-77.479858,36.171753,-74.234497,38.467896) instrument of the US Mid-Atlantic Coast on March 8. The linear streaks of multiple airline contrails are visible, especially at the mouth of the Chesapeake Bay. The area where the debris were spotted is very lightly traveled by commercial aircraft. In warmer temperatures of tropical regions, jets often don't leave trails, but further south it is cold enough MH370 might have left one. Sometimes jet trails are also visible as clear tracks in existing cloud cover. Contrails above a cloud layer will also sometimes be visible as shadows on the lower cloud layer. Here's a [possible contrail ](https://earthdata.nasa.gov/labs/worldview/?switch=geographic products=baselayers,MODIS_Terra_CorrectedReflectance_Bands367~overlays,sedac_bound time=2014-03-08 map=81.310905,-53.341592,84.556267,-51.04545) in an area west of where the debris were spotted. The colors are from a different spectral band being viewed. I'd appreciate comments from weather knowledgeable redditors whether this is likely an artificial or natural cloud formation.  Others should look for and tag possible contrails in the MODIS data for March 8 as well as any other country's geosynch and polar orbiting weather satellite image data that can be accessed by the public </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Possible MH-370 Crash Site? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-03-10 17:40:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Why don't we run into each other? Study of pedestrian collision avoidance strategies in variety of collision aspects </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-03-05 00:21:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Another Martian meteorite with structures suggesting past biotic activity --i.e. "life" on Mars </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-03-03 21:45:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Study fails to find simple genetic basis for right or left handedness despite observation of left handedness running in families </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-02-28 00:22:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Are State Governments dictating how the National Weather Service forecasts warnings for their state? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-02-27 22:40:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> How do the scientists studying Kepler data for signs of planet transits determine they're not seeing sun (star) spots? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-02-27 14:41:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> With the announcement of a bunch of new planets discovered in the kepler data, multiple articles have included a statement indicating the biggest problem they have is distinguishing planet transits from an eclipsing binary star. In looking around for some information on Betelgeuse recently found a paper describing how scientists have imaged really big "sun spots" on Betelgeuse. Since stars rotate, such spots would traverse across the surface of the planet. Spots on the sun also appear, disappear, and reappear over multiple rotations. Timing of such appearances  could approximate the periodicity of a planetary transits. How is this possibility eliminated from Kepler analyses?
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> How does the neutronium in neutron stars decompose when it goes supernova? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-02-24 18:37:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Immunology in the skin - Educational and terrifying [Triggers](multiple) </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-02-18 20:23:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Does quality of the wind for offshore windfarms really outweigh the additional engineering costs associated with bringing the power back onshore with underwater powerlines? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-02-13 19:32:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> HSBC Bank may Collapse </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-01-25 23:21:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Why is Gravity assumed to have been the first force to separate from the unified forces in the early universe? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-01-20 20:23:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> In [various descriptions](http://hyperphysics.phy-astr.gsu.edu/hbase/astro/unify.html) of the chronology of the early universe, gravity is shown as the first force to separate from the unified forces. It is followed by the separation of the strong, then weak nuclear forces, leaving the four fundamental forces gravity, strong, weak, and electromagnetism.  However, if you look at the relative strength of the forces, they are in order strong, weak, electromagnetism, and gravity. In inverse order of the distance over which the forces operate they are again, strong, weak, electromagnetism, and gravity. Further, on a separate line of reasoning, when discussing the Planck length, one of the rationales for why it cannot be measured is that any apparatus big enough to measure it would be so massive it would collapse into a blackhole. Collapsing into a blackhole seems to be intimately tied to the force of gravity and the mass density of an object. Yet the early universe is postulated to have extremely high density. At the end of the inflationary era, all the mass of the universe was in a volume the size of a grapefruit. If gravity had indeed separated from the other forces, why would the early universe not have immediately collapsed into a blackhole? Is the assumption that gravity separated from the other forces first just a convenient assumption because we have no functioning/consistent theory of quantum gravity like we have for the other forces?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Very large pineapple bananas provided for scale </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-12-23 14:55:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> This Brussel sprout came from the top of the stalk. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-12-21 23:43:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Scammers purporting to be security department from credit card company? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-12-20 14:11:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> In the past few weeks I've received calls at my home from a robocaller purporting to be the security department from credit cards held both by my wife, and separate card held by me. The call opens with a statement that there has been suspicious activity on the credit card that needs to be verified. It then asked if the person speaking is my name or my wifes name. Voice recognition listens for "yes" or "no", then asks for verification of identity with personal information. Call for my wife asked for last 4 of SSN (did not provide). This turned out to be for a Target stores card. They did not admit to having made the call, but informed her of the Target breach. Call for me asked for birth date, then when this was provided, asked for zipcode. At this point I hung up. Called security number on the back of card (Chase Bank Visa) and ascertained they had not called. This appears to be targeted spearphishing seeking to get personal identity verification information for card number/name/phone number they already have obtained through some previous data breach or hack.  Has anyone else experienced these calls? Anyone heard of this as an ongoing scam.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Earth is only just within the Sun's habitable zone : Nature News   Comment </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-12-11 20:04:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> CNN sets cultural context for town voting on shooting down drones </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-12-11 18:41:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Apples   Oranges: Comparison of competitive eaters feeding rate by food type </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-11-22 12:39:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> TIL In 2008 foreign governments sent more than $450M in earthquake aid to China, including $100k from Samoa, a tiny poor island country </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-11-17 18:24:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Information On Endangered Red Wolf Killers In NC Reward Raised to $21000 </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-11-11 21:45:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Someone is killing the nearly extinct Red Wolves in the wildlife refuges of coastal North Carolina. [Washington Post] (http://www.washingtonpost.com/national/health-science/a-wolf-bounty-not-in-nc-in-a-switch-theres-a-reward-for-a-human-killer-of-rare-red-wolves/2013/11/10/328aef68-47dc-11e3-a196-3544a03c2351_story.html) article describes the events. [Fish and Wildlife Facebook Post](https://www.facebook.com/nctws/posts/540251139394968) gives points of contact to claim the reward  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> TIL - China has a strategic pork reserve </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-11-06 14:40:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Paper suggests universe will dissipate when random quantum fluctuation leads to collapse of the Higgs field </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-11-05 13:55:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Have eating a diet of foods high in antioxidant compounds ever been shown to have metabolic effect on oxygen radical levels in cells? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-11-04 23:00:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The bumper on this 50 year old abandoned car is bright and shiny </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-10-26 17:11:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Synaesthetics have reported higher levels of the oceanic boundlessness and visionary restructuralization during sex than control subjects </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-10-24 00:27:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Why does the news media keep repeating the Utah boyscout leaders lame alibi? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-10-21 23:07:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> How close does an asteroid have to come to the Earth to receive a really significant deviation in its near term orbit (1 or 2 decades)? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-10-18 15:09:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [CNN is going nuts today] (http://www.cnn.com/2013/10/18/tech/asteroid-near-pass/index.html?hpt=hp_t1) over an asteroid that passed 4M miles away last month. Meanwhile we've had several fairly significant rocks pass between earth and the moon (there was a big one passing the same day the Chelyabinsk meteor hit Russia). Afterwards, I haven't seen much analysis showing how much these asteroid's orbits have been deflected and how different they are afterwards. The JPL small body orbit browser is pretty clear that it shows only the two-body solution of the asteroid orbits with the sun. It seems unlikely an asteroid passing 4M miles away is going to end up at a significantly different place than it would have already been passing. Hence the question - how close does one really need to pass to the Earth before we really don't know where it is going to be in 10 or 20 years? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Buildings on the Brunei University campus look like the "Empire Strikes Back" walking tanks </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-10-17 22:17:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> My drinking straw at the radiology clinic today was a medical device </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-10-16 20:57:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Why does the republican party website get a .gov domain? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-10-14 22:59:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Saw a news photo the other day of a republican rally with a banner bearing the letters "GOP.GOV". I had been under the impression the .gov domain was limited to official governmental bodies. Thought it was fake, but sure enough gop.gov is the republican party official website. In contrast, the democrats website is www.democrats.org --i.e. consistent with what you'd expect for an organization.  Who decides what organizations can have a .gov domain, and who specifically let the republicans have one? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Could Obama declare martial law to avoid defaulting on the debt? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-10-07 22:41:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> With the current stalemate in DC, the country seems to be hurtling toward defaulting on payment of the national debt. If Obama declared martial law, would that give him the power to unilaterally raise the debt limit and avoid the default? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> How do heavy elements get created from exploding neutron stars? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-10-07 21:18:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Bluetooth heart rate monitor work when you're cycling </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-10-02 19:49:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Have been using my iphone 5 as my strava GPS for about a year now and really enjoy getting the statistics. Would like to add heart rate monitor for further data. However, a friend warned me the bluetooth signal for the heart rate monitor probably wouldnt connect when it has to pass through my body. Although Wahoo monitor with iphone is listed as supported with Strava, it likely depends on the connection geometry. While runners would typically keep their iphone in a holder on their upper arm, most bikers keep their phone in their jersey back pocket. Thus for biking, the signal has to pass through a big meaty water filled bag (your torso). Does anyone have experience with bluetooth connect heart rate monitors with iphone while cycling? Any issues? All is well? Any experiences positive or negative would be appreciated </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Is Curiosity Watching? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-09-27 19:21:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Over the next few days [Comet ISON will be making its closest approach to Mars] (http://imgur.com/eaj5HdK). [Recent MSL raw images appear to be looking at the night sky] (http://mars.jpl.nasa.gov/msl-raw-images/msss/00397/mcam/0397ML1652001000C0_DXXX.jpg). Is MSL looking for ISON?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Why the twists in the Illinois/Kentucky Boundary in the Ohio River? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-09-24 20:00:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Retracing an old boat journey in Google maps recently, I noticed some strangeness in the boundary line between the states in the river. For the most part it appears to boundary was set such that Illinois ended at the river's edge, but it deviates to the middle in some places. In a few places it twists into [curled over sections](http://goo.gl/maps/5YTO0) that don't look like they could have ever conformed to a shoreline. What's the story behind how this borderline is drawn? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Wizards sleeve? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-09-21 04:01:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> TIL - It is a felony to drive on a public highway with fuel in plastic soft drink bottles (as Rev Terry Jones learned on Wed) </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-09-13 14:26:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Why not target Assad personally? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-08-29 19:55:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If we're willing to attack Syria over their use of chemical weapons and we believe Assad was personally responsible for their use against the Syrian rebels, what are the arguments against designing our attack specifically as a decapitation strike against him personally? We attack terrorist leaders involved in planning terrorist strikes in which they take no direct part. What is the difference between those terrorist leaders and a head of state who orders the use of chemical weapons against civilians? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Who in the US benefits from a US attack on Syria? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-08-28 22:13:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  As tragic and heart wrenching as the war in Syria might be, there doesn't appear to be a case for over riding  US national interest in Syria. Despite this lack, various republican leaders such as John McCain have been advocating for intervention for months. So, taking the cynical view, which of McCain's paymasters are telling him to advocate for the attack?  Who would be the beneficiaries of a US attack on Syria? Is this mainly about the military spending that would be needed to sustain and replace the armaments used or are there other industries that would benefit too?   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Catastrophic event destroyed Mars atmosphere 4B years ago </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-07-19 16:17:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Because no one would understand if she said "turtle eater" </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-06-29 00:50:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Do the bureaucrats actually control US Government? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-06-24 16:10:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> In the 1980s when the US was in trade conflict with Japan over imports and US debt, it became popular to describe the limited power of the Japanese premier. The thrust of the articles was Japanese policies were actually controlled by a cabal of bureaucrats in Japanese ministries who were not accountable to the electorate. Over the course of the Obama administration, US government decisions and policies which conflict sharply with Obama's positions have come to light. Among these, the FDA decision to restrict sales of Plan B contraceptives, the failure to close Guantanamo, and the widespread electronic surveillance of the US population.  All these give rise to the question - are the actions of the US executive branch really under the control and management of the presidency? Do the bureaucrats, and the hidden hands of corporate, congressional, or other parties actually control actions and policies of the US government? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Costa Concordia lying on its side off the coast of Giglio in Google Maps Satellite view </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-06-20 20:33:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Illinois shows Kentucky its junk </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-06-12 23:11:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Internet video ad reps of reddit: why only one ad over and over? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-06-08 16:47:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Internet videos with commercials interspersed at intervals within a show appear to be modelled on the traditional TV commercial interruption paradigm; but with Internet video, they play the same damn commercial every time. I had thought this was just due to the scarcity of advertising sales for a new commercial market when Hulu first started; but as Internet tv has caught on, it appears to be deliberate. What is the thought process behind this in advertising circles?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Reporters use Google, find breach, get branded as hackers </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-05-21 23:39:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Islands in the Net </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-04-20 02:27:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Listening to the live coverage of the manhunt for the Boston bomber, I am reminded of the scene from Bruce Sterlings "islands in the net" where they're hunting down the rogue Russian ballistic missile sub. Wondering if I should go out on the street and cheer when they take him </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Can we identify any of the Sun's "siblings" in our galactic region based on isotopic fingerprints? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-04-15 23:09:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Reading recently about interstellar dust grains identified in some meteorites and from the Stardust mission samples, these grains were identified by the difference in isotopic ratios that the Sun inherited from the presolar nebula. Thinking about the pictures of multiple proto-stars forming in the Orion and Eagle nebula stellar nurseries, it seemed like these stars forming from the same nebular should share the same isotopic fingerprint. If this is the case, wouldn't there be stars out there that formed in the same nebula  as the Sun? Have we identified any starts that appear to have the same isotopic fingerprint as our own solar system, indicating they formed from the same nebular 4.x billion years ago? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> First it was sympathy for the ruined football careers of rapists now coddling violence prone basketball coach. Where does CNN get its values? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-04-05 00:06:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What negative associations with the Christian Right in response to their opposition to gay marriage? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-04-01 13:52:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> In what appears to be an organized campaign, Christian Right politicians are attempting to whip up popular opposition to same sex marriage by grouping it with beatiality and pedophilia as if such associations were a natural common classification of all three activities. Turning the tables, what are some similar, natural associations with the Christian Right that illustrate the same principle? Baptists drinking the blood of sacrificed babies comes to mind, but a bit awkward to use in a sentence.

EDIT
So this was mainly in response to Ben Carson's statement 
"Well, my thoughts are that marriage is between a man and a woman. It's a well-established, fundamental pillar of society and no group, be they gays, be they NAMBLA [North American Man/Boy Love Association], be they people who believe in bestiality. It doesn't matter what they are. They don't get to change the definition

His words weren't said in isolation. The attempts to equate consensual gay love with bestiality and child sexual abuse have been going on for months. I'm looking for something like "Organizations with a history of child abuse, blackmail, and extortion, such as Catholic Dioceses, should not have a voice in determining the morality of laws up for consideration any more than Mafia would be allowed to affect financial disclosure laws" </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Is there any correspondence between fluctuations in the cosmic background radiation and the megastructure of the visible universe? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-03-23 18:50:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Explanations of the variation in the cosmic background radiation say it is the imprint of quantum fluctuations in the early universe. Those same variations are said to have seeded the distribution of matter which gave rise to it's clumping together into stars, galaxies, and galaxy clusters. Is this all pure theory? Or is there some correspondence that can be drawn from hot and cold spots in the CBR in the sky and galaxy clusters in those same places in the sky? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The Robopocalypse starts with a whimper, not a bang </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-03-21 01:16:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Stars orbiting the Milky Way's central black hole are too young: should not have been able to form nearby, aren't old enough to have traveled </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-03-20 21:39:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The window design on this church looks like a cat </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-03-18 01:29:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> US Constitution: Appropriation Bills Introduced In the House. Boehner: Senate Get Off Your Ass To Save Mine </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-02-26 20:36:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> TIL - professions with the highest degree of psychopathic tendencies are CEOs, Lawyers, Media Journalists, Salespeople, and Surgeons. Why am I not surprised? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-02-25 16:07:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> How can do asteroid exploitation companies plan to smelt and refined metals in space? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-02-19 22:25:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Two different companies have recently announced plans to begin mining asteroids for rare metals. Composition of meteorites from the big Russian meteor is being described as 10% iron mixed in with olivine and sulfites. Science fiction has painted a number of scenarios for smelting asteroids in space, mostly by using focused solar energy and exotic methods of steering molten metals with directed magnetic fields. Have the companies that are proposing to start mining asteroids in the next 20-30 years provided any details for how they plan to extract the mined materials in the weightless and vacuum environment of space? Is it possible without inventing new technologies or boosting incredibly large factories into orbit? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Could we lasso an asteroid during a near earth encounter? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-02-08 16:16:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Asteroid 2012 DA14, discovered only about a year ago, will make the closest approach of any asteroid of its size since we started seriously worrying about collisions. It is a shame we couldn't have a space probe prepared in that time to latch onto the rock when it passed so close by. Understanding at least part of the problem in doing so is the lack of time to get a spacecraft into position and accelerated to the velocity at which it will be passing the earth. Would it have been possible to attach a space craft to a  net hooked to a tether on the spacecraft to essentially lasso the passing rock and yank it along with the asteroid. Do we possess any materials strong enough to withstand such the  shock of such a capture? Assuming the spacecraft was traveling in an orbit aligned with the asteroid's trajectory, how many G's would the spacecraft experience in such a capture?
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Metaphysics discussion on origins </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-02-08 14:44:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Maybe the flying cars they promised us really just around the corner </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-02-07 02:33:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What does it mean when NASA cites the Mars rovers were only designed for 90 day mission.  </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-02-06 19:15:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> China's version of Radar Lock-on to Japanese ship: Just a missile launch military drill. How reassuring.  </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-02-05 15:28:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The "term" crusade is apparently as weighted in Islamic countries as "jihad" is in Western nations. Peaceful compromise would be to retire both words from common lexicon </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-02-04 19:17:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> So what's next? Will 7th Day Adventist employers be able to deny coverage for vaccinations to their employees? Can Jewish employers demand all employees get circumcised? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-02-01 20:38:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Is the mitochondrial DNA in a single human cell the same for different mitocondria? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-01-22 02:12:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Mitocondria organelles in animal cells are thought to have evolved originally from symbiotic bacteria that took up residence in other cells. They have their own DNA separate from the DNA in the cell neucleus. Only our mothers pass us mitochondrial DNA in the egg; but an egg cell has multiple mitocondria. Do each of them have identical DNA? Is it possible for different populations of mDNA to exist within a single individual and get passed down to children in different proportions? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Sciences solves one of life's eternal questions </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-01-09 19:05:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Creationist appointed chairman of congressional committee controlling NIH science funding </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-01-08 22:54:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Andromeda Galaxy Dwarves Form A Ring </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-01-04 18:59:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> By the same argument, publishing pedophile addresses endangers public safety </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-01-04 03:16:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The man with the most interesting poop in the world </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-12-24 17:18:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Why was Nasa concerned the Grail spacecraft might crash in "culturally significant" areas on the Moon? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-12-19 15:43:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Nasa recently the Grail mission spacecraft, Ebb and Flow, into a mountain near the lunar north pole. The spacecraft were flying in a fairly low orbit (14 miles) and their fuel nearing exhaustion when Nasa decided to crash them. One of the reasons cited for doing so was the spacecraft orbits would eventually decay and Nasa did not want them to crash in a culturally significant area, like one of the previous moon landing sites. 

Why was orbit decay an issue? Isn't the Moon's atmosphere so close to total vacuum that orbital drag is non-existent? What kind of timeframe for natural orbital decay would we be talking about? Years, centuries, millennium? 
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> White House cites Fed Controlled Substances Act as pre-empting state marijuana laws. CSA rationale: drug use is inter-state commerce.  </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-12-06 21:29:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Are significant numbers of military members illegal voters in the states where they live? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-09-30 17:36:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> With the recent controversies where republican controlled states have sought to purge the voter rolls of "illegal voters", most of whom happen to be in heavily democratic party voting populations, it got me wondering about military voters, of whom there are quite a few in swing states such as virginia and colorado. Military members can choose to be residents of any state in the country, called their "home of record" in their military records. Many military members take advantage of this to make their home of record one of the states that do not have a state income tax. Yet they live in and consume government services such as public schools, roads, etc. funded by state taxes in the state where they reside. Military members are also supposed to only register to vote in their "home of record" state, voting with absentee ballots. Military members also tend as a group to vote heavily republican. So in these republican controlled states where they have been seeking to purge the voter rolls of illegal voters, have they been cross checking voter rolls with military records or state income tax records to determine whether military members have registered to vote in the local state elections without changing their home of record? Does the military verify its members have not registered to vote in a state different from their home of record? Is this a potentially large population of illegal voters?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Is a star's solar system orbital plane determined by its galactic orbital plane?   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-09-14 19:15:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Looking up at the summer triangle last night I realized it contains both the star, Vega (or Altair, I've seen them both cited) to which the solar system is currently headed, and the Kepler probe field of view. Kepler detects planets that pass between their primary star and the Kepler probe/Earth/Solar System. Thus it can only see planets whose orbital plane is in line with the direction to the earth. Is it only a coincidence that we're looking at stars along the line in which our own star is traveling in its galactic orbit? Or, is there some reason to believe the orbital planes of the solar systems are lined up along their galactic orbit/velocity vectors? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Scientists developing technology to turn humans into batteries to power robots of the future </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-03-13 14:16:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
