<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject2622</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-02-11 09:29:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Oh man. I hope you don't get gunned down by someone looking for that POS.  I'd change my name.

Dude, this is a legit concern.  Then again, I noticed you used the word "favourite"... You're not American, are you? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-02-11 09:20:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You're probably white too. It's like you're complete opposites! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-02-11 08:57:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So is/does/was your ass! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-02-11 08:28:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hear You Me - Jimmy Eat World </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-02-11 08:22:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Don't be a fucking douche. Be genuine and polite. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-02-11 08:14:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> PM me if you want. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-02-11 08:09:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm in. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-02-11 08:07:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm not going to give you fuel for your sick sexual pleasure! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-02-11 07:59:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You don't need "lines", just talk to us. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-02-11 07:56:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I was a virgin til I was 21. My brother was a virgin til he was 23.

But when I finally got laid, we fucked for an hour and a half straight except the three times she stopped me because she came. 

Your day will come and it will be fucking magnificent. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-02-11 07:45:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I saw this and I was like "I hope this is a fucking joke"

Now I just feel bad.

Have you ever assaulted anyone? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-02-11 07:34:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I live a few minutes from Punxsy. You couldn't pay me to be there. haha </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-02-11 07:16:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Jefferson! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-02-11 07:15:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If you don't know how to drive a standard/manual, fucking learn. You get better gas mileage and you have better control.

Do research before you buy because cars have VERY different maintenance costs.  Learn about your car. Follow maintenance guidelines. They're recommended for a reason. Too many times I've seen people destroying engines because the cost of a new timing belt or head gasket was just too expensive. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-02-11 07:05:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I miss Leno... It sucks that they gave his spot to Conan. OH WAIT! Assholes... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-02-11 07:01:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> In PA: "There's a deer about 25 yards ahead! We can get him!" </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-02-11 06:02:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I live next door to my parents also.  I'm always surprised when I hear this but it's hardly uncommon.

My older brother bought our neighbors house fairly cheap because of some personal stuff and the lady needed out so she put in a good word with the bank and she only wanted what she absolutely needed... And come on, free food next door 24/7?  I've gone grocery shopping maybe three times since I moved. (I usually just have my mom pick me up some when she goes because I work crazy hours). But she also says thing like "Oh, we already have some of that."   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-02-11 02:55:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> TWIST:  It's your neighbor </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-02-11 00:34:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I didn't have to do the talking, but I was on the scene of a fatal car accident and the girl's phone started ringing. I picked it up to hand it to the trooper and right there on the screen... "Mom"

It breaks my heart every time I drive on that road. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-02-11 00:25:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What kind of homeless?

Living on the street or living with you? the answer means the difference between upvote and downvote... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-02-09 19:26:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's sounds like your dog is a rapist... Press 3 if he's watching you.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-02-09 03:22:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I don't suppose you know where I can find D.B. Cooper? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-02-09 02:39:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I think there were two or three that fully answered the question.  I still enjoyed all the stories though. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-02-09 02:37:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I can't believe I forgot about this... 

There is a sort of gated community near my house. Anyone can get in, you just gotta say "Hey, I'm taking my friend home" or something at the guard house. Even just keep your car rolling slowly and wave and they won't stop you. 

Anyway. My cousin and his buddy were In there one night cruising around and drinking after a long day of moving him into his new place. They still had some stuff in the back seat including a 32 inch tv from his bedroom. This is a BIG place and it's built in a forest. People get lost in there all the time. He managed to find the camp ground and knew that if he stayed there he'd be able to find his way out in the morning. A while later, security rolls up. Apparently there had been a few break ins and thefts at the campground. The security guard sees the tv in his backseat and calls the real cops before he even gets out of his car.  He walks over to my cousin and asks what they're doing and of course, he just says they're cruising around. The guard smells alcohol and asks if he can have a look in the car my cousin says "No" because of the alcohol, not knowing the guard is looking at the tv.  after that I'm not sure what happened but he ended up only getting a drunk in public out of the stop.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-02-09 02:23:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What do you consider to be the greatest moment of your career?  Or your life? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-02-09 02:06:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I've tried talking the guys into a calender fundraiser... No dice.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-02-09 02:04:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This could be a HIMYM episode from Ted, Marshal, and Lily's college days. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-02-09 02:03:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> We found him! The sting operation worked!  You're under arrest, sir! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-02-09 02:02:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That, good sir, is a fine vase. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-02-09 02:00:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm a male that has had my share of fights and almost died of alcohol poisoning at 19 and I can't stomach it anymore. And the car was never close enough to identify the headlights until I slowed down which was about thirty seconds before I got pulled over.

 And I happen to have a lot of money, so I drive a nice car. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-02-09 01:54:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I was an 8th of a mile in front of then until i realized they weren't going to let up, then I slowed down hoping they would catch up and pass me. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-02-08 21:11:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Fucking. Epic. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-02-08 16:17:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That would be sweet. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-02-08 16:14:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Do you get paid for court appearances, or is that like a "take the day off" kind of thing? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-02-08 16:04:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That is some shit. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-02-08 16:04:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Good point. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-02-08 16:03:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Good guy Policeman. Gives you a ticket, lets you off by not showing up to court. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-02-08 16:02:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I sent you a PM </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-02-08 15:57:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You don't have to rub it in... Our government is full of prudes. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-02-08 15:56:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That's awesome. mopeds are the shit. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-02-08 15:55:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Any suggestions for ways to stay awake? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-02-08 15:52:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I hope it's framed on your wall. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-02-08 15:51:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> How do you refrain from flipping the fuck out of morons that make your job harder? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-02-08 15:50:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I know a guy that almost got nabbed for DUI because he was sleeping it off in his back seat but this saved his ass... "Officer, I lost my keys about 4 hours ago. I couldn't go anywhere if i wanted to." </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-02-08 15:47:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Their friends make me wish I had friends. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-02-08 15:46:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> "Yes, operator? Fetch me the police." </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-02-08 15:45:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I wonder if anyone has ever tried turning stolen drugs in to their vehicle/ home insurance... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-02-08 15:42:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I would like to hear your name now. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-02-08 15:40:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Whats the difference whether you stay awake or go to sleep? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-02-08 15:37:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> There are too damn many subreddits... I never know half of them exist until I post something. We're having a lot of fun here though so it's not all bad. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-02-08 15:36:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm pretty sure you're the only person to actually answer the question.  

That's what I was afraid of.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-02-08 15:34:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Absolutely.  I think we may need to start a subreddit for AA meetings though.. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-02-08 15:29:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I imagine a lengthy silence.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-02-08 15:28:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Oh yeah, it's here. haha </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-02-08 15:27:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thanks. I'll try. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-02-08 15:24:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> EXACTLY! It's shit like this... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-02-08 15:23:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I've heard something to that effect, but I'm not sure. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-02-08 15:21:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Racing is awesome.  I can't wait until spring.

Being a firefighter is fun, but you have to be able to accept that you can't save everybody.  It helps to remember that you being there could mean the difference between someone living and dying.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-02-08 15:17:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Good on you. A lot of people would have just brushed it off and never apologized. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-02-08 15:15:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I like your style. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-02-08 15:14:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> He was just making sure everyone could see who she was pointing at.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-02-08 15:13:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I guess I do have a certificate too. EVOC I took it because I'm a firefighter. I also race cars (on a track). </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-02-08 15:10:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I've heard that song... [This is it, right?](http://www.youtube.com/watch?v=skFWsc_-i14)
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-02-08 15:08:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> And that my friends, was the tastiest beer test_tickles has ever had. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-02-08 15:05:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Gotta love the classy ones. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-02-08 15:04:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What makes you qualified to make you analysis of deadly car accidents?

I'm not sure what it is. It's not technically a thing I don't think... but here is the gist of it. 

If you stood the two of us on a street corner with our eyes closed then we opened our eyes for five seconds,  I'd be able to tell you a shitload of what's happening on the street. whereas others might just have time to process what is happening directly in front of them. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-02-08 14:57:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> usually you can get away with it by saying "I was just trying to keep pace with the other drivers" </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-02-08 14:53:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I have a unique qualification.  I have the ability to process what I'm seeing a lot faster than the average person.  If I'm going any less than 45 mph I get bored and lose focus thus making me a more dangerous driver at slow speeds. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-02-08 14:51:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Department of Transportation.  They're sole purpose is to fuck your day up...

Their job is to take samples of truck traffic on highways to make sure that companies are following health restrictions for drivers, weight and maintenance requirements for equipment, and check for leaking fluids for environmental safety. What else would you like to know? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-02-08 14:47:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> In the US we call those DUI checkpoints. And they position cruisers to give chase if anyone decides to turn around. 

Funny story. I race dirt cars on the weekends and I got stopped at a checkpoint on my way home, still wearing my fire suit with my helmet in the passenger seat.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-02-08 14:42:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's only impolite if you're endangering others. I was not. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-02-08 14:41:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That sucks. You should transfer. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-02-08 14:37:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> But at what cost?! I can't bear the shame. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-02-08 14:31:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> When I was young I wanted to be a lawyer.  Let me know if you ever need me.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-02-08 14:19:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> How difficult was finding a job in law enforcement? 

Aside from my dad's business, that's the only thing I've ever wanted to do. Now that the postal service is kind of sinking and I've been looking into it more, I've found that it's hard to get a job around here because the state is looking to hire women and minorities. But what they don't understand is that we just don't have anything but white people around here and not many women are interested. And the small towns won't hire any full time officers because they don't want to pay benefits. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-02-08 14:10:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> OR there's that chance that the driver is a sadistic bastard that will actually speed up... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-02-08 14:07:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> And probably got pissed for being arrested behind a dumpster. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-02-08 14:06:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That's insane. I'll never pee again. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-02-08 14:04:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> One does not simply "reply"  to a police officer's command. haha </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-02-08 14:03:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> criminal - "I HAVE THE RIGHT TO REMAIN SILENT, YOU KNOW!"

Cop - "Please..." </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-02-08 14:02:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Have you heard about the cop that smoked some confiscated MJ with his wife and then called 911 because  "Time is going sooo slow"? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-02-08 14:00:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You know it! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-02-08 14:00:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> When you're on subject2622 thread, you're always going to get an upvote, and usually a reply. That's how I roll.  Thanks for the video! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-02-08 13:58:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That's awesome.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-02-08 13:54:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Volunteers. Are there any other kind? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-02-08 13:52:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Sweet sweet justice... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-02-08 13:51:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Your brother is a hero. Accidental or otherwise. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-02-08 13:50:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> My book would be titled:
"What I may have done that I don't think I did, but the police are telling me that I probably did so I guess I'm just going to roll with that" </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-02-08 13:49:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Agreed. 

And to you as well. I just got home from the first half of my work day and am preparing for a nap, myself.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-02-08 13:47:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> No. His friend called him and asked him to come pick him up from the party.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-02-08 13:46:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> They never got any type of "official" speed.   I'm also a firefighter and an all around good guy.  I've never been fined for speeding either and I've been pulled over 3 or 4 times in my 7 year driving career. Once was because some new local guy thought I stole my own car though.  I think every time I get caught speeding they check to see if I've been fined before but when they see that I haven't they assume that I'm not constantly speeding... If that makes any sense. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-02-08 13:40:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The fuck? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-02-08 13:40:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Technically you can, but it's kind of a dick thing to do. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Lawyers/police of Reddit, What is the WORST way you've seen someone incriminate him/her self when they were actually innocent? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-02-08 01:38:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm scared that if I'm ever accused of something, I'm going to go down for it because I try to explain things all the time and just end up digging myself in deeper and deeper.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> I walked into a bathroom stall at work. When I turned around to leave...  </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-02-05 13:19:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Why does a glass of water that you leave sit develop tiny bubbles along the surface of the inside of the glass? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-02-05 09:46:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I imagine it has something to do with the fact that water contains oxygen. Or due to tiny spaces in the glass. Not important, just a random question I had. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Fall Out Boy is BACK! </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-02-04 21:19:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> This is what I think happened to the lights! </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-02-04 06:36:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Most of us haven't... </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-02-03 07:18:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Because I can, not because it's the cool thing to do now. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-02-03 06:16:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> He's just a little... Oh Shit. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-12-23 02:23:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> This is me in 9th grade.  </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-12-07 03:29:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Found this in one of my elementary school yearbooks...  </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-11-20 05:19:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Donavon Stinson looks like Grumpy Cat. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-11-16 00:38:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> This is a bad month... </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-11-09 23:54:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
