<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject4368</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-30 16:05:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Obama drone bombed the shit out of the middle East for 8 years and I never saw out of the american public so much as a single complaint. You want to talk about inconvenience? Try being dead. Sure this new policy is terrible. Don't get me wrong. But why does it seem like Trump can do no right, but Obama can do no wrong (atleast in the eyes of a liberal). Trump's not been in office a week and everyone's jumping down his throat. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-29 19:11:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I loved this game so much! I was hesitant to get it at first. Doom 3 was too slow for my tastes and since Duke Nukem Forever, I don't really buy into these rehashings. Then I saw this guy on youtube do a review on it. After that I was hooked. Wish I could remember the channel - the video was great: he ran around his apartment or whatever shooting demons with a shotgun. It was great! :D Now its gonna bug me until find the video... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-29 18:34:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Special RX with Michael Rappaport and Josh Peck. I saw it around the same time as Kick Ass came to theaters. It follows same guideline almost: Regular Joe Schmo comics nerd decides to fight crime. What makes this one unique is how everything is presented as he gets his powers and decides what to do with them; all the while the audience is unaware whether or not it's all in his head or it's really happening, and the editing is superb with funny moments interspliced in the dramatic moments. Add a dash of science fiction and time travel and you have one hell of a budget superhero movie. Even with movies like Super and Kick Ass and other "homegrown" hero archetypes in films, this one truly shines on its own. It got some bum reviews apparently on release but I don't see why - it's fantastic. I'd like to see a YouTube review on it personally. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-29 17:47:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm 28 and still want this. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-28 01:02:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Shut up, bird. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-28 00:24:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Speaking of low budget time travel films I found this short one on YouTube awhile back that doesn't look like it hadn't had much of a budget at all 
https://youtu.be/uHywX3DbLRQ it's not horribly long. The FX are pretty cool for being no budget. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-27 15:38:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I wish I could downvote lazy Trump jokes more than once. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-26 16:34:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Why is Tim Meadows not the unofficial mascot of everything yet? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-26 16:31:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Since when did everything pixel art just become "8bit"? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-25 16:03:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Trip trip trippity Dem old tripping balls </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-25 06:06:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If you have stigmatisms, you can barely see the 3d effect much anyway. You just get a head ache instead. :/ </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-21 20:31:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The best part of reddit is discovering something about yourself you didn't know you should have known but didn't.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-21 20:21:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That's because all those people without jobs refused to attend this time. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-21 20:09:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> this is really really good! maybe a couple thigns tho - the dialouge seemed off at some parts and some shots seem a bit blurry at times but good job! i hope to see more! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
