<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject8593</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-07-17 23:00:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Aw, thank you! I love Bon Bon, her hair reminds me of a vintage pin-up somehow, so she just had to be made. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-07-17 22:51:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thank you! Alice is probably my favourite of the bunny designs so far. Alice in Wonderland was a huge inspiration for creating them, so it made sense to pay homage. :) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-07-17 22:48:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thank you! The ponies are probably my favourites to create (the beanie ones anyway) as I get to go back and forth from all my equipment - sewing machine, embroidery machine and hand sewing - so it keeps things interesting. They're also a challenge, and I do love a challenge. :) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-07-17 22:44:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thank you! Making them makes me smile, so I'm happy other people find them cute too! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-07-17 22:43:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That's the one! Thanks! :) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-07-17 22:41:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Aw, thank you very much for your compliments, they mean so much! I'm sorry about your struggles with depression/anxiety. I did find that the meds completely robbed my creativity. My main hobby had been writing ever since I was a little girl and I was determined to become an author up until I started on the medication. But as soon as I started taking the meds there was just nothing. Just a blank space in my brain. I felt like it had totally stolen my whole sense of purpose in life - if I couldn't write, I couldn't live! 

So I actually took up crocheting with the advice from a friend who was also suffering with depression at the time and found that it helped her. The monotony helped me relax and slowly over time I found my creativity seeping back in a whole new hands-on way. 

I came off medication at the end of last year, but I've still not been able to write a word of fiction ever since. Every time I think about writing or try to write I actually feel the anxiety returning, churning in my stomach, so I don't try any more. I fear it's forever linked with that terrible mental state now. Which is upsetting considering it was my whole life for over twenty years, but at the same time, I'm so grateful with what I have right now and the ability to create SOMETHING at least. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> A year and half ago I was diagnosed with severe depression and anxiety which destroyed every single part of my life. I taught myself to sew cute plushies to fill the void and force a smile. Here's a few of the things I've made. (I'm almost 100% better now! Sewing saved my life!) </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-07-17 21:58:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-07-15 21:11:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I think your prices are perfect. Your work really is art! People often underestimate the amount of work that goes into handmade items and that's quite sad. Just goes to show how comfortable - and maybe blinded - we've become with cheap manufacturing.

I also sell plushies on Etsy and I've just recently quit my job to take it up full time. I regularly have clients playing between 25 - 125 ($40 - $214) for my items.

Keep up with the amazing work, your plushies are adorable! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Last week was Bon Bon, this week I made Fluttershy! </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-07-13 20:30:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-07-06 11:49:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Ah, that is unfortunate! But thank you for the compliments! I'll definitely be up for a commission in the future. Plushing is literally my full time job, so commissions are always open (for anything!). Gotta pay those bills! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Bon Bon Beanie Plush! </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-07-05 21:28:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-07-05 21:26:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This exact Bon Bon is on ebay at the moment: http://www.ebay.com/itm/111400373771

And I also take commissions through my etsy store: https://www.etsy.com/uk/shop/thetinyteaparty </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-07-05 21:20:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thank you! I've done a ton of standing ponies recently and just felt the need to draft up a new plush pattern and try something a big different. :) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-07-05 15:29:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thanks. :) I'm really proud of how she turned out. That mane and tail were a pain to sew! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> First Bon-Bon Beanie Plush! What do you guys think? :) </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-07-05 11:10:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-07-05 00:11:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thank you! Yes, I embroidered his eyes and little paw pads straight onto the fabric. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Handmade Mew beanie plush. I'm pretty proud of how he turned out. :) </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-07-04 23:58:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
