<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject2004</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-14 18:23:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The culture of the country's that these groups inhabit need to change. Right now, they are funded by opposing governments who want to fight over petty shit that is probably thousands of years old. Shiite vs. Sunni, Kurdish, vs. whoever, blah blah. They are more concerned with their tribal fights than ridding the regions of terrorism. And I think you're severely downplaying the effect that these "30k" members have had on the areas where they operate.https://www.nytimes.com/interactive/2016/03/25/world/map-isis-attacks-around-the-world.html?_r=0

They're not a group that you can just ignore.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-14 18:18:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> No, we created the vacuum when we didn't make a 50 year plan to ensure a stable government was put into place. We shouldn't have gone to Iraq in the first place, since there are enough things to spend money on here (homelessness, aging infastructure, education, high speed rails, etc). But we did go, so we should have stayed. 

If people want to allow governments to remain in charge that chop their citizens hands off for stealing, execute gay people and adulterers, lock women up for driving, drop gas on minorities, that's something they'll have to live with I guess? Like I said before, the Western world is fucked either way. Either you do nothing and everyone flips out that nothing is being done to prevent these horrors (Sudan, Ethiopia, etc) or you drop a fuck ton of bombs and everyone flips out that you interfere in another country's affairs. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-14 18:12:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If no one does anything about them? It absolutely will happen. Do you think they'd just be content to run around in the desert killing each other when they could make it to say.... Paris, Sweden, London by simply getting on an airplane or a boat unimpeded? The only thing that will slow them down is bombs and psychological warfare unfortunately. Once they are beaten down enough, the culture needs to be changed, which will take at least 2-3 generations. The US has bombed a lot of people that they had no business bombing, but this is not one of those situations. 

Also you have to acknowledge the catch 22 that the United States finds itself in every day. The most powerful military in the world either does nothing and gets chastised for a lack of action, or we do take action and everyone labels the United States as warmongers. So, fucked either way. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-14 17:54:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah you'll be fine. I've smoked hundreds of pounds of meat with it, never had a problem. I don't prefer the taste of mesquite but I don't dislike it either. Cherry is my favorite, when I can find it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-14 17:51:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The bomb was dropped on ISIS. We could just leave them alone if you want? In 50 years they'll make it to whatever country you're in and start raping the females in your family and decapitating the males. Oh and they think it's entertaining. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-14 16:55:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> To be fair, she probably shouldn't have asked in the first place! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-14 05:20:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> From a wheelchair. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-14 04:16:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> San Antonio vs. Boston. Spurs win again, Pop, Ginobili and Parker all retire. Tim Duncan becomes the next coach. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-14 00:53:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> My buddy did something similar. This girl asked to sit in his lap and he said "this chair won't hold both of us." I looked over in disbelief, then he looked at me in disbelief, then she looked at him with murderous eyes and we bailed out as fast as we could. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-14 00:24:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> My grandmother has dementia. Mom took get to get her hair cut a few months back. Out of nowhere, in the middle of the haircut she starts singing "eeny meeny miney mo, catch a n***er by the toe". The lady cutting her hair was black. Luckily she had been warned beforehand that Grammy has dementia and she continued with the haircut. She got a big ass tip. Same granny also called my wife a prairie n***er (she's an Indian). When she dies it will be for everyone's good. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-13 20:33:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah but he's in Canada. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-13 17:47:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> We just won 5 in a row, GTFO! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-12 03:17:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I saw him years ago when the Lakers came to Dallas. Him, Kobe and Nash were putting shots up, i was right by the court with my best friend. We yelled to Metta that we loved him and he came running over, thanked us for coming and had a huge smile on his face. Also got to talk to Kobe, Nash and Elton Brand for a minute. They were all wicked nice, but Metta genuinely seemed excited to say hi to us. That moment has stuck with me. Dude is awesome. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-11 23:17:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hmmmm.... They're getting close to Vegas buffet prices. Is there a time limit?? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-11 05:47:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Beats  the hell out of pecan lodge! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-11 04:56:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You're welcome. If you've got any other BBQ related questions let me know:) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-11 04:46:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> $17.99 all you can eat. It's twenty minutes from my house. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-10 18:48:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I play at Casino Royale, it's a great little casino with $5 craps. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
