<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject8863</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> She is like a cat, she licks feet and the inside of shoes, she only shows affection when she needs to eat, poop, or pee. Meet Ghira. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-09 02:32:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> 2k telvsion gaming pc in a small form factor </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-09 01:34:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Looking to build something with the 2k potential 4k gaming for the living room. Never built a MiniATX system and haven't had a full fledge computer beyond laptops in over 10 years. Want to have it be quite and easy to move around and fit into a shelf on my ikea entertainment center. 

I get a discount for Intel so wanna build around that and just don't know about any other parts like power supply or miniATX board. Wanna use Nvidia GTX1080 as I have worked with them for CUDA purposes and compute jobs and I actually like the way they do the drivers updates.

http://www.ikea.com/us/en/images/products/lappland-tv-storage-unit-white__0246280_PE385389_S4.JPG </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Is it just me or did they base the huge giant ghost on Dan Aykroyd </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-07 23:24:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> EIL5: PC gamer memes related to Intel Vs AMD and PCmasterrace in general? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-03 07:45:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What the heck is the whole Jewtel thing and saying AMD is better? I don't get it at all and really just seems cringe as all f@#$ like something a 12 year old would say. 

I have had both intel and AMD systems and for what I do I find linux runs better on intel with better with AMD / ATI video cards. I run mac as well with a macbook pro but the whole apple "fag" thing i get because gamers vs mac junk but seriously I don't get some of the immature memes and even the PC master race connotations all seem to swirl around "eugenics" imagery and subtle racial superiority complex tied to what computer system, operating system, and gpu you use. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> NHK World - Japanology - Kei "K" cars documentary </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-22 23:38:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Ghostbusters (2016) is more like The Ghost Busters (1975) than Ghostbusters (1984) </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-19 02:52:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm just going to say the bumbling nature of the movie feels more like the slapstick humor from the old 70's tv show by Filmmation rather than the genre breaking horror / comedy that was the 80s film by Columbia pictures.

- [FilmMation The Ghost Busters \(1975\)](https://youtu.be/lBZCUiR7Iq8?list=PLIl2eWOVM20HMp85S3KZFgftJRgwStzIv)

- [FilmMation The Ghostbusters \(1986\)](https://youtu.be/F-XOyBlJcJU?list=PL22u5r1GtBckWYCqMScmXevC_OYNcPAYM) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Gigabyte GA-Z170X-UD5 TH - Thunderbolt 3.0 and usb 3.1 c support in Hackintosh? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-19 01:21:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hi,

So I was looking for an affordable hackintosh setup that provided me with thunderbolt 3.0 ports on the board. I just saw that the [Gigabyte GA-Z170X-UD5 TH](http://amzn.to/27Br1wp) was listed on TonymacX86 as a working board but I can't find any information about builds using it. Anyone here have any experience with it? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> UHD Blu-Ray playback on PC / Mac / Linux? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-18 23:42:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hey so does anyone know if there is support for UHD blu-ray playback yet for PC / Mac / Linux? It's just h265 video but I know AACS 2.0 DRM isn't cracked but is this a matter of just AACS 2.0 decryption or will the UHD blu-ray disks be readable by a standard blu-ray drive on the pc/ </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Kaiser billed me 7 months after an ER visit when I had switched insurrances. Now wants me to pay $300 </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-14 22:38:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So i moved to portland back in the end of July. I was on MediCal at the time coming from California and Was still covered for a month when I had to go to the ER for serious back pains I thought were something worse. I called MediCal Healthnet before I went to the ER and they said that I was still covered for a Month  after moving so it was ok to go to the ER in Portland. 

Kaiser got my information and actually still has the information I originally gave them but only now in May of 2016 has actually billed me. The MediCal Healthnet no longer is active and I have insurance through my internship that isn't Kaiser. Is there a way to fix this screw up it feels from their part because at the time I was covered with MediCal Healthnet? If the original ER visit was while I was still covered isn't MediCal supposed to honor it? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Thoughts about De-aging CGI in Captain America Civil War   Ant-man </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-07 20:42:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Black beans keto friendly? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-02 00:17:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hey so i was wondering if cooked basic black beans are good on keto. They are high in fiber and many of the basic minerals and I feel its an easy go to with eggs bacon and cheese in a bowl with fresh avocado. Is there a particular bean better than others yo go for? Like canned wised that is just simple to prep and eat? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Weasels, stoats, and ferrets all perform a hilarious weasel war dance. Researchers have concluded that a majority of rabbits killed by stoats have actually died of fright after being subjected to the dance </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-01 23:55:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Recommendations for Hillsboro / Tanasbourne area CSA (community supported agriculture) memberships? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-01 07:17:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Trying to find a decent recommended CSA with a good selection of veggies and other things like possible dairy and or eggs. Anyone know or use one they can recommend? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [Spoiler] Dr Holden Radcliffe Comic books analog </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-28 05:37:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [High Evolutionary](https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/High_Evolutionary), in Romania or [Transia](https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Transia) and is a geneticist who is fixated on human genetics and transhumanism with a serious fix on the inhumans. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Building a game machine with parts from my employee discount </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-26 02:01:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> so i get a discount for the company i work at. I was gonna pick up a pack they have for $500 that includes a Intel PCI SSD, Intel 6700k, GA-Z170X-Gaming G1 Mother board. 

Now What video card should I get if I want to use just add cards over time as they get cheaper in SLI or Crossfire? 

The discount I get on Video cards is negligible and I already have extra SSD drives as well for secondary Drivers. 

Should i go Nvidia or ATI?

What ddr4 memory should i go with?

Also what case do you recommend for this board if i want something clean without LEDs and crazy gimmicks? I want to put this near my home theater system for the short term till I get a dedicated 4k gaming monitor. Also want to have this be Vive ready for later.

Function is the most important factor here for me here and I just want something clean looking. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Soooooo, PayPal tell me about gender equality and inclusion in an all male leadership company panel </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-22 21:05:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> DS216play - Network slowdowns since putting it on my network </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-13 17:11:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I have been having crawling network speeds since I put the DS216play on my network. It's on a switch from a Netgear 802.11ac router that is just set up as an AP and switch mode only. That switch/AP is then on a port to the router which is on another Trendnet gigabit switch that then plugs into a Ubiquiti EdgeRouter which is handling the actual routing and DHCP server.

I'm gonna play around with the switches to see if it could be the Netgear AP / Switch going wonky but I doubt it is. 

Anyone else having similar issues like this? The slowdowns happen even when I'm not downloading anything and the login interface is very unresponsive majority of the time. I frequently reboot it when its getting super slow. I'm running DSM 6 right now. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Anyone know of a program like 1Keyboard that would let me use my Macbook Pro as a bluetooth keyboard to control a PC? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-30 22:43:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I was wondering if anyone knows of any 1keyboard like apps to control a PC? I use 1Keyboard with my ipad and apple tv but I would love to be able to control my work PC with using my macbook pro as the keyboard and just be able to switch like I do easily between using it and the pc.

http://www.eyalw.com/1keyboard </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Running a DS216play with DSM 5.2, Plex 0.9.16.3 and with wired network to apple tv. Video is constantly buffering </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-29 04:15:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Running a DS216play with DSM 5.2, Plex 0.9.16.3 and with wired gigabit network to apple tv. Video is constantly buffering. I don't know what to do to fix it. It was working earlier but it seem like it randomly keeps doing this to me. It keeps saying that I don't have a fast enough connection to play the file. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Why cant we capture car emissions while we drive? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-11 18:11:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I was wondering why its not physically possible to have a carbon cooling, condensing, and capture system on the exhaust of a car? We let it cool off slightly through the exhaust pipe and then through a muffler but just allow it to float off. Cant we somehow extend this process to give us a solid waste product of carbon and oxygen instead of gaseous one that has far more detrimental ecological effects. Is that not feasible?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> How Authoritarianism Took Over the GOP and Allowed for the Emergence of Emperor Trump Trump's doctrine is authoritarianism, which explains why he continues to exceed conventional expectations. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-07 01:53:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Got an authoritarian streak? Study says odds are, you're for Trump. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-07 01:51:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> How Authoritarianism Explains Whether Youre A Conservative Who Likes Trump (Or Not) </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-07 01:49:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The rise of American authoritarianism A niche group of political scientists may have uncovered what's driving Donald Trump's ascent. What they found has implications that go well beyond 2016. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-07 01:35:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Need advice on a new build from a guy who hasn't had a gaming pc since Athlon XP was the hotness </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-02 22:56:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So i got a job for a large company that makes a certain set of computer processors and chip sets doing software engineering. I can get an intel 6700k for $115, a gigabyte Z170X-Gaming G1 for $250 and a 980ti Gigabyte video card for 400. I'm wondering what kind of case do i need to get then, what kind of power suppply should I get if plan to add more graphics cards down the line, and what is the most silent and reliable cooling system that isn't full out crazy reservoir water tank custom molded tubing water cooled? 

Been a long time since I built a dedicated gaming PC. Advice is greatly appreciated. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> I knew I saw this Zoom plot before ... </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-24 09:49:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Having problems installing on school server without root access </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-18 20:44:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So i'm having problems installing it locally for my student account. 

I used the following Script

https://gist.github.com/haslup/db28b1eefc8b717d43bc

    #!/bin/bash
    
    # Script for installing tmux on systems where you don't have root access.
    # tmux will be installed in $HOME/local/bin.
    # It's assumed that wget and a C/C++ compiler are installed.
    
    # exit on error
    set -e
    
    TMUX_VERSION=2.1
    
    # create our directories
    mkdir -p $HOME/local $HOME/tmux_tmp
    cd $HOME/tmux_tmp
    
    # download source files for tmux, libevent, and ncurses
    wget https://github.com/tmux/tmux/releases/download/2.1/tmux-2.1.tar.gz
    wget https://github.com/downloads/libevent/libevent/libevent-2.0.19-stable.tar.gz
    wget ftp://ftp.gnu.org/gnu/ncurses/ncurses-5.9.tar.gz
    
    # extract files, configure, and compile
    
    ############
    # libevent #
    ############
    tar xvzf libevent-2.0.19-stable.tar.gz
    cd libevent-2.0.19-stable
    ./configure --prefix=$HOME/local --disable-shared
    make
    make install
    cd ..
    
    ############
    # ncurses  #
    ############
    tar xvzf ncurses-5.9.tar.gz
    cd ncurses-5.9
    ./configure --prefix=$HOME/local
    make
    make install
    cd ..
    
    ############
    # tmux     #
    ############
    tar xvzf tmux-${TMUX_VERSION}.tar.gz
    cd tmux-${TMUX_VERSION}
    ./configure CFLAGS="-I$HOME/local/include -I$HOME/local/include/ncurses" LDFLAGS="-L$HOME/local/lib -L$HOME/local/include/ncurses -L$HOME/local/include"
    CPPFLAGS="-I$HOME/local/include -I$HOME/local/include/ncurses" LDFLAGS="-static -L$HOME/local/include -L$HOME/local/include/ncurses -L$HOME/local/lib" make
    cp tmux $HOME/local/bin
    cd ..
    
    # cleanup
    rm -rf $HOME/tmux_tmp
    
    echo "$HOME/local/bin/tmux is now available. You can optionally add $HOME/local/bin to your PATH."        

But I get this error while it's compiling

    In file included from ../ncurses/curses.priv.h:283:0,
                     from ../ncurses/lib_gen.c:19:
    _10345.c:835:15: error: expected ) before int
    ../include/curses.h:1594:56: note: in definition of macro mouse_trafo
     #define mouse_trafo(y,x,to_screen) wmouse_trafo(stdscr,y,x,to_screen)
                                                            ^
    make[1]: *** [../objects/lib_gen.o] Error 1
    make[1]: Leaving directory `/home/student/patrick/tmux_tmp/ncurses-5.9/ncurses'
    make: *** [all] Error 2

Any advice on how to fix this? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Asustek preps add-in-card with Thunderbolt 3/USB type-C ports </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-18 17:50:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Man in the Iron Mask - Morse code </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-12 07:14:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Anyone know if the Man In the Iron Mask was knocking in morse code on the window in the cell scene from "Welcome to Earth-2"? Also anyone have any idea who he is? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Slow Cooker Keto </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-10 00:06:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Can people please start posting recipes for slow Cooker keto dishes? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Looking to Collect S.H. Figuarts and was wondering what is the difference between the USA Set, Zyuranger USA set, and the Japanese set? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-06 11:33:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> S.H Figuarts Bandai Power Rangers Mighty Morphin'   Sentai Zyuranger usa   japan version sets. Is there a difference in build quality, where they were made, or is it just packaging differences? Which ones should I get if I'm just gonna take them out of their box and play with them and put them up around my office desk? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Next Gen Pi? USB 3.1   Gigabit? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-28 23:33:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Does anyone know if there is anything like this? A Quad core ghz board with at least 1 gig of ram but also has USB 3.1 and Gigabit network on board? There is something like Banana Pi and Banana Pro but is there anything in developing the newer usb 3.1 connectors? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Oregon Occupation Leaders Ammon and Ryan Bundy Arrested, One Dead </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-27 04:32:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Looking to build a electronics workbench and need a purchase list for the tools and testing equipment I should get. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-19 19:04:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Just looking for a full tool and instrument purchasing guide for a middle range quality products for a work bench. So soldering iron, reflow tool, clippers, multimeter, and so forth. Anyone know a good list so I can just check it off easily? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Affordable 5.1 audio speakers and sub woofer for a Sony STR-DN850? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-19 18:26:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Looking to setup 5.1 surround sound audio for a new Sony STR-DN850 i got for only $190 It has a RCA plug for the sub woofer so i'm not sure if it needs a powered plug or what. I'm pretty new to how to set up the surround sound on this currently using a free older Sony WD750 receiver that hooks up via optical and it had a bunch of speakers with it but i'm looking to get nicer and newer ones. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Thunderbolt 3 Hackintosh? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-02 10:10:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So there are currently now 4 mother boards all mabe by gigabyte with thunderbolt 3.

Anyone know anything about these and using them to make a hackintosh?

Gigabyte GA-Z170X-UD5 TH (Rev. 1.0) 

- http://www.gigabyte.tw/products/product-page.aspx?pid=5479#ov

Gigabyte GA-Z170X-Gaming 7 (rev. 1.0)

- http://www.gigabyte.com/products/product-page.aspx?pid=5481#ov

Gigabyte GA-Z170X-Gaming G1 (rev. 1.0) 

- http://www.gigabyte.com/products/product-page.aspx?pid=5478#ov

Gigabyte GA-Z170X-Gaming GT (rev. 1.0)

- http://www.gigabyte.com/products/product-page.aspx?pid=5515#ov </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Bought my girlfriend a "New Nintendo 3DS XL" MicroSDHC / MicroSDXC questions here, is their a wiki to keep track of tested and working SD cards? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-31 04:16:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So I bought my first Nintendo product since the nintendo 64 buying my girlfriend the "New Nintendo 3DS XL". I know it comes with a 4gb MicroSD card but what is the max size it supports? If I got her a Samsung 128GB EVO Micro SDXC (MB-MP128DA/AM) would it work in the New 3DS as long as I format it Fat32? 

Does the New 3DS support SDXC or just SDHC?


Also why haven't people started a wiki to keep track of tested SD cards? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Retropie RetroArch controller config question: Multiple buttons at one time (start + select + L shoulder) to exit emulation </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-21 13:06:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So i'm using SNES9x-next and unlike all of the other made for pi version of emulators it used retroarch which is a bitch to configure as it defaults to keyboard for input for what ever reason. 

Anyway I finally figured how to configure the input now but I need to add the ability to have a Multiple button at one time (start + select + L shoulder) to exit emulation hotkey and one to bring up the menu for RetroArch.

Thanks in advance </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What brand of METAL pot   pans should I purchase   invest in? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-20 22:28:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> My mom raved about all-clad and got them one pan at a time while I was growing up but they are expensive as anything to a broke guy like myself. 

What do you typically see in restaurants being used?

I want to get 2 fry pans, 3 sauce pans, 2 saute pans, double boiler, multi pot with strainer, and a dutch oven. 

**NO NONSTICK, ONLY BARE METAL** </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> First year doing secret santa .... :( sadness </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-12 12:02:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Cargo container / Shipping Container architecture in the Portland area? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-12 11:38:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm a huge fan of shipping container / cargo container architecture simply called cargotecture. Besides the [Starbucks](http://www.oregonlive.com/window-shop/index.ssf/2013/08/starbucks_trucks_in_prototype.html) prototype LEED certified Cargo container drive through are there any other major commercial or residential uses of cargo containers in the portland area? 

Also does anyone know of any local architectural firms that can do design or structural engineering work using cargo containers as the base building material in the 150 mile range from portland?
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Cargo container / Shipping Container architecture in the Portland area? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-12 11:34:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm a huge fan of shipping container / cargo container architecture simply called cargotecture. Besides the [Starbucks](http://www.oregonlive.com/window-shop/index.ssf/2013/08/starbucks_trucks_in_prototype.html) prototype LEED certified Cargo container drive through are there any other major commercial or residential uses of cargo containers in the portland area? 

Also does anyone know of any local architectural firms that can do design or structural engineering work using cargo containers as the base building material in the 150 mile range from portland?

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> MRW Ben Carson joins Donald Trump in threatening to leave GOP </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-12 11:01:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Multitrack recording mixers </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-11 06:23:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hey, I'm trying to find a multi track mixer that plugs in via USB 2.0 or USB 3.0. I want it to send each input as a separate track for Audition or Logic X. What is a good mixer that is under 200 dollars to do this with? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What if the United States brought back the draft but you had a choice of options for deployment </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-04 18:35:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Actually I think we should have a choice of 
What if the United States brought back the draft but you had a choice of options for deployment depending on what age you start.

- 2 year active service military of your choice with 8 months training at age 18
- 3 years Americorps : your income level determines where you go help at, higher income go to lower income areas to help support and you live in Americorp provided group accommodations at ages 16, 17, or 18
- 3 years Peace Corps : yyour income level determines where you go help at, higher income go to lower income areas to help support and you live in Peace Corps provided group accommodations at ages 16, 17, or 18


The 3 years options should start at 16 at the earliest and that way we provide free education in exchange so all students who otherwise are not advance enough are able to go to remedial college level math classes instead of high school. I think this would save many kids from the typical bullying that high school fosters and makes them learn some empathy. While doing AmeriCorps or PeaceCorps we could even do school exchange programs with it and start allowing Foreign university credits to count in the United States as well maybe returning to the National University idea that creates universal credits for experience attained while doing each different draft or practicum experience that would mean more for jobs. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [Medication] Who else is on Latuda now </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-02 15:58:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I got put on it several months ago for my BP type 2. It has leveled me out amazingly. I was was on lamictal before and technically still on but I don't take it anymore as It was causing significant drowsy effects to me if I took it in the morning. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> foodstamps keto </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-11-30 10:02:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> im on foodstamps. I get $120 a month. What is a good list of items to buy and some easy to make meals that can be done in this budget. I'm finding it nearly impossible since meat costs so much and I'm looking for advice for the best meal plan and shopping list to buy that i can at most spend an additional 30 maybe 40 dollars so $150 total for grocery budget a month.

i have trader joes, safeway, winco, and myers near by.

hot prepared foods are not purchasable on food stamps. neither is protein powders or vitamins.

again i have barely any time to cook and trying to make this as on the go friendly as possible.

mostly I'm making large casserole dish sausage feta Spinage frittata on Sunday that lasts till Wednesday and then string cheesing and baked egg cheese avocado in the morning while i get ready till Sunday when I can cook the frittata again. i do stevia dropper and heavy whipping cream coffee too with cold brew coffee. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Have gigabit internet hooked up to Ubiquit Edge router Lite with Dlink R6300v1 AC1900 in AP mode. But my speed test on wireless is only 350mbps while on wired is 875 mbps ... help? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-11-27 11:00:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Not sure what i'm doing wrong here but I know 802.11 AC shouldn't have that much of an overhead. Any suggestions or how best to configure my setup. The wireless router is in the same room as me when I use it for speed tests. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Unit testing and developing tools for testing code </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-11-27 10:08:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> How do you learn to start writing unit tests and code testing tools? Beyond reading compile logs I don't have an idea how unit testing works or how you go about doing it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> ELI5: Why do white people complain about reverse racism to minority scholarships? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-11-27 08:01:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Provocative assholes like this really piss me off and they know they are doing it to be a dick like James O'Keefe </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-11-27 07:11:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Marvel Phase 1 Movie Digital Downloads? Where can I get them as part of a package? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-11-22 06:28:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I really don't like purchasing blu-ray movies if i don't get a digital download with it. I would have purchased the Phase 1 special edition if they would have just included the digital downloads with it. The fact that disney includes the digital download on pretty much any platform makes me love that they got marvel. Does anyone know if there is a way to get the digital download for all of the phase 1 movies in a single purchase and not have to pay full price on top of the blu-ray movies for them? I wish they just would have included them again with the phase 1 collectors set such a bone head move on their part for this. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Ketostix guide? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-11-13 17:06:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So I'm one week in and I have gone from large dark purple to the middle color moderate. Where should I be and how do I read these sticks? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Just mayo as easy fat? No carbs is that ok? Also type of fats? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-11-09 16:39:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So I'm finding it hard to get my fat up to 80% of calories and have taken to scooping on "just mayo" in spoonfuls to make up for it. Is that OK? Also what type of fats should I eat and not eat? Saturated, monosaturated? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What subreddit should I post the question on suggestions for "where to buy a foam mattress online?" </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-11-05 00:30:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Looking to purchase a foam Mattress online, any suggestions on who to go to for a good firm one? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-11-05 00:01:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> MRW I have to deal with Apples stupid product decisions that make my life difficult, looking at you magsafe and lack of licensed 3rd party products. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-10-28 22:35:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What is polymorphism? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-10-26 01:45:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It is a term I keep hearing and reading up on it I am finding it confusing can someone please explain it to me. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Portland Community College Coke Machine powered by Android, glitching out and in a boot loop for its mobile pay. [x-post r/android] </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-10-23 19:19:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Coke Machine powered by Android, saw it glitching out and in a boot loop for its mobile pay feature </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-10-23 13:12:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Patching on OSX? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-10-19 02:30:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I really want to play some good rom hacks but it seems all the ips patching tools are on windows. How do i go about in finding patching tools for mac and also what are some good recommendations for GBA and SNES hacked roms? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Best movie theater experience for a videophile who cares about screen, sound, projector quality, and seating arrangement in Portland area </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-10-16 21:48:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm trying to find the best theater for Star Wars when it comes out. I like stadium seating, wide screen, a screen that the theater makes sure is not over stretched or has runs in the material or burns in and has THX sound. Leather seats would be a perk. Also for the fact I'm not a big 3D fan but if the theater knows what they are doing they will remove the splitter which if left on lowers the brightness of a 2d movie. If you know which theaters know what they are doing for projectionists that also helps.

Any recommendations? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [X-Post /r/videos] Nike Sweatshops: Behind the Swoosh. A couple spends a month living in an Indonesian village living on the wages a Nike shoemaker makes. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-10-07 19:47:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> I just realized I have 10 minutes left of a cake day </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-10-04 11:20:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Why hiddy-ho neighbor! I live next door to a really swell group of people. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-09-23 07:26:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Scumbag CEO - Yes you raise the price on medication needed for AIDS patients who get sick you are a scumbag </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-09-22 07:18:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Where are some places in portland to try for brunch? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-09-20 20:20:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Any places that have stellar brunches that me and my girlfriend should try? For me, I love me some pancakes, stuffed french toast, eggs Benedict, crab cakes, salmon cakes, and the such. My girlfriend loves eggs of any sort typically, omelettes, sunny side up and scrambled.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Recommendations for aftermarket 2 din head units with Android Auto AND Apple CarPlay? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-09-19 19:52:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Is there a list of 2 din head units that have both Android Auto and Apple Carplay in them. I use both a Nexus and iPhone and so does my girlfriend. If not a lists any recommendations of dual platform head units? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Got it! </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-09-12 11:52:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Get it! </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-09-12 11:39:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Know any places to get good Takoyaki   Okonomiyaki in Portland? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-08-24 07:47:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Takoyaki is a ball-shaped Japanese snack made of a wheat flour-based batter and cooked in a special takoyaki pan. It is typically filled with minced or diced octopus, tempura scraps, pickled ginger, and green onion.

Okonomiyaki is a Japanese savory pancake containing a variety of ingredients. The name is derived from the word okonomi, meaning "what you like" or "what you want", and yaki meaning "grilled" or "cooked".

Recommendations for places that serve both that you can vouch for would be great.

*EDIT*

**No I do not want to make them myself. YES I do like to go out and eat them because i like to have them made for me as a treat.**  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Just Personal Computer Master Race things, when you get symmetrical 1gigabit internet for $60 a month. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-08-24 01:28:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Meet Ghira, my step puppy. She is a giant cat / bunny. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-08-19 23:45:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> I'm surprised they haven't show colloidal silver for treatment of the infected. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-08-19 03:16:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It would make sense to try colloidal silver in the plot for people newly infected. While silver builds up in the system and can be toxic it can still be used in small dosages as many nutters use it for "holistic usage" </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Best option for AndroidTV for HEVC H265 4k and HD 1080p playback? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-08-19 00:28:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What is the best option other than PLEX for AndroidTV for HEVC H265 4k and HD 1080p playback? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Can't get MAME to work at all </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-08-11 21:22:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm using 1.0.4 build that latest for the experimental branch. It has the 1.49 MAME core but no games will load at all. It won't open up the emulator window at all. I'm not sure why. Any suggestions? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Lenovo announces powerhouse laptops powered by new mobile Xeon processors with Thunderbolt 3 </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-08-11 08:46:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Vudu on Nvidia Shield AndroidTV? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-08-08 18:39:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Does anyone know if Vudu app is available for AndroidTV like the Nvidia shield? I want to have support for Ultraviolet movies i have via Vudu. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> European broadcaster SkyNews's Youtube live stream got a DMCA takedown notice from Fox News for showing Republican Debate online. Both broadcasters are owned by Rupert Murdoch. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-08-07 05:08:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Know a good lawyer in Hillsboro for dogbite case? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-31 21:07:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Girlfriend got bit by a dog at a dog park. Need to find lawyer that anyone can recommend. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Another Dog attacked my girlfriend's husky then it bit her hand when she pulled it off her husky at Hondo dog park today in Hillsboro, need advice </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-30 10:51:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So we got all the information including rabies and medical records plus a photo of the dog license and driver license and contact info on the dog owner. It happened after the dog got aggressive after it saw my girlfriend dog playing with another dog. They got separated and the other owner took the dog away but 5 minutes later she unleashed it again and it came back finding my girlfriend dog who was still on a leash and attacked again. 

girlfriend had to get cast for possible fractured wrist and wounds cleaned out. Besides reporting it to Washington County Animal control which we did at the hospital and staying in contact with the attacking dog's owner for medical reimbursement once we get the ER co-pay, medication copay, and follow up visit copay bills what else should we do? Not sure we really need to go a legal avenue with this. Looked into the Oregon and Washington County Dog laws and since we have it reported with the dog license and owner contact info and information Washington County are supposed to now do an investigation. We have pictures and witness contacts as well. Anything else I should be mindful of? 

We just moved here last week. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> amc theaters in portland oregon? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-18 20:35:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Anyone know any info if there will be a AMC Theater opening up in the TriMet accessible area? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Do you have Fibersphere gigabit internet? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-17 17:38:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hi,

So i just moved here from los angeles and I signed up for Fibershere in my apartment. The service is supposed to be gigabit but i'm only getting like 125megabits right now. Also it seems that my torrent downloads are only getting 10 kbps and steam updates are only getting 10Megabytes. Could be my router but anyone have any issues with them or recommend a router i should use?

I have a Netgear R6300v1 

*Update:*

***Wired gigabit:***

Last Result:

Download Speed: 338462 kbps (42307.8 KB/sec transfer rate)

Upload Speed: 261259 kbps (32657.4 KB/sec transfer rate)

Latency: 8 ms

Jitter: 5 ms

Packet Loss: 0%

7/17/2015, 2:02:48 PM

***Wireless 802.11AC:***

Last Result:

Download Speed: 53007 kbps (6625.9 KB/sec transfer rate)

Upload Speed: 19983 kbps (2497.9 KB/sec transfer rate)

Latency: 10 ms

Jitter: 5 ms

Packet Loss: 0%

7/17/2015, 2:08:09 PM

**FINAL EDIT**

All is fixed getting my full speeds and downloading torrents at upwards of 15MegaBytes per second and steam is maxing out at 10 Megabytes per second too. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> First world gigabit internet problems </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-17 03:29:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Bipolar type 2 with Seasonal Effective disorder. Moving to Portland. Anyone have any experience with full spectrum light bulbs? Do they come in LED bulb form? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-13 11:27:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Just as it says I got Bipolar type 2 with very light hypo manic swings. Dysthymic so i'm i tend to go depressive. My depressive swings are triggered by the winter months usually when i lived on the east coast. When i moved to los angeles is was much better and rarely had any issues with how much sun I got and with my current medication combination.

But the issue is i'm moving to Portland with my girlfriend and was wondering if anyone knows about full spectrum light bulbs in helping with SAD and if they come in LED form to save money on electricity and if they do what brands are good? What frequencies of the EM Spectrum for light do I need to look for? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Updated Trimet MAX lightrail Map with Orange Line in Super Mario 3 Style </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-10 20:44:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Los Angeles County transit agency, Metro, has released a set of "Blue Ribbon Committee" proposals including cutting local bus services to fund more core networks of rapid buses </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-09 21:54:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Which Macbooks Pros support metal graphics? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-17 03:43:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I have a late 2013 Macbook Pro with NVIDIA GeForce GT 750M and Intel Iris pro. Does this mean or not mean it supports metal? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What r/all looks like for me with filters right now. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-11 07:45:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Is there anyway to manually add a quick setting button option in Lollipop Android 5.x? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-06 20:41:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Back when it was Kitkat whenever i plugged in my USB cable to my computer USB tether showed up on the Quick settings pull down. Now it doesn't show up in kitkat and while i know it shows the settings you use the most like hotspot, if you use it, its not the USB tether. I'm wondering if anyone knows if there are ways to select and manually add quick settings in Lollipop like you could in Kitkat. I really have grown to hate Lollipop's pull down status bar because of this. I miss Kitkat's approach to how it did the status bar / pull down menus. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [TOMT][audio] Trip hop / jazz electronic organ song that is maybe 15 years old that has this rift for the key part of the song </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-30 04:33:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> https://soundcloud.com/roanhouse/electronic-organ-music-earworm-name-this-song-please

I have this ear worm stuck in my head this is a repeated notes of the song that then drops an octave and then climbs the entire scale and then repeats. I want to think its a trip hop or electronic music jazz mix thing I can't remember and it's seriously driving me batty today.

-----***EDIT****---


Found it my self I can't believe i fucked this up I knew who did it all the time It was DJ Shadow Organ Donor

https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=U4E60Ffa9yQ

The reason i had it stuck in my head is because I heard Dizzee Rascal - Fix Up, Look Sharp

https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=4B06gdaXJeY

Which got me to remember this song which was from Dj Hero

Fix Up Look Sharp vs Organ Donor - Dizzee Rascal vs Dj Shadow

https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=AAUmDMMgYGY

This then had me hunting for the original song which I thought was DJ Shadow but i couldn't remember because cognitive dissidence caused by the ear worm and other music. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Electronic Organ Music Earworm Name this song please </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-30 04:23:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Anyone else have this display of center glitch on Mac OS X Yosemite with LEGO Batman 3: Beyond Gotham purchased from Steam? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-30 00:13:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Arcgency is a Copenhagen office dedicated to Resource Conscious Architecture. Their office was made to be moved. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-26 18:55:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [Spoiler] Phase 2 Easter Eggs </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-13 19:48:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What was the point of this? Making New 52 Reverse Flash   Professors Zoom </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-09 07:24:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Baltimore riots happened before and will happen again in the same places - Remember the 1968 riots in context to 2015 </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-28 00:31:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Baltimore riots happened before and will happen again in the same places - Remember the 1968 riots in context to 2015 </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-28 00:30:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Shipping Container Farms </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-17 22:23:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Trying to find title of a movie, there is a supernatural Serial killer jumping from body to body via water as two detectives try to stop it with the help of a ditzy girl and Corvette driving medical Examiner. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-16 15:20:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I saw this movie back in 2004 I think. A Serial Killer is killing people randomly and it turns out its some sort of fallen angel that hated heaven because it was hell to it because blissful and not painful or something to that effect. Its jumping body to body via water into a new host to kill a new victim. Two detectives, one young and one old are trying to track it down. The younger one makes a friend with a strange ditzy kogal girl who is strangely wise and has an understanding of what is going on. They also get the help from a sexy corvette driving female medical Examiner who at the climax of the movie is taken over by this supernatural water born serial killer. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> How Cisco feels about the bees. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-15 22:14:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [Comicbooks] How would the Marvel Comics Multiverse incursions effect the MCU? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-14 01:40:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Just wondering with MCU being universe-199999 how if any will this story of exploding universes effect or not effect the continuity of it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [Spoilers][Daredevil] Madame Gao "Homeland" farther away than China? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-11 20:06:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Is your unpaid summer internship illegal? A breakdown of the laws on working for free. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-10 09:54:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> When Is It OK to Not Pay an Intern?

Is your unpaid summer internship illegal? A breakdown of the laws on working for free.

byBlair HickmanandChristie Thompson
ProPublica, June 14, 2013, 1:05 p.m.



**What laws determine when an intern should or should not be paid?**

The Fair Labor Standards Act, or FLSA, regulates minimum wage and overtime for U.S. workers, including interns. The Department of Labors Wage and Hour Division is responsible for enforcing the law, and has asix-factor testto determine whether interns at private sector employers must be paid minimum wage.

**According to the Department of Labor, an unpaid internship must meet all these criteria:**

- The internship is similar to training which would be given in an educational environment.
- Its for the benefit of the intern
- The intern doesnt displace paid employees
- The employer doesnt benefit from work the intern is doing, and on occasion its operations may actually be impeded.
- The intern isnt promised a job at the end (unpaid tryouts arent allowed)
- Both the intern and their boss understand its an unpaid position

**So are unpaid internships ever OK?**

Very rarely, for work done at for-profit companies. According to the Department of Labor's test, companies cant derive an immediate advantage from an interns work. And in the private sector, work that doesnt benefit the company is rare.

Its fair to say most private-sector employers who employ volunteers are violating the law, said David Yamada, a professor of law at Suffolk University in Boston.

**What if they provide a stipend or lunch money? Does that count?**

Probably not, assuming its a private sector employee covered by the FLSA, according to Yamada. If an internship at a for-profit employer doesnt meet the factors laid out in the six-point test, they most likely have to pay their interns minimum wage.

**What about internships at nonprofits?**

According to the Department of Labor, nonprofits have an additional exception for unpaid interns that "volunteer their time." The government's guidelinesstate thatunpaid internships in the public sector and for non-profit charitable organizations...are generally permissible.

**What about gigs with the government?**

For most interns on Capitol Hill, its perfectly legal for them to be working for free. Congressconveniently exempted itselffrom the Fair Labor Standards Act, meaning they dont have to pay their interns. (Its just one of many workplace laws that Congress doesnt have to follow.) Mostfederal-level internships, including the White Houses program, are also unpaid.

**Does getting college credit mean its OK to not get paid?**

Not really. Many companies attempt to use academic credit as legal justification for an unpaid internships. But this weeksBlack Swan rulingsuggests college credit is not a reason to not pay your interns, a move that, as Yamada put it, opens an interesting door.

http://www.propublica.org/article/when-interns-should-be-paid-explained </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> No time for solar races, i must go to my people! </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-09 09:03:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [HOUSING][Needed] Young Couple with 6 year old lazy Husky dog looking for a place / room for $1200 on the Westside </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-09 04:46:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm 30 years old and disabled returning student studying at Santa Monica College and my girlfriend is 27 and works currently as a head receptionist for veterinary hospital in the Palisades. We are looking for a place or a shared apartment that takes dogs on the westside. Ghira is my girlfriend's dog that acts more like a combination cat / bunny. She is a playfully lazy sweet Husky and is spayed. She doesn't do well with small dogs as she is scaredy cat but we would have to see.

My background is I used to do IT and software training and freelance Tech journalism. I'm now going back to school studying for computer science AS to transfer for my 4 year BS. My girlfriend Alex is going back to school for grad school too. We are quite nerdy. I'm a video game guy, we both play board games, and I love to cook. We come with an apple tv, PS3, 36" HDTV and a handful of great boardgames. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> MRW reverse flash took off his mask [Remix] (I had to fix it) </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-04 08:34:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Apple just needs to add a Flash / light to the iPads already </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-03 23:13:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I know this is a silly idea to some but it happens, people use their iPads like a camera. You know you have seen it. They should just add the flash already.

http://i.imgur.com/gsJ8em7.jpg

http://i.imgur.com/QZ3YB.png

http://i.imgur.com/15MRNt9.jpg

http://i.imgur.com/M1nvfwN.jpg

Secondary, a flash would be nice for document scanner apps to take pictures in strange lit spaces. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Metro Proposes Simplified Naming Convention for Rail Lines. Proposed plan would replace color names with letters, a la the NYC Subway. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-03 08:11:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> My Choice for Norman Osborn </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-01 21:50:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Hulu has the wrong episode up for iZombie S1E03 - "The Exterminator" </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-01 08:17:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Why on earth is the Share button for Email only? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-23 19:49:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If i click the share link under a post it opens up a form to forward it via email. Can We please just get a way to post the title and short URL to the post it self with comments that posts to the different social media services? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Santa Monica's mountain lions caught on camera [xpost r/pics] </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-13 08:02:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Anyone have have Time Warner Ultimate 300 mbps internet? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-25 23:01:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Anyone have have Time Warner Ultimate 300 mbps internet? They are offering it for $64 a month right now I was told with no extra fees, Flat $64 with no taxes if you own your own modem. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Amazon makes an error and I win double </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-21 20:33:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Renato Garcia, of San Juan, Puerto Rico .... RISE! </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-19 17:13:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Operation Blue Line w the Teenage Mutant Ninja Turtles </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-13 08:08:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Oh what is so important about Amiibo? What do they do when paired with the NFC reader? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-01 04:44:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm kinda confused to the point of the Amiibo. Do they give you anything special when playing a game? Are they just there to be collected in a form of materialism? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Costa Mesa Waldorf School in Orange County, California expands school using 32 Recycled Shipping Containers </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-31 21:13:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> New Union Station Bus Platform to Begin Construction in April [x-post r/Transit] </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-27 02:44:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Thomas is accused of defrauding the government by using fake patient names for prescription drugs that were then illegally shipped in bulk to Indiana and Nebraska. The phony names included L.L. Bean, Harry Potter, Mike Marker, and Carrol Sharpie, according to the indictment. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-25 17:37:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Live in an Apartment, Condo, Duplex, or multi family home in Los Angeles County and have a landlord that wont fix things or is not following building code? Here is where you go, the Los Angeles Housing + Community Investment Department (HCIDLA) </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-20 17:04:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I saw people didn't know about this in another post about future rain flooding and a guy mentioning his balcony not having drains required by code.

[The Los Angeles Housing + Community Investment Department \(HCIDLA\)](http://lahd.lacity.org/) is in charge of building code inspections on apartments and multi family condos / duplexes. 

HCIDLA How to report or file a code violation complaint webpage - [[link](http://lahd.lacity.org/lahdinternet/CodeEnforcement/Programs/tabid/390/language/en-US/Default.aspx)]

- Phone number: 

HCIDLA Information and Complaint Line 

weekdays between 9:00 am-4:00 pm

(866) 557-7368;

- Visit one of their office locations - http://cris.lacity.org/cris/informationcenter/code/offices.htm

- Online Code Violation Reporting Website - http://cris.lacity.org/cris/informationcenter/code/propprofile.htm
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> ELI5: Under the US Communications Act Title II if US broadband is classified a "telecommunications service" instead of an "information service" it would make broadband a public utility, opening it to basic access rights for competitors / consumers and give FCC teeth to enforce it, correct? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-14 17:11:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [FOR SALE] ATOMOS SAMURAI 10-bit HD-SDI 1080p Camera-Mounted Recorder / monitor - $550 </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-05 04:58:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The Samurai is a portable touchscreen-operated HD recorder, monitor and playback device for video professionals. It captures pristine 10-bit 4:2:2 video and audio direct from any camera with HD/SD-SDI output. The Samurai consumes very little power, ensures long recording times (up to 16.5 hours on a 750GB disk) and the efficient use of batteries.

I have been using it for recording trade show events and am looking to upgrade for a 4k workflow. Retails for $995. Works brilliantly. Comes with two Hard drive caddy cards, Two Sony type batteries, dual Battery charger, HD-SDI mini to full size cables, portable USB 3.0 / Firewire 800 transfer deck, and pelican carrying case.

I have taken extremely good care of my equipment and as you can see from photos it is almost like new.

http://losangeles.craigslist.org/wst/pho/4832766854.html </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> PSBattle: It's Vision time! </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-01 08:15:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> TIL only 816 New York City Police Department officers have died on duty since 1806 </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-12-30 20:02:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> A holiday message from your amicable provincial Sir Arachnid </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-12-25 11:07:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [FOR SALE] ATOMOS SAMURAI 10-bit HD-SDI 1080p Camera-Mounted Recorder / monitor - $700 </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-12-24 18:41:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The Samurai is a portable touchscreen-operated HD recorder, monitor and playback device for video professionals. It captures pristine 10-bit 4:2:2 video and audio direct from any camera with HD/SD-SDI output. The Samurai consumes very little power, ensures long recording times (up to 16.5 hours on a 750GB disk) and the efficient use of batteries.

I have been using it for recording trade show events and am looking to upgrade for a 4k workflow. Retails for $995. Works brilliantly. Comes with two Hard drive caddy cards, Two Sony type batteries, dual Battery charger, HD-SDI mini to full size cables, portable USB 3.0 / Firewire 800 transfer deck, and pelican carrying case.

I have taken extremely good care of my equipment and as you can see from photos it is almost like new.

http://losangeles.craigslist.org/wst/pho/4818492170.html
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [FOR SALE] Metabones Canon EF to E-Mount (NEX) active lens camera adapter - $200 </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-12-24 18:18:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Selling for $200 

This adapter allows you to put any EF style lens with active focus on the following NEX Sony cameras:


- NEX-FS700
- NEX-FS100
- NEX-EA50
- NEX-VG30
- NEX-VG20
- NEX-VG10
- NEX-7
- NEX-6
- NEX-5R
- NEX-5N
- NEX-5
- NEX-C3
- NEX-3


Only thing is it doesn't support Full frame sensors.
But works great for anyone with the FS700 and FS100.

http://losangeles.craigslist.org/wst/pho/4818472680.html </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [H] Batman: Arkham Asylum Game of the Year Edition (PC / MAC)   Batman: Arkham City - Game of the Year Edition (PC / MAC) [W] LEGO Batman 3: Beyond Gotham </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-12-13 03:14:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What are your personal "irksome" changes bought on by Lollipop to personal android usability? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-12-12 04:39:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> My personal one was they no longer show a USB tether button option in the pull down menu like with kitkat. I have now to go through the settings menu  Hotspot  USB tether

Before I could just plug in and slide down and turn on and was good for tethering go.

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Obese guy looking for a gym in the 90064 off pico / sawtelle </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-11-29 21:55:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm wondering if anyone has any recommendations for a gym in the 90064 area code. I'm a morbidly obese guy with a limited budget and I only find it easy to work out when I have access to free weights and elliptical / rowing machines. Also access to having pilates / yoga classes too would be nice. Looking to do endurance / lean muscle / core development to help with burning fat faster. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [C][Homework][Extra Credit] How do you add two very large numbers using Borland 32bit compiler without using an array. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-11-26 03:18:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So this is an extra credit assignment. I know how to do this with an array but since i'm not allowed to i'm not sure. Boreland C compiler is only 32 bit and does not support the 'long long' data type that GCC supports for 64bit applications. 

So the program is to add two numbers: 

1999999999999999999999999999999999999999999996667766999999

and

888888888888888888888888888888888888888888888888888888888888888888888888

then display the total.

Again I can not use an array and I am also limited to 32bit data types.

Here is the exact text from the assignment:

 Write a complete C/Java program to add two very large numbers together as follows:
 Enter the first number
 1999999999999999999999999999999999999999999996667766999999

 Enter the second number
 888888888888888888888888888888888888888888888888888888888888888888888888

 Sum is

 Display the total here
  
 Note: You should not use an array.
      


**EDIT**

Professor just clarified in an email:


There should be no limit to the number we input. Array makes it limit.

link list is the solution not an array. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [C] Computing Median and Mode from an Array of float data entries without sorting / changing Array </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-11-21 04:51:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I am having a trouble of it figuring out how to process the data in the first place and how to do it without changing how the data in the array is placed.

i would be calling in the array "data[]" and a pointer to the counter that tells how many entries are in the array.

The array has 200 possible entries but as you input data it keeps a counter so if you quit entry it will let you resume entering data or start a new data set. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [C] displaying contents of an array using for loops, and printf to format out put of rows of text. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-11-21 03:46:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm trying to output entries in an array. I want to print it out not as just one long line of text like this loop does:

    for(i=0 ; i  count2 ; i++)
       	{
    		printf("%3.2f ",data[i]);
    	}

which is akin to this:

      1.00 2.00 3.00 4.00 5.00 6.00 7.00 8.00 9.00 10.00 11.00 12.00 13.00 14.00 15.00 10000.00 12312.00 13212.00 12312.00 12312.00  
            
           

I want to print it out so it has the numbers print out like this:

           1.00       2.00       3.00       4.00       5.00
           
           6.00       7.00       8.00       9.00      10.00  
         
          11.00      12.00      13.00      14.00      15.00
      
       10000.00   12312.00   13212.00   12312.00   12312.00 

what is the nested loop i need to make to do this kinda of print out. I forget and can't remember. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [C][Homework] sending an EOF causing and issue between Windows CMD and Mac Terminal in different compiles of a program </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-11-19 07:48:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So i wrote a program that while entering a while loop to enter in numbers into a array if you press Ctrl-Z, sending an EOF, it stop entry and then displays the entry of the array up to where you entered it.

Now it works fine under Windows but when I pushed Ctrl-D, which is the mac terminal / linux / bash equivalent it caused a crazy loop that just does the exit out of the loop for the while loop but keeps sending some sort of keypress that causes a menu it returns too to just circle infinitely.

Here is the code: https://github.com/PatrickRoanhouse/CS-50-Tuesday-Night/blob/0f8de38e01f3cdbb1d69c5199f70bcfec650933b/C/Assignments/statistics.c </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The Amazing Arachnid Fellow Template </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-11-19 02:14:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Am I the only one who was reminded of this from last nights episode? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-11-16 02:17:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Idiot simple guide how to use WugFresh Nexus Root Toolkit to help install Android 5.0 Lollipop for Nexus Devices. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-11-15 01:01:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> TIL and went WTF that Beverly Hills uses 286 gallons per person per day in September. Meanwhile, the East LA used just 48 gallons per person per day, the lowest in the southland. But the worst is wealthy Orange County suburb Cowan Heights, at 569 gallons of water per person per day! </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-11-10 11:26:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [C][Homework] Passing pointers to sub functions and then to other sub functions. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-11-08 01:11:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Ok so i have this assignment where i need to make a Mini Statistics application in C that processes data to an array from data entered. It must keep a count of how many entries you make and then once it gets and EOF stop taking the input. It then returns you back to the home menu where you can then select to view the processed statistics from the data. It then takes you back to the home menu and then when you try to enter in data again if it see there is already data it will ask if you want to add more or start a new data set.

I'm trying to make sure i'm getting the pointer I need right to keep a counter that when the program starts initializes to count = 0 but then as it processed down to sub-functions and functions that call other functions it is passed properly so it can be counted and then minus 1 to not display the EOF entry as well as know where to display to and start reentry of data from.

if you enter in CTRL-Z or CTRL-D or the end-of-file symbol while entering in data on a line entry on your system it drops out of the data entry loop and takes you back to the main menu. I want to add a message saying "Data entry completed at line  %d," *count before the menu shows back up.

I'm not sure if i'm doing it right  though.


**I can't use structs, I'm not allowed to use gets or fgets yet. I have to do this with scanf on the inputs.**

So its pointers and arrays. 

So am I doing it right to pass the count between them and if not what am i doing wrong

my data is stored in the array data and then the MAX is a defined number for 200 entries and the counter for where it is written last to in the array for the counter is count

https://gist.github.com/PatrickRoanhouse/525cea91106db62fce43 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [C] writing to an array that ends entry with an End Of File, but then lets you resume entry to a set or start a new set of data to the array. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-10-31 20:45:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> 
Ok so so I have an assignment to write a menu-driven mini-statistics package. A user should be able to enter up to 200 items of float data.

The program should calculate or show:

1. The data it self in an organized table format
1. the number of items
1. the mean
1. the standard deviation
1. the variance
1. the median
1. the mode of the data
1. The high values in the data
1. the low values in the data

When entering the data though if you enter in CTRL-Z or CTRL-D or the end-of-file symbol on your system it drops out of the data entry loop and takes you back to the main menu.

The menu options are easy enough

1. Enter data
2. Display the processed data
3. Quit program

But when you go back to enter data again it will ask you the program should also ask if you wish to add more data to your data set or create a new data set.

So I'm not sure how to do this kind of function where it stores a count of if I have already entered in data. Also i'm not quite sure how to do the End of File with the entering data into an array.

I have some pseudo code for my enterdata() function but all the rest of the code done. I'm assuming the fact that i'm calling the menu items back i use a counter with the entry to see if it had already been entered and if not then i reset the data entry counter. But i'm not fully sure.


Some advice is greatly appreciated.

I have a gist right here for it.

https://gist.github.com/8a00cc470e59db50c489.git
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> CHP officer says stealing nude photos from female arrestees phones a 'game' between LAPD   CHP, with trading pictures between departments and offices. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-10-25 23:54:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The culmination of 10 years of animation in the Bruce Timm DC Animated Universe and the writing of Dwayne McDuffie gave way to one of the best twists and best season finale of any DC property. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-10-16 22:01:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Anyone know any good westside primary care doctors that take medi-cal? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-10-16 02:12:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So I got on medi-cal and was wondering if anyone knows any good primary care doctors in the westside? Some that can be gotten to via the big blue bus is a plus. Currently I'm near Sawtelle and Pico if that can give any idea of someone near me?

Also a therapist   psychologist too if you know any that take medi-cal too.

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Health insurance will only cover rental of a CPAP machine, which costs upfront $190 plus $25 a month </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-08-22 21:25:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I want to buy one outright and I was wondering if I could get some suggestions.

Looking for something portable if possible.

My sleep study results were: 

* AHI 28.5
* O2 nadir 77%
* CPAP titrated to 13 cm H20 with large oro-nasal mask

Help on this greatly needed 
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Ferguson police response is police playing army men in 'a municipal version of shock and awe' </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-08-14 20:01:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> US Congressional Rep. Steve King (Rep-IA) says Ferguson police not racially profiling protesters because they appeared to be of a "single origin, a single continental origin might be the way to phrase that." </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-08-14 19:59:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
