<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject670</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Life Hardened Dog </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-10-09 19:21:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-10-08 17:20:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> My guess is that [Jace, Architect of Thought](http://magiccards.info/rtr/en/44.html) is uniquely qualified to deal with 1/X creatures.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-10-08 16:38:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> When did she say "my turn?" </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-10-08 16:26:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Did you write the (hover)/(rollover) text for the comic yourself or something? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> How much do Planeswalker's finals even matter? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-10-08 05:28:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Ummm.... where am I? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-10-06 19:08:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> My Nana </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-10-04 15:26:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> TIL that the religious order which worships Vladimir Putin as the reincarnation of Paul consists ONLY of women. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-10-01 16:56:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> TIL Rice grown in the US has more arsenic in single serving than what the EPA allows in a quart of drinking water. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-09-29 02:33:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-09-28 15:07:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You need [this](http://magiccards.info/cp/en/9.html). </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-09-28 07:57:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> But, we treat each form of life differently. Ask a chicken or a skin cell if being alive is enough for legal rights.

So, while you are correct, one would have hoped you would have understood the context of the question. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-09-27 20:20:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What if McDs had a Republican website and a Demacrat website?

"Mitt likes eating Hotdogs"

"Obama can't get enough fries!"

If your an atheist, click here to see why atheists like McDs! If you love Jesus, click here instead! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Everyone loves Doom Blade, but hates Essence Scatter. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-09-24 05:57:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-09-21 14:28:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I always thought "Assemble" would just be a keyword for [this ability](http://magiccards.info/query?q=o%3Aput+o%3Aa+o%3Acreature+o%3Atoken+t%3A%22creature%22 v=card s=cname) or [this ability](http://magiccards.info/fut/en/109.html).  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-09-14 00:00:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> No, no you'll not. You'll get into an unresolvable rules argument and leave feeling bitter you did not get more lands. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-09-13 20:22:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yes, it will retain the X, but--as a side note--it will not cause the reverberate to be shuffled into the deck. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-09-13 17:47:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Rancor does not pump toughness. If it did, then you would be [correct](http://gatherer.wizards.com/Pages/Card/Details.aspx?multiverseid=205112). (check under Rulings)

*10/1/2009	All damage that would be dealt to Protean Hydra is prevented, even if it doesn't have that many +1/+1 counters on it. This is true even if Protean Hydra has no +1/+1 counters on it at all (and is able to remain on the battlefield because some other effect is boosting its toughness). If the amount of damage that would be dealt to Protean Hydra is greater than the number of +1/+1 counters on it, all the +1/+1 counters on Protean Hydra are removed from it.* </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-09-13 17:42:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I think you're just looking at [Reinforcements](http://gatherer.wizards.com/Pages/Card/Details.aspx?multiverseid=184597) and [Remember the Fallen](http://gatherer.wizards.com/Pages/Card/Details.aspx?multiverseid=218078) then.  

You could try and pull some shenanigans with soulshift and [Ashes of the Fallen](http://gatherer.wizards.com/Pages/Card/Details.aspx?multiverseid=87334) or with [Mycosynth Lattice](http://gatherer.wizards.com/Pages/Card/Details.aspx?multiverseid=50527) and all of whites artifact retrieval cards (most of which hit 1 cc), but neither sound worth it.
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Why does everyone on Ravnica hate Izzet? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-09-11 15:22:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Are they the villains of the set? 

I know all of the guilds hate all of the guilds, and that less than half of the set has been spoiled. But, it does seem like a disproportionate number of the other guilds' flavor text talk about having to stop Izzet/Niv. 

Rakdos seems to not even be drawing as much hate from the other guilds as Izzet </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-09-10 23:00:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Nerdy AND expensive! Are those **Alpha**... nope, NVM, false alarm, just *Collectors Edition.* </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Why would they do this? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-09-09 11:43:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-09-03 18:43:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> http://www.youtube.com/watch?v=F0bMWRt7ZLI </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> ObamaChair </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-09-03 18:38:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Twins! </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-09-03 17:15:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Which RTR reprints would be a good idea, and which would not? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-09-03 07:17:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-09-02 08:14:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If he played it on his turn one he could have dropped his Golem his one turn easily which was strictly better than playing his thorn on that turn against storm combo. 

However, that minor point is immaterial next to the fact he simply CAN'T play it turn two like he does. You would NEVER cast Chalices for 0 *before* playing a Mox. Unless you like (countering your own spells)and/or(cheating) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-09-01 21:24:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This statement would make more sense if he did not already HAVE to show his hand, with the card in question in it.... as I already said (and linked to the exact moment it happened) in the OP.

Your statements might be more useful if you watch the videos you are commenting on. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Guns in NM for non-citizens; home safety advice </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-09-01 11:40:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> My wife recently moved to NM while I finish up my degree. In the apartment complex she moved to a 20something male knocked on her door and tried to get her to buy some children's books from a website based on a laminated pamphlet he had.  He then started asking her questions about her current living arrangements and finished by asking for money.  She was a little shaken from the whole ordeal. One of my suggestions was that she take some shooting lessons. However, she isn't a US citizen (she is a permeant resident). She was telling me she would not be able to get a gun license in NM. 

Does anyone have any suggestions or knowledge about how to handle this situation?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-09-01 11:23:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If it was a Mox, why did he not just play it on his turn one? We can see it in his hand then! Nothing makes any sense anymore!

I guess this is just one of those great mysteries my mind was never meant to comprehend. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-09-01 10:39:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> But, what COULD it be? I know of no magic card with the properties presented. I was hoping r/magicTCG might shed some light on that.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Is the guy on the left cheating? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-09-01 09:06:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This has been driving me nuts all day. I don't know anything about this game or know any of the players, but I want to know just to know.

At [2:04 he plays it](http://www.youtube.com/watch?v=MqUuALUbwAM#t=2m03s). I can't make out the card, but they call it a "Mox Prox." Every other card played in all the videos are given their proper name, so I don't know why they call it that. But, if it was a Mox it should have cost 1 because of [Thorn of Amethyst](http://magiccards.info/lw/en/262.html), and then have been counted because [Chalice](http://magiccards.info/mi/en/150.html) is at 0. It was in his [opening hand](http://www.youtube.com/watch?v=MqUuALUbwAM#t=0m30s) we see when he was distressed, and he did not play it turn one. So, maybe it was a land, issue resolved. 

 BUT, in the next game he plays what seems to be the same card *(they again call it a "Mox Prox")* [after he already played and used a Wasteland](http://www.youtube.com/watch?v=11gvaMLgC28#t=0m52s).

So, what is going on? It is a land? Is it a Mox? Both? Neither? What the heck is a "Mox Prox?" Please, I just want to know...... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-09-01 06:42:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If it was a mox it should have cost 1 because of [Thorn of Amethyst](http://magiccards.info/lw/en/262.html), and then have been counted because [Chalice](http://magiccards.info/mi/en/150.html) is at 0. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-09-01 03:29:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> In that same group of videos, what is "Mox Prox?"

At [2:04 he plays it](http://www.youtube.com/watch?v=MqUuALUbwAM#t=2m03s). I can't make out the card. Whatever it is it was in his opening hand and he did not use it on turn 1. So it might be a land, but with a name like "Mox Prox" I'm unsure.

If it was a mox it should have cost 1 because of [Thorn of Amethyst](http://magiccards.info/lw/en/262.html), and then have been counted because [Chalice](http://magiccards.info/mi/en/150.html) is at 0. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-09-01 01:40:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I hope that's not true, or he really cheated hard.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Can anyone make the card out in this video? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-09-01 00:43:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> At [2:04 he plays it](http://www.youtube.com/watch?v=MqUuALUbwAM#t=2m03s). I can't make out the card. Whatever it is it was in his opening hand and he did not use it on turn 1. So it might be a land, but with a name like "Mox Prox" I'm unsure.

Edit: If it was a mox it should have cost 1 because of [Thorn of Amethyst](http://magiccards.info/lw/en/262.html), and then have been counted because [Chalice](http://magiccards.info/mi/en/150.html) is at 0. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-08-31 23:44:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I can't make out the card. Whatever it is it was in his opening hand and he did not use it on turn 1. So it might be a land, but with a name like "Mox Prox" I'm unsure.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-08-30 23:36:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I built it on Apprentice:

20 Black Lotus

20 Ancestral Recall

20 Lightning Bolt

Wins turn one every time.

Edit: Oh, I'm dumb, NVM. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-08-30 16:51:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Really? Because when I die and my wife has all of these cards she doesn't like taking up space, I would rather she sell them and use the money. I would HATE for her to get ripped off when she does that, obviously, but I would **especially** not want her to hang on to them if they made her depressed, like it seems they do for the OP. 

I think it would be rather selfish of me to expect her to hang on to something that makes her sad, takes up space, and could be potentially worth something after I'm gone.  But, maybe that's just me. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-08-30 15:47:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> First, find out what addition the oldest ones are (check the binder, the box you can probably just look for ones that 'look old'). This can be done pretty quick, [use this guild](http://www.abugames.com/Magic_the_Gathering_Edition_Guide.html). (Alpha/Beta/Unlimited cards are $$$, even though they often have crappy looking art)

As was said, if they are any from 1993-1998 then you might have something worth a lot.  Otherwise, you might want to plug a few of the cards in the binder into [this search](http://blacklotusproject.com/) and see what values you get back.

Now, this part is key.  Most players have all of their most value cards in a "deck."  The deck is probably in its own case somewhere. It normally is 60-100 cards.  So, if you have some smaller box inside of a larger box that has 60-100 cards, you might want to plug some of the names into that card searcher and see what you have.  When doing that look for cards with an [old copyright date](http://www.abugames.com/images/guidetoeditions/4th_Edition_Date.jpg), ones with a gold/red set symbol (see the guild for what a set symbol is), or ones with NO copyright date (those are normally worth the most).

If you don't find any cards worth something you care about, just take it to your local comic shop and sell them. If you find ones worth a bit (or ANY cards from Alpha/Beta/Unlimited or with no copyright date), you probably should post here again for more advice.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-08-25 04:28:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Needs more [Collector Protector](http://magiccards.info/uh/en/7.html). Why rip up all their cards when you can own them instead? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-08-21 04:48:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> No, nor am I the one on the card. It's just one of my favorites for various reasons. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-08-21 03:54:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> When will we do [Rootwater Thief](http://magiccards.info/ne/en/40.html)?

;) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-08-20 06:55:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Your statements are objectively false. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-08-20 06:18:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> "*Witz's deck is actually from his Ohio State Championship win; Academy's reign in Standard was exceedingly short (bannings and all that). But don't worry! Magic in 19981999 was largely a flurry of Tolarian Academys, Time Spirals, Windfalls, Dream Halls, Yawgmoth's Bargains... Plenty plenty. So... Mox Diamond (discarding Ancient Tomb)
Mana Vault, tap for 3 Voltaic Key (2 left), untap Mana Vault (1 then 4 after the re-tap) Lotus Petal (we'll leave that for now)
Tolarian Academy, tap for UUUU Time Spiral (2 floating, untap the Academy) After a Time Spiral drawing seven you could probably figure a way to win. It would probably involve Mind Over Matter (allowing repeated untaps of the Academy, eventually fueling Stroke of Genius and / or further Spirals). What turn, you ask? One.*" http://www.wizards.com/magic/magazine/article.aspx?x=mtg/daily/td/207 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-08-20 06:10:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Why would anyone just want to pander to magic card players? 

I guess I don't understand your perceived motivation for the comic; nor do I really understand what you hope to accomplish with your hostility. If you don't like a link, down vote it. If enough people don't like it, it will fall into oblivion quickly. Thus, if people don't like something it goes away, and if they do like it it lingers.

That's -like- how reddit works. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-08-20 05:25:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Pandering to whom? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-08-20 01:50:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm pretty sure [Mind Over Matter](http://magiccards.info/ex/en/40.html) would impact standard if it was reprinted. [Gilded Lotus](http://magiccards.info/m13/en/206.html) + [Blue Sun's](http://magiccards.info/mbs/en/20.html) jumps to mind and just being able to tap down guys for free every turn is not even that bad. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-08-20 01:21:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Which ones are fucking horrible? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-08-20 01:01:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Right ; remove 3 counters and swing for 12, then next turn swing for 9. Kill someone right quick with [that deck](http://www.wizards.com/magic/samplehand.asp?x=mtg/daily/td/207 decknum=8) back in the day. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-08-20 00:51:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [Fires of Yavimaya](http://magiccards.info/pc2/en/92.html) was good because of [Saproling Burst](http://magiccards.info/ne/en/113.html) and [Blastoderm](http://magiccards.info/ne/en/102.html).

It is meta depended, but [just look](http://magiccards.info/m13/en/129.html) how much "All your creatures have haste" costs now-a-days. 

Getting a free minnie [Seal of Strength](http://magiccards.info/ne/en/115.html) is not bad either. Dodge some kinds of removal or free combat trick. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> All the cards you love to hate. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-08-19 23:30:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-08-15 03:16:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Nothing is resolving when you cast the spell. The stack looks like this:

1) Reverberate (targeting Ghostly Flicker)

2) Ghostly Flicker

You let the reverberate resolve and then the copy resolve and the stack looks like this:

1) Archaeomancer ETB trigger (targeting Reverberate)

2) Ghostly Flicker
 
You let the ETB trigger resolve and get your Reverberate back. The Ghostly Flicker has long since lost track of its targets, but it's still on the stack waiting to fizzle. You need to pass priority between each resolution, but you don't have to "go all the way to the bottom." No. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-08-15 02:26:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This can be done with one less Archaeomancer and one less Lotus, but you would need to have at least 2 mana.

You could cast the Flicker and with it on the stack, copy it, targeting the Lotus and the 'mancer with the copy. The copy resolves and you get it back, with the flicker still on the stack. Rince an repeat, with 2 less cards. Just don't let the flicker resolve until you have infinite mana. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> I feel old, all this makes me think is 'Why isn't Rancor seeing more play?' </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-08-13 04:19:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-08-09 22:55:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It simply states: Batterskull + Stoneforge = Broken

It does not explain why: Batterskull  Stoneforge. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-08-09 18:28:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Alright, then explain to the guy I was answering why Stoneforge was banned not batterskull, since that was the question I was answering. So, if my answer is the wrong one, what is the right one? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-08-09 17:01:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> No, Stoneforce was banned.  If you banned Batterskull they would still have [swords](http://magiccards.info/query?q=%22sword+of%22+%28e%3Anph%2Fen+or+e%3Ambs%2Fen+or+e%3Asom%2Fen%29 v=card s=cname) to go for. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Poor Augur of Bolas, if only it really worked that way. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-08-05 05:29:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What's up with standard? How's Delver these days? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-07-21 21:04:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-07-16 03:07:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> How many people over the decades have only played one game of Magic precisely because their 'teacher' acted like Jake?  

I cannot even begin to guess. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-07-16 00:17:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This card has the exact formatting it would have in [MSE](http://magicseteditor.sourceforge.net/), right down to the size of the image and file name. Also, [this](http://forums.mtgsalvation.com/attachment.php?attachmentid=133193 d=1342232295) is the pic we have of that card. The final nail in the coffin for it being real is that it does not have a watermark. 

It is pretty cool, however. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> One of the ONLY complaints about the first Ravnica was that the sets were too predictable, is that still true? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-07-15 22:44:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> M13 is all, like, you know, 'Whatever,' man... 'Whatever' </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-07-01 22:32:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What do people think of this week's No Shyfts? (besides that it can't top last week's) </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-06-25 00:44:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> No Shyfts: What red card are they waiting for? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-06-17 19:46:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-06-11 22:57:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Well, if competitive players are your target I don't know why they made it cost 1UG not UG.

That is another question I have about these. They always seem to make new cards that would be perfectly fine in standard, but they're only legal in Legacy and Vintage. If you're printing cards only legal in those formats, why not up the power-level a little? Would it have kill a format to make [Silent-Blade Oni](http://magiccards.info/pc2/en/105.html) cost 1-2 less to play and 1-2 less to Ninjutsu? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-06-11 22:52:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's Magic. What about it is consequential? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-06-11 15:23:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yes, the planes are like that.

But if you are making +20 new cards JUST for this multiplayer set you'd think that would be a good time to make lots of multiplayer cards. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Good Point, how come PlaneChase did not have more multiplayer cards? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-06-11 03:14:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-06-04 02:20:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> "Pssssst!"   "Want to fling this goblin?" </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What should've this week's No Shyfts! have said? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-06-04 02:02:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-05-31 19:16:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If your cube is color balanced and everyone at the table doesn't like playing red -as you say- then any red card would be enough for me to play it knowing it would be wide open.

Other that that, without knowing the composition of your cube the question is unanswerable. In some cubes [Fireball](http://magiccards.info/m12/en/131.html) would be pick one pack one every-time, in others [Urabrask the Hidden](http://magiccards.info/nph/en/98.html) or [Bogardan Hellkite](http://magiccards.info/ddg/en/47.html) might not ever make the cut. In the sets with those cards, I would draft red if I saw them in pack one, but it's set dependent. If Hellkite was in Innistrad instead of Time Spiral I might not draft it because Innistrad is a faster format. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-05-29 19:11:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The answer to the question is buried under tons of shit arguing about what 'overrated' means.

If you feel a thread explaining the comic is necessary, I invite you to make it yourself. You could not help but do a better job of it than I. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-05-29 19:01:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I now understand what you were saying, but I am now confused why you are being hostil to me when you -apparently- agree with me. 

Honestly, this whole thread is just a clusterfuck.  I just wanted to know why in panel 2 they talked about him having a 'walker spark *before* he was bonded to the devils. While you and I bickered about something we both agree on, Folcon kindly answered that question of mine in a single sentence. I feel like I should just delete this thread since it has served its propose. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-05-29 14:04:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Ah, thank you. That is where my misunderstanding came from. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-05-29 14:03:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> and he is a new planeswalker either way.

I never made any specific assertation that being a planeswalker means he should be worth more.

and people love planeswalkers.

 I'm not saying that planeswalkers should be worth more. 

Now I am even more confused. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-05-29 05:23:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I did not say it "should" be worth $25, I am saying he "should" be worth less because people are not using him to play magic, which is traditionally what one does with magic cards. 

I am also pointing out that if one rates something higher than one should because of inconsequential attributes, like -say- card type, instead of consequential attributes, like -say- playability, one is overrating that something.

Being an instant is better than being a sorcery, but that does not mean all instants are better than all sorceries. Assigning a higher value to a bad instant simply because some other instants are worth money would be **overrating** that bad instant. 
The same holds true for planeswalkers.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-05-29 05:02:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Him not seeing play does not necessary mean he is underrated; it could just mean he is a bad card, which would mean $15 is too high, not too low.  Thus, he would be overrated, not underrated. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-05-29 04:56:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I did read it, and that's why I was confused. If you -yourself- read the story you will note he did not get his spark until after he bonded with the demons.

$15 for a card not seeing play does not strike me as "underrated." If anything, saying "Well, he's a planeswalker, so he should be worth more" seems to me to be the very definition of *overrating* something. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-05-29 04:40:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm more talking about panel 2. Also, how is he "underrated?" He's going for $15. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-05-26 21:35:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thank you, exactly my point. If you want to show a link in motivation you would first have to show Muslims have a higher % of petos than a neutral group. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> I thought Sorin was the hero for this block? What did he do? Also, who burns a Shyft!? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-05-21 14:58:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-05-19 01:31:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> And stalin was an atheist.

I we are arguing about "most." Not "a few of the crazies from the group." </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-05-18 22:59:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Alright, well enlighten me. Show me that most modern Muslims use this to justify pedophile. I did not realize pedophile was widespread in the Islamic community to do their prophet's actions. I am also unaware that most people at Fox New think it's ok to rape African-Americans just like their idols the founding father did. Can you send me that citation too?


Demonizing the past is as bad as idolizing it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-05-18 18:12:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If you don't like "evil" I can replace it with your words of "not mean such thing is in the right."

The person being talked to is not trying to use the actions of Muhammad to justify stachatory rape.  As far as I know, no one here is. 

Which makes me ask why people are even bringing up that others use Muhammad's actions to justify contemporary pedophile? Does anyone here NOT think it's abhorrent? Done anyone here NOT think doing so would be ludicrous? Heck, most modern Muslims feel it would be.

I am not here to criticize the satirization of a historical figure. Make all the humorous cartoons you want. However, I am here to criticizes the critic of someone that was trying to put those actions in their proper historical context.  

Giving people a better understanding of what is being depicted is not censorship. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-05-18 17:33:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Of course it would be wrong to act that way **today** but we are not talking about someone acting that way *today,* we are talking about someone acting that way 1500 years ago.  

I agree with you that no one should use things that were common practice 1500 years ago to justify how one acts in today's society; however, no one on this thread IS.  They are simply pointing out that at the time it was not **socially** wrong to act that way, and -in fact- might have been seen as practical. 

It is ignorant to judge someone as evil just because they lived in a time and place that did not have your enlightened sensibilities.

Spitefully, I hope some teenager 1500 years from now draws a picture of you bloodily eating a cute cow *(or whavever)* and posts it on the psyweb to show how evil you "are." </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-05-17 23:00:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Also, the way the new blinkers are worded the creature is under your control when it comes back in even if you don't *own* it.

So, you can [Traitorous Blood](http://magiccards.info/isd/en/166.html) something and then [Cloudshift](http://magiccards.info/query?q=!Cloudshift) it and now they'll not get it back at end of turn. 

The creature is a new object and under your control. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-05-17 21:45:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It seems to be working for me. Its talking about going back to Ravnica, horrible elves, and furry Jace. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-05-17 19:22:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So far in each core set they have brought back something in oder to foreshadow the upcoming block (like [scry](http://magiccards.info/m11/en/70.html)).  

There is strong evidence this core set will have multicolored cards as the returning theme. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-05-16 21:14:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [How about a cycle of baneslayers?](http://5colorcontrol.com/images/fanart/Jokecards/cycle.jpg) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-05-15 22:06:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah, I think your approximations are fine, and I think it's really cool that you did this; the Un values just jumped out at me because they were so much higher than the price of a pack from those sets.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-05-15 21:53:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I've never opened any packs from those sets so I don't know, sorry :( But I found this about Alpha:
Due to the printing process, it is possible to get land cards in a rare, uncommon, or common card slot. The chance is approximately 3.31% for rares, 21.5% for uncommons and 38.02% for commons. This is because they put lands on all three printed sheets.

http://wiki.mtgsalvation.com/article/Alpha </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-05-15 21:40:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I think your Un-prices are off. They seem to assume that a basic land is a Common, and you have a chance to get one in a Common slot.  This is not the case.

Basic lands come one each pack as a basic land, not as a common.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-05-15 17:03:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If no one cares, why did so many people reply? If it's stupid, why not down vote it to let me know? That's what I'm asking. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-05-15 16:56:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> 2 out of 12 would mean "most" not "some." 

Anyway, most secular historical scholars would disagree with your claim that Jesus did not exist http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Historical_Jesus#Scholarly_methods 

The disagreement about Jesus normally centers about the extraordinary claims made about him. The claim that he walked around and preached stuff not being extraordinary, certainly not for the time. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-05-15 16:48:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Greater than 12 comments.

Less than 3 votes.

Can someone explain, this keeps happening to me. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-05-14 16:33:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [Catgeddon](http://images2.wikia.nocookie.net/__cb20070412010353/uncyclopedia/images/2/24/There_can_only_be_one_Longcat.jpg) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-05-14 14:11:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [Try this.](http://www.5colorcontrol.com/comic.php) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Innistrad doesn't have a happy ending for everyone. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-05-13 22:24:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-05-12 14:53:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Needs [Reassembling Skeleton](http://magiccards.info/query?q=!Reassembling%20Skeleton). 

Regeneration does not save a creature being sacrificed, but Reassembling Skeleton's ability will bring it back no matter how it go into the 'yard. With all your sac effects, you need that. 

Some other Skeletons of note: [Skeletal Vampire](http://magiccards.info/gvl/en/46.html), [Augur of Skulls](http://magiccards.info/query?q=Augur+of+Skulls v=card s=cname), and [Skithiryx, the Blight Dragon](http://magiccards.info/som/en/79.html). </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-05-12 00:15:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That's not 45 cards. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-05-11 16:50:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'd get 3 Ice Age packs so I could beat you with a [Shyft](http://gatherer.wizards.com/pages/card/Discussion.aspx?multiverseid=2532). </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-05-09 22:51:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Sounds like that ep of *It's Me or the Dog* were the dog was really sweet until its owner left.  Then it would try to assure its dominance over the GF. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Pie Bear </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-05-09 22:33:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-05-08 02:08:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> There is no such thing as "enough removal" in limited.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-05-07 23:41:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> First, you need to relax. If you psych yourself out about how a PTQ is 'so much different' then an FMN you'll just end up being super-nervous and end up playing poorly.

Second, just remember to be polite, fair, but hard on your opponent. No take backs; some players at a PTQ might try to play to your soft-side if they think you have one. Some nice guys will not and will suck up any mistakes they make, but others might complain and try to play on your emotions. Remember, expect the same level of play out of your opponent that you would expect out of yourself, not the other way around.

Most importantly, always call a judge if you are unsure about something. **Do not** try to work it out with the other guy. If you're not sure about what the proper procedure for whatever just happened, always call a judge and ask.  That's what they're there for. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-05-07 05:53:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Familiarize yourself with [the set](http://www.wizards.com/magic/tcg/article.aspx?x=mtg/tcg/avacynrestored/cig).

Since you're new don't even bother trying to "read signals" or something. I would just take the best card in each pack until you've got yourself 2 colors or so. If you are inexperienced I would just draft two colors. Don't go in knowing what those two colors are, but pick them halfway through the first pack or so.

Oh, and draft removal.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-05-06 23:25:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [Planeswalkers](http://www.wizards.com/magic/tcg/article.aspx?x=magic/rules/planeswalkers) would be a big change.

Also, no more stacking damage and a bunch of other [rules changes](http://www.wizards.com/magic/magazine/article.aspx?x=mtg/daily/feature/42a). 

Those are the big changes rules-wise, are you asking about something else?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-05-06 03:20:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [Reassembling Skeleton](http://magiccards.info/m12/en/104.html) does not have a "regenerating ability." It has an ability that works only when it is in the graveyard. That ability does not care how it ended up in the graveyard, countered, destroyed, or milled makes no difference. So, if it is countered you can still pay 1B and put it into play.  You also don't have to do it right away, but can do it on a later turn.

Welding Jar cannot be used on an artifact that is being counted for two reasons. One, it can only target a permanent, which a creature on the stack is not. Two, regenerating means that the next time it is destroyed (by a destroy effect or lethal damage) instead it is tapped, removed from combat, and has all damage removed from it.  "Counting" is not the same as "destroying" so regeneration does not stop it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-05-04 22:40:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [Poe's Law](http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Poe's_law) is probably the reason no one can tell if you're joking. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Atheism vs Religion: Survival of the Fittest! </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-05-04 22:13:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I was hoping we could talk about which people thought was more "evolutionarily sound," and let me explain what I mean by that. 
You can either be religious or atheistic, you can't be both. This means that both ideas are "competing for real estate" within a person's mind. As more people take up one idea, necessarily less people have the other. This is very analogous to natural selection within species, as one species beats out another to fill the same niche.

The "niche" here is human thought. 

As Robert Wright wrote in his book *The Evolution of God* we've seen this same kind of battle take place between religions. In the distant past, religion was clearly the way to think, since almost all human cultures evolved thinking it. You could not find a civilization *(higher than hunter/gather)* that did not have a form of religion. One religion would be better suited to get and convert more people, and as it did -necessarily- other religions shrink and were eventually replaced. The battle for the human soul, as it were. However, NOW more and more we are seeing a new "species" emerge in the form of atheism, and it too is competing for the same niche in human thought. Which will stick in the minds of men(and women) better? Which is more believable?

People are born without religion, but that form of nontheism is easily replaced with something else. That is the unthinking blank state of mind in which religion and other concepts can easily take root. I am not talking about that form of nontheism; I am talking about the "atheistic philosophy" *(as in, anything other than the "default" position)*; is IT more "fit" than religion? Is it better at converting people? Does it have what it takes to beat out religion? Or will it "die out" as many philosophies have before it? Or maybe religion will just die a natural death? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-05-04 21:51:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Something like this would require too much human impute per-card for it to be useful as a website. You idea about how often a card is used would me much simpler, and I think StarCity already has something along those lines.

I was entertaining the idea you might be able to write an equation that could give you the relative power level of cards in upcoming sets with more of an objective feel to it. I think you're also correct in that just randomly assigning numbers to the different values isn't the way to go about it. I was hoping to do some more tweaking, but the equation started getting too long and I just gave up.  Which is when I posted it here.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-05-04 20:31:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You're not being mean and I agree with your criticism. I spent about 20 mins thinking about it and writing it and than thought to myself "This is silly, so I better show the internet." </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-05-04 20:09:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Did they increase their own addition to the prize pool?  Or did they solely use the thing Wizards gave them for free as justification for raising the price?

If they added more stuff to the prize pool and raised the price, I guess I don't see any problems with that.  If they just did it because Wizards gave them something for free, then they're being scummy. *(and probably are ripping their customers off in less obvious, but equally scummy ways. Something like overcharging for a tournament is a symptom, not a disease.)* </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-05-04 19:31:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Well, I guess I am less upset because I plan on using my dice and my tokens. I am sorry you have no use for your dice and tokens; maybe you should sell them on ebay? *(which makes me wonder if you would be just as upset if the things inside were playable cards, but not cards you -personally- would ever play. Also, commons are readily available at any store. So I don't see how you'd rather them over dice based on that criterion.)*

The only thing I really don't like about this promotion is I can't seem to find an unopened Helvault *ANYWHERE.* I would be willing to pay big bucks for one for my collection of Magic oddities. I guess I will just have to settle for the opened one my local store owner gave me. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-05-04 18:01:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Probably needs a summation to represent those things over time.  Like [Dark Confidant](http://magiccards.info/query?q=!Dark%20Confidant)'s card advantage would be Sum(X/turns) or something.

Also for limitations.  How would [Doom Blade](http://magiccards.info/query?q=!Doom%20Blade) be compared to [Vindicate](http://magiccards.info/query?q=!Vindicate)? 

It needs an multiplier for instant speed. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> This equation for "Bustedness" needs A LOT of work! </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-05-04 17:57:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-05-04 16:40:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I read that article you are referring to and found it PR-sugarcoated.  I think it's clear why they canceled something as popular as Player Reward's, because of the abuses.  That they are planning on trying to find a less abusable way to make something as popular as Player Reward's, I have no doubt. That these kind of events at prereleases are an example of something they are trying -as you point out- I would also agree with.

In your post you seem to be saying that "useless" and "worthless" are the same thing. While the dice I got might not be worth $$$, I am planning on using them.  I find spindowns to be quite useful, if not worth money.  I do have a deck that [makes angels](http://magiccards.info/isd/en/213.html), so I should have a use for the tokens as well.  However, I understand your point about wanting something of value, which is the very reason I would like them to continue this kind of event. Maybe next time I will get something of value as well as something I can use.

As for the rest of your post, a mythic rare costs just as much to print as a common. Everyone likes opening mythic rares.  Wizards likes to keep some things in reserve in part so they can make more money. However, I -personally- don't hold the fact my Helvault didn't have any foils in it against Wizards anymore than I hold the fact I did not open any [Tamiyo's](http://magiccards.info/avr/en/79.html) in my packs.  Would I have liked to open a Tamiyo? Yes, but the fact that I did not makes the fact someone else did more special to them. I don't hold that against anyone. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-05-04 15:57:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Player's rewards were not "traded" for anything.  They got rid of them because the system was too easy to abuse.  People would run lots of fake sanctioned tournaments and claim players XYZ were involved, when really no tournament was happening.  Wizards had to pick between making it harder to run sanctioned tournaments and harder to register players, or do away with the prizes for playing in them. A handful of people ruined it for everyone.

I am finding it more and more likely that Wizards will also not do any more events like the Helvault.  I hope reddit is not representative, but if it is I don't see why they would continue with a program that seems to be generating such bad PR. 

I hope they continue it because I like getting free stuff and would like a chance to get a foil one next time, but I seem to be in the minority. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Frost Giant vs Frost Titan: Where 6 mana creatures have been and where they are now. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-05-03 02:36:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What do you want from me now? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-04-30 21:25:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [Crit] The Quintessential Mary-Sue [4310 words] [Fiction] </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-04-27 23:04:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [The Quintessential Mary-Sue](http://mrgreyman.deviantart.com/art/The-Quintessential-Mary-Sue-251827667) 

I attempted to capture the essence of this reoccurring wish fulfillment clich. I will accept any level of criticism; despite the nature of my work I do hope someday to produce something of value. This is not it, but I needed to get it out of my system.

There is also a [part two *word count:7797*](http://mrgreyman.deviantart.com/art/Mary-Sue-Part2-The-Three-Sues-254047856) and a [part three *word count:3320*](http://mrgreyman.deviantart.com/art/Mary-Sue-Final-Revelations-255491705) if the first wasn't enough for you. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> We named the dog Indiana (Jones).
 </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-04-27 22:53:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Where are you on the spectrum of theistic probability, and WHY? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-04-27 02:56:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [Spectrum of theistic probability:](http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Spectrum_of_theistic_probability#Dawkins.27_formulation)

* 1) Strong Theist; claims they *know* there is a God, without doubt.

* 2) Believes there is a God, but would not claim they know without doubt.

* 3) Weak Theist; uncertain, but feels a God is more likely than not.

* 4) Pure Agnostic; doesn't know and/or doesn't care. Finds the question ridiculous without presented evidence.

* 5) Weak Atheist; uncertain, but feels a god is more unlikely than not.

* 6) Believes there isn't a god, but would not claim they *know* without doubt.

* 7) Strong Atheist; claims they **know** there isn't a god, without doubt. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Where are you on the spectrum of theistic probability, and why? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-04-26 18:02:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [Spectrum of theistic probability:](http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Spectrum_of_theistic_probability#Dawkins.27_formulation)

* 1) Strong Theist; claims they *know* there is a God, without doubt.

* 2) Believes there is a God, but would not claim they know without doubt.

* 3) Weak Theist; uncertain, but feels a God is more likely than not.

* 4) Pure Agnostic; doesn't know and/or doesn't care. Finds the question ridiculous without presented evidence.

* 5) Weak Atheist; uncertain, but feels a god is more unlikely than not.

* 6) Believes there isn't a god, but would not claim they *know* without doubt.

* 7) Strong Atheist; claims they **know** there isn't a god, without doubt. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> From a Marketing stand point, was this a good move by Wizards? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-04-23 04:14:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> I WANT TO SEE THE BODY! (Wizards declares all non-Bolas elder dragons dead) </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-04-18 17:30:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [ASK WIZARDS](http://www.wizards.com/Magic/Magazine/Article.aspx?x=mtg/daily/activity/947)
 But in the past storyline, **the four Elder Dragons other than Nicol Bolas perished long ago**, so their chapter might be done. 

How can they just **casually** declare them dead like that?  There aren't even any stories *AT ALL* about [Arcades Sabboth](http://gatherer.wizards.com/pages/card/Discussion.aspx?multiverseid=1644), for example. Not one. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> How often will this happen in the Prerelease? Continually?  </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-04-15 22:42:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What the Hell is a Helvault? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-04-11 18:09:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> When Can I Get those lands? Also, App? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-03-31 00:01:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Will this kinda thing ever be acceptable on a real Magic Card? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-03-24 19:08:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Why is Venser dead in this pic? All the men look alike too... </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-03-19 14:53:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> None of This is Right about Magic, it is? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-03-17 19:04:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> ZOMBIE ROSEWATER! </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-01-23 19:48:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
