<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject7383</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-02-04 03:27:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Your gifs are awesome! I've been seeing them since last year and I wondered who made them.

If I weren't a poor undergrad myself I'd donate; if you're willing to share information for free I was curious about what program you used for these.

Also, since you're a physics student, what programs you use for modeling in general? I'm a chemist slowly turning to the dark side, but don't know the path of the sith. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Volunteering in a Lab While Teaching in a Middle/High School </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-01-18 17:56:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm currently a third year undergrad considering doing [Teach for America] (http://www.teachforamerica.org/) before going to graduate school.

Many of my top picks for grad school allow deferment if someone who's been accepted decides to do this program, but I'd like to keep my hands dirty to some degree while teaching; does anyone have experience volunteering in a lab part time or over summers while teaching or doing something else? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-01-18 17:43:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Asimov has some chemistry in his works, probably the most interesting of which is [thiotimoline] (http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Thiotimoline), a strained organic molecule that allows time travel. Asimov is really good at integrating science into his works, you can find a fair amount of math too, if that's your thing.

As said already, Vonnegut has chemistry in Cat's Cradle; Vonnegut actually studied chemistry at Cornell for a while and his brother was an atmospheric chemist, so his other books may have trace amounts of chemistry (but he hated studying it). </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-12-29 21:53:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> For what it's worth I know a 4th year ChemE who will be going to grad school for theoretical chemistry; just because your degree isn't in standard chem doesn't mean you're forced into engineering. Ask around and see if you can get a position in a chemistry lab at your current school.

Look into REUs instead of internships if you're really willing to dedicate yourself to it.


Also, this is probably lack of experience with you guys, but regular ChemEs don't seem to be the type who are really super interested in chemistry to the point they'll self-study for fun; you should really consider chemistry. (Bit of a warning, I'm pretty sure ChemEs make a lot more money, if that's a big motive for you.) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-12-07 08:29:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [Phenylacetaldehyde] (http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Phenylacetaldehyde)

I was a psych major taking a BS 1 credit "plants   you" course, the professor talked about this molecule's role in the allure of chocolate and roses; it worked, and ended up being the nucleation site for my interest in chemistry! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-12-07 04:46:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Fourier information, that's not true. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-12-07 04:28:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> |memorize

As a TA, I wish you guys would stop doing this; you're making OChem much harder than it needs to be. It's all about pattern recognition! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-12-04 17:18:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [This video] (http://www.youtube.com/watch?v=zPqEEZa2Gis) has an explanation of what causes it to fall slowly, as a bonus, there's also a supercooled magnet going around a mobius strip of other magnets by quantum levitation! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-12-03 21:08:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The most "painful" thing I've ever smelled was 25% ammonia.

Not paying attention, leaned over the bottle in the fume hood and took a deep breath through my nose. Felt like fire.

I jerked my head out, hit it on the sash and just stood there with my mouth open, ears ringing, and eyes watering. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-11-06 04:00:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Animal Farm.

I was in 7th grade and kept getting kicked out of my gifted class. The teacher sent me out to the hallway one day as usual, but came out after a few moments, handed me Animal Farm, and said something to the effect of:

 "You're a troublemaker, I think you'd like Orwell."

I still have that copy. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-10-13 05:25:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> We're starting the process of reactivating the chapter at my university. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-08-15 20:42:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's really short, and [free in the iBooks store.] (https://itunes.apple.com/us/book/metamorphosis/id395543620?mt=11)

But, from what I can remember of my teen-angst-filled essay way back in high school English, it's something of a diatribe of how the modern working man is equitable to a bug, doing things he hates for the sake of making money; once he can't fill the capacity of money maker for the family (likened to a company) they turned on him,

because that's what the man does, man.

[Kafka was a socialist/anarchist.] (http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Franz_Kafka#Political_views)

Edit: [Links] (http://images.wikia.com/zelda/images/e/e9/Link_%28Four_Swords%29.png) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> A girl from my university painted this flask for me (x-post r/breakingbad) </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-08-11 17:34:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> A friend of mine is an artist and she painted this flask for me </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-08-11 17:16:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-08-10 00:53:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [Finally!] (http://i1.ytimg.com/vi/Gr0SvQUVxSs/mqdefault.jpg) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-08-10 00:29:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Casein coagulation in response to acid.

Edit: [Here's a short video talking about protein denaturing and coagulation] (http://highered.mcgraw-hill.com/sites/0072943696/student_view0/chapter2/animation__protein_denaturation.html) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-08-08 20:36:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I had to quit when he called a bell curve fractal. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-08-01 19:16:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Definitely a drug; looks to be a tryptamine derivative.

Edit: [Ibogaine] (http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Ibogaine) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-06-22 17:40:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  It reeks of elitism and you come off as a jerk.

Looks like you had the answer just 3 lines up. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-06-18 18:42:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If you're that nervous, get Dr. David Klein's "Organic Chemistry as a Second Language."

Its slow pace bored me personally, but it certainly does drill *concepts* into your head; this class is not about memorization, it's about seeing patterns and applying them.

It has the stigma of "hard" from "lol I wanna be a doctor because doctor" premeds; this seems to be the case with many "hard" things, learning is much easier if you focus on the material more than the hearsay about it.

Edit: grammar </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-06-18 06:36:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That's a misnomer, it's a copolymer, which basically means it's in the structure as a repeating unit.

Not to suggest OP should go putting it in his mouth though, since, in addition to the whole wearing down your enamel bit, it does in fact leave behind a residue likely consisting of some stuff [that could make your kidneys mad at you.] (http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Melamine#Chronic_toxicity)

tl;dr: as a general rule, don't put cleaning products in your mouth. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-06-18 01:32:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Ah, New River Gorge was the first place I ever climbed outside of gyms!
Best of luck running from the rat race. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-06-16 17:11:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> At my school in the US the chemistry major requires the calculus sequence, and diffEQ is officially recommended; I'd suggest some linear algebra too, just to be safe, and if you're weird and like math (like me) get some PDE and complex analysis too.

That didn't answer your question, just letting you know what you're in for.


I didn't take my school's module, but I'd guess, broadly, you'll be doing "precalc," some light SV calc, and a bit of algebra and trigonometry. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-06-11 21:14:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> As someone who switched from biochem to chem (specifically protein interactions/genetics to organic electronics), I can tell you I certainly don't regret it.
Pursue your passions, half the time "hard" classes are only that way because of the stigma they carry by word of mouth.

You will almost certainly stand a better chance having taken more relevant coursework. You're not applying to med school, GPA is not the top determining factor. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-06-05 04:04:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Dr. David Klein's "Organic Chemistry as a Second Language" is very good, he also has a full book that my class, and the class I'm TAing this fall use.

The problems dispersed throughout the chapters are often too slowly paced, which is good for most organic students, since it drills the concepts into your head.

As a rule of thumb in OChem, do **not** memorize, *understand*.

Edit:
[UIUC](http://www.chem.uiuc.edu/weborganic/organictutorials.htm) has a great study program too. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-06-04 05:48:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I think you're misinterpreting what OP means.
(S)he wants to contact the author for advice since it isn't working in this case, not claim fraud. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-06-03 05:11:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Depends on the nature of the courses, consider pre-studying some of those classes over the summer, especially PChem if you're not so hot with math. Contact some of the professors and ask to see the syllabus and tentative course load. I hear the first grad OChem course is about 1/2 undergrad review, at least at my school.

This past semester I took: Honor's OChem II and lab, MV calc, DiffEQ, Physics I and lab, along with ~10 hrs/wk in a research lab, leadership in student ACS, and tutored some friends in OChem. I won't call it easy, but it wasn't as hard as other people thought it would be, and I definitely wouldn't consider myself exceptional; I had a reasonable amount of free time despite MV calc being more work than it was supposed to be and having no experience with physics prior (and I think kinematics is sleep inducing). </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-06-03 04:55:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'd never taken calculus before I got to college; I was actually afraid to take it. I added a math minor after calc 2 and did just fine taking calc 3 and diffEQ at the same time; challenge yourself, you'd be surprised what you might find out!

As for prep, iamnotazombie44 is correct, you don't really get to use it until later in chemistry, however, you should see a fair amount of it in your physics classes early on. Consider going above and beyond and taking linear algebra, it's used a TON in my QM class. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-05-30 02:35:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I've done all of those but linear, which I'll take in the fall; my school names things differently, linear and diffEQ are separate courses (diffEQ is actually 2 courses), and calc 3 is MV calc.

In my experience, calc 2 was so much fun it made me declare a mathematics minor.

Calc 3 (multivariable) was said to be a "reward for getting through calc 2." Maybe it was because the math department here is bleeding money, but we had an over the top course load, the course admin didn't seem to understand what constitutes "too much work," the material is fairly easy to grasp if you can conceptualize everything and imagine the graphs. Get cozy with integrations.

DiffEQ was...boring, despite having a very smart and funny professor, but that's the nature of the course, it was far easier than calc 2, I had it the same semester as MV calc, and it took significantly less time. It had some degree of memorization, which always sucks, but wasn't too bad. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-05-29 19:23:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm about to put in for a physics BA myself, and I'm also a second (rising into third) year chemistry undergraduate, so I can't offer too much advice on my own experience.

I had declared a math minor and adding a physics degree makes that minor more applicable, going into courses already knowing the math from an actual mathematics department course is hugely beneficial.

I do know a girl who decided to add physics as a second major, the advisors didn't actually file her application so that caused a slew of difficulties (but my university is known for trying to push people out to keep the 4 year graduation rate looking pretty in the statistics).

She said to file for it as early as possible, and make sure that the administration gets it filed.

As far as coursework, she told me there was tons of overlap and having both actually made classes somewhat easier. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-05-28 11:12:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [MIT OCW](http://ocw.mit.edu/courses/find-by-topic/)
Near everything you could ever need; the scholar courses are particularly well done.
Happy learning! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-05-21 00:48:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Bit of a warning, I did this for a class of first graders a few months ago, it smells bad, not like chemical bad, like dilute vomit bad; it may have been the kind I used, though you should still try it at home if you're doing this for a demonstration. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-05-20 15:01:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> +1 I work in these. (So that's really good news for me!)

In addition to being ridiculously cool on the chemical front, they have tons of applications; Heliatek wants to put OPVs in glass panes; someday, your home could be powered by its windows.

There's still loads to be done, the aforementioned company has the world record for PCE and it's only 12%. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-05-17 14:45:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Anyone here ever run a column on a fluorescent compound?

As annoying as the stains are working with them, they look like something akin to the northern lights in flash chromatography. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-05-16 04:45:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Fiancepeas is right.
Chemistry major weed outs vary by institution, I believe at my school it's instrumental analysis. OChem is the typical premed weed-out but it does trip up some chemists; Dr. David Klein's books are phenomenal for this class and I recommend it to people I don't have time to tutor.

I'm in a QM and spec (PChem 2) course now and the nature of the course is so unorthodox the professor is having us write our own exams (but there are only 7 of us). If you took AP chem you should be able to handle the gen chems, maybe skip the first.

I actually started off in neurogenetics lab doing protein purifications my freshman year, the project stalled and I went to a physical organic lab. For both labs I just emailed the PhD in charge and said I was interested in their research and wanted to know if they had any room for an undergrad; you may or may not be asked to interview, they won't expect you to know their stuff in and out (especially early on), but it'd be safe to glance over a couple publications to get an idea.

Professors have different expectations and quirks, there's no real finite science to getting a position; just get an idea of what you're interested in and ask about it, some will want you to have course experience, some won't, but typically starting early gets you some wiggle room on expectations since you have potential to stay on for all 4 years. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-05-15 13:45:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I started off as an English and Psychology double major just drifting through taking whatever I felt like, but always found chemistry interesting; my first semester I took general chem 1 and got a B-, two short years later and I'm about a month away from authorship on an upcoming publication, president of the chemistry club, and my retiring professor is offering me a job tutoring OChem and calculus for him at his new business (plus a few other accolades but I'm not trying to be a braggart, just make a point).

My advice would be don't get discouraged by "weed-out" courses; if you stumble, pick yourself up and keep going, you never know what you might accomplish. Don't stray from the "enhanced" or "honors" designated courses; in my experience, these classes are easier due to smaller size and more enthusiastic professors.

Also, don't think that just because you like it on paper you'll like it in lab (and start research ASAP!); bench chemistry can be extremely frustrating and arduous, but, if you really love it you'll just find yourself keeping at it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
