<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject9012</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-15 18:42:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> have a seat bud </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-15 18:36:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> on an unrelated note Facebook is down! Prime Day and facebook down day fuck yea!!!!! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-15 18:32:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [32" Lg 720p Smart Tv](http://www.amazon.com/gp/product/B00ZVD007O?ref_=gb1h_tit_m-5_2162_fd8e91dd smid=ATVPDKIKX0DER) deal is over </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-15 18:21:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> imho we will not see those until this evening to keep us all clicking refresh all day. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-15 18:20:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> nope </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-15 18:18:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> 32" 720p Smart tv by LG nothing special imho regular price $270. On sale for $199. They probably have a fuck ton too. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-15 18:15:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> yes  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-15 18:14:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> it's up right now
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-15 18:11:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> the 32" LG is up right now. 

edit: I originally said Vizio , my blunder. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-15 18:10:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> My local thrift stores always have great stuff except video games. Retro gaming is almost as big as Next Gen (new systems) in my area. Only time you find a deal is at a yardsale of some unlucky basterds grandparents. Consider yourself super lucky!!! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-15 17:40:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I really thought I noticed a difference on my buddies Tv that is 1080 p like mine but 120hz where mine is only 60hz. I'm still getting a new tv specifically for my PS4. It will be 120 hz regardless. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-15 17:32:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Doesn't change the fact he wore heels because Lucille Ball was taller than him. Which means he was down playing his height. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-15 17:29:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> hmmm I'll take a look. Thanks again
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-15 17:12:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> dam I really thought this would be a difference maker on ps4. Thanks for the heads up.
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-15 17:09:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I have a theory that the 40" will be released this evening so people like us that are waiting for it will see all the other sales as the day progresses and start impulse buying as we wait. As I just did lol </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-15 17:03:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If it's 120hz then I'm all over it regardless of brand. Otherwise I'll pass. My ps4 told me it wants 120hz </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-15 15:41:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That looks really easy to walk around with or put in your pocket while on the go! How much $ all together? My grandson loves new technology!! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-15 13:26:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Popeye  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-15 13:19:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Did you get the free sailboat? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-15 13:12:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> no just poseable. pull string was a later model. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-15 13:11:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This is NOT the pull string version. His jacket looks like it was once sewn at the buttons to keep it on. Now the jacket comes off. Some kid decided to draw over his eyebrows and lips with what looks like black magic marker. His white shirt has some light brown discoloration. I bout shat myself when I saw it today at the Goodwill here in town. I had the pull string edition when I was young and thought that he would have it but he does not.
    How can I get the marker off his face without taking his original paint off? I could sand it right off but his red lips and true black eyebrows will go with it. Any suggestions? Thanks in advance!
    Buy it now on EBAY looks about $15-$20

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-15 02:07:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You're kidding right. 360 games kept looking better all the way up to Gta V right before the next gens were released. Stay gold Ponyboy </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-15 02:04:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> i need a gif of him pointing at "it" ball up in his hand. "Do it!" </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-15 01:55:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> My longest ever was roughly 2 hours on Skyrim. My character on Gta V looked exactly like me and took about 45 min. Which is probably an average time for me. You figure you're goingto be this toon the whole game it better be legit. It's like when people buy cheap shoes. You're on your feet like all day treat the bottom of your feet better/spend at least 45 min building a character. Duh. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-15 01:51:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yea he won't be confused about gaming's history. lol At least give him full screen Dad fuck sake </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-15 01:30:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Garbage. Blunt and Honest. A man has opinions. A man doesn't care about the repercussions. Seriously though I paid $60 for it and played it 3 times maybe. I never liked it from the start. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-15 01:28:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I really don't like Tom Cruise. That being said Edge of Tomorrow starring Tom Cruise is fucking amazing.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-15 01:23:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Matt Damon and Ben Afleck in Jay and Silent Bob Strike Back. 
 "Applesauce bitch" </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-15 00:29:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Coolest: Probably GPS on handheld devices and cell phones. (so smart phones lol)

Disappointing: World Relations haven't gotten any better, probably worse. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-15 00:24:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thanks for all the tips guys and gals. I'll try and post a pic once I get around to cleaning him off. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-15 00:22:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Dude is getting cooler by the day. I still don't care for his films though. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-14 20:49:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> "Did you guys see the game? I was at it. Roethlisberger was all like. . ." </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-14 20:41:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> * This is NOT the pull string version. His jacket looks like it was once sewn at the buttons to keep it on. Now the jacket comes off. Some kid decided to draw over his eyebrows and lips with what looks like black magic marker. His white shirt has some light brown discoloration. I bout shat myself when I saw it today at the Goodwill here in town. I had the pull string edition when I was young and thought that he would have it but he does not.
* How can I get the marker off his face without taking his original paint off? I could sand it right off but his red lips and true black eyebrows will go with it. Any suggestions? Thanks in advance!
* Buy it now on EBAY looks about $15-$20 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-14 20:09:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I have a Wu Tang disc that I did as well with just sharpie on a yellow Beast a couple years ago and the Sharpie never faded or smudged a bit. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-14 20:04:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Seems about right. Summer time everyone is looking for something different to do. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-14 19:59:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Final Fantasy Online. My brother really wants me to play with him but I just can't get into it. I like ESO imho </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-14 19:56:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> There's a few snapchat communities online. Google Snapchat Forum or something like that. I'm sure the subreddit here for it will suffice. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-14 19:53:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> great advice. Thanks </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-14 19:43:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> anytime  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-14 15:38:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> tell me about it </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-14 15:37:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That's me on the right as Two Face and my little brother on the left as Robin. I convinced my little bro that it would be cooler to be Robin (he wanted to be the bat) since I was Two Face. I remember the inside of the Two Face mask smelled like white chocolate.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-14 15:21:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Burritos brother Burritos. Throw some leftovers in a flour wrap with some cheese and sour cream(or your favorite condiment) put that bad boy on the panini press for 5 min and Bam! You got yourself a leftover Bureet. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-14 15:17:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> * Shave your face.
* Trim your hair (comb to the side.)
* wear a tie. 
* Eye Contact is a MUST. 
* Try not be nervous. 
* Be yourself. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-14 15:14:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> * Game: Nickelodeon Guts (who doesn't want to scale the crag)
* Show: Deadwood (the Game of Thrones of the Willd Wild West)
* Movie: Starship Troopers (amazing storyline even better graphics) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-14 15:10:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Tristan </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-14 15:08:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> And that's how I felt when I was in Waterloo, cause when I walked in Waterloo and smiled at people they treated me like a vampire </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-14 07:04:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [imgur](http://i.imgur.com/8y5ABu4.gif) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-14 06:35:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This is awesome! Thanks op. Only one thing it says Hugh Jackman played the role of Wolverine for 15 years following X Men but it will  end up being more like 17 or 18 years right? They just need a + beside 15 years. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-14 06:26:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Peter Dinklage as Tyrion Lannister </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-14 06:21:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I loved the fly swatter game. My grama saw me playing it one day and I let her take a spin. That day eventually led to my grama owning her own 64 lol now she has an android tablet and she's 86!  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-14 06:19:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Super Ghouls and Ghosts. Hard as hell and some moton lag when too many things on are on the screen but overall great game. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-14 06:14:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You had to put your shirt over it to block spit then you were in the "know" </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-14 06:13:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I reminds me of the game Rad Racer for Nes. It came with blue and red 3d glasses and if you hit select everything went double in blue and red and the sky looked similar to this. Rad Racer was the shiiiiiiit. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-14 06:07:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'd buy that for a dollar! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-14 06:06:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That is really cheesy if you ask me and I'm glad we won't get to see a zombie Uncle Ben or Dennis Leary </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-14 05:53:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I think you'll have the guys that love them and have been "waiting" for them and you'll have the guys that don't want to take away from the nostalgia of retro gaming. That being said I think a consumer edition would be cool, but will it change retro gaming? No. Will they sell some early on? Yes. IMHO </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-14 05:43:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Ponyo is rated G and my favorite from Studio Ghilibi. I like them all but Ponyo has such staying power, beautiful animation, and a cast with so much diversity it's amazing. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-14 05:33:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> X-Men Days of Future Past. I balled at the ending. I didn't tear up a little, I straight up cried. Such a feeling of coming full circle. The best idea for a reboot to a series ever imo. The Rogue Cut that just came out makes it even better. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-14 05:25:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Ted 2 over and over again </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-14 05:22:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's between Shaun of the Dead and Zombieland for me. Apparently zombies and humor go hand in hand. I heard a story about Woody Harelson attacking a guy in an airport and saying he was still in the mind set of fending off zombies from a movie he had just wrapped... I wonder if it's true. Shaun of the dead had a sense of realness to it that I really liked and I really could identify with the step dad bits. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-14 04:56:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Wow that's my home course and I've come soooo close to acing 13. I'm left handed and come within feet of acing 13 and 14 quite a bit. That's awesome you gave it to him. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-14 04:38:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I really like the ["Thumtrac" Birdie by Innova.](http://www.innovadiscs.com/discs/putt-and-approach-discs/speed-1/birdie.html) It's great for aggressive putting and the grip, well it's in the name. I've only heard about them until a recent trip to Sports Authority. I picked one up for $10 and the accuracy I have with this thing is literally unbelievable. It's definitely worth a gander. All I used pryor was my Aviar and I loved it. The Birdie has improved my putt and approach game so much that it's the clear choice over the Aviar for me.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-14 04:26:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [Imgur](http://i.imgur.com/9QWYPhS.jpg) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
