<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject2260</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-02 03:50:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Rabbits. I hate their fidgety, sudden movements. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Piggy, a.k.a. The Notorious P.I.G. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-27 00:46:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-25 04:30:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Ocarina of Time when I was 7 years old. I didn't know the value of a dollar back in 1998, but oh well. Still top 5 favorite game of all time. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-25 04:18:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Me and the rest of my newly discovered vagina-wielding crew would lead the greatest revolution of irony against Third Wave Feminism.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-25 04:08:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Be ridiculously specific about what I was going to do out loud for everyone to hear.

In grocery store: "I'm gonna go pee out of my vagina!"

In Starbucks: "I would like a pumpkin spice latte because I'm a yoga pants-wearing, titty-rocking woman." </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-25 03:58:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> History: World Empires. It very well could have been interesting, but I've learned that the professor's passion (or lack thereof) makes or breaks the class regardless of the subject. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-25 03:47:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This is gonna sound super vague, but when you're just sitting around and thinking about random shit, then all of a sudden you get a rush of happiness seemingly out of nowhere. It's that feeling of "huh, everything is a-okay." Then you realize your next student loan payment is due tomorrow and all of that goes out the window. Still, those random rushes of true bliss that appear out of nowhere even if you're doing nothing is pretty spectacular. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-04 03:46:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I should clarify and say I'm willing to open up to having a roommate or two, as that's probably more realistic and will cut down on how much I pay. Where in NE is good? People tell me NE but that seems to be divided into several neighborhoods itself. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-03 05:22:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thank you all so much for taking the time to reply. I definitely have a much better idea of where to do some research. Hopefully I can make it up there in a month or two to check the city out and these neighborhoods.

I've also come across Whittier in some searches. What can you guys tell me about that area? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Moving to Minneapolis this Summer. I need help figuring out the best neighborhood for me to live in. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-01 02:37:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I am in need of a change of scenery as I've spent far too long (18 years) in Raleigh, NC. Minneapolis has been on my radar for the past 6 months, but I don't know exactly where I should live. Here are some details to help you guys help me:

- I am a 24, almost 25 year-old male.
- I'd like to be in a super walkable, bike-friendly area with easy access to public transit. I got in a car accident recently and decided I'm going to live car-free instead. I've heard it's easy to do depending on where in MPLS you live.
- I'd like to be as close to the action as I can within my budget. I like having a good nightlife scene, craft beer, restaurants, shopping, live music etc. within a walking distance, bike ride or short bus ride away.
- It has to be relatively safe (not everywhere is perfect, but I don't want to fear for my life on the regular)
- I currently work part time in retail and part time as a copywriter independent contractor. I'm looking for copywriting/creative writing work in general fulltime. Not sure if that really tells you anything as I'm sure these jobs are spread all throughout the city.
- I'm only looking for a studio apartment (min: $500, max: $850/month)

If there's any other information you need to inform your answer, I'd be more than happy to provide that. Thanks in advance!


 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Reddit, what's the funniest resume/cover letter you've read that actually got the applicant the job? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-25 01:39:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-12 01:03:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I have no idea! You know those moments where you thought you saw something weird out of the corner of your eye, but then it isn't there? This wasn't one of those. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> It's been 8 years since I've seen the Visitor </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-11 19:58:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> There is nothing more haunting than the unknown. The thing about the unknown is that its not in your presence, you are in its presence. One October night, about 2 weeks before Halloween, I couldnt decide whether I was in the presence of the living and breathing, or the dead and silent.

I was in my living room relaxing in my favorite chair and watching television. Immediately to the right of my chair was a side table with a lamp jutting from the red oak finish. Beyond the table were a set of windows that decorated the entire wall. If you peeked through the glass, you would be looking at our small outdoor deck with a grill and a few steps that lead to the backyard grass. Despite my numerous protests since moving into that house, my parents insisted that we never closed the blinds, even at night. 

My parents were in a slumber upstairs while I watched television late at night. Even if I werent paying attention, I preferred to keep the T.V. on when its dark outside. I hate dead silence; If Nothing were a living being, I hated when it stroked my spine with its cold, jagged nails. I liked the house to be filled with some sort of noise that quelled the silent soundtrack orchestrated by Nothing.

While Ive always maintained that the light is a friend at nighttime, it betrays you when you cant see out of the windows. I kept the lamp on the table next to me lit as I got deeper into the movie. Before I flicked the light on, I knew what was beyond the window. The moon reminded me what Id see the next day: my deck, the grass, the naked trees, and the red leaves that peppered the lawn. When the lamp illuminated the living room, Its as if the light painted the windows black.

Nearing 4 in the morning, I decided that it was time to call it a night. I turned the T.V. off and took a minute to motivate myself to get out of my chair. I twisted the lamps switch to submerge the living room into darkness. Once again, the windows appeared transparent and showcased the world beyond the glass. However, the light of the moon revealed a new feature that disrupted my routine viewing. 

A pale, crooked face was staring right back at me.

Whoever or whatever it was, it stood there on the deck. Only a glass window with numerous hand prints on it separated us. The face had two black eyes that werent on level with each other. A crooked red smile ran its course almost diagonally; it looked like a drop of blood that followed a crack in the Earth that ran down hill. Its torso was as dark as my insides. The moonlight barely sketched the outline of the entity. If anything, the pale face was just hovering unassisted. Like a painting, the figure never moved.

If it were human, its breath wouldve clouded the window given how close it stood. Air never seemed to push its chests outwards, or pull it back in. The eyes remained black like a spooked horse; if it had blinked, its eyes would cease to be a mirror. No such thing happened. I shuffled to the left so I could bypass all of the furniture. Oddly enough, its eyes never followed me. I was in its peripheral and it did not twist its neck even slightly.

Given Halloween was only about 2 weeks away, this very easily couldve been someone showing off their costume way too early and trying to scare people. Hell, Ive done it. I bolted away from the living room, up the stairs, and into my parents bedroom. I woke them up to tell them that someone was on our porch. 

When the three of us returned, the figure was not there. 

In the following weeks, even on Halloween night, the figure had never returned. Ill never know if it was a person, an apparition, or some otherworldly visitor. All I know is my image reflected on the the eye of the visitor just like it did on the window. I see my image reflected in the window every day. I dont know if Ill ever see my image reflected in its eyes again, but it doesn't matter because it will always haunt my memory.

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-01 23:02:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thanks, kind stranger! You gotta do what you gotta do, haha. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-01 23:01:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Perhaps, but I figured taking a knife to your spine rather than your shoulder blade would be much more uncomfortable. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> A Cure for the Itch </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-28 00:26:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Something is tickling my spine, and it has caused the bone to itch.It's the kind of itch that seemingly has no cure; it just travels to another area that's harder to reach. My arms struggle to snake all the way to the center of my back where the most vital organs reside. The knob of bone that divides my arm and shoulder cannot bend backwards any further without cracking it.

The blade of a knife adds a few extra inches to the furthest extent of my arm. It's capable of massaging the itch, but is still no cure. I cannot tell if my mind is just playing trick, teasing each inch of my anatomy.Maybe the itch migrated deeper into my flesh.My arm cannot stretch beyond its limits to use my fingernails to collect scraps of the epidermis and its neighboring layers. Instead, the knife plunges deeper into the flesh than my fingernails ever could.

I've dug deep enough so the point of the knife can scratch the bone with the antagonizing itch. I've scraped at it for a few minutes now and yet the itch proceeds to get worse. It's almost like a family of insects are trying to escape the permanent darkness that is my inner body. They've chewed through what they could and recuperated on the bay of the bone, digesting their meal. Maybe it's a snake slithering about my ribcage as if each rib bone was a tree branch. The knife has made contact with some kind of foreign presence.

I've had enough.

I suspend two ropes from the roof of the house and attach metal hooks to each of them at the ends. I place one hook on one side of my spine, then the other hook on the other side. The hooks securely grip the flesh surrounding my spinal cord. With everything in place, I jump off of the roof until the ropes have stretched as far as they could, pulling the hooks the opposite direction out of my back. Flesh braided with veins dangle from the hooks on the side of the house. A pair of black, jagged wings protrude from my new wounds and take advantage of the wind beneath them.

Flight has taken place.

The itch is cured. 
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-27 23:57:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So, how'd you sleep last night? :) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The Silence Was Loud </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-26 16:43:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> My bedroom, the adjacent bedroom, and the connecting bathroom were all accounted for. Each light was put to rest and each door was closed. I flirted with a peaceful slumber rather quickly. It felt like I could be unconscious any minute. The darkness orchestrated a peaceful silence.

A womans scream disrupted the silence. It was the kind of scream one would expel if they saw something or were experiencing something particularly frightening. It wasnt my mother  she was out of town that weekend visiting family  and there were no other females in the house. My body shot up, but I refused to leave the comfort of my own bed. 

Suddenly, my bathroom door thundered with a pulse of knocking. At first, it was steady and persistent, continuing for a solid minute or so. As time progressed, the knocking slowed and the volume of the sound decreased. Eventually, the knocking came to a stop. The room was back to its original silence, except there was nothing peaceful about it. I quivered in my bed as I was too scared to bolt out the room. 

The silence was disrupted yet again by what sounded like someone desperately gasping for air. The breathing seemed to belong to the same person who belted out that loud scream just minutes before. Akin to the knocking on the door, the breathing slowed until it came to a halt. The scene became dead silent again. I saw the knob of my bathroom door slowly twist. The door inched open to reveal the bathroom submerged in darkness. If something existed in there, it was staring me down while my eyes struggled to part the darkness.

A beam of light pierced through the darkness from underneath the bathroom door that lead into the adjacent bedroom. The light stretched several feet across the floor, barely illuminating the rest of the room. Directly in front of the door, a pool of maroon was revealed by the light. Falling droplets add to its size. My eyes followed upward to determine the source. The light outlined a pair of feet swaying back and forth. Drops of blood jumped from the toes into the puddle underneath. Like a dying animal finishing its last breath, the toes wiggled briefly before ceasing completely.

An unidentified woman hangs in my bathroom.

Because the light was unable to brighten the entire room, it only revealed up to her knees. The light would not allow me to get acquainted with whoever it was dangling in my bathroom. The body continued to swing gently until it faced the door with the light peaking through the crack. Once she faced the door, her body stopped swinging. After several moments, she started turning again. She did not swing like before, rather it seemed the rope did not assist whatsoever. Her body faced towards me. I was given one last moment of silence and my heart could no longer beat. 

The same scream from before erupts from the dangling woman.
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The Silence Was Loud </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-26 04:47:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The Silence Was Loud (NSFW) </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-26 04:37:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
