<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject7132</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-16 06:04:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah man, I wouldn't be able to keep a straight face in that situation either. Not necessarily a TIFU, but rather a moment where you wore your incredulity on your sleeve, and the whole "not talking now" is a natural extension of your now obvious long term incompatibility. Next! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-16 05:57:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I wish I had a restore point.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-16 05:37:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm told ibuprofen is good for flower back pain.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-16 05:36:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You should have told her it was a movie quote from God's Not Dead.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-15 06:30:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Well, the purgatory you are in, waiting, is about the worst feeling in the world. 

Keep your cool - no matter what happens. I know that this is unsolicited advice but cannot resist imparting hard earned wisdom to you. Stay cool, be respectful, act calm. Results are the only thing that matter, and you need your focus to be on whether to "stay or leave" (this relationship) after she explains herself. That is the one thing that matters, and the one thing you are in control of.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-15 06:14:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I hope she's ok.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-15 05:59:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm pretty sure those guys were just going with the flow. In this case, heavy flow.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-15 05:47:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Time to temp.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-15 03:09:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Exciting and provocative and tea.  Hmm. Any tea will do. Sip it out of the navel of a super model.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-15 02:58:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The exponent.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-14 13:59:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You had me at Reason, but lost me at "make us". What a fun question. I rallied to building a dream team and then went right over a cliff when considering implementation.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-14 07:21:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Well, so is that jar. It's full of busted nuts.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-14 07:15:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Forward looking.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-13 13:34:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Here's an up vote. I hope you get to experience it for yourself, and wouldn't it be cool if this post was the one that accomplished this? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-12 08:28:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Copy and paste this to TIFU and I'll bet you get 3,000 up votes.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-04 08:30:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> ....The night shift.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-26 03:10:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Great site. Thanks!  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-29 04:38:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm not sure why final two paragraphs are in bold, not intentional. Hope it's not construed as rude.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Dropbox is infected. I'm extremely stressed. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-29 04:36:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-15 12:49:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> First off, totally agree with OP on UFO as a prime example.

I will add glitches. Stuff like missing time experiences. Reddit.glitch offers a vast data trove of these types of experiences. Fascinating posts and yet, stripped of their anonymity, I doubt many redditors would feel comfortable sharing these types of experiences with the public. I expect that we will someday herald today's "fringe" physicists as pioneers in the conversation that relegates glitches to normal.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-14 05:25:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> As for the book, two thumbs up. Flow, continuity, suspense, style all lend themselves to fast, gripping, fun, immersive reading. Reminds me of Clive Cussler. I listened to the Coast to Coast interview with Tom Delonge and AJ Hartley prior to reading, thanks to the Dropbox link provided here last week, and I think that learning the backstory enhanced my interest and enjoyment. 

As to the veracity, I am in wait-and-see mode. This book was only the first of his many anticipated deliverables, both fiction and non fiction. It will be interesting to see the level of endorsement that he receives from long tenured peers in the community, like Leslie Kean and John Podesta. 
  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-02 05:03:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> PEO? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-30 13:55:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Splooge </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-26 11:43:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Are you the same guy that cries at double rainbows? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> My son, 15, is an International Baccalaureate high school student. He seeks an online / telecommute opportunity. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-21 03:38:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Any leads are appreciated. He must fulfill his volunteer hour (25) obligation by May 1. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> PEO </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-08 23:36:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I am a co-founder a PEO. By definition, we provide payroll and workers' comp insurance. Our PEO relies exclusively upon insurance agents for referrals. In turn, we pay residual commissions. 

I'm hoping that this post reaches any agents that have an interest in learning more about who we are and what we do. I don't see a non-solicitation rule, and yet at the same time if this offends I'll remove upon request. Thanks for reading. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [Question] Adobe document is printing out with phantom pages. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-08 21:26:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I am sending out a 6-page employee packet to new hires. The packet is completed (by the employee), saved, printed, signed, and then attached and returned by email to me. In most cases it comes back as 6 pages. In some cases it comes back a 17 pages and the extras are old pages that were previously discarded. Can someone tell me how to prevent this from happening? The only consistent thing we have determined so far is that it is old computers that are printing this as 17 pages.
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-06 04:18:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Ty! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-04 00:06:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Ty </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [Task] $6 US. Convert two pages of documents from English into Spanish. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-03 21:50:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [Closed]

The first page is a one page list of instructions, bullet points.

The second page is several paragraphs that will go into an employee application.

I can email them to you if you want to see before choosing whether to accept. thanks!
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-28 05:44:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> People do what they do because they want to. Whether they admit this to you - or even to themselves. Did you ever see the movie "he's not that into to you?" It does a nice job exploring the imbalances that occur in relationships where differing needs and interests result in confusion similar to your post.

You have options in how you react: distancing yourself, lowering your expectations, and / or accepting them are all examples of moving beyond analysis and into a place where you are happier. Ultimately your own happiness is your goal. Reducing your reliance on others will make you stronger (and it also attracts more compatible people into your life). </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-28 05:13:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> To answer your second question: As with any large data set, patterns emerge. Correlating patterns like into generalizations like "people living longer" equals "ruined it for everyone" is the province of the lesser intellect. You are right to spot this generalization, and right to inquire after the basis for it, and right to test it for logical fallacy.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-07 06:40:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Apparently the man didn't have his own grandmother to steal from.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-24 20:59:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You make a good point.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-24 05:50:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> https://www.jacam.com/contact/

In case anyone wants to share their opinion with the nice folks at JACAM.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-21 17:23:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> These are great!  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-18 23:41:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Magna Cum Loudly </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-18 23:40:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Lol. Thankfully, no! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-18 20:00:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Prior to college, I spent quite a few years watching my wrist erect a huge penis. It was hard on me. But I came through.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-18 13:53:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Good point.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-18 13:51:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I thought Jesus was the son of dog.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-18 04:32:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Very uplifting.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-18 02:51:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I like the long game when it comes to owning. Here are the upsides to the long game:

- the tax advantage of being able to write off loan interest. 
- the long term positive roi on real estate. 
- the financial discipline that owning a home teaches (baptism by fire)
- over time you can pay the principal down (make payments on the back)
- rent it out of you outgrow it
- equity line against it if you need to draw on equity in the future 

Good luck. There is no bad decision renting vs owning. 
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-18 02:41:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I obviously am not informed on you metabolic situation, but perhaps time to start counting calories. If you have been overeating, then you will find that once your stomach shrinks you'll find the hunger pains are less and smaller portions will fill you up. Between that and the gym you might be quite happy with yourself in less time than you think. 

As for the girl, well...what she said was mean and I wouldn't waste a worry on her. Continue to focus on you and your self image, inside and out, and the girls will come.

Hope some of this advice is relevant and helpful.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-17 04:25:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Agreed. Spot on.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-17 04:25:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Dexter </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-17 04:24:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I eat and drink less, which recalibrates me.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-16 00:10:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> 9/11 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-15 05:36:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> General rule of thumb: if Rick Scott likes it, it's probably a bad idea.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> TIL Bill Gates has listed the best books hes read this year </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-12 17:51:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-12 04:00:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thank you! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-11 23:36:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thank you! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-11 17:09:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Or FB. Could be run entirely by algorithm.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-11 17:09:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That's actually pretty brilliant.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-11 17:02:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's just awkward making small talk with your Mom when you're standing right next to her.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-11 14:31:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> To Herr Donald: "You're flyered!"  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-11 14:06:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thank you, Random_Pandas.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-11 13:49:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Well, I hope you appreciate your remaining fingertips more. Never take them for granite.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-11 07:41:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Good. At least you have gained perspective. Russian Americans tend to do very, very well in the U.S. That's a fact.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-11 07:25:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> 'Merica? It's high time you finish your journey. Head for the nearest city, or simply point yourself north until you see snow. America is alive and well, and is looking forward to meeting you. We champion those whose ire is raised by bigotry.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-11 07:05:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> ...of weed!! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-11 06:23:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> No, I do not. Audible laugh </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-11 06:10:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Edinburgh, among my most favorite places to visit. Australians, among my most favorite travel companions. I'll chalk this up to one bad apple.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-11 06:01:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Don't get in over your head.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-11 05:37:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If the morning involves sleeping... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-11 05:33:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Upvotes.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-11 05:32:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You might get behind in your work.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-11 05:26:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Taint funny.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-11 05:01:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That reads like an Escher painting.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-10 15:59:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I can't believe Han Solo said that.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-09 17:41:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I need to drop my Diet Coke habit.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-09 13:31:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Provoking primordial grunts of "that was a real tree slapper".  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-09 04:06:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Cigar City Jai Alai IPA. Refreshing and yet still packs around 8%.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-09 03:21:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So long, and thanks for all the fish.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-08 14:17:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Turn 40.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-08 14:06:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's a dick peak.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-08 03:27:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Well done.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-07 17:52:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I am very grateful for all the upvotes :) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-05 22:00:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Same.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Driving high versus driving drunk: Drunks run stop signs. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-05 18:45:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Stoners stop and wait for them to turn green.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-05 18:09:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You blew your load twice.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-05 18:04:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Love.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-05 17:47:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Drunks run stop signs. Stoners stop and wait for them to turn green.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-05 14:12:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This was taken into consideration.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-05 00:27:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah. Nice uptick.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-04 13:38:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Prepare by stashing a few extra donuts for emergencies, because the lines at DD are about to get a lot longer.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-11-25 11:40:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I like it both conceptually and by the numbers. Also, by living there for several years you will gain great insight on any idiosyncrasies of the house and the neighborhood, so that when you do move out and on with your life you will have a solid game plan to assure that the house stays a winner. 
I have had good experiences with college tenants.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-11-24 05:03:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Little fellow was referred to as a taligrade in second to last paragraph.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The Earth is Alive </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-11-22 18:11:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-11-18 10:10:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Interesting and thoughtful analysis. Officially, Twitter imposes a phone number requirement only on suspected TOR-node spammers. Unofficially, the implementation of this security measure appears to be a bit more far reaching...and, speaking to your point, perhaps Twitter's algorithm-derived criteria for requiring a phone number are (or do go) deeper than they choose to publicly admit.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-11-17 19:50:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This has interrupted the data collection efforts of government agencies monitoring the known ISIS Twitter accounts. Blunder. Attention mongering.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-11-01 23:30:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Was it looking for eye candy? (Sorry, pun police...couldn't help myself!) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-10-24 18:46:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Smell like cigarettes.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-10-23 06:17:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I hear you. Either way, it's one of the more fascinating glitches - real or cerebral - I've seen. If I ever come across another entry like this, anywhere, I'll find and post the link to this thread, or pm you.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-10-23 05:10:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Was it perhaps St. Elmo's Fire, a plasma energy discharge, often at or above a sharp object? Here's a link on this phenom: 

https://en.m.wikipedia.org/wiki/St._Elmo%27s_fire

I did a bit of googling on your experience, and this was the only thing I found; unfortunately, nothing to support the accompanying sweet smell, notwithstanding the alternative suggestion of neurological dysfunction.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-10-21 14:26:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Atheism.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-10-21 13:58:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I swallowed some cards, and am hoping for a royal flush.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-10-21 13:50:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That is over the top funny.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-10-21 13:45:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> They could have just shagged on the plane.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-10-21 13:39:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That happens in porn, too.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-10-21 07:14:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The grades are important, sure. Finishing (college) is of primary importance, and exceptional grades are secondary. Finishing college with a great network and reputation, decent grades, and leveraging your network and reputation to get a good job, priceless. Doing this and watching your costs along the way by going to a community college / state school (if American), even better. 

Starting college, getting hammered at every opportunity, sputtering out after two years, stuck with loans to pay, meh. I did this. Took me forever to catch up. 

If you're lazy, just be efficient. But stay in the game. Much later in life I mitigated some darker undercurrents that contributed to my own laziness, namely adhd and depression, by exercising and taking an antidepressant. You may have some personal demons to face, too. If so, fight the fight. Worth it. College is chalk full of opportunities to enrich your life experience and, ultimately, your financial well being. The more you can dial yourself in to this, the better.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-10-21 06:29:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> 411 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-10-21 06:16:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Also good: simulated universe hypothesis as presented by physicist Nick Bostrom. http://www.youtube.com/watch?v=nnl6nY8YKHs

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-10-20 00:18:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Send some of those over to the States, please! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-10-20 00:11:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Not to mention, it's the ninth quality.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-10-08 21:53:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Are you exercising? You're not 18 anymore. And young kids raise male estrogen levels. Exercise raises T, which in men correlates well with improving one's ability to discern life direction.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-10-07 13:42:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Direct link to petition.  https://www.change.org/p/superintendant-school-officials-fight-for-hayden-long
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-09-29 04:17:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Religion. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-09-23 14:11:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thanks. Very helpful tool. I just ran it in every one of my active domains. I actually found what appear to be some spam triggers on one of them. 

I ended up overcoming the issue I posted about by replying to the reply-to link provided within each of the 35 "spam-undeliverable" alerts, and per the instructions, uploading a copy of each original (sent) email. 

24-hours later, the problem was completely remedied. 

Then, in order to distance our ongoing email marketing campaigns from our main company domain, I created a marketing landing page (under a similar domain name), and campaigns run out of the site. 
Not surprisingly, that site is the one that your tool revealed some spam blocking. 
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-09-21 19:17:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thank you! 

Also, GoDaddy has a 250 email limit per SMTP per day if I understand correctly. I've instructed my VA to limit sent emails to this number. I have been doing 400-600 per day with no trouble, for years, but I guess ignorance is bliss. Now that I'm actually researching this stuff I'm becoming more conservative. Any input is appreciated (on whether capping my daily emails is smart) is appreciated.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-09-21 16:05:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You're welcome.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-09-20 21:45:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hi! To be clear, you are charging just $1.50 total per every 100 words?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-09-20 20:31:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Right on. Mine is growing fast. It is good to know that the size component is definitely not a limiting factor.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-09-20 20:24:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thanks! I'll have this vetted as well.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-09-20 18:25:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Perfect. I'll move forward with this product.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-09-20 18:24:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thank you!

I've forwarded both your response and moldyputty's to my overseas VA team leader to implement.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-09-20 18:11:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thanks! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> In search of automating my email campaign </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-09-20 17:47:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I need this to look as though the emails are hand sent by my staff. I need to load my contacts in (approximately 50,000) from excel. I need to hit a button and have each email go out with the contact first name embedded twice in the email, and their company name once. My three questions:

Can I do this?
Which app/software/cloudware do I need to buy?
Does the bottom of the email give any indication of the app/software/cloudware. Like "sent by constant contact" in small print?

For years, I have had an overseas staff that take my email template, paste it into an email, and add the custom items, and send. They do 400 a day. The overseas staff emails are all part of my web domain, etc, and I have had no spam issues because my contacts are all people in my industry receiving updates. 

My intention is to automate this project. 

Any help is greatly appreciated.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-09-19 19:34:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The recent thread may be helpful. 

https://www.reddit.com/r/Entrepreneur/comments/3k5g4v/why_did_you_become_an_entrepreneur/ 

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-09-19 19:30:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Make your nonbeliever watch Mad Men.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Any good E-Verify providers? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-09-19 02:35:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I need to do a bunch of e-verifies on an ongoing basis. I'm seeking someone who will do this for me. Any recommendation is appreciated.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-09-17 14:48:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The 10-99 should sign a doc acknowledging that he is an independent contractor. Specifically define his freedom to take other contracts, set his own schedule, and utilize his personal email. That having been said, he acknowledges that you will provide him with the option of using a company email if he agrees to disclose that he is an independent contractor below his signature. 

Then draft a bunch of small print below sig and stick in there. 

Also make his position one of the following: Sales Consultant, Independent Sales Consultant, or Sales Contractor.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-09-17 14:09:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm in agreement with you.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-09-17 14:07:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hiring employees in the U.S. requires a learning curve, but it's not that steep. And, Zen (or whomever) can handle the bulk of the compliance in this regard. You will simply remit to Zen by ACH the balance of wages plus FICA, FUTA, SUTA and workers comp (required in OH on non-owners; incidentally, you will report any office employee under class code 8810 which is cheap; sales employees are 8742, also cheap). 

As for 10-99, I'd go that route for web design. 

I'd personally do 10-99 for your sales people, too. As for throwing a little weekly 10-99 cash to your sales people who need a few bucks each week, well, put it in your accounting as payment on a project (help with marketing, whatever). 

I have many employees, and many 10-99 people, and have an expert understanding of their respective definitions and compliance requirements. And I am no rocket scientist.  

Here's comp 101:
https://www.bwc.ohio.gov/downloads/blankpdf/OAC4123-17-08.pdf

https://www.bwc.ohio.gov/employer/forms/suppcoverage/SFESuppCoverage.asp
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-09-17 13:36:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Oh, correction. I meant to say that my sales team are all 10-99. I was mentally fading at 1am. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-09-17 06:47:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> lol. I tend to only like hiring employees and overseas virtual assistants for work related to operations / administrative work. Not a rule, just my general pattern of behavior. 

My sales team are all I-9.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-09-17 06:27:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I like: 

- independent contractors for sales: Honest income; easy to set up; easy to track; few moving parts. 

- employees and VA's for ops/admin. 

- partners who bring sweat and / or equity

I am cautious about whom we hire, and how, and whether we expand. Yet I have friends I'd hire and friends I would not hire. My point: They're not mutually exclusive. 

You've demonstrated a good track record in business and in life. You're structuring mutually beneficial relationships to meet your individual wants and needs. I wager that your instincts will tell you what to do. If expansion makes sense, you'll pull the trigger. If you're seeing too many moving parts, bad timing, or high risk, I think you'll throttle back. If you make a false move, you'll adapt or retrace. 

One piece of advice: outsource that employee paperwork if you do go that route. Do the Zen suggestion, or hire a local accountant. That stuff is onerous. And rote. You need to stay in your zone. 






 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-09-17 05:37:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Sure. I've owned an insurance agency without ever being licensed. You can own anything.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-09-16 13:58:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I have built my own VA team to assist my US companies. Perhaps my experience / model will help you:

Several years ago I used onlinejobs.ph, which was excellent, and upon finding a good person I then had her recruit others. Essentially she became the manager and the additionals that she found became my team. I paid her a US $1 / hr override on her recruits, and US $3.5 / hr on all work she herself did for me. 

She's no longer with me, but the top recruit is now my new manager and he now recruits team members. I pay him US $3.50 / hr. Plus his US $1 override. Weekly, PayPal. I pay the team US $0.75 / hr. 

As a manager he is my single point of contact. He spreadsheets work status into my shared Dropbox and updates me by email and Voxer. Voxer is a free app and functions like a Nextel phone. I pay him, he pays everyone. 

Each team member has a name that I created and utilizes an email address created thru my domain. As such, if they are sending emails to my clients and prospects it is not obvious that they are VA's. I should also mention that I write the template emails which they then modify and personalize per recipient. 

Their emails signatures bear my company logo and contact info but with a twist: I have placed my cell number into their signatures. I do this so that all phone responses come to me. Yeah, I get calls all the time from people asking for one of my team members...and I just say that their phone is forwarded to me today and that I'm a colleague who can answer their questions. 

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-09-16 13:34:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Weed delivery. You'll be using a scale every day. :)

Seriously, though, 10k, I'd open a PEO brokerage. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-09-16 06:27:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Make sure you do well on SAT. Grades, too. Not necessary for either to be perfect, based on your needs at present. In life, however, you want to avoid egregious stats in three things: academics, credit, and driving. I call it staying off the radar. But I digress.

After you wrap up high school, consider going to a community college in order to improve cash flow and / or reduce or eliminate loan dependence. Community college is inexpensive and, generally speaking, if you do reasonably well you will qualify for practically guaranteed admission into your state school to do junior / senior years.

Upsides: You can schedule community college classes around your entrepreneurial pursuits, lower your bottom line cost of living, and still head off to university if / when you decide it feels right. In short, you hedge your bet. 

You are still in your formative years. Those two years of gen eds looming in your academic future will in fact help build you, strengthen you, and improve your character, despite your current misgivings. (Yes, admittedly they are hard to quantify, but building a well rounded intellect in a challenging, formal setting is more than just an ancient Roman tradition. It works). The social component of college is a second non-linear benefit, but nonetheless huge; as an example, let's quickly delve into the networking benefit. Colleges are breeding grounds for innovation; those 1%-ers find each other in college, and the proof is in the incredible number of ventures that have been born by a person like you building, or at least beginning, a dream out of a dorm room. 

I left college. I went into sales. My wife, by contrast, will start her doctoral soon. She knew early on that her interests were math, engineering, and astro-physics. I knew that my long term goals were not-yet-defined, and that finding my way was going to require an off-the-beaten path process of immersion into a myriad of short term life experiences. In retrospect, I would have opted for the more moderate model I am describing for you. The word moderate sounds meh (damn those Romans) but the reality is it is very challenging and rewarding. 

There is an old saying: if you want find someone to make time for you, ask the busiest person. It sounds counterintuitive, but it is true.
My opinion: Indulge your intellect and your entrepreneurialism. You can do both. 

Best success.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-09-16 05:09:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Send my PEO some clients. I'll pay you a residual...neighbor.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-09-16 05:08:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What exactly is your conundrum? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-09-13 20:54:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I see value in the replies that are kicking your tires. I also think that others - and I include myself among them - see that there may well be emerging a successful method to your unique brand of magic. If you are, ultimately, a success, yours will be a cautionary tale, like a "Kids, do not try this stunt at home" sort of thing.

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-09-13 20:18:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> OP I recommend that you pursue dialogue with this respondent. I was just waiting until someone said, hey, I have some experience and I want to consider investing. You have nothing to lose by engaging in dialogue, and potentially a condiserable upside if a strategic collaboration can get you to critical mass. 

For what it's worth, I think you are doing a ton of things right, speaking from the gut and also joining the chorus of other positive reviews in this regard.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-09-12 19:14:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Earth Outfitters: Latitude. Longitude. Altitude. Attitude. 

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-09-12 18:59:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I like.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-09-12 15:25:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Attitude. Altitude. Gratitude.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-09-12 15:23:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Attitude versus altitude.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-09-12 15:20:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Love the higher law.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-09-12 15:18:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> High and dry.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-09-12 15:15:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Shift into high gear.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-09-12 15:05:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Walk the rock.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-09-12 15:02:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Multiverse compliant.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-09-12 14:49:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Because it is bare. :) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-09-11 06:02:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> There are several vaguaries, generalizations and suppositions in your post, and they trend toward sounding optimistic. Not a criticism, but just an acknowledgement to serve as a precursor to my response:

Based on the information provided, my bare bones - and yet nonetheless emphatic - answer is to err on the side of caution: Open just the one, and I mean to do so if and only if you have really done your homework. (Conversely, IF I were to base my answer on what you "think", and IF you could get 'em launched in time for the holiday shopping season, and IF you have experience, and IF you have capital, and IF you have savings, then I would say to play multiple RMU's and hope for the 80/20 rule to manifest a bunch of base hits and a few home runs).

If it's the holiday season that has you excited and in a rush, I can't blame you. But when you're in a lease with a mall (or malls) during the doldrum months, the long game may be more harrowing than you anticipate. I guess I just want you to ask yourself if, stripped of the dopaminegic release of dreaming big, this idea of yours can still stand on its own legs, or if this thing could flop. If the answer is the latter, then mitigate the risk by executing your dream in a more microcosmic fashion, ie by doing just one RMU, and book the win, and in so doing buy a year to innovate your next novel idea and expansion campaign whilst all the while gaining valuable hands-on experience.

Addendum: When you say "expand.../...without being present", I hope that you are alluding to, say, approaching existing RMU vendors and setting them up with your product. Because strategic collaboration sounds well worth exploring as an alternative to building this B M out yourself. 

For now, I sense that you are protecting your idea and strategy and, again, I can't blame you. Hopefully you have some successful friends in your personal brain trust to bounce this idea off of as well. People who know you, your strengths and weaknesses, etc. People who tell you when you rock, but who also tell you when you have bad breath.

Best success. 
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-09-10 12:47:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thank you. I own a PEO.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-09-09 20:00:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I would say Restaurantman9 gave a good synopsis up top. 

Also, on a side note, Google around for a free non-disclosure agreement. If you decide to play defense, you can have your fellow collaborators sign it.

One thing, and it's a delicate issue to ask you to wrap your head around. Good ideas are everywhere. Putting together a good team and bringing them to fruition is a challenge and an adventure. It will require you to extend trust, and to sometimes extend trust to the point you are vulnerable. This is a necessary part of building your team. If you get too bogged down trying to protect your idea, you run the risk of stifling the spark that is necessary to begin this process. "Do-it-yourselfers" fall into this category. The furthest a do-it-yourselfer can get in entrepreneurialship is to "self-employed". In parting, I say stay nimble and agile and enjoy the lightness of being that comes with beginning at the beginning.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-09-09 18:36:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> His secretary. His CTO. His lawyer. The reschedule of the meeting. Whether this is good or bad, intentional or not, I see indicators that he establishes dominance, wins the deal, and then move on to the next one. So know this: if you do business with him, then you are really going to be doing business with his team - so you'd best like his team. 

If you do this meeting: You are going to express your concerns, and he is going to convince you that your questions are intelligent and that his program is the perfect solution. The harder you work on posing intelligent questions, the better he will sound to you. He is building an echo chamber. Cognitive empathy is the province of sociopaths. 

When you are done, remember that the name of the game is not to determine if he can help, but whether he is the best solution. So, use everything you learn from his model to evaluate not just as your potential strategic alliance, but also in terms of its value versus doing it without him.

Also, if you oblige and reschedule, you are sending a non-verbal cue that you are less important than his schedule. Be aware that this all may be part of his model: to establish very early on that he is a very busy man. I see Alpha all over this. Personally, I would be wary. I would also know that he knows that you are being told to be wary. If you are the enabler type, just run now. If you are psychologically stoic, go and watch a master at his game. If you remain interested, then study the team, his references, and continue to measure this versus all other options.    </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-09-09 13:52:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Right on, thanks. 

I feel the same way about NDAs (not sure they work / how, when do you use, if at all). The upside: I never have a problem signing an NDA. My assumption is that you have the tact, diplomacy and the confidence to send that right person your NDA if / when you decide it's appropriate; they will gladly sign it to allay your concern. 

On how much to tell...I don't have an answer. Finding that right person is so crucial. I hate to say it but I operate on feel. There is a great book, How to Be a Star at Work. Horrible title. The book is the culmination of an expensive, extensive multi-year study commissioned by some Fortune 500 to answer the question, "Why do some of our employees become stars?" The data is so mind blowing that they had to revisit, retool and extend the study to really, truly get their heads around the answers, and on the second go around the answers remained the same. I suggest you find that book as it will help you to hone your instincts on networking to "stars". I'll leave you with this nugget: Star people form networks that transcend corporate hierarchal networks. 

Sorry, your Dad! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-09-09 12:13:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Not the norm. 

In my experience, engineering students are a pretty cool lot. 

You can go a more traditional route, but my gut says your likelihood of seeing this through to fruition will diminish in proportion to the encumbrance that accompanies the traditional route.

There is no right or wrong, however. The beauty of embarking on your adventure is that it is your call.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> www.micro-invest.com </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-09-08 21:00:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm an entrepreneur. This post is not indicative of my portfolio of corporations. This is just me, in my early forties, wanting to develop knowledge in an area where I am deficient. And I could use help. Here goes:

I bought this domain a few years ago. I want to monetize it. To be clear, my goal is not to make a fortune. It is simply to start building practical knowledge. Right now, I am overwhelmed by the myriad of books and tools at one's disposal in the world of web development and e-commerce. I am seeking the bare minimum that it will take to make it generate revenue and a profit, however small. I've heard it's possible to create a landing page and place ads onto it, and am curious as to whether this is the way to go. Any help is appreciated.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Secureserver is blocking clients from my email </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-31 05:55:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> We own a payroll company. We do a ton of emailing, both domestic and abroad. Suddenly a significant number of our emails are getting returned to us as undeliverable, along with a securenet "suspected spam" message. 

I've replied to the "prove I'm not a spammer" link and supplied copies of messages as per the request. 

I've called GoDaddy twice. They at first told me I'm not blacklisted and suggested we remove hyperlinks from emails, check for mis-spellings, and remove our JPEG signature logo. We did. No improvement. I called again and got an IT guy to admit he can't discern whether we are blacklisted or not. He said he was escalating it to a higher tech. That was a week ago. I email the tech for an update every day. No response. 

I'll add that our IT department isolated this as a Godaddy issue. They contacted GoDaddy prior to my involvement. They struck out. Frustrated, I took over. 

This problem started two weeks ago. 

Any advice is greatly appreciated! 





 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> PEO </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-05 22:39:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
