<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject7826</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2011-10-27 01:26:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The rock snot looks like zombie by-product:

http://mdc.mo.gov/fishing/protect-your-fishing/didymo  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2011-10-22 04:47:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Don't you mean  ? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2011-10-22 03:32:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Upboat for you, grumpy grammar mangling hater. Analysis is just good clean fun. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2011-10-19 07:39:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This looks like a prop from Ghostrider. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2011-10-19 07:16:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Man, what a terrible video edit. Yikes.

(Note, this is not a comment on the ideas. Whoever did the editing ought not be asked back.)
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2011-10-07 06:17:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> A fresh book? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2011-10-06 22:35:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> "coneys," actually </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2011-10-04 19:00:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yup. Basic math illiteracy. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2011-10-03 08:25:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [Relevant link](http://www.toilet-related-ailments.com/squatting.html) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> TIL that the diacritical marks used to transcribe Chinese tones in Pinyin are a graphic representation of the actual sounds </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2011-10-02 21:00:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2011-10-02 20:47:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> These might be too "classical" for you, but here you go.

Check google books for 19th century poets who were women: Alice Christiana Thompson Meynell, Sara Orne Jewett, Emily Dickenson, all the Brontes, Louise Guiney. There are also anthologies there that are out of copyright.

Here's a Meynell poem that could be excerpted, first-person, for example: http://www.poemhunter.com/poem/in-autumn/

Shakespeare's songs (from the plays) and sonnets (some from a female perspective) are short and classic. Also William Blake poems. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2011-10-01 17:40:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Upvote for that great spelling. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2011-10-01 17:37:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> (Shaking head in disbelief and walking away...) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2011-09-23 19:23:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Where do you think Tomb Raider got the idea? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2011-09-20 19:40:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This happened to me and my reaction was to fall on the grenade.

A new very senior VP, who was not being accepted by the existing team, basically wanted to clean house and eventually replace people with his own crew. He planned to do this under the guise of "cost cutting," eliminating 50+ people.

I went to the owners of the company (who didn't know of the extent of the plans) and checked whether they thought it was a good idea. They didn't, and so they immediately started intervening with the VP who was going to cut folks. In the meantime, I went to the people about to be cut, many of whom worked for me, and warned them - some were able to jump to other gigs, some were able to survive politically. Some were let go, but not nearly as many as the big boss had wanted to eliminate. He was foiled, and super pissed off. I am still proud of this one, many years later.

Needless to say, I would *not* have been able to use this company as a ref with future employers. To solve this, three of us took off and started our own company as soon as we could, which gave us an excuse for not being able to get a good ref...

At the very least, you should warn people that you know are about to take out loans and that kind of thing, but only if you are SURE that the list won't change! Otherwise, treat it as a rumor with your associates, and start sussing out alternate jobs yourself. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Wait a minute, that goat is a beast... </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2011-09-19 23:33:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2011-08-17 05:27:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Ah, the stripper disease. Tie, dollar bills... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2011-08-02 07:43:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I've always wished that they could use more complex symmetries... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2011-07-28 18:06:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Night-time walks will be so much easier now... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2011-07-21 00:23:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> TIL that memeface is a word. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2011-07-20 18:04:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> For a long time, I could only code with a keyboard under my fingers that responded to emacs commands. Otherwise I'd block. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2011-07-13 01:27:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Integrating two different realtime engines is no easy feat, and it is impressive that Max for Live is able to pull them together without crashes. I am not disrespecting CSound - it is a venerable program that has worked well for years. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Hadron "particle synth" released </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2011-07-12 06:17:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hadron, a brand-spanking-new, open source, hackable, granular synth for Ableton Live, has been released. It is a sophisticated synth, and it is kind of amazing that it even works at all, since its DSP functions are built in CSound and its UI is built in Max for Live. Complicated, but it works well enough. Nice. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2011-06-27 05:22:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> In the complex domain, e isn't much use without pi... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2011-06-20 21:06:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Who cares if they would have stuck by their answers? It would have made for some hilarious hedging! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2011-06-15 02:23:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> We like to think of it as "best at"... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2011-06-06 17:47:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I CANNOT BELIEVE that he did not suggest that breeding with Catherine would be the best thing for the world. They would be so naturally compatible, given their shared background... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2011-06-03 03:31:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Quite a bone. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2011-05-31 20:09:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah, that extended complex plane is pretty controversial.

He is a shining example of how to dive off of the shoulders of giants into the mosh pit of truthiness. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2011-05-31 19:36:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [CaRMetal](http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/CaRMetal) is free and will do this. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2011-05-30 19:31:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> They haven't.

Some people that go to Vegas beat the house, right? That is the nature of activities based on statistics - once in a while, somebody is lucky.

Also, there are a lot of people with a lot of money who game the system, and/or who prey upon the small investor. (Which is sometimes legal and sometimes...iffy...) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2011-05-30 18:48:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You cannot predict statistical "bad news" before it happens. Act of mother nature, criminal acts, etc etc. And these have huge impact on market. Even if you have perfect insider knowledge, you still get screwed by them in the long run.

Indexes are the way to go. In this case, you both profit and lose from the statistical nature of things, and in the long run, you make a little money.

Of course, if you just want to make bets and then live by the consequences, then the market is much more fun than a casino, because it is so complicated and there are so many factors to claim or blame. If you really want to make bets, then trade options! (I worked in options trading for years...) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> TIL what "CS" in CS Lewis abbreviates. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2011-05-27 01:11:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2011-05-18 21:31:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Visualization tools introduced in the 80s pioneered direct parameter manipulation and instant update. Nothing particularly new here? I particularly dislike the characterization as "less equation-ey". The UI for *equations* is tried and true, and powerful. (Not that interactive tools are bad!) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2011-05-17 18:15:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> 2 handed hammering (midi editing?) on the final note in the sequence... "Classical" technique on a tacked upright; the end of days is nigh. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2011-05-17 17:52:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Xenakis wrote beautiful music, and there are some (myself included) who think that he is still ahead of the curve. Read his excellent book, Formalized Music, to learn more about the maths involved. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2011-05-16 19:44:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It feels like you're SURFING, not drowning! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2011-05-05 17:52:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So Cave Johnson was into tying knots, eh? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2011-05-05 17:39:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Water pong! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2011-04-30 18:25:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Too bad autotune won't let you use alternate tunings - the scales are close to being middle-eastern. Best use of background tritone since Purple Haze! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
