<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject4934</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> As awful as life after 75 or so is going to be. My new hope is to live to 105 just to have been alive through 3 centuries. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-23 08:50:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What is your dream day? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-22 20:09:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [WP] As you travel the endless plains of Earth you find yourself lost and can't see the usual surroundings you've come to know. Then you see a tower in the distance that stretches above the clouds. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-22 19:12:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> So I typed Murkadurkah into google and these are the following words... Damnit guys. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-21 22:22:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> So it's pretty well known at this point that cracking your knuckles does not cause arthritis. But is there any evidence on what cracking other joints/bones could cause? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-21 04:12:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> I have ignored a lot of footage for the new Fast and Furious movie because as much as I love the series.. I really don't want to see this one. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-20 17:32:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You know.. You can say what you want about the series. How it went from a cliche car racing movie to an action movie to an over the top extreme action flick..

But I grew up with this series. This is the one movie that me and my mom would go to see on the day it released and as unrealistic as it was, I was able to lose myself in it for 2 hours.

But.. Now with Paul sadly gone. I really don't want to watch the new one. I will of course book tickets for it on release day, the first viewing of it and most likely see it multiple times in the cinema. But.. As good or bad as it's going to be there is going to be a scene in the movie when they say goodbye to Paul... Writing this now I'm crying because I simply find it hard to believe. I never wrote about it when he died because I was in denial. Lately his name has become the front of car jokes and shit and I've let his importance in my life slip but the movies he made were the only connection I had with my mom and still is. 

I don't know why I wrote  this other than to hear other people's thoughts on the matter. Will you be going to see it as either a fan of the series or just to see how it goes? Did his death hit you hard or are you someone who doesn't get affected by celebrity deaths? 

Just leave your thoughts below and I'll get back to you when I'm back from the store.

[This is what sparked the thought btw] (https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=o8UCI7r1Aqw) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> I'm sitting here listening to the Fast and Furious 7 soundtrack and one of these songs will be played when Paul Walker dies on screen and I have no idea what one.. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-20 17:04:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Do I truly HAVE to play xiii 1+2 before Lightning Returns? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-20 03:50:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So about a year ago I played the lightning returns demo (or whenever it came out) and I absolutely loved it. But because it's the third in a three part series I went back and bought xiii. But I really couldn't get into it. I don't know what it was but.. I couldn't get into xiii yet I could play LR's demo 3-4 times a day. Maybe it's the turn based gameplay or something but.. I just couldn't get into xiii.

In saying that. Is there any way I could play LR without having finished xiii 1+2? Could I just look up summaries or endings to both of them and move on or even just go straight into LR because I've heard they mention the past in a easy to follow way and I already know the blonde guy at some point goes to the 'dark side'.

Love to hear your advice on the matter. Thanks. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Has anyone read The Sworn by Gail Z. Martin? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-20 02:01:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So I am genuinely the worst kind of book reader out there in the fact that I judge a book by it's cover and only read something that I know the story of simply because it became a show or movie, which then actually makes it harder for me to enjoy it because I know the plot. Trust me, I know how horrible I am.

In saying that. I bought this book about 2 years ago and when I got home, I sat in in my collection of read and unread books (I have maybe 10 books..Sorry.).

So now that I'm looking to start actually reading like the rest of you, is it good? I have a horrible fear that I'll read it and it will be awful but I don't know it because I'm inexperienced in the topic. 

Forgive how ignorant I am and how I judge a book by it's cover, how I only read something that becomes mainstream but I'm trying to change that.

Thanks :) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What are some good movies with a strong literature or book focus throughout the movie? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-19 21:12:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I've seen both Liberal Arts and Stuck in Love. 

Are there any others? I'd pref a romance but I don't mind really.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Why have I heard nothing of "The Water Diviner"? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-19 18:55:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So I was browsing a certain torrent site for a show I watch but I seen a title The Water Diviner and came to learn it was a Russell Crowe movie. But I've heard absolutely nothing about it.

I watchedd 30 seconds of the trailer and like the look of it so I stopped the trailer so I don't know any more about the movie before watching. But has anyone actually seen any marketing for this movie or will it be another Edge of Tomorrow (in a completely different genre of course.) ? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> New to the series but you guys are hilarious. (Realm Reborn reviews on steam.) </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-18 18:41:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> 11 reviews of Final Fantasy: A Realm Reborn on Steam. They're amazing. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-18 18:40:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Is there a way of telling when a star becomes a supernova? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-18 10:54:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So I plan on getting a telescope at some point during the summer and I plan on spending endless nights looking out at the stars. 

But something I have dreamed of is witnessing a supernova. I don't even know if this is possible because of the light a supernova puts off (right?). So if I were to hope to witness such a thing, would it be true luck on were I point my scope that night or is there a scientist, website, group, out there that can predict when a star is about to give in?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Redditors with a degree in a field of science. What is the field and what is your life like with it? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-18 05:33:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So certain degrees eventually just end up being a piece of paper instead of a stable job or lifestyle. Those of you that have something like a degree in physics or micro-biology or something. What is your day to day life like? Did the degree pay off in the end or are you basically another average Joe with your name on a fancy piece of paper? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Brad Pitt in Inglourious Basterds is absolutely incredible. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-18 03:32:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So I just watched it for the first time and like every other Tarantino movie, it was just his style and beautiful.

But the highlight for me (apart from Christoph Waltz being the masterpiece he is) was Brad Pitt.

He was just so nonchalant about every in regards to killing Nazis. His thick, thick southern accent and then my highlight of the movie..  His Italian accent. Pretty certain he literally says bonjurno with a deeper tone to his voice and that's it. 

Hell of a movie though. The only problem I had with it was the noticeably fake leg after the actress got shot.

9/10 for me.
  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Topic for next PKA: Some sweet, sweet justice porn. (Links inside.) </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-16 15:29:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> A certain CCCCCunt on xfactor NZ.

[This is how it started] (https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=1UA4ZfvNmz0 t=33)

[This is how it ended] (http://static.mediaworks.co.nz/3news/xfactornews.html#axzz3UVlNhdEe) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What is your favorite confirmed interaction between to celebrities? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-16 05:31:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What do you think would happen if Putin DIDN'T turn up? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-16 04:28:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Game of Thrones Season 5: Preview (HBO) </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-16 03:19:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Focus is a pretty solid movie. (Spoilers) </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-16 02:59:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So I just wrapped up Focus with Will Smith and Margot Robbie.

I had a little bit of interest before release of this movie and decided I'm going to lay down and watch it. 

It was a great choice to do that. This is of course, an opinion, and an opinion of a 18 year old who gets too deep into a movie and usually misjudges something or ignores plot holes.

So.. trying to write this I can only summarize the movie when trying to give a real review so I'll just point out my favorite parts and flaws.

So at the football game. Right before it, when they get all the cash, you hear the guy he runs with tell him not to gamble. Whatever he does, don't gamble. Then you see him playing around with Margot, making little bets about the crowd which is fun, then the asian guy jumps in, who I quite frankly enjoyed. But anyway, once he starts gambling and you get these shots of his face, how he's feeling, his thought pattern run through his face.. I honestly concerned. I expected the 1mil to be lost and then throughout the movie he'd run "that one big job" Margot dreamed of. But that doesn't happen because like the other twists in this movie, it was all planned. Margot spots him, I can't think of his characters name, or the actor, but the heavy guy. That's when she notices and Will proceeds to explain it all to her.

Then after that is my first flaw. I found Margots facial expression when he left her in the car.. It was kind of over acted from how I seen it. I understand they meant something to eachother and whatever but how her entire face goes into a sign of shock and paralyzing pain.. I felt it to be over acted but am most likely wrong.

Then when they found eachother later in the movie I thought at times they meant somehting to eachother, then they were playing eachother.. Then he tricks the "villain" of the movie into his exr(?) and makes 27million. I expected them to be caught of course.. But.. 

When he opened up about using her I felt sad, like really sad.. It shows everyone can be played, it was all just a performance and it makes you realize what you're actually watching is all one big performance and none of it is real because he is in fact married and a multi millionaire with kids.. 

When he got shot, that caught me off guard and then once I heard "Mellow" I realized who the bald guy was (I can't think of his name for the life of me but I know his face quite well). The emotional story in the car was a nice add on, I found him hilarious when he just left with all the cash and that is that.

Overall, I really enjoyed it but write really poor reviews and hopefully one day I will make sense but until then readers can suffer through my naivety and inexperience.

Love to hear your thoughts on it.  8/10 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> When exactly are we (xbox gold users) going to get Bioshock Infinite? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-16 01:04:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So when I turned on my xbox, the "Games with Gold" icon had Bioschock as it's picture but when I clicked into it, Tomb Raider was still set as the option. I then remembered the same thing for whatever game came before tomb raider and to get Tomb Raider I just had to go to the store page for it and download for free. But it didn't work this time with Bioshock, I still have to pay. 

Any idea why this is happening?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> How many 3 star maps do you have and how long did it take you to get it? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-15 05:42:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Getting 150 points seems like a looooong way away.

I have 3 hours gametime and I just peaked at 94 points. How in the hell do people get 150? Is there one certain map that is small enough for sheer chaos or what? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> So it turns out a lot of us were curious.. NSFW!!!!!!! </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-14 16:39:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Whatever you think about Titanfall.. This intro is pretty amazing. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-14 15:55:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> How do I change my starting spawn? Which house it puts me in </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-14 14:50:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I bought a high up apartment/penthouse yesterday and one by one moved each car from my shitty condo, over to it.

But it still spawns me in the condo. How do I change that? And is there a way to sell that condo now or what?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Guys.. How the F do I start the campaign? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-14 01:44:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So I understand this game doesn't have typical campaign and I found the option.. But it never puts me into it.

Or does it? i've been put into attrition and hardpoint so far, is that the campaign style? We play pvp and I just listen for dialogue when I can or am I just being thrown into other gamemodes because they can't find me a gmae?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> How to train your dragon 2 is out on Netflix (US) right now. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-13 16:37:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> So I just bought Titanfall Deluxe Edition on 360. What should I know about the game going into it? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-13 15:57:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So I have always had a bit of curiosity about this game and today I found out it was on sale for 30 euro.

But Ive also always been very worried about buying it because I've heard it doesn't have much replay value, customization or 'the long run' so to speak.

But I said fuck it and bought it anyway. I just hope I get long enough out of it, which i intend to, it just depends on the player base I guess. I also know the dlc is all free..

But what else should I know? Is the story good? Do I 'need' to play the story before multiplayer? Are there any tips for MP I should know? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Anyone here want to do some heists on 360? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-13 15:42:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm hosting the first part of the prison break job and am really struggling to get a group together.

You can be with or without a mic, just know what you're doing.

Add BradysIGN </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Looking for people to run the entire Prison heist with on 360. I'm hosting. Add BradysIGN. No mics required, just know what you're doing.. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-13 15:24:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Is this game really ruined by hackers right now? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-13 15:13:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So I just came into 30 euro, which is pretty substantial for a guy who is saving for a trip to Paris and college next year.

But I thought I'd give myself a break and buy something and thought of this game..

But all the reviews on Steam say leave it alone because it's ruined by hackers. Is it true? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> I guess I'll never get my albino foot.. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-13 12:05:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> When you realize Woody's shitty workers/contractors are fucking us over too.. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-13 03:16:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> (No Spoilers) Would I be better off pausing my read through right now to pick up The World of Ice and Fire </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-13 03:03:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Here. I posted this question on /r/gameofthrones earlier and thought I'd just link you to it to make it easier :)

[Here] (http://www.reddit.com/r/gameofthrones/comments/2yujso/no_spoilers_would_i_be_crazy_to_pause_my_reading/) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> If I was to start reading a book as I try to get into the field of physics, astronomy, cosmology etc. What book should I buy? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-13 02:18:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [360] Anyone here able to host the third heist? With or without group. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-13 00:04:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I need it. I've ran prison break too often at this point and humane labs always breaks down because of leavers. 

Mic pref but i don't have one so neither should you if you want... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [No Spoilers] Would I be crazy to pause my reading of ASOIAF to pick up The World of ice and fire? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-12 23:49:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So I finished ACOK a week or 2 ago and I picked up ASOS. Now I understand ASOS is the best in the series, or at least most action packed. So would I be crazy to start reading that, as I pack and prepare for a trip to Paris and while I'm moving house. (so a lot of stress basically and chaos).

Or would I be better off just picking up "The World" until the chaos is over. And take in I'm fascinated by the old Targaryens, beyond the wall, the battle for kings landing etc. Although I've heard it's not that great because Martin was only a co-author...?

To be honest.. I'm just looking for some fan reviews of The World of Ice and Fire because I feel starting up ASOS in the chaos right now instead of leaving it for when I'm settled back in and have the time to indulge it, is madness. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [No Spoilers] Is there any sign of Episode 3 in Telltale Games' Game Of Thrones? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-12 22:41:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Seeing as Titanfall's dlc or season pass is free right now. Is the game worth picking up for 360? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-12 19:50:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [360] Looking for a group with mics preferably and can host the heist.. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-12 17:40:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I have done Prison Break and Humane Labs. I'd like to try a new one but I don't know how. I can't host any heists because there is a large ass pay in right? Either that or I need a place big enough to host it. 

I don't have a mic but I do have a quick setup to message you within seconds of you speaking to me. 

I'm on right now. Add BradysIGN 

Pref: Driver, ground shooter or ninja on occasion.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> I got Netflix this day last month for the first time with the idea of watching a lot more movies than I normally do. After a month all I have watched is the TV show section... </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-12 16:48:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Heists may be the single best addition to a game ever. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-12 11:30:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So when I play GTA online it's just to run races and waste time...

But now with heists out. It's all I do. 

I went from stealing a prison bus, to blasting my way out of prison, to parachuting into Humane Labs with night vision and swimming through an underwater tunnel to a pick up spot where I had to shoot up flares to signal my location.

It just has such an epic feel to it. It's hard to explain but the first time you run a heist and it goes well... It's such a great feeling (even if I am only getting 10-15%).

I just thought, with all the chaos of people screaming about server problems that I'd share how I feel about the content itself and by god I couldn't be happier.

Thank you Rockstar. Once again you managed to live up to the hype. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What is it like to read "A Brief History of Time", or "The Grand Design" ? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-12 03:37:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So I'm watching The Theory of Everything for the second time and it has me thinking. 

I like to believe I read, but I really don't. 

I like to believe I understand certain aspects of science and go further than just reading an article, which I don't.

So now I plan on picking up one of the two books in the title. But how do they read? Is it all just equations, how this came to be that, if this happens then that happens because of it. 

Or is it an easy book to pick up and is written in such a way that anyone really, could read it?

If you have read either of them I'd love to hear your thoughts on them as I should be buying one within the next 16 hours so I'd like to know what I'm getting into. OR if there is a different book completely that does a good job of opening up my knowledge base and just dropping a block of science into. 

Forgive that last analogy/metaphor... It's 2am and I haven't slept in more than 3 hours a night in 3 days. 

Just leave your replies here and I should get back to them in about 6 hours. Thanks :) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Anyone on here want to run Humane Labs on 360? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-12 01:05:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm trying this stealth mission... And it just keeps failing us. How do we do it? If you have a group can we run it or something to show me?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Anyone up for heists on 360 right now? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-11 10:25:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm doing the prison heist for the first time and the guy I'm with keeps crashing the plane on escape so I'm looking to put together a team that actually knows the role they're in.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Is there anyone out there that is against Chapman ending up with Vause? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-11 05:02:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Hola Unblocker users. Is the US version of Netflix blocked right now? Anchor free or something? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-11 03:00:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Those of you that have been in solitary or 'the shoe'. What was it like and how long were you there? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-11 02:45:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Will I need a mic to do a heist? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-10 21:30:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So I haven't kept up with heists at all.. Whenever I play gta it's just to do races online. So what's the deal with heists? I'm guess it's just like the single player version right? So would I need a mic to get it going or would playing without one go just fine once we have our shit together?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Can we talk about HBO and all it's GO and NOW glory? This is a rant, just so you know... </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-10 01:43:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> How would YOU make a guard outside Buckingham Palace talk? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-09 21:10:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You know the guys. Dumb hats, red coats. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What stats should I be looking for on my jedi consular? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-09 20:59:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So I just started the game, got some loot and filled out most slots with armor. But after armor.. Do I go for endurance? Force? Willpower? Etc. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Hawking was diagnosed with ALS at 21. He was given a 2 year life expectancy. 52 years later he's still alive. How? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-09 12:51:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [No Spoilers] Can we get a Kickstarter or something started to make a Game of Thrones MMO? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-08 23:16:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So lets face it. Just about every franchise out there has an mmo right now. Lotr, Star Trek, Star wars, etc.

But... Can we just imagine  a GOT mmo for a moment? The world that we all know and love comes to life even more than it already is. 

I've thought out a few pieces. For starts, you'd choose your sex. then where you are from in the world, choose to be a northerner, southern, bravos etc. Then choose the house you represent. Then your class. Then off you go.

For each choice, like most mmo's, your starting choices will have effects.

For example: If you were to be from the north you could have cold resistance.

If you were to be represent the Lannisters you get extra starting gold, a higher cap or a bigger inventory.

Dothraki could have +fire damage or fire resistance. 

Greyjoys could have something water related. Hold breath for longer or ship combat could be a thing which they excel at.

Starks of course, if they choose a hunter could have a direwolf as a pet. 

Stannis could of course have a god mode with zero cooldown. 

This is just an idea I thought up while making pizza so it could be an awful idea but I'd genuinely love this. It of course would takes years and because of it, it could be in the works already. I just hope if/when this idea comes around it is someone who cares about the world at the helm of it.

Love to hear your thoughts on this. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Is Exodus: Gods and Kings worth watching? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-08 22:35:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So the only thing I've heard about this movie is the whole white's only controversy. But I cared very, very little about that. 

Apart from that... What's the vote on the movie? Is it worth a watch?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Why do referral links not give me 7 days of sub time? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-08 22:09:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So I tried this a few days back with an account I already had and it wasn't working so I expected the problem to be the fact it's an account already registered in game.

So I went ahead and clicked a referral link while logged out of the website. It looked like it was all going well. I clicked the link, it sent me to the registry page, I registered, made my password and everything and finished at the download window. 

But then when I logged into the game... It didn't work? I don't really know what I get for being a sub yet exactly but right now I literally want it for a race. I don't know the name but I want to be the blind guys with cloth over their eyes. Call it what you will, it's a high preference for me just because I like the look of it. 

Do I just get the extra xp buff and use of chat with the 7 day trial or should it have given me all advantages of subbing. If so it didn't work because once I tried to make my char I had no race options. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> TIL: George Lucas' eldest daughter Amanda is a professional MMA fighter. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-08 21:11:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> So I just watched the episode about getting a certain baby back. (SPOILERS AHEAD)Matt Smith series btw. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-08 18:28:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So I have recently taken up this series after years of ignorantly judging it. And by god it's incredible. I've always hoped for Pond and Doctor to get together but I've come to accept the brother/sister setup they have.

But I just found out River is Pond's baby... Like... Holy fucking shit.

After all this time of just expecting River and Doc to have fun confrontations and slowly see her drift out of the relationship just as he gets into it... But I never.. Ever expected this. 

I'm only starting the next episode Let's Kill Hitler so I expect more to unravel but I had to rant about this for a second.

Holy shit.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Is there a reason WoD dungeon queues take a ridiculous amount of time? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-08 02:03:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So I have just left this problem alone for a while now and accepted it but now I just have to rant for a second.

First off. The lack of dungeons for level 90-100 in my opinion is quite, quite bad. It's what? 6-7 dungeons for 10 levels? Now I understand the fact the quests and story is pretty great and has a certain epic feeling to it (the soundtrack helps) but there are so few dungeons and the ones I've played (up to Skyreach) really aren't that great IMO.

Now. Why the F am I waiting 20-40 minutes for a dungeon? I was once told it took so long at low levels because there weren't many people doing them. They took 15 minutes at most. I am waiting almost twice that time for a level 97-100 dungeon. Is there an official reason for this? Has Blizz gave a word on the matter? It's not a matter of boredom. I am questing between dungeons but that isn't a reason to take so long. The grind to get 100 is killing me inside simply because I feel all I do is wait, run, kill a bullet sponge and then have to wait another 30 minutes. 

All in all, this is just an opinion so I'd like to hear yours. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> This was such a fun episode. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-08 00:32:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So I just wrapped up 220... I'm already thinking about reloading it. 

The second half of the show was definitely the better half. But you have to actually 'watch' it. for me anyway, I click the show on and tab out of that window. This week I left it open and it was soo.. so much better. 

You got to see the faces slowly take in the effects of the drinks. 

I don't really know what to see other than this is probably, at least in my opinion, on par if not better than the show with Wolf.. It's a bold statement I know but t'is an opinion.

Hats off to the guys for doing it.

*Fuck Jesus*  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [Tv all] The Rains of Castamere song truly is unforgettable and appears a lot more than you'd realize. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-07 02:00:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So I just finished the 2nd season as I'm going through my first re-watch of the show since release and I have noticed how often they use the tune to RoC. A few episodes end with it playing and it's used for a good few 'moment's' in the show. Did anyone else realize it on their rewatch or did you get rid of the scars they received at the Red Wedding?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> So I just heard gravity is weaker than some other forces. What does that mean exactly? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-06 18:06:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm watching a documentary on Netflix called Particle Fever. It's about the hadron collider and how it was built or the first time I turned on.. I'm not sure yet and I'm sorry my ignorance is shining through. I wish I knew that which I spoke of.

But anyway. One of the scientists here was talking about asking the real questions. He listed a few things and then said "why is gravity weaker than other forces?"... 

What forces are stronger than gravity and has there been any progress in answering this since.. 2010 let's say.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> So I just started watching Doctor Who and one thing keeps getting me.. Does anyone else think Karen Gillan can sometimes look like an older version of Sophie Turner? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-06 03:27:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So I'm watching the Matt Smith version after years of saying I'd never watch the show and how it just looks bad.... It's so.... So good. Everything from the witty humor to the overall story arc. How she waited years for him. How he is the very last of his kind. How at some point in his life he marries... That other doctor. Although..... I really hope he falls for Amy. I really do. +I'm betting they get around to her going back in time to get married in her normal time. 

+They got Iain Glen for 2 episodes so.. That was fun to see.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> So Big Hero 6... Is such a good movie. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-05 16:52:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> SPOILER ALERT!!!!!! 

So I just finished watching it and before we go any further just know I tend to avoid watching animated movies. I don't know why but I just never took interest in them until my brother was watching it yesterday and the part I seen gave me a giggle. 

But then I started watching it and it was quite fun.. Until his brother dies. I was not expecting that shit. Like.. They just killed off his fucking brother. 

Baymax(?) is so fun to watch on screen. Everything from when he first pops up in the bedroom and awkwardly makes his way over to Hiro and then to the moment he sacrifices himself for them and does so in such a human way... I cried.. Like really, really cried watching that. I don't really know what I'm trying to say other than how fun it was to watch. This is a poorly written rant and I'm sorry about that but damn I enjoyed that. Are there any other animated movies I'd enjoy? If so leave them in the comments. Thanks! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Why should I subscribe if I'm new to the game? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-05 00:09:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm level 3 right now and already considering a subscription. Although the money it costs is not really a small amount to me.. I'd be willing to pay for even a month or so. But what does it get me? I've had a look at the stuff it says but I don't really understand if it's super important. I'd like to be able to use chat of course but apart from that... Is there any reason to or should i hold out until level 50?

+What is the deal with light vs darkness on my char. Apart from gear and some visual differences, are the choices important?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [No Spoilers] What is your favorite part of the world in ASOIAF? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-04 10:56:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I mean everything from the politics and backstabbing of kings landing. To the stories of beyond the wall, the actuality of what is beyond the wall and people live. To the Iron Islands. To Bravos, Qarth, Yunkai(?) and everyone beyond. 

Personally I am fascinated with whatever is beyond the wall. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> This is not exactly what Kyle would have seen and the sky may have been different but this is an example of what he seen in Texax. (PKN 28) </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-04 03:38:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [No Spoilers] If you can rank the books from best to worst, can you do it? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-03 13:33:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm just about to wrap up ACOK and I wasn't incredibly happy with it, apart from certain moments of course which I will not say because its a no spoiler thread but in terms of the other books, is this one of the better ones or one of the worst (although still good) ? To be fair.. it may just be that I wasn't a big fan of season 2 in general because it didn't really have any super memorable moments from it (although sometimes my memory is poor) so going into ACOK i wasn't excited about it too much and I understand that is my wrong doing so that's why I'm here.

What order would you put the books in without giving too many reasons why?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [All Tv spoilers] If you could bring one character back from the dead, who would it be? TV ONLY! </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-03 11:54:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm really struggling here to choose between Oberyn and Drogo.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> I think I've just found Kyle. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-03 10:00:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [Tv spoilers] How do you feel about the fact the show creators know the ending and some key notes but have to make their way to it alone? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-02 06:35:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So we know the show is finishing before the book and we know Martin gave D D the ending and some of the key plot points but not everything. Knowing this I've come to think about how it could go. 

Because we have the whole Bran and the Children thing going on, magic and what not. Throwing fireballs if I remember. Then you have the whole white walker situation, the dragons.

I don't know any of the story outside the show and the first two books but is there some way we could see Bran controlling dragons to destroy the whitewalkers? Because like... They're kinda hard to kill. They need to be burnt to stay dead and Bran is north of the wall already so we'd need to understand why exactly the dragons end up above the wall. WHICH I HAVE AN IDEA ABOUT. 

Before we go there I just have to say.. If this show is going towards an epic finish, everyone uniting, everyone dying, white walker battles, dragons everywhere, dragons eventually reaching Kings Landing (hopefully).... They are really going to have a high, high budget. 
This is ahead of the show or even in the show without you knowing about it but it's a theory I have so don't read if you want to figure it out on your own. (It's in relation to Jon Snow's mother.)

[] (#s "So Jon Snow has no mom yet in the books right? And well. I can't exactly remember how I came to the conclusion but I after connecting Robert to Lyanna, then Lyanna had a connection to the Targaryen's right? Rhaegar I think? Then 'A song of Ice and Fire' so.. Am I right, at least in the ball park of thinking Jon Snow is somehow related to Dany? Now I understand it's all just theories right now but after enough evidence can you figure it out? I've heard there are forums everywhere but I'm afraid to go there. Spoilers and all.") 

I just realized I made this post to talk about the differences the show could have to the book and ended up just ranting on about something else. 

I just meant.. The show could go full hollywood and do everything I've said and then the books could come out, and be really relaxed (as relaxed as Martin can write). So I am honestly happy they're going to be finishing first, it gives them room to work around the story, although I've heard they're already doing that pretty well.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> People all across the world seem to have the same idea that sleep is great and the best part of some days. But when I think about it... I'd remove sleep from my life if I could. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-02 03:49:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [Season 1] Rewatching season 1 and this scene comes on. I have forgotten about it over the years but damn is it incredible. Just the power and emotion in this moment. May be a new favorite. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-02 02:37:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Amazing archery skills in slow motion with analysis -SmarterEveryDay </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-01 17:56:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [No Spoilers] What is your favorite Game of Thrones/ Song of Ice and Fire wallpaper? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-01 12:10:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [I have this one except better res] (http://www.wallpaperhi.com/thumbnails/detail/20120223/game%20of%20thrones%20stark%20winter%20is%20coming%20banner%20george%20r%20r%20martin%20song%20of%20ice%20and%20fire%20house%20stark_www.wallpaperhi.com_5.jpg)
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> So I just watched 15 minutes of cinematics for this game and have to know. Does it make you feel as epic as it looked? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-28 19:02:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So I understand that the fighting and gameplay is going to be basic MMO stuff but how is the story and world you play in? 

I played WoW for a bit and i didn't even bother reading the quests after a while because it was just run, collect, kill, repeat.

How are the quests in this game?

 How does the world itself feel and how does that work? Is there a teleport-taxi type system for travelling between planets or do you own a ship you fly. 

Is there ship combat? 

What is the max level and what is late game like? In WoW you had raids and farming for gear. Is it the same in this game? 

I am just really interested in this because I am 18, so for me Episode 1-3 were my originals, which is probably why i never loved the series as others do. But I really hope to go back and watch the movies, read up on it or whatever so I'm ready for episode 7 because watching the cinematic really reminded me of the potential this series. The sheer force of the jedi's. The soundtrack. The epic battles and quest for good vs evil. I just have to know if you feel any of that in this game or if it makes you actually feel like you're important.

Thanks.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> So I just finished Season 3 and thought I'd share how I feel. SPOILERS FOR ALL 13 EPISODES! </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-28 04:03:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So before I start I have to add in something. I tend to rant a bit about things that don't matter and reading it may be hard because I ramble a lot but I'll do my best to stay on track. 

Right now it's 2:30 am. Season 3 released at 8am for me yesterday morning and I couldn't sleep last night and instead of waking up around 2-3 pm I said fuck it and stayed awake through the night just to get a good start for the season. 

The first episode had a pretty memorable moment to me. He just straight up pissed on his dad's grave. Then the rest of the episode followed the life of Doug and showed glimpes of Frank on tv and in meeting. It really did a good job at making me feel bad for Doug. How he lost everything just because he had some creepy love for a girl. How he just desperately wanted to work with Frank again and literally, by the looks of it, broke his arm, put a wooden spoon under it then wrapped it up and used the damn spoon as a brace replacement so to speak and that made me just question how I've always felt about Doug. 

The next 'great moment' I remember is the debate/interview between Frank, Sharp and Dunbar. I loved this entire scene. It was just so straight forward and 'this is politics'. How Sharp, before the scene, tried to make a deal with Dunbar but she declined so Sharp went right ahead and accused Dunbar of being sexist and being a shitty parent. Then out of no where, Frank drops the bomb on Sharp (who was basically winning the debate for him, without him ever having to speak out too much) and tells everyone her kids are in private school too. 

Then the whole Remy and Sharp + Tony (? The writer) and the other writer.. The 2 little love plots.. I would like to think they hold a big place in the story, backstabbing and scandals or w/e but I just felt they were a bit unnecessary or at least got more screen time than they needed. +The Remy and Sharp scene, when he's walking out and turns back for them to kiss.. I've never felt so pushed out of a show in my life. It was just brutally predictable, forced and was just a poor, poor scene in my opinion. 

After that we the whole Petrov thing. You know... Writing this, I'm trying to think of scenes, characters and stuff. I completely forgot about Petrov for some reason but.. I really enjoyed watching him on screen. How he just said fuck it and kissed Claire at the start and then set up his own troops to die just so plays could be made. (+when he showed off his scars.. Total badass russian moment) 

You have the whole Claire on the UN thing. How she was pusing out Durant (if that's her name?) then makes a deal out of them being equals. They have a few drinks and that whole deal is forgotten about and I can't remember seeing her on screen after that. 

Doug and Rachel/Cassie. It was incredibly uninteresting imo. I'm sure we were meant to feel for Doug and the choice he had to make but.... I just didn't. Once he got info she was back he went back to being creepy/ psycho Doug for her, which I enjoy to watch but that final scene could have been done a bit more. It was just emotionless or something.

Then I have to give a few mentions to EVERY TIME FRANK LOST HIS SHIT. He needed to do it more. In 13 episodes he probably 'snapped' 4 or 5 times.  

Then the final scene.. Going into this season and seeing Claire get sick I was expecting a bad illness or ever for her to die  so I paid attention to that and after a while I really just accepted the fact they will either be mourning her at the end of the season or she's leaving. Which she did.

That scene about him taking control. not the sex one, oh btw, I still don't understand exactly why she did that. I'm talking about the final 'big' scene. When they're in the office, she says he is what's missing and he grabs her by the jaw and starts to lose his shit but doesn't lose it too much (sadly) and he takes control of that scene which I loved. Then she just comes out in a later scene and leaves him. I grinned at that but that was it.

Now this is the hard part... I don't remember much after that. I understand binge watching a show just mashes it all together but I found myself enjoying the show. Though.... Not as much as I had enjoyed the first and second season. I don't know what was missing. I just didn't feel any threat this season, at all. We had the abortion note scare but that was instantly dealt with when he gave Doug a job. 

Like in season 1 he had constant shit on his plate that could straight up ruin his career and cripple everything. Kate Mara's character was constantly mixing up shit. The Russo guy who they killed off. Once Kate's character became unnecessary and a pain he pushed her out in front of a fucking train. THAT RUINED ME. Claire had the whole sex scandal deal, then the rape plot. How we found it Frank had that thing going on with an old friend at the reunion, which was also a fun as hell episode to watch. 

I just don't have words for it. 

24 hours ago I was literally deciding to stay awake so I can get to House of Cards the second it releases... I loved it for the opening hour or so then it just became another show that had a stand out moments and nothing else. I understand that a lot happened and they moved by some serious plot but it really doesn't feel like they did. 

I'm sad to say it but after waiting so long for it to release and all the excitement I had for it.. It didn't live up to it. 

SURE. Maybe I am horribly wrong in  this and binge watching it was the worst choice I could make but I will be going back to watch it and this time I'm going to do an episode a week and do my best to get better at reviewing it. Who knows, maybe actually get good at sharing how I feel and putting aside my bias hype or distaste for certain parts of the show.

If you made it through the reading I'd love to hear your thoughts on the season. Out of 10... I'd give it 8 or 8.5.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> I just have something to say about Season 3 Episode 11. It is of course a spoiler. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-28 01:41:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So i don't watch politics.. Apart from this show. So seeing that debate was something fairly new to me. 

But that was a fucking incredible scene to watch. Everything from Sharp stepping up being sexist to dropping the bomb about Dunbars kids being sent away so she doesn't have to raise them. Then Frank turning to Sharp and bringing her private school kids into it... 

I LOVE THIS FUCKING SHOW MAN. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> How exactly does PTR work? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-28 00:11:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So I like to think I know the basics to D3. I have about 150 hours or so (completely guessing). And yes, I understand typical d3 players are laughing at my time right now but lets leave that behind before I rant on for no reason.

So I'm letting PTR install and I just have a few questions. First off, why is it a completely new install? Couldn't it just be a patch type deal? How do characters work in terms of crossing over? Can I pick up my season 2 monk from my normal account to the PTR? Does the gear I find it PTR drag across or must I keep that in PTR until the patch comes out, then I can drag across, if tghat makes sense? Then the final thing is a kinda odd question. Is there a 2000% legendary drop on PTR right now or was the title of the stream I watched just stating a stat he had on gear or a bug he found with gear?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> It's says I failed the test. Anyone out there who's knows about computers. Can I run this game? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-27 07:48:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [No Spoilers] Can we talk about Winds of Winter for a minute? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-27 05:01:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So like it says in the title, no spoilers here but this is just something I realized. 

You guys have been waiting on this book for years now right? and it's still a year or 2 away... This book is  hopefully going to be around 900-1000 pages. Depending on how fast you read, that book can last you a few days or a few weeks. But then it's done with and you are going to have to wait another few years (hopefully not as long).

With knowing this I have to ask how you guys will deal with it. Will you pick it up and read through the last book again before reading it. Binge read and just consume it over a week (if you even could?) or will you steady it out, savoring it by doing maybe a chapter a day, 2 day, 100 pages a week maybe?.. I don't know, I've never been that into a series to be big on it's launch date and seeing as I'm 300 pages into ACOK I'm going to be waiting for WoW with the rest of you although I have no plan for it. I guess I'd like to steady it out but lets be honest.. It's kinda hard to put this book down once you start.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Why exactly have we not discovered everything there is to discover in the depths of the ocean? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-27 02:21:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> So the further we into space the further back in time we are looking. Because a black hole emits no light whatsoever. How are we looking at and saying it's back in time? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-27 02:01:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Just throwing it out there for anyone who may have forgotten but House of Cards is out tomorrow (8am GMT!) </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-27 01:28:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I got into the show because of this show so I thought I'd remind the people who may have forgotten about it or don't know exactly when it starts. 

Just looking out for you guys :)
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Is there a set time for the House of Cards release tomorrow GMT? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-26 23:35:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I didn't have Netflix for last season's release so I have no idea what time it dropped. Should I expect it at midnight GMT? 10am? Noon? 6pm?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Those of you that have seen 'Blackfish', would you still go to Seaworld or ever think about bringing your kids? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-26 21:52:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Those of you that played the newest Thief game. Was it any good? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-26 19:03:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I seen a few screenshots of this game up around it's release and yet that's all I ever heard of it.

Was the story any good? Is it a long game? Is there a loot type system and shop (i may  have seen the character taking gold from a box or something)? In terms of stealth games, how does this hold up seeing as it's literally called Thief? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [Discussion] Is Destiny worth buying at this point, knowing I've never once done a raid or done any of the late game sh*t? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-26 03:55:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So I played the beta, loved it. Picked the game up just before the first expansion dropped and enjoyed it BUT.. I was that little bit late to the game, so it made finding a group to learn with was pretty hard and.. I don't exactly understand light levels and how to farm for gear in this game.
So here I am, 8 months(?) after release and just want to know. If I pick up the game again is there a place I can go to find out how to farm for a weapon, get light gear or w/e, how to get a high enough gear for raids (if that's even a thing, I just played a bit of wow a few months back and you needed a high gear level to raid). +Being late to raids is usually a horrible thing. If I got into vault of glass or whatever it's called (forgive my ignorance) I would have nooooo idea what to do. I seen some clips and someone had a shield, there was a fog type deal going on, then just a never dying boss.
Also, if you're on xbox 360 and looking to play but be patient enough to help me (on skype [typing or speaking], I don't have a headset for xbox) just let me know. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Is Destiny worth buying at this point, knowing I've never once done a raid or done any of the late game sh*t? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-26 03:44:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> A whole lot of people are going to scream and shout how amazing Aquaman is even though they've abused him for years. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-26 02:27:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> People that have seen 'Serena'. Is it worth watching? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-25 20:30:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So it's Jen Lawrence and Bradley Cooper. But I've seen absolutely nothing for this movie.. Is it worth watching?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> So.. Now that Parks and Rec is sadly over. What should I watch next? PandR is the only American comedy show I've seen. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-25 13:57:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The res is bad I know but.. These two moments have officially broken me. It's 4am and I'm bawling crying. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-25 05:21:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> My fear for Alzheimer disease outweighs my fear of death by an incredible degree. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-25 01:51:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> For anyone waiting on the Parks finale, here is the website. Filled with interviews and behind the scenes. Even the latest episodes. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-24 22:59:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> If you had to a fictional villain as your life long best friend, from birth til' death. Who would it be and why? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-24 19:22:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> had to have* 

Sorry. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Can anyone provide a link to an IQ test that actually works without me paying? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-24 11:30:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Nick Offerman- Hanky song. From his Netflix special. (Gold in my opinion) </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-24 03:44:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Can we talk about Dear Zachary please? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-24 02:57:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I think that will be the one and only time in my life that I watch that movie.
It's the single most sad yet happy yet brutally angering movie I've ever watched.

There were moments of just out right crying, covering my mouth as the tears rolled down my eyes. Then there were moments of happiness. When you see him walking, how he looked like his dad.... Even now writing this I'm crying again.

As for anger.. I can't put it into words. I'm not even going to speak of her other than the idea that one day people forget her name and she's lost in time.

I genuinely don't understand how Kate and David did it. How even after losing a son the kept going. They fought the battles they needed for that baby. Then they lost the baby... I don't think I'd ever have made it that far. Now to learn they didn't stop there and kept going to change the bullshit system that let it all happen. I just....
Let me hear your thoughts on this movie. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> So I just binged watched all 6 seasons and 11 episodes of Parks and Rec.. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-24 01:02:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I honestly don't know what to say. I caught up just in time for the finale apparently so that's a thing.. 

So a few thoughts. 

It's probably the best cast show on Tv. I didn't know much about the show going into it apart from Chris Pratt and the few words around Reddit about Amy Poehler (I seen that one speech about her being 'blonde tina fey') and that's about it.

So where do I start? I found it impossible to pick a favorite character. They all have their own traits. 

Leslie was... Well, she's Leslie.

Ann was a great character and I loved her with Leslie but when she left I didn't feel a massive loss.

Andy. He was perfectly dumb and goofy without being over the top. Some of his one liners were just incredible (I'm going to be saying that a lot I expect).

April. You know.. I knew her face going into this and didn't expect to be a big fan of her. I was wrong.. When she was trying to get with Andy in the early seasons, they were probably some of my favorite scenes (I'm a sucker for cute romance and some aww moments). +Some of her satanic, hate filled one liners were pretty good and how she only really had a few touching moments in the show made it better.

Ben. I love Ben. I knew the actors face going into the show and really quite honestly expected to hate him. But then his witty accountant humor and his nerd moments were great. Specifically the Batman costume and then the Iron Throne(although Leslie made that scene).

Chris T. I'm not going to lie.. It took me a while to get around to liking this guy. His constant happiness, upbeat attitude and everything, I found it odd and off putting. But then I got used to it and boy I love it. "that is literally"... He's great. 

Gerry, Jerry, Larry, Terry. He is probably the best butt of a joke I've ever seen. Everything from him finding out he was adopted to being the mayor of Pawnee. How he got that wife. How easy his life is at home and he came out of retirement for them and he still never got a word in, no matter the idea he had. 

Tom. Tom is right there with Ann for me. He never left the show, but if he did.... I wouldn't have missed him that much. He is fun and his ideas/patents were a good giggle but I found that to be it.

Donna. Donna was fun I guess. She was always around and everything but did have a few moments. How she had a fiance in Denver or something and all these other out of work things going on. 

Before I get on to Ron... I have to give an honorable mention to those f*cking twins. From the second the guy got on screen to the last time either of them are shown.. I hated them deeply. They were perfect. 

Oh. And Mark. He was pretty good I guess. I don't remember many great Mark moments. 

Now... Ron Motherfucking Swanson. Yup. I just realized who my favorite is. That is all. 

So.. After listing everything I'm thinking about the characters I don't know what else to say. This show has given me, by far, the most bursts of laughter. I want to do an 'everything from this to this' but I'm blanking painfully hard and lets be serious, there are way too many of them to choose from(although not right now).

One thing I do have to say though... Season 7 really didn't do it for me. I don't know what it was. It was just 'off' somehow. Maybe it's just because they didn't all share the office, because it wasn't a typical group deal. How they are all moving apart slowly, which is how it should end I know but it's not that great. I have to admit I cried when Ron told Leslie he went to ask for that job. How he was a rock the entire series and then he felt alone and had to deal with it on his own until they got locked in that office. 

This is a really long rant that is a mess but I'll post anyway. Love to hear your thoughts on the show.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> So I'm about to leap into this game for the first time. Anyone want to hold my hand and teach me the ropes? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-22 06:37:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> A question about the Tv adaption of the Green Arrow. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-22 01:55:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So I've recently got into the Green Arrow comics (on the 4th of Year One) and I've noticed a few difference from the TV show. How his dad was on the boat and the entire thing was set up for him to die. +Sarah was there. But in the comics he is just alone and he was never meant to go on the boat because he was being robbed. 

So with this is mind and now knowing Ollie is destined to marry Black Canary in the comics at some point (which by the way, is that Laurel or Sarah). That being said, am I now to expect the TV Ollie to fall back towards Laurel or am I okay to hope and wish for Ollie to accept Felicity's love and they live happily ever after? 

This was poorly written I know. All I have to say is sorry, it's been a long day. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> When it comes to listing the soundtracks you have been a part of. Can anyone beat out Hanz Zimmer? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-20 04:00:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> How does Fallout 3 run on xbox? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-19 23:22:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I've often heard it runs like shit. Does it really? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Where do I start when it comes to reading the comics/graphic novels? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-19 20:27:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So I like to think I'm a big comic book fan but in reality I just love the movies, games, tv shows. 

So I've decided I'm going to get into the comics. But I have nooooo idea where to start. Like you have all these different versions of each hero. Young batman, old batman, the detective. Where do I start? 

Specifically I'd be looking for Superman, Green Arrow, The Flash and maybe touch on Batman. Maybe some green lantern too then slowly move into all the Justice League stuff.

So where would I start? Is there an app I can get for my pc? Is there a website that I can sub to and read them as a side-scrolling deal? Do I need to order them online and if so how much is the typical comic book? I wouldn't be looking for any super special editions or anything, just enough to start my adventure I guess. 

Just to add in. Going to my local store and asking for advice is a no-go... I don't have a store within reasonable distance.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What comic book game do you hope Rocksteady make a run at? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-19 20:00:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Rocksteady are the company behind the Arkham series. 

I am just sitting here waiting for Injustice to download while watching Man of Steel. Completely unrelated to Rocksteady until..

What is Rocksteady were to make a game based on another comic book hero now that Arkham Knight is the last in the Batman series. Would they make a good Superman game? Dark, gritty, violent. Would they do Flash, a Green Lantern series, Green Arrow...?

I'm just ranting on as I wait for this download but I'd like to hear your thoughts.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [BF4]I can buy one dlc for BF4 tomorrow. What one should it be? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-19 05:09:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm not really picky about big map or small map, land map or sea map. But in terms of content, what is the best dlc? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Was Arkham Origins a good origin story or just good story in general? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-19 04:24:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So I played the first Arkham game and did enjoy it. The detective, stealthy feel to it was great and refreshing but I don't remember the story much but I did enjoy it. 

I skipped Arkam city because I had no console but I got to play pieces of it on occasion but I never thought about buying it once I picked up a console.

So now Origins is on sale for 15 euro (which is a decent amount of money for me right now) and I have to know. Is Origins just a fancy title for another game in the Arkham series or while I actually get a good and flowing origin story? 

(I guess this could be added here but if it's not this game it's going to be Injustice and Skate 3 instead of it.. Even though I doubt they'd have great stories, it's just the other option.)(ooooorr.. You know... Fallout 3 is just 15 euro.) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Favorite war movie that is on Netflix? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-19 03:35:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Those of you that have witnessed a 'supernatural' experience. Can you talk about it a bit? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-18 18:05:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Redditors who have been in prison. How was your experience? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-18 17:54:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> How long were you in? What was it for(if not too personal)? Did your conviction make it easier or harder in terms of living. You know the way rapists or pedophiles supposedly have a harder time than others.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Netflix are releasing House of Cards on the 27th and that is a Friday. Is this just another way of Netflix telling me they're taking another weekend away from me? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-18 00:04:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Some people may find this unrelated to the game but I have a tip that may help with the mindless grinding. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-17 18:17:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So lets face it, the season just started and we're all flying around, rushing rifts and doing grifts for that loot. But unless you're rolling in a party (like me) it may become tiresome or just... Not super entertaining for the first few hours, levels, however you want to look at it. 

But putting aside that pointless paragraph I've come to find myself listening to the game of thrones audiobook while I grind. This is in fact stereotyping in the way that d3 players love other fantasy stuff and have watched game of thrones and if you have and have considered reading, just listen to the audiobooks while you grind this. It completes 2 tasks at once. Getting gundo gear for your monk and enjoying the great adventure that is A Song of Ice and Fire.

You may find this post scrambled, written poorly and just a mess in general, which it is. I just thought I'd share my new favorite way to grind D3. 

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> I never watch Basketball but I'm watching the 2015 all star game right now. Why is there no Kobe? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-17 06:15:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So I genuinely never watch Basketball but I thought I'd watch this game because to be honest, it looks like they're having a lot of fun so why not watch it?

But why is there no Kobe in this game? Was he injured? Did he just not make the cut? ( I find that impossible). Could he just not make it? 

Forgive my ignorance, I'm just sitting here wondering. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [S2/ACOK] Something I just read about Jorah.. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-16 23:47:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So all this time I've been joking about friendzone Jorah and how he's forever alone, hopelessly chasing Dany...

And he's doing it all because Dany looks like his second wife? I got so sad reading that for some reason. How he told the story of how they met, what happened and then struggled his  way to the end of the story then getting up and leaving without ever mentioning what she looked like... Until she asked.

I shall no longer laugh at him when he throws himself towards her to do her deeds.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [TV] I have a question regarding casting(for lack of a better word) about a certain character for Season 5. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-16 06:06:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> SO BEFORE WE DIVE INTO THIS. I HAVE NO READ THE LATER BOOKS SO PLEASE DON'T SPOIL ANYTHING THAT DOESN'T NEED TO BE SPOILED FOR SEASON 5!!!

So Bran is not in this season. Just completely gone from the world for an entire season. 

Is this because they rushed his story? At least, I'm guessing they rushed his story because, well.. It seems rushed I guess? 

How do you guys feel about this because where they left us with Bran, was pretty exciting and seems to have a major, major role in the world. But.. They're just gonna stop it there for a season (2 years if you go from season 4 finale)... That's kinda frustrating right?

I don't know where I was going with this post but I had to share my jumbled up thoughts about the matter because it seems weird to me that they're dropping a main character for a season and plan on just bringing him back up the season after. Like how will they fill that in, all this time has passed and now he's just done his training? I don't know.. 

Love to hear your thoughts on this but like I shouted at the start, I'm only about 100 pages into ACOK so if you can hold back on anything that may ruin my experience I'd appreciate that but if it is just some small details that would help me understand this I'd be grateful. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> There is someone out there who has no idea who ISIS are and I am jealous of that fact. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-16 04:16:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Wolf: "My dad left when I was 5" Woody: "Oh that's right, I forgot you were black"..... </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-14 20:37:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Oh.... Oh my... 

This PKA may be my favorite ep of all time. 

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Anyone up for starting a group for Season 2? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-14 03:07:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm NA and have a decent bit of time in the game but nothing super (75 paragon) so I'm super new in terms of player and didn't really try last season simply because I didn't know what it was about but I'mm up for trying this time.

Anyone wanna do a few rifts or something?

UPDATE: I'm level 23.. Playing hunter btw </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What were the episodes filled with Fallout talk? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-14 01:36:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> PKA 217 and PKN 25 are up on Podbean. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-12 22:32:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> I loved Kingdom of Heaven(directors cut of course). Is there anything out similar to that, that I may enjoy? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-12 21:20:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What are some great Keanu Reeves movies? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-12 18:49:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So when I think of Keanu Reeves I'd think Matrix. (although lately I think John Wick). But apart from those movies, what else has he been in that is worth watching? I seen he was in that martial arts movie a year ago or something but I've heard awful things about that.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Is this quote true? "there are more stars in the sky than there are grains of sand on Earth. BUT, there are more atoms in a grain of sand than there are stars in the sky." </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-11 22:48:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Is there a way to add music into a video but behind the voices speaking on Adobe Premiere Pro? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-11 13:27:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So a guy I know is trying to put together a little movie. Just basics, he has the video, the speaking and the music he is using..

The only problem is that.

Whenever he goes to add the  music it replaces the voices and when he adds the voices it replaces the music.

He only has the trial and I'm 95% sure he's using this program (it's been a few days since we talked).

So is there a way to do this? A forum to help? A video tutorial?

Anything? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> If I were to go live on a planet that for every day there, it was a year here. How would my body age? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-11 11:16:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> With all the advancements in technology over the last few years. Iron man is more realistic than god. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-10 23:15:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> I just got the American Netflix. What should I watch? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-10 22:02:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So I like to believe I have a lot of movies under my belt but I don't really. I usually struggle to watch movies during the day because I'm busy playing a game, reading or whatever. But now with Netflix I can just scroll, click and watch. 

So far I've watched Chef and tried American Horror Story (leaving that behind).

What else should I watch that I may not think of while looking through the recent section on a torrent site?

I'm down for something artsy (but not too far artsy). A documentary. A tv show. 

I just want to make use of what I have been missing and don't know where to start.

TL;DR Just suggest some movies/documentaries/tv shows that are available on NA Netflix </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Guys.... Bethesda are hosting this years E3 conference.... GUYS! </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-10 18:00:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Is American Horror Stories all it's made out to be? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-09 22:35:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Story* SOORRYYY

..


So I've heard a lot lately about AHS and I have to know. Is it that good? 

Are the stories, plots actually good or creepy/scary to some degree? How is the acting? 

I just want to know if I should watch this show because I don't do much horror when it comes to tv or movies but if it's a great show I'll watch it for that. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Is 18 too old to go back to 5th year and finish school? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-09 09:39:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So a bit of backstory. Right now I'm in Youthreach.

After my Junior I moved from Dublin to Meath and where I moved to, both schools were full and the waiting list was too long for my mam's patience and she put me into youthreach. 

2 years later and I'm about to finish youthreach with a level 4.

the only problem is... What I plan on doing in college would be some kind of history and literature (as broad as that sounds) and going to youthreach I have completely forgotten my history facts and everything.

So anyway, I feel if I want to succeed in college I should go back to school and re-learn everything I've forgotten (which I have the time for.. sadly). 

Is it too late? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Can I trust the "Mystery Files" collection of documentaries? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-09 09:00:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So if you seen my post earlier you'd know I'm looking for doc's to watch on certain topics. 

Seeing as I've never been a huge documentary viewer I don't really know where to start and I'm painfully naive so if I were to watch something that was complete BS but presented in a way that seemed flawless, without further inspection I would probably believe it.

So anyway, I've found a series to start off my journey and just have to know if I can trust what they say. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Ellen talking to Harmony Zhu. A 9 year old piano player who goes to Julliard. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-09 06:50:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Are there any good documentaries of any of the 3 subjects? (in description) </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-09 06:32:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The time of Piracy, Nassau and all that.

The French Revolution.

Medieval times (Queen Elizabeth and everything [If I'm thinking of the right queen..]) .

I'd also like to add in Roman times.

Thanks all. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> I just started watching a Unity playthough and I have to give Ubisoft one thing. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-09 01:37:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This game so far (He's just about to chase the girl as Arno) is absolutely beautiful. I don't have the luxury of a next gen console so maybe it's just that all I see are last gen games but this game.... it's stunning. So far the story seems pretty interesting so I guess I have to say that with caution too seeing as not many people have loved the game.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [No Spoilers] What time is the "A day in the life of HBO" on tonight, GMT time? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-08 23:53:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I ask simply because if my past interactions with late night releases, the show would be on a certain website about 40 minutes to an hour after release. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Are there any tricks to listening to audiobooks? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-08 03:41:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So this is a tricky question to ask but...
I am reading A Song of Ice and Fire right now, but I'm painfully busy so it's hard to find time but when I do it usually flies by and I never get anywhere with the book.
I've looked into the audio books and I've tried a chapter or 2 but every time I do, my mind loses focus and I miss the details I read the book for and I feel at a real loss.
Is there anything I can do to make my mind focus a bit more on the reading? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Are there any tricks to listening to audiobooks? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-08 03:30:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So this is a tricky question to ask but...

I am reading A Song of Ice and Fire right now, but I'm painfully busy so it's hard to find time but when I do it usually flies by and I never get anywhere with the book.

I've looked into the audio books and I've tried a chapter or 2 but every time I do, my mind loses focus and I miss the details I read the book for and I feel at a real loss.

Is there anything I can do  to make my mind focus a bit more on the reading?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> I am loving this Game of Thrones talk. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-07 18:08:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's really all I have to say.

I enjoyed the Woody's mom stories and the usual pka banter but...

The last section of the show talking about the GoT books and the show...It's now what I look forward to when I see PKA is out. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Are there any Unity playthroughs out there that don't go through many bugs, glitches? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-07 13:13:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So I don't have next gen and I would have thought by now the game would be fixed, but I've heard it's not? So has anyone seen a playthrough of the game that had very little problems but someone entertaining behind the wheel? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> A question of time relativity, can you help? (It is a long, drawn out question, sorry....) </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-07 04:05:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> When you think of a pornstar's child you feel kinda bad for them, knowing either another kid will find footage one day or their mom will tell them. Just imagine the conversation Kim Kardashian is going to have with her child. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-07 03:43:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [BF4] If I had Premium for ps3 and now have an xbox. Does Premium drag across and if it does, how would I log into my ea account on xbox? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-07 02:56:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [Season 1 AGOT Spoilers] So I'm rewatching after reading the book and.... </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-07 00:14:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You'd think it would be easier to watch because I know how the show goes and I have read the book over the last few weeks but...

It's so, so much harder. Knowing the fate of Ned this season makes it worse. He keeps having these little touching scenes with his family and even the king and I am just sitting here thinking *"Maybe it'll be different this time.. He can't die this time..."*

When he told Jon he'd tell him about his mother the next time they see eachother. 

How he just talked to Arya about owning a sword, how Sansa will have to marry Joffrey one...

It's so painful to watch but so great at the same time.

Just have to add in something.. I just watched the scene when Dany realizes she's pregnant... I smiled and felt happy for her..... *oh wait -.-* </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What made Revelations such a bad game? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-06 18:23:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So I've often looked to rank the AC games and I've always noticed others who have ranked the games, put Revelations at the bottom of the list. 

So here I am watching the trailer for it and I just can't understand why people found it to be a bad game? Now the last time I played it was on release and I was but a boy when I played it and only really remember the ending (which I quite enjoyed I think?).

So from any other fans I have to ask, do you agree with it being the weakest game or did I just find the vocal minority? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Can we talk about The Imitation Game's closing scene for a second? [SPOILERS] </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-06 03:13:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So going into this movie I knew nothing of Turing and well...

Let me start of by saying I truly loved the movie. I loved Cumberbatch's performance (young Turing just as much I have to say). I would say what I love but it's a long list. Everything from the entire cast to the soundtrack to the pacing. 

But....

When I read he committed suicide.... I broke down crying.

Everything he did, how he kept it together, how he saved all those lives, made those decisions... I genuinely cannot understand how they made him do that. After all that..... I've never been hit as hard as this in terms of a movies ending.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What is your favorite franchise of all time? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-05 22:38:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It can be anything from a video game franchise to a fast food franchise, a drink franchise or even just a sports franchise.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Is Assassins Creed Black Flag worth going back to? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-05 12:49:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So I played a few days of back some time last year and now that Black Sails is back I'm on a bit of a pirate, open world, violent buzz (you all know the one). But after playing it for a few days last year and getting a bit into the story (maybe 15 hours game time and only 4-5 playing story). I have to know, those of you that have played it more than once, how do the story, sailing, pirate banter, missions all hold up? 

Any opinion from someone who has finished the game I'd like to hear. Thanks. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What has been your favorite phase of Reddit? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-05 04:53:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Is BookDepository a legit, trustworthy website? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-05 01:56:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Someone who has played Dragon Age Inquisition on xbox 360. How does it play? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-05 01:36:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I have to ask. I'm looking at buying a 50 euro game that is highly aimed towards the next gen so before buying it I have to know a few things..

How does it run?

What are the load times like?

Are the graphics nice and do the textures bug out often?

I just need to know these things. I bought Shadow of Mordor with every thought in my head of spending hours upon hours on it and didn't even finish it because of how distracting load times and texture bugs were. If this game is the same I'd love to know but if it runs like any other last gen game I'd love to know too. Thanks, </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Parents of un-vaccinated children. What made you make that choice? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-03 15:05:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [BFHL]Is Hardline out yet on 360? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-03 13:26:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I woke up this morning(8am gmt) and it was still not up and now I'm in school but if it's up I'll get someone to download it while I'm here.. Is it? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> How is this for my first 'real' custom deck? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-03 12:03:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> http://imgur.com/29GCEPW </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> I'm new to this game. How is this deck for my first made? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-03 11:47:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Is this game still populated and worth buying right now on 360? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-03 00:33:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So I was never planning on buying this game. Simply because i had a playstation on it's release but I've recently picked up a 360. Am I too late to the game? I watched a race to max level, or whatever it is and I still even with that, don't know much, if anything about the game other than the basics, its a fast paced shooter. But I've also heard in terms of customization and long term content it is pretty weak. Is this worth buying now this late into it's life? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [BFHL] How exactly do I get into the beta on 360? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-03 00:13:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So I'm in ireland which puts me GMT. Will i get the game once it is midnight and does it just show up on the store? will it just become available at a certain time pst, est, whatever and then show up? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Are there any great Pirate based games out there? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-02 22:10:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Anything from AC: Black Flag to an RTS. I just don't hear of many pirate games around. I can't run many games so if it's older I'll be happy with it but if it's a console game I'll also try it out. 

Just drop down some reviews of any pirate games you've played. I'd love to widen the pool. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [No Spoilers] Is there a noticeable difference between season 2 of the show and A Clash Of Kings? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-02 15:35:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So I'm just about to finish reading AGOT and I've noticed how it's pretty much how the show goes, not much differs between them(I'm sticking to no spoilers so I can't say what, it's minor though). Because of this, having seen the show first, I found it hard to read because it was predictable and I knew what to expect so I got nothing new from it really (apart from the fun in reading and the more in-depth story of course). Now that I'm about to buy ACOK, having already seen the show, is it the same kinda deal? Will I know what to expect or is this where the show starts to move away from the book?

On a sidenote, ACOK is only season 2 right or is it both 2 and 3? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Is Fallout 4 going to become the next Half Life 3? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-02 04:56:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's just been so long and all we ever get are rumors that are shot down. Also, this game has been hyped more than any game I can think of (valve games excluded) and it doesn't even have a story, a title, or any confirmation it's in the works. Am I wrong in feeling it's never going to happen and we'll look back in 10 years and joke about Fallout 4 coming out as we do now with HL3?

I have to add in. I don't want this to be the case, it's just an idea. I want fallout as much as the next guy but this is just a thought I gave some time to. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> I know that at some point in my life I've talked to a girl online who was in reality a guy pretending. What I really want to know is how many guys I've talked to that are actually girls IRL </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-02 03:05:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The music in this scene probably made me more emotional than any soundtrack before it. The Last of Us intro, "the Sarah scene", you know the one. [Spoilers] </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-01 22:12:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Syndicate's attempt at eating a Ghost Chilli Pepper went a completely different direction that Jordie's. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-01 07:14:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> I'm feeling super nostalgic right now. What is the best online version of YuGiOh to play? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-01 04:11:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [No Spoilers] How do you guys feel about no Winds of Winter this year and the fact HBO are going to beat him to the finish? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-31 16:12:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So forgive me if you disagree but I haven't had to wait because I'm only starting the book and I don't know how long ago the last book was released but I have to say this. Everyone is giving him an awful, awful time about the fact HBO are going to beat him to finish his own series but has anyone thought about how much time he has to spend doing publicity for the show, all the interviews? How his life, as I have to imagine, has blown up to an unimaginable degree right? If someone could tell me how long it's been since the last book release I'd appreciate it. But do you guys really, truly want to rush him just because the show is catching him? Do you not trust that by the time he does release it, it would be a whole, whole lot better than it would have been if he cut off parts and threw it out for sale just because a new season is coming up on the show? I'd just like to know if anyone else see's it from his side or if you really don't understand  what is taking him so long.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Now that it has been out a while and I'm looking to buy a new game. Sims 3 or 4? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-31 02:47:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Take in, I won't be getting any DLC at the start. Which game is the more fun to play or the more fluid game? Which one has more content in the base game? I'd just love to hear your comparisons but please. have time in the game you're advising. Thanks :) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Yes, I linked a trailer earlier but guys. Here's the official one straight off the facebook page. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-31 00:16:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> "Who's Fucking" .. An interview that well.. Just watch it. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-30 22:20:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Wild Card Trailer </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-30 14:14:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Game of thrones season 5 leaked trailer (not the best quality but it's pretty good for a cinema recording) </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-30 11:06:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [No spoilers] What's the deal with these posters I'm seeing a lot of? Are they exclusive to IMAX viewers or will I be able to order them online? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-30 01:07:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm from Ireland and I love a good poster so I'd love to own these but... We don't get an IMAX event so if I miss out on some fine ass wall decorations because HBO didn't bring the event to Ireland I'll be pretty let down. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [AGOT] So I just realized something... </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-29 00:10:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's hitting me harder than I ever expected but.. I just noticed I read my final every Eddard Stark chapter a few hours ago. I didn't realize it at the time but I was downloading an audiobook version and while I was looking for my chapter I started to browse how many chapters were left and it dawned on me, I can't find Ned. See, it's not that was a giant Ned fan, don't get me wrong he had more honor than a man can give credit for and he was truly all for family and justice but I never connected with him. But... His final chapter is him, rotting away in a cell, losing his mind... It is probably the single hardest chapter I've ever had to read(I don't read much but yeah.. I'm trying). He is just in pure darkness, losing it, not knowing if he'd be alive tomorrow, if it was tomorrow or if it was still the same day... I'm loving the books so far but noticing this made me think about his chapter a lot more and it does hurt that his final point of view is that.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [No Spoilers] Guys... We're gonna have a trailer for season 5 within the next 2 weeks.. Can we just take that in? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-28 02:10:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So I'm in Ireland so I'm not getting any imax viewings but we're more than likely going to get a trailer for it a few days after a shitty leak comes out.. I am only starting to reading the books and even doing that it's taking a long, long time simply because I have no willpower and I am just a gamer, plain and simple, I play LoL for maybe 5+ hours a day and that's including school so.. Yeah, I have a problem but back on point. I just can't wait for this trailer because it's both a trailer for a motherfucking season 5 and it should hopefully get me pumped enough to read more than I do. This post got a bit off topic but I'm just excited...  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> So I just watched Whiplash and am now looking to try jazz. Where should I start? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-27 17:13:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So before whiplash I've never thought about jazz much but now I'm going to give it a try. But where should I start?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> In Your Eyes... I can't get enough of it. Are the any movies with that kind of feel or story to it I can watch? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-27 06:05:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So Zoe Kazan.... She's kind of perfect in my eyes but I've seen everything she has and most recently In Your Eyes. I'm not searching for movies like this with her in it(because I've seen them all) but just a movie like this or anything with a really fun to watch, growing relationship on screen.
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Just to clear this up. What happens to the gear I take off the shelves of a blacksmith? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-26 22:11:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So in Skyrim you'd be arrested or attacked but in this they just let you get on with it. Is the only downfall to it that I can't sell it back but I can still use it? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> This is an awfully dumb question but... </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-25 03:19:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If I go Wood Elf and my friend went Nord, could we party up or does this game run along the idea of everyone hating eachother? So the only other MMO I've played is wow and I went alliance and he went horde so we couldn't play together, is it the same setup in this or does choosing the group matter as much? +I'm speaking about quests and dungeons(if this game has them) and not pvp. 
(Sidenote... What is the max level in this game?) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Am I wrong in wanting a prequel to John Wick? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-25 00:34:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The entire movie goes on how everyone knows him. The guy you send to get the boogeyman, the man who laid the foundation for the villain of the movie... Do we not want to see that story? What he was like before the escape and finish with how he got out.. I may be wrong and we could leave this to be a perfect one hit but as we've seen before(taken), people tend to run off the power a one-hit movie makes so if they do, would you want a sequel or prequel? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Interstellar was more emotional than we all expected it to be first time around. But the second time is much worse..[Spoiler Alert] </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-23 23:18:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So the first time you watch interstellar(this is all going off how I reacted to it) we got a bit of the feels when he was leaving but then truly sobbed when he got his messages after coming off the water planet. Then you have the Matt Damon, docking scene which was still as intense as hell and you still get the feeling from the soundtrack. Thats another thing! the first time watching it I was focused incredibly on the dialogue and story but this time I noticed the background music playing in scenes. For example towards the end when he's trying to send a sign and the present version of Murph opens the book to see "stay" and they make the music that bit more noticeable, its incredible. As for the scene's with the ghost, specifically when she reads out stay to him as a child, after seeing the movie I know it was him and that was truly gut wrenching. Knowing he is trying to tell himself to stay, it's horrifying. I am of course leaving out some thoughts but please, if you are wondering about watching it again, do it and focus more on the little things, the soundtrack, the foreshadowing, it's just truly a superb movie no matter the opinion of reddit, this will be my second favorite movie of all time. (it would take a true, true piece of work to take that title). So those are my thoughts after re-watching it. I'd love to hear what you think if you've seen it more than once.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Am I really about to have to pause and resume this download the entire way? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-23 20:37:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So I'm installing the game and its the uber massive 28 gb file to start but every few minutes or seconds lately it hits peak and then declines until at zero. Do i really have to hit pause and resume it every time that happens? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> It's a long, long reach but could I run h1z1 all on low? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-23 11:03:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Elder Scrolls Online - The Three Fates Cinematic Trailer Supercut ..... Are the comments right about what they say? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-23 00:10:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> I complained yesterday about having to buy it but... Damn you Blizzard! </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-22 14:12:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Can I run HoTS?(This is a link to my laptop specs) </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-22 02:33:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Riot Games: PrimeTime League of Legends (twitch link) </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-22 00:19:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> I have been applied to play this game's beta about a year now and I log on to see this shit. I have been waiting a fucking year and they're just gonna throw it out expecting me to pay FOR A BETA! no. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-21 11:29:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [No spoilers] The new ThreeEyedRaven vids are out.. but my link isn't working? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-21 00:55:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If yours loads up can you tell me? I'd kike to know it's its just me or all around </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What is the most realistic movie about college to date? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-20 17:44:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Can someone explain Birdman to me? [Spoilers] </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-19 21:06:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So I just watched it and... I really enjoyed it but I'm confused as all hell. It started off with me thinking he just had an alter ego type deal, mental illness or whatever. Then he finds himself flying through New York(which is cleared up when you realize he got a cab) and that made me think more mental illness. Then when you got to see all the street performers on stage, spiderman and the transformers etc I started to think if they're talking about the mental issues celebrities can get by being who they are, always reaching to be something after being on the top or how they live a different life to the rest of us and it's not all happiness. Then at the end he shot his nose off after some kind of epiphany? He then went ahead and climbed out his window and I thought his time he did actually jump but then Emma Stone's character looked up and began to laugh, which basically told us he could fly(?) Oh and to add in that entire scene before he flew across the city, he started flying, deflecting bullets, rockets flying everywhere, swat guys. I truly did love the movie and it made it seem it was all one big take(day after day of course) but when the did a scene it seemed to run flawlessly for minutes on end and the camera work was incredible but... Can someone please help me understand this? Of course everything I wrote may be wrong but I wouldn't have a problem with that. I'm just confused.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Being Irish and saying I want McGregor to lose tonight feels illegal.. Fuck the law I guess? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-19 02:03:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Are there any HD streams of tonights event? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-18 23:49:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [No spoilers] How far into ASOIAF would I have to read by April to be caught up to the show? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-18 23:27:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Have they announced how far into the series this season will go? I understand you can't just pick up the books in the middle of it so I'm starting at AGOT but for me to finish the entire series I'd have to do 50 pages a day every day until April 12th and with my schedule i just cant so basically. Would I have to the end of Part 1 of A storm of swords or A feast of crows? Forgive my awful knowledge of where the books start and stop I'm only now reading them, </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Can someone sum up or link to me something that sums up the first Witcher game as I install Witcher 2? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-18 22:00:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> People of Reddit with strong willpower... How do you do it? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-18 02:04:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> "I find I need less sleep as I grow older, and I am grown very old. I often spend my nights with ghosts, remembering times fifty years ast as if they were yesterday".. This truly scares the hell out of me. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-18 01:54:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'd like to add I'm reading A song of ice and fire for the first time and this is a quote by Maester Aemon in A Game of Thrones. Page 434 for anyone who wants to read it in context.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Man dies after playing online games for THREE days straight... Um... I don't know how I feel about this. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-17 20:02:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [No spoilers] Are there any collectors editions or just plain beautiful hardback versions of ASOIAF or a great collection to own? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-16 16:52:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So I have the first book and I've began to read after 4 years of saying I will but I'm a big, big fan of collecting and owning the upgraded version(so to speak) of the normal books. So right now I have the paperback version of a game of thrones with just the plain sand colour and dragon on the front. What other versions can I buy? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Are there any Irish soldiers here I could talk to or question? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-16 01:16:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
