<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject2331</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-04 04:20:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Can't deny her foreign policy is good :P </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-04 04:19:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If we have mandatory service, everyone is a veteran and technically everyone earned our free stuff :D </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-04 04:17:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Dude zoomed in right on her eyes lol </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-04 04:16:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That was actually pretty good lol </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-04 04:15:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah that was my thought. No answer lol </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-04 04:13:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> LOL THAT CAMERA ZOOM </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-04 04:12:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Can't wait to hear this :P </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-04 04:10:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> UHC is for every person to be covered. Don't think she's against that. She's against single payer. She's also in bed with insurance companies  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-04 04:08:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> These aren't good ideas on paper. THERE IS PROOF ALL OVER. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-04 04:07:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Lmfao xD </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-04 04:05:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm more than happy for a woman president, just not this woman. She's not right for the jib </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-04 04:04:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hilary vs Hilary  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-04 04:03:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> But but but.... Okay :( </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-04 04:01:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I wouldn't wanna hold his hand either lol...

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-04 04:01:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Lol  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-04 04:01:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That blazer makes her look fat  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-04 03:56:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Shit tends to get awkward when your husband infidelity is publicil </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-04 03:54:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Jesus how old is Jane? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-04 03:53:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Lol a Chevy  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-04 03:52:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Lol that makes sense  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-04 03:52:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Holy fuck, climate change from the Chinese? What the ever loving shit balls </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-04 03:48:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hahahah  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-04 03:47:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Makes sense. I felt like it was way to quiet  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-04 03:47:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Lol :P </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-04 03:44:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Oh no heroin.. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-04 03:42:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Is it normal for such a small amount of people? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-04 03:41:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That is a nice chair though  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-04 03:39:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Kill her with kindness :P </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-04 03:39:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> *claps* </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-04 03:28:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> As a veteran... I have tingles. Thank you Bernie  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-04 03:25:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> http://freeintertv.com/view/id-200 CNN stream  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-04 03:22:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> freeintertv.com/view/id-200  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-04 03:19:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's amazing how he speaks right to my heart :) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-04 03:19:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Fucking right!  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-04 03:19:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Me too :( </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> 5 Conservative Talking Points..Feel the Bern! </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-04 02:50:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-04 02:14:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Let's donate ramen! We can all afford that! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> 5 Conservative Myths about Bernie Sanders </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-04 02:13:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-04 01:54:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That's okay xD </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-04 01:51:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Let's do this Bernie! Every time Hillary says something stupid, donate to Bernie! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-03 21:21:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Lol, "slippery slope" is a term I've been hearing a lot lately lol... For every single thing going on lol </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-03 14:46:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I've listened to many perspectives on this and they're all pretty similar. Personally, I can't speak to "innocent" civilians. Yes, there are some situations where there is collateral damage. Someone might get taken out. And yes there are "guilty by association". 

What needs to be realized is that even if we used just HUMINT sources, we could still end up with unnecessary casualties. The way I see it, and maybe I'm bias because this is my job, is that because of this program, manned assets don't have to fly in hostile areas. We can actually get good ISR data before sending dudes in there.  Getting a "drone" out there is significantly cheaper, safer, and productive. 

I hate that there is unnecessary death, but it is a product of evil and war. I think of the lives we do save by utilizing this program.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-03 14:38:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Well, I mean, *technically* he does use the word free a lot... But I see it as a sound investment so SHUT UP AND TAKE MY MONEY </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-03 13:58:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So I gotta ask, why don't you agree with the drone program? 

*someone who may or may not work in such a field* </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-03 13:51:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Are you calling us a bunch of fags? 

I'm kidding.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-03 11:11:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I honestly don't know. I've only recently starting getting into the foreign policy. I think where the problems might fall is that Saudi is basically funding the fuckers (maybe I'm making that up). But Saudi has the 3rd largest military budget :P I know that lol </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-03 06:26:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Not just *A* tie, but SIX. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-03 05:40:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That's why I can't see her as a reliable candidate. She lies. And lies. And denies.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-03 05:11:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Not a fan of Hilldog, but if she admitted to changing her mind, I wouldn't look at her with such disdain lol </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-03 05:10:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> From the little bit I was able to read, I saw $0.50 per $100. That's not that bad lol that's a gum ball machine right there </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-03 05:02:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Great job! Question though! What is debt-free college vs tuition free? 

Personal view: if debt free college is what I think it is, (i.e affordable) i think that would sit better with people over FREE college. Honestly, when that gets brought up in discussions, that's a huge complaint. 

I understand where the money will be coming from and it doesn't bother ME, but I find people getting upset because they see it as being taxed/punished for being wealthy.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-03 04:52:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Well, by imposing the tax on pollution, he's essentially discouraging it lol. You pollute? You pay! Youre green? Tax break! (Not sure on that last bit lol) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-03 04:48:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Isis for example. He believes all the countries that we have supported in the past ( Saudi, Turkey, Kuwait) need to take the lead on Isis. They will still have our full support, but our soldiers won't be the first out. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-03 04:46:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> A few days ago, I did this. I was about halfway through before I realized that you could choose more than yes or no. Some of my answers weren't what I really thought because I didn't notice that. I was on mobile so I was a bit too lazy to do it again. 

As my results were generating, i jokingly said " I swear if it's Hillary, I'm gonna kill myself. Sure enough, 90% Hillary, 85% Bernie. I then pretended to hang myself with my headphones lol. (Woman of my word) 

Anyway, that was an excellent tool. It gave me a chance to ask my coworkers what they thought as well... They're all a bunch of nuts, so naturally we disagreed on just about everything lol </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-03 04:40:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I find that perfectly acceptable. If someone were to say " I know I said this before, but based on societal changes and research, I feel this way now" 

If someone says they feel one way, and then changes their stance, and denies ever having felt another way, that, is not acceptable. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-02 16:21:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> And her name is Clorox!  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-02 16:12:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> When I first moved into my new house, I invited my neighbors across the street over for a bbq. They were around mine and my husbands age, so we figured why not. 

I told them 2 weeks in advance, and asked if they were coming 3 days prior. Both answers were yes. Day of I was walking the dog and spotted dude outside. Asked him if he was coming, and he was like "yeah, yeah! Well be there later!" 

Eventually it was like, 430pm and we hadn't seen them, so I popped back over there for this clown to tell me his wife made other plans.

I feel like they didn't want to go in the first place, which is 100% fine, but no is a better answer than dancing around the subject. I was more pissed that we had waited so long for an answer. That by the time we got the ribs on the grill, it was dark as fuck.

If someone is offering to spend money and feed you and your family, don't fucking change your mind at the last second. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-02 07:24:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Either way we won. People have finally seen Bernie. People have finally seen the support behind him. Goodnight guys, we did it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Can you guys help me explain why I support Bernie? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-01 11:29:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> My experience with the patches </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-27 10:01:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hey guys! I just wanted to share my experience with nicotine patches!

For starters, I'm not even counting the days, because I feel like it will impede my process a little bit. I started with the 21mg patch probably a week ago. I think I'm about halfway through my first box. 

When I first put it on, that first day, I allowed myself to smoke whenever I wanted. I smoked 3. I was like, okay, tomorrow I'm going to smoke one less. So, the next day I smoked 2, next day 1, and then down to none.

After I got to not smoking at all, I would put the patch on as soon as I finished breakfast, which was my normal first cigarette of the day. After 2 days of doing that, I started trying to put the patch on  later and later each day, so I would be getting less nicotine throughout the day. Also, I take the patch off at night, since I don't usually get in during sleep time anyway. (the first couple of nights I left it on and it caused me to constantly wake up through the night).

Like I said, I'm not exactly sure what day I'm on at this point, but when I put a patch on now, I actually get a slight nicotine buzz. I know that I'm supposed to stay on the 21 mg for like, 6 weeks, but I feel that because I'm doing so well with them now, I would skip straight to the 14mg, doing the same thing I am now, and then eventually to the 7mg, down to none.

I really feel like this is going to work. My husband is also working on quitting. (I'm deployed right now, so he's doing his own thing at this point). I'm actually trying to convince my dad to try quitting as well! 

If anyone has an input on my plan, or can share their own stories, that'll be awesome!! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Why am I sleeping so much? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-12 17:48:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hey guys!

I have been deployed for about 2 1/2 weeks now. Since then, whenever I got to take a "nap" for around 30-45 minutes, I sleep for HOURS.  For example, toady, around 4pm I set an alarm for 4:45 and didn't wake up until 7:00pm. I know it doesn't seem like much, but I go to bed around 8:30 or 930 and wake up at 430 am. I struggle to wake up. Whenever I finally get out of bed I'm fine. We'll go to breakfast and then go to work. 

By the time I get to work,  it takes about 20 minutes for me to be completely exhausted again. Sometimes I'm able to sneak in a nap, and i feel pretty good for a few hours, but by the time I get back to my room, around 1 or 2 pm, I'm completely exhausted again!

I've been making slight changes to my diet and lifestyle, but I don't feel like any of them are drastic enough for this much sleeping. I have begun working out, but not too hard I don't think. A little sore the next day, but nothing like what I've felt before.

Food wise, breakfast is almost always the same, an omelet with hash browns, side of fruit. I don't often get to eat lunch and lately I've been sleeping through dinner and my workout! But when I do eat, I try to keep it small and simple, salad with chicken side of veggies. The chow hall here is kinda crappy, so that's basically all I can eat.

I've also started the attempt to quit smoking. I'm wearing the patch. However, I feel this is irrelevant since my sleeping was an issue before.

Just wanted to get some input guys!

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Getting in to MMA? (22F) </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-11-17 14:21:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hey guys!

After watching a few MMA fights, I have to say, I'm really interested in AT LEAST learning how to fight. It looks like an incredible work out, and it gives me a chance to learn how to whoop some ass, should I need it.

I would very much like to start MMA-style training. I'm about to deploy for 3 months, so I'll have access to a great gym. However, I probably won't have access to any martial arts classes.

What are the best workouts to condition myself to get into kickboxing? I'm currently 5'5 and about 190lbs, so I'm overweight to say the least. (I don't look it, thank goodness)

In the midst of this conditioning, I'm also wanting to cut about 30 or so pounds. I'm already aware of dieting, and I'll be able to stick to it on deployment since chicken and vegetables is probably the only safe thing lol

I appreciate any input! Don't hate on me for being a fatty ;_; </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Kitty Kisses! </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-11-07 17:29:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Honey is a Nibbler! </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-11-01 21:18:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Dingo's Got My Baby (2014) - How a mother's panic turned her into a joke </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-10-29 12:42:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Pay off debts or save it? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-10-15 18:35:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hey PF!

I recently withdrew my Roth TSP that I had through the military. I separated, so I am no longer able to add to it. I have an IRA through my job now, so I still have something.

The withdrawal handed me about $2300. I know that doesn't seem like much, but I feel like it is in my situation. I understand that early withdrawal gets you taxed ~20%...I'm assuming that gets applied at the end of the year, since I got the full amount deposited into my account.

I'm curious if I should put this into savings or pay off my debt. Here's a break down of my debts:

Car Payment: $109.43 per month 3.1% int. debt total:$ 3651.02

Capitol One Quicksilver: Balance:$1650.90 0% int until Dec. After that, 22% APR

Sears Credit Card: Balance: $1215.38 0% int. until April 2016 ( no idea what it will be after that)

I also have a mortgage, but first payment isn't due until December.

I make ~$1600 every 2 weeks (~$3200 per month). You should also know that I will be deploying with my company in the next month or so. From what I have been told, my pay will basically double each month. So, realistically, my debts will be paid off in the next few months no matter what.

Any advice for me PF? thanks in advance :D  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Balance Transfer on Credit Card </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-10-12 19:52:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Balance Transfer on Credit Card </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-10-12 16:31:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hey PF!

I currently have a Capitol One Quicksilver credit card that offers 1% cash back on every purchase. 22% APR (can someone explain APR? is that broken up throughout the year?) I initially signed up for it back in April and have no interest until December. The current balance is $1,377.39 credit limit is $5000. My balance is about to increase by approximately $300 for company travel. (they reimburse me,but it takes about a month or so to get it back)

Since December is fast approaching, I was talking to a coworker about it and he suggested I find a credit card that has a no-interest-introductory period, the perks I want, along with a balance transfer. Does anyone know of any credit cards like this? I like the cash back perks because I get advances from my company and I can reap some free money.

I have an alright credit score. 689 I think. (I also have a Sears credit card (no interest) with a balance) My score WAS 727 back in April, but I got the credit card for a move across the country, acquired a balance, got a ton of credit checks for my rental home and utilities. It took quite the hit, lol.

I also just purchased a house this past Friday (woot woot!) so my score might have changed again.

Just trying to figure out what I should do. Thanks in advance :) 
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Do we live in the 1950s or something? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-10-04 20:40:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I get a whole bunch of shit about the fact my husband doesn't work. I make enough money for us to live comfortably. I constantly hear the term "suga-momma". My husband does his part in other ways. He takes care of the house. He wakes up with me every morning at 3am to make my coffee and pack my lunch. If it were the other way around, it would be looked at as normal for me to stay at home. 

To be clear, my husband is going to start job hunting once we save up enough to get another car. We live 30-45 minutes away from everything, so sharing a car is just too many ch of a hassle at this point. I know all I have to do is tell people to shut up and mind their own, but damn. Do we really live in a society where it's not okay for the man to stay at home? 

Okay rant over.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Can anyone make a Petpage layout for me? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-10-01 17:20:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hi guys!

I was just wondering if some kind redditor would make a layout for me? Its for a petpage I am hosting for my guild. The last layout I had was made by a guildie and it was great. I somehow totally fucked up the coding. I tried to venture out on my own, but it just didn't work T_T;;

I feel like what I want is relatively simple, I'm just too dumb to figure it out XD Anyway, if anyone is willing to do this for me, lemme know and I'll give you my specifications :) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What's the good word with Menstrual Cups? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-09-21 18:52:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hi, TwoX~

I've heard about menstrual cups the past few years. DivaCup,MoonCup, etc. I would be interested in trying one, but I don't know much about it!

I know you just pop it in and forget it, depending on your flow, then just rinse it out when it's full. Well, what if I'm in a public restroom without a private sink? How would I rinse it out? I feel like that would gross people out if I just did it out in the open like that, lol.

Anyway, you guys got any insight for me? Best brand? Do you pee with it in, like a tampon? Can it like...fall out? How is it with leakage? I already wear a pad with a tampon anyway, so I'm fine with wearing a pad. Just trying to educated guys :3 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Starting a VA Claim </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-09-21 17:37:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hi guys! Thanks for your service!

Anywho, I separated about a year ago (Sept 29, 2014). In March of '14, while I was deployed, I started having issues with my left wrist, namely while doing pushups.(Felt like my wrist was going to give out under me, pains shooting up my arm). I couldn't even prop my head up on my left hand for long because it would start to hurt.

I went to the on-site flight doctor there, and they took an X-Ray, but said they couldn't see a problem and chocked it up to being carpal tunnel...doesn't make sense since I hardly ever use my left wrist...They gave my a wrist brace and some Naproxen.

When I got  back to the states, I went to the doctor and he did some movement assessments and said he didn't see any issues. Gave me Mobic and that was that. When I was beginning my separation process in June of '14, my supervisor suggested I file a claim (for anything, and everything). Personally, that didn't feel right to me, since I was technically fine, so I never filed.

Now, all of a sudden, I'm having flare-ups in my wrist. Usually it would only hurt if I put pressure on it, but lately just moving it, it kinda hurts.

What I want to know, is if I should go to my normal provider, bring it up with them, get X-rays, and whatever they suggest, and then start things with the VA? I want to make this as painless as possible (literally and figuratively). </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> VA loan question </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-09-12 18:27:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> When the VA comes out to do their inspection on my house, is that technically the same as hiring a home inspector? My agent recommended I get an inspector out ( she doesn't know a whole lot about the VA process yet) is 275$ a good price for someone to come out? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Find a Real Estate Agent </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-09-08 19:44:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hi there! posted this in /r/personalfinance and was told to come here!

I'm trying to find a real estate agent to help me appraise my house. I have NO idea how to go about finding an agent.

My landlord WANTS 185k for the house (his agent already told him that's not gonna happen. He thinks it's worth 154k) He showed us houses in the area, and that number doesn't quite sit with me. All the houses are going in the 130's range and are larger than mine, with more usable land.

I'm using my VA loan, so I know it will get appraised by them, but I want to have a 3rd number to go off of. I know I need an agent as well, who is going to fight for me. What is the BEST way to judge someone when searching? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Finding a Real Estate agent </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-09-08 19:05:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Possibility of buying my house...should I? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-09-04 21:54:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I got a phone call a few minutes ago from my landlord's real estate rep. He said that my LL is interested in selling the house.

 I met him last week after he came out to assess the house. I mentioned to him that I would be interested in buying this house, should it become available. 

From my research, my LL bought the house at 55k and it's worth 120kish. ( this is from zillow). I currently pay $1000 a month for rent. It's a 3 bed,  2 bath, big backyard and front yard. I will say it's not in the best area, but that doesn't concern hubby and I too much. If we buy and get a 15year loan, that would put our payments around $800 a month, right?

I am a veteran, so I am eligible for the VA loan.  I know with the VA loan that you do not have to put a down payment, but you pay closing costs. Can you bundle the closing costs with the actual loan?

I currently make $3200 a month. I have a Sears credit card with $1800 balance ( no interest right now) $1000 balance on my Capitol one ( no interest until Dec.) I owe $3800 on my car. Right now our saving is... Nonexistent. (We moved across the country less than 6 months ago, slowly recovering lol)
 
On top of that, I deploy for my job, which significantly increases my income while I'm there's. I will be deploying around mid-October and returning late February- early March. So I know my debt will be going up, but I can pay it off relatively fast.

If we don't buy, we have to move again and will still have no money and no house to call our own.

My questions are: is this something we should pursue?  

Edit: I want to include that the house was built in 1988 and is very structurally sound. We've not had an issues since we've lived here </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Bras, bras, bras! </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-09-04 01:32:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hey guys!

I'm in the market for some new bras. Victoria secret measures me as 38DDD and they fit comfortably. Buuuut they're upwards of $50. So I usually only buy one and wear that one until it tears.

Any of you lady have any coupon codes or store suggestions? I also need a sports bra, but VS doesn't carry my size in store, so I would have it order online and pay even more for shipping. Input appreciated :) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Indoor/outdoor cat </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-09-04 00:41:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So my cat, Mr. Chubbs, LOVES being outside. He is about a year old and has always been an indoor cat, minus our supervised outdoor adventures.

I want to do whatever I can to keep him happy, but he never seems content after a trip outside. I would love it if I could leave him outside unattended, but I'm terrified of him getting hurt. We live in California, so everything is desert.

Is there any safe way to transition my dear Chubbs to being indoor and outdoor? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Should I come back?? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-09-03 17:59:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hey guys! 

I've been a Mapler for like...10 years? Off and on of course. Last time I played was a little over a year ago. Should I come back? I'm looking for something to fill the time. I've got an MSI Apache gaming laptop, however I've always struggled using a laptop keyboard. I could of course, use and external keyboard, but then I'll have too much shit everywhere.

If I do come back, does anyone have any tips for using a laptop key board? Also, what have I missed? What should I be on the lookout for? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Pet hair solutions? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-08-30 04:36:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hi there!

I have a black lab/hound mix and a cat. Their hair is EVERYWHERE. I eat so much pet hair, I'm surprised I'm not shittin out hair balls!

I have all tile floors and one big throw rug in the living room. Aside from having to sweep every single day, what do you guys recommend? I brush my dog every other day and whenever the cat sits still long enough. 

I've considered getting a room a, but I'm afraid of spending 300$ on something that might break or get clogged from all the hair. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Diflucan..x2? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-08-29 20:51:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hey ladies!

I posted earlier this week about a raging yeast infection caused by my antibiotics. I went to the doctor, got a prescription for diflucan, took it after dinner, and waited. This was Monday btw. 

It's Saturday now and my yeast infection doesn't seem to have gone away. I have the occasional itch, but nothing bad. I do, however, have the funky cottage cheese discharge. ( not terribly though) 

Should I got back to the doctor in Monday and get a refill? Anyone else had to get a second dose to kill the evil? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Weekend visitors </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-08-29 20:30:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Every Saturday, without fail, the Jehovah's Witnesses, or Mormons or whatever they are, ring my doorbell. 

Would a "no trespassing" sign deter them? Should I just ask them to stop coming? I'm not sure if it would work, since there are a few different groups that come by. 

It's not really that big of a deal, I just don't wanna hear about the " next big Jesus event that everyone's invited to".  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> EJuice making my throat close up?!? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-08-29 00:26:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So, I'm trying to switch to vaping and for some reason, my throat starts to close. I have tried the juice with propylene(sp?) glycol and straight vegetable glycerin. I've tried the store bought and the homemade stuff my husband makes.


The only common denominator at this point is the nicotine, but I'm fine with smoking cigarettes.  I've tried adjusting the watts and all the other doodads on my build, but I always end up with a closed throat. It also makes me have a productive cough for a few minutes after a hit. I'm trying to cut down on cigarettes and eventually quit. 

I forgot to add that I tried vaping about 2 years ago and I didn't have any reactions.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Antibiotic Rant(TMI) </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-08-24 15:20:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I currently hate my vagina/reproductive system. I recently had a root canal and was given antibiotics to fend off infection. 

My tooth isn't infected, so that's good. My vagina on the other hand fucking hurts. I have a raging yeast infection. I've done my best to not touch it, but christ almighty it itches, inside and out. I knew when I finished my week-long dosage of Doxycycline that this could happen, but this might be the worst YI I've ever had. Symptoms started showing Friday afternoon-ish. I've taken 5 baking soda baths and drank some nasty ass apple cider vinegar. 

As great as antibiotics are because they can wreck the evil inside, sometimes it feels like they're doing more harm than good. It even renders my birth control useless-ish? Oddly enough, while I was actively taking the AB, my vagina was feeling awesome. I didn't have my normal lady odor and that was great lol. But as soon as I stopped taking 'em, it feels like death.

Okay, I'm done ranting. I do plan on calling my doctor today to try and get an appointment because this shit HURTS!! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Ghoul Catchers </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-08-17 21:49:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So, I have come to the conclusion that Ghoul Catchers is a perpetually broken game, unless you have an iPhone. I've tried on my laptop, 2 Android phones, Kindle Fire, and Samsung Galaxy tablet. I try to log in and I get the "Username and Password do not match" message. They do match. ...am I dumb? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Good/cheap Vets? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-08-04 19:14:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hey guys! Just moved to Lake LA back in April (no, I don't do/sell meth lol). Looking for a reliable vet for my fur babies! Anyone got any suggestions? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> I got a REALLY big pickle </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-08-02 02:21:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> We want to get out of the house, so we go to someone else's house </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-27 21:43:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Issues with Mom </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-19 02:00:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hey TwoX! This is gonna be long, so prepare yourself lol

Just wanted to come here to get a little advice as to what I should do about the relationship with my mother. Don't get me wrong, we get along just fine, but I feel like my mom is the most self-centered and selfish person.

I lived with my dad and grandma for most of my life. When I turned 13 I lived with my mom until I moved out at 18 and joined the military. I've always been able to tell my mom everything and anything. However, during the majority of my teen years, my mom was married to a total crackhead. He was a nice enough person, but obviously the drugs caused all kinds of problems.

I was never allowed to be alone with my mom because he got jealous and worried that we were talking shit about him. Which, to be fair we were, but we had every reason to. He was verbally abusive to both of us and put a huge strain on our relationship. A couple of years ago, she finally divorced him. Yay, go mom. All that aside, I really think her marriage set the tone for the entire basis of OUR relationship.

I can pretty much gather from my sisters that my mom has always been kind of selfish, but I really feel like it's reached an all time high. From 2011-2014, I lived on the otherside of the country. She never once offered to visit me. I always had to go see her. I moved back to the East Coast in September of 2014 with my husband. ( I got out of the military) We lived with my in-laws until April. My mom lived 45 minutes away and didn't work. She didn't once come to see me. I always had to go see her. I always did because I didn't want to cause problems where they weren't necessary.

Adding into the whole "45 minutes away thing", I got married in May of 2014 while I was on leave. Our wedding was really last minute. WE wanted to get married at the pond where we had our first date. My mom basically said she wouldn't come because she would have to drive 45 minutes. So we had our wedding closer to her house. To be fair, my wedding turned out great, but the point is she tried to make it all about her. My husband's family had to drive 45 minutes. To add even more insult to injury, my in-laws invited her and her new husband over to their house SEVERAL times, and she made up and excuse not to come EVERY time.

Currently, I live in California, so I'm across the country again for my new job. My mom and her husband flew into Vegas today. My mom keeps going on and on about me going to see her. She's about 3 hours away. I want her to come see ME. I want her to see where I live. She got all upset that I couldn't take a day off to come see her, but I took off 2 days when my husband's parents were here earlier in the week. They flew out here SPECIFICALLY to see us. Why would I not take time off?

My biggest question here is, WHAT DO I DO? How do I tell my mom that I'm not coming to see her because she's never put forth the effort to see me? Should I just cut ties with my mom, in the sense of visiting? Maybe I'm just ranting, but I'm really at a breaking point, and so is my husband. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> This is Honey. She may or may not be human. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-18 01:56:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> My son looks like Justin Beiber. Setting the house on fire, brb. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-18 01:19:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> For those going to Cannon AFB </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-16 16:40:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I've seen a few posts of people going to Cannon, and asking what there is to do. I've decided to compile a list of what I recommend. I left Cannon in September of 2014, so if anything has popped up since then, I probably don't know about it.

If you like to drink, you'll like CAFB. If you like cheap drinks, go to the Drop Zone. Even better if you live in the dorms, just stumble your ass home. If you don't like to drink/underage, and you have a car, sign up to do AADD. Something to do, and drunk people are hilarious.

Ned Houk Park is on the outskirts and it's really nice. Good hiking trails, good for biking. AND THERE'S GRASS!! I've only been there once, and I enjoyed it, as did my dog.

I'm pretty sure the base has a dog park now, so take the pup for a trip. The Chapel and Outdoor Rec offer a lot of trips like snowboarding, couple's retreats, and nice events for single airmen. Most take you to Taos, Ruidoso, Albuquerque...I never took any trips through them. Even if you decide to venture off on your own. Outdoor Rec will rent you equipment for cheap. 

If you live in the dorms, dorm management throws a BBQ every once in a while... and they have free beer!

I was on a Roller Derby Team while I was there. (Not sure if they're still up and running, but if anyone is interested in this, I can contact someone). This is good for the guys and the gals! They always need referees and non-skating officials. Even if the Clovis team isn't around anymore, Amarillo and Lubbock also have teams.

I haven't explored Amarillo much, but I heard the shopping is good. (Hour and a half away)

Lubbock was a place my friends and I frequented often (Hour and a half away). There's a couple of clubs out there ( I recommend HEAVEN, it's a gay club, but it was tons of fun) They have a decent mall and some good restraunts. For those of you who don't know any better, don't eat off shore seafood. Lubbock also has an airport. Tickets are a little bit more expensive than Albuquerque, but it's easier to find someone willing to drive you to LBB than it is ABQ.

Speaking of Albuquerque (3.5- 4 hours away). I've been there approximately 6 times. Each time was to take someone to the airport/pick them up. My husband and I drove through there on the way to California, and I have to say, it's beautiful.  I'm sure there are great places to hike. There's a few casinos, and a Hard Rock Cafe. 

I'm not sure if the base theatre is still running, but definitely do that. Super cheap for a movie. That place is good for more than just an all-call.  /u/FerTheDiddly said that it is free entry and they sell beer.

Another thing, if you like to bang chicks..wear a condom. Cannon is a fucking cess-pool. Everybody is having sex with each other and most people there have had an STD at least once. Especially the dorm rats.

Check out Hillcrest Park. It's dinky, but it's green. EDIT: They have a zoo. Second biggest in the state. And it's a good place for your dog to run. Thanks /u/FerTheDiddly

I think there is a place called Yute Lake where you can camp and fish. Pretty sure you can rent a boat from Outdoor Rec as well.

One of the surrounding towns is Portales. I know they have a brewery. I never really went out there because I was too lazy to explore. Nice houses out there too.

Add in from Comments: Buy a gun and take up some shooting. I believe they just opened an indoor range right off base. There's also Patriot Outdoors. Thanks /u/TheCorvus303

Add in from Comments: Sign up for OPFOR. You got out on the range (Melrose) and help train the SOF dudes. One of my friends got to do this and he said he had a blast. Thanks /u/FerTheDiddly

This is about all I can come up with now, but I will add more as I think of it. If you have any questions, feel free to ask! I was there for 2 1/2 years and managed to survive.

Edit: Welcome to Af-Can-istan. Clovi-Dishu. Make the most of it. Make friends. 

Men: You're going to have to find your women elsewhere... unless you go after a military chick, the women in Clovis are sketchy.

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Anyone hear about a drowning today? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-15 04:39:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> My family and I were visiting San Diego today and stopped by the beach. I believe it was La Jolla (whatever one is a stone's throw from the Birch Aquarium). We saw a man get pulled out of the water. I believe he was a scuba diver. He was wearing a wetsuit, so he could have been surfing. They were administering CPR until EMTs got there. 

We didn't stick around long enough to see if he survived. Does anyone have any info? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> ELI5: Why don't they kill prisoners in a less toxic way in order to leave their organs viable, thus saving lives? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-05 06:31:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Create a World help SIMS 3 </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-02 20:42:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hi Guys!

I'm just about to pick up playing The Sims 3 again. One thing I have never been able to figure out, in all of my Sim years, is how to use the create a world tool. There's a certain organization I would like for my towns just isn't there in the prebuilt and downloadables. 

If anyone could direct me to a decent guide, it would by much appreciated :) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Lost birth control pack :O </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-06 04:02:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Moving with cat and dog </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-08 01:52:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> My husband and I will be moving from Florida to California in a few weeks.

I am here to ask about the best way to move our pets. We have a cat and a dog. We will be getting a U-Haul with a trailer to tow our car (full tow).
 My plan is to the animals in the towed car, put a plastic sheet on my back seats for the dog (she gets car sick), and to place my cat in the front seat in a carrier. Is it safe to have my animals in the car, vs the U-Haul? Is it legal? Am I allowed to think about our comfort in this situation. 

We will be stopping every 3-4 hours for fuel, so we can let the dog out to potty, and put the cat's litter box in the car. I don't want my cat roaming the car while we aren't in it, since he has claws and likes to claw everything, lol..

Please let me know whether or not this is a good plan. If it is not, please provide me with some alternatives. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Looking for people to play with </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-07 20:18:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hi, guys!

Yesterday, I started playing ToonTown Rewritten. I started playing TTO when I was 13, so about 9 years ago (with long-winded breaks of course).

Right now, I'm looking for people who would be willing to play TTR with me. When I say that, I mean helping each other with tasks and such. Everytime I ask someone in game, they say "yeah, sure." Then disappear. 

Let me know if you're interested! Leave a comment and we can arrange a meeting place!
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Received job offer and accepted, HR won't respond. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-02 22:14:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I posted something similar a few weeks ago, but now the situation is a little different.

I interviewed with my company on March 3rd. I was also given an offer and I accepted. They did not give me a start date because they still needed to complete the background check.

I was prior military, so I think it shouldn't take that long. I joined at 18 and got out at 21. Also, I have a security clearance. 

Anywho, I heard from the company who is responsible for background checks, a few days after my acceptance. I sent them the paper work they needed and haven't heard about it since.

I have emailed HR with questions about a start date and for an explanation of my moving benefits. This was 2 weeks ago. I didn't hear from her for a week, so I emailed the recruiter who I have never had an issue getting in contact with. 

I emailed her last Wednesday, and she responded almost immediately. She told me she would forward my email to the HR lady and I would hear from her by close of business on Thursday. Never heard anything. Their offices are closed every other Friday, so didn't hear anything then either.

I waited it out on Monday, to give her a chance to get to my email. Didn't hear anything. I emailed her again on Tuesday and still haven't heard anything.

I'm not trying to hound them, but I can't wait much longer. This job will require me to move from my home in Florida to California. I'm afraid this is going to turn into a "you-have-two-weeks-to-get-here" kinda thing.

My question is, should I try to email HR again? Should I email the reliable recruiter again, and let her know I never heard from HR? Should I just suck it up and wait?

Update: I emailed the recruiter again because I'm impatient. 5She  minutes later, HR lady called me. I apologized off the bat for bombarding them with emails and she said that realistically, that's the best way to get anything done. I now have a start date  of April 27 and information on my moving benefits (they pay for everything and give me temporary housing, fuck yeah) But really, I only have 2 weeks to move, lol. At least in my head. I would like to get out there prior to the start date to ensure I can actually go look at houses and such. Thanks for the input guys ;D </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Moving and towing a trailer with 2010 Honda Civic </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-26 02:16:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> My husband and I will be moving from Florida to California pretty soon. 

Our original plan was to rent a 10ft Uhual and tow our car. Due to our finances, we are looking into towing a 4 X 8 trailer with our 2010 Honda Civic (4 door 2wd). 

Based on what I saw on the Uhual website, as long as we have a tow hitch rated for 2000lbs, we'll be able to town a maximum of 1,150 lbs.

My question is, how bad will this hurt my car? Is it worth the wear and tear? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Offered employment with no start date and have to move across the country (Advice) </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-20 00:52:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I posted this in r/jobs, but I figured I could get more help here. 

On March 3rd, I interviewed with my company and received and signed an offer letter immediately after. I knew going in that they wanted me because of my experience.

I believe my background check started on March 5th. I was in the military for 3 years, and this is my first job, besides that. I've been unemployed since September and I'm getting worried because the money is running out.

I currently live in Florida, and will have to relocate to California. Because I have no start date, I can't really get any quotes on moving trucks (price changes based on dates), I haven't really TRIED to lock down a home rental, because I'm afraid of getting my heart set on a particular home and then being beat out by someone else.

I will be making relatively good money, and receiving a lump sum for moving expenses in my first paycheck. At this point in time, my husband and I have enough money to pay for a truck (based on a quote we got for a specific date) pay deposits on a home (at the lowest end of our price range), electric, etc, if we pick up and move right now. But obviously, that's not a good idea without ACTUALLY being employed. The longer I have to wait for a start date, the less money we are going to have. We live with my in laws, so we don't have any bills outside of our car/insurance/cell phones... aside from a few medical bills.

The point of this post is to ask what I should do. We are planning on getting a loan, but we don't know how much is appropriate. But, I spoke to my sister in law, who is a loan officer, and she basically said that my offer letter means nothing to banks, that until I have a start date that won't give me anything. She also said that my best option, if I get denied a personal loan, would be to refinance my car. ( I have no idea what this means)

 In California, it is not required for a landlord to give you a fridge, but my inlaws are giving us a mini fridge, so that's not really a problem. We will need a washer and dryer (washer first and foremost, I'll hang my shit outside, lol).

If anyone has any advice please comment away! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Offered employment with no start date and have to move across the country (HELP) </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-19 23:19:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> On March 3rd, I interviewed with my company and received and signed an offer letter immediately after. I knew going in that they  wanted me because of my experience.

I believe my background check started on March 5th. I was in the military for 3 years, and this is my first job, besides that. I've been unemployed since September and I'm getting worried because the money is running out.

I currently live in Florida, and will have to relocate to California. 
Because I have no start date, I can't really get any quotes on moving trucks (price changes based on dates), I haven't really TRIED to lock down a home rental, because I'm afraid of getting my heart set on a particular home and then being beat out by someone else.

I will be making relatively good money, and receiving a lump sum  for moving expenses in my first paycheck. At this point in time, my husband and I have enough money to pay for a truck (based on a quote we got for a specific date) pay deposits on a home (at the lowest end of our price range), electric, etc. The problem is, we are going to be FLAT broke until I get paid, which could take some time to stabilize. 

The point of this post is to ask what I should do. We are planning on getting a loan, but we don't know how much is appropriate. In California, it is not required for a landlord to give you a fridge, but my inlaws are giving us a mini fridge, so that's not really a problem. We will need a washer and dryer (washer first and foremost, I'll hang my shit outside, lol). 

If anyone has any advice please comment away!! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> In-Laws. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-12-27 21:57:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I currently live with my mother and father-in-law. I was in the military and separated, so this is our best option until we find employment. Let me just say, I'm very appreciative of what they are doing for us, but I just gotta rant about them.

Nice people, don't really have an issues with them. They drive me up the fucking wall, though. I'm accused of being lazy and not doing anything all day. Yeah, I sleep until 1pm sometimes, but I still do everything I'm supposed to.

I ensure the house is clean every day when they get home from work, I feed their dog and chickens. I told my MIL if she would tell me what to make for dinner, I would make it and she wouldn't have to do a thing. I STILL GET BITCHED AT. 

These people are so dirty. I spend at least an hour a day on the kitchen, and it just gets SO BAD. Everytime they use the stove, I have to scrub the fuck out of it. They could use just ONE burner (gas stove) and the entire stove needs to be cleaned again.  That's just the tip of the iceberg right there.

What really set me off is what happened over the past few days. On Christmas day,  I went over to my sister's house and didn't get home until around 5pm. I usually feed the dogs around 3pm, so I asked MIL, "have the dogs been fed?" she replies, "MY dog is." REALLY? I FEED YOUR DOG EVERY FUCKING DAY AND YOU CAN'T FEED MINE JUST ONCE???? GAH!

Yesterday, around 3pm, I walked outside to smoke. I let their dog in the house so I could let mine out. (They stay in the yard when they are let out individually, but when they are out together, they tend to run off.) Anyway I went outside and smoked, and 8 minutes later I call for my dog and she isn't coming. So I go inside and what do I see? The back door is fucking open and nobody told me. Wow. The dogs ran off because once I had let their dog inside, she darted out the back door.

Now at this point, everyone is blaming me for this happening. My FIL is already upset because a few days ago, their other dog died. (He had heartworm and we knew it was coming) My dog came back around 7pm (4hrs later). So now everyone is mad at me because I'm happy my dog came back. (Last time they ran off, my hubby and I would drive around the nearby neighborhoods every few hours to look for both dogs. Whenever my MIL would go outside to call, she would only call for her dog.) Now, around 930pm their dog still isn't back, so me, hubby, SIL and her hubbs, go look in the woods. It's dark as shit, its swampy, and full of ticks. No sign of her. We drive around looking, no sign of her.

Around 5 am, I was outside smoking and scrolling through the lost pets page for our area. (I had been all night, everytime I smoked, but didn't see it on my newsfeed) Anyway, I saw that someone had seen two dogs, described as our dogs, get hit by a car. I run inside and tell hubby, and we all get in the car (excluding MIL/FIL) and go to the last known area. (It was posted at 9pm, so chances were slim)

We drive up and down the streets, calling for her, to no avail. Our husbands get out of the car and are searching the ditches and everything. We can't find her, so we head home. Every hour or so we would check outside for her. (I stayed up til 8am) MIL finally decided to look for her own damn dog, and found her in a neighbor's yard.

I came out in the living room, and she says " She's so sick, she got hit by a car..blah blah blah." At some point it evolved into, "we're not blaming you, we're blaming Honey." (my dog).  what the everliving fuck. You're seriously blaming a dog for doing what dogs do... and running? WHAT THE FUCK. And then somehow, this conversation gets turned on me being lazy. Dear freaking god.

TL:DR: I fucking hate people. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> TIFU by collecting firewood. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-12-11 04:26:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This happened a few hours ago.

There is supposed to be a "freeze" tonight where I live. My husband decided he was going to start a fire, so he asked me to go outside and help him collect wood. My husband took the wood from out large stock pile in the front yard, tapped out the wood and placed it in my arms. I was able to carry about 6 or 7 pieces.

I go inside and drop the wood in front of the fire place. The very first piece that my husband had placed in my arms had a giant fucking spider on it. This piece of wood had been in my arms for a good 3 minutes. I have a crazy fear of spiders so I started crying and ran into the kitchen.

This thing was about the size of a silver dollar. We didn't have any bug spray, so we tried to kill it with oven cleaner. The spider was absolutely drenched and drowning in this shit and it wouldn't fucking die. My husband doesn't like spiders either so it was up to my mother-in-law to smack the shit out of it with a dust pan and then throw it out the door.

I'm never getting firewood again.

TL:DR: Got fire wood, had a spider, cried like a bitch. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> TIFU by visiting my dad. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-12-08 14:59:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Note: This is long.

Backstory: My dad is a truck driver and was going to be close by this weekend. I live in a part of Florida that he doesn't get to very often, so my husband and I decided to drive the brief 4 1/2 hours to get there for a weekend of fun!

The Story: My husband and I leave our house around 1pm(Friday). Other than being extremely hungover from the night before, I was happily driving and nom nom noming on my McDonalds. About 1 hour down the road, I realize something.  I FORGOT MY FUCKING BIRTH CONTROL. Now, anyone who knows anything about the pill knows you don't miss pills, you just don't.

So, I turn around and head back home. We arrive at the house, let the dog out of the car for a few minutes, and I grab my pills. It is now around 3pm. About 2 hours behind schedule. Oh well, just a few more hours, no big deal.

Fast forward another hour, all is going well when my dog decides to puke the most massive, stinky puke ever. I had a sheet down, and thankfully towels underneath, so nothing got on my seat. We pull over and shake out the sheet.  Problem solved, on our way again.

We finally arrive around 8pm. We eat some linguine with clams, dick around, and go to bed. We wake up around 8am, chill in the hotel room with my dad and stepmom.

That night (Saturday), we go to the bar with my parents and a few of their trucker friends. We're all having a good time, getting a little faded, eating some chicken wings and dancing to the juke box. My dad went to the bar around 2pm, so needless to say, he was pretty drunk around 9pm when he decided to go back to the room. One of his friends decides to go to the room and beg my dad to sing. My dad doesn't want to, warns the dude to leave him alone, and he just won't let it go. This leads to my parents fighting. An all-out, fuck you, fuck you, and fuck you, kind of fight.

Around 11pm, I was sick of trying to mediate, so I went back to the bar for a few more drinks. My husband shows up and sits with me, then my dad shows up. Some completely plastered black guy decides to poke my dad in the ribs. This dude was around 6'3 (according to my dad he was at least 28 feet tall, lol). Anyway, my dad turns and looks at him and is giving this stare like, "I'm going to kick your fucking ass". I run in between them and say to the guy, "Please apologize to him, he's in a bad mood, and I don't want any problems. I'll buy you a beer if you want." I give him a quick bro hug (the handshake, backtap kind). He tells me to give him a kiss on the cheek, to which I respond "I'm married, that's inappropriate". My husband doesn't like this, so he says, "Are you trying to put the moves on my wife?" Black guy walks over, husband says, "get the fuck out of here". Dad gives hubby mad props, black guy walks off, we go outside to smoke.

While we're outside smoking, black guy shows up again. We play it off cool like nothing happened, he gets an attitude and calls us racist. He walks inside. Another dude who was out there says, "I bet he has a fucking gun." Oh, great. We walk back over to our room while we have the chance. A few minutes go by and my husband and I go walk the dogs. Now, my dog doesn't bark unless there is trouble, so when she starts barking and I look up, WHO DO I FUCKING SEE? Black guy from the bar. You've got to be fucking kidding me. This guy looks like he's ready for trouble. He walks by us, and doesn't even look at us. Phew.

THEN BAM! Cops roll up. We ask who they're looking for, and they say a black male in all red. We tell him he went "that way". They stop him and then come back in tell us that he didn't actually have a gun. I guess he pissed off more people when he went back into the bar, so they called the cops. Okay, problem solved, let's go to bed.

Next Morning (Sunday), I wake up with quite the hangover, which is weird because I didn't even get drunk the night before and I was actually drinking water. FML. Anyway, my dad runs over to the nearest fast food place to pick up breakfast for everyone. Who do we see walk up through the parking lot? Black guy from the bar. WTF. He walks up to our door, (which was open, as it was nice out) and stands there for a second. My step-mom, nicely asks how he's doing. And let me tell you, this dude can't even fucking talk he's so drunk. We don't think he slept from the night before. AND he's carrying around a bottle of Ciroc. Well, then he decides to step INTO our room. I say, "Please don't walk in our room, get out." He comes in closer, so my husband ushers him out the door, and shuts the door in his face. Dude walks over to the window and starts pounding on the window. Husband closes curtains. Dad walks up, see dude trying to peek in the window. Guy clenches his fist, dad gets pissed, tells me to call the cops.

As soon as he heard that we were calling the cops, he walked off. I called the cops and they show up about 5-10 minutes later. We explain that there was an altercation the night before with this guy, and they take off to look for him. Since they had stopped him the night before, they were able to pick him up. They drove back by to let us know that they threw him in jail for the day. Cool. I feel a dick, but he was an asshat. 

Later that day, I was going through some pictures my parents had gotten out of storage for me. I found some pictures of my mom, my nana... OH MY FUCKING GOD ITS MY DAD'S ASSHOLE. I see pictures of my dad's asshole, my mom sucking his dick, my step mom sucking his dick, him giving it to my step mom. LIKE REALLY? I'm scarred for fucking life. /r/Eyebleach Anyway, I enjoy the rest of my day, eat some steaks and go to bed.

Now, my parents have left and I'm sitting in the hotel typing this. We survived the weekend. Which is honestly a miracle every time we hang out with my parents, lol. We should be should be leaving in about an hour to head back home. Which reminds me, my dog has barely eaten this whole trip and she hasn't pooped. I really hope she doesn't shit in the car.

TLDR; Hungover, Forgot BC pills, turned around. Dog pukes. Go to bar, everyone gets drunk, fight ensues. Black guy trolls us at bar, cops show up. Next day black guy shows up, get him thrown in jail. Look at old pics, see dad's dick. Scarred. Dog won't shit.
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> TIFU by feeding my dogs turkey grease </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-11-29 10:04:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I actually fucked up the Friday before Thanksgiving. My mother-in-law, who I live with, is a school teacher and at her school, the Friday before Turkey Day, they have their own little feast. That being said, she made a turkey on Thursday for school.

Since I am unemployed, I maintain the household as far as cleaning goes. So, Friday morning I was cleaning the kitchen and I got the idea to use the turkey grease to coat the dog food. Not alot, just a quick splash to give the food a nice coating. The dogs happily chowed down on their food and gave me lots of kisses to show their appreciation. Look at me! Being a good mom to my fur babies!

A little back ground on the dogs, there are three. Chester is a 9 year old black lab, who we are pretty sure is close to dying due to his heartworm. His asshole leaks as it is, but he's pretty good at controlling his bowels.

Then there is Nyla, a beautiful 2 year old German Shepherd. Total sweetheart. She isn't very good at letting people know she needs to go to the bathroom, but don't usually have any issues with her.

Last but certainly not least, my darling 2 year old Black Lab/Hound mix, Honey. Best dog ever, I swear. She never barks, never shits in the house, she cuddles. 

Now for the real fuck up. My in laws went on vacation for Thanksgiving, so my husband and I had the house to ourselves. Nyla usually sleeps in their room. We put her in the hallway near our room, so if she barked or anything, we would be able to hear her. We let Honey out there with her so she wouldn't get lonely. Nyla kept whining for hours. I let her out at least twice while this was going on.

It's about 4 in the morning when hubby and I decided to hit the hay. We open the door to go to the bathroom to brush our teeth...what we see and smell is awful. Starting from our bedroom door, going 8 feet into the bathroom and then back out to the hallway, ANOTHER 8 feet, is the nastiest, greenest, foulest smelling shit I've ever seen.

All I could do was stare in awe at how she managed to shit so much, it trailed for a good 16 feet. After a quick bitch session, we began to clean it up. I went to the laundry room (this is where Chester sleeps) to fetch the mop. LOW AND BEHOLD ANOTHER MASSIVE FUCKING SHIT. This shit pile was bigger than a dinner plate. And it was runny, smelly, and green.

By the time this was all cleaned up, it was about 5 in the morning. I thought to my self, wow, Honey is such a good girl! Didn't even shit like the rest of them! We ended up putting Nyla on the back porch in case she shit again.

Next morning: I wake up to let the dogs out. What do I find? Shit. Chester had shit in the laundry room again. This time it was all over the washing machine and dryer. Nyla also shit all over the back porch. She even shit on her bed. By this time, I'm absolutely fed up! But I thought, hey, what can you do? Nyla slept on the back porch again, Chester in the laundry room, and Honey in bed with us.

Next day: I get out of bed and prepare my self for the literal shit show I'm about to see. YAY! There isn't any shit! There is a god!

Later that day: I'm sitting in bed eating some General Tso's Chicken (NOM NOM NOM). I say to my husband, "Babe, I've cleaned up so much shit these past two days, I can still smell it" He gets up and moves our recliner and says " Well, Honey shit too." SO ONCE AGAIN, I get to clean up shit. Shit that had been sitting there for 2 days and was dry around the sides, wet in the middle.

Needless to say, I will never again feed my mammals turkey grease.

TL:DR Tried to be a loving owner and fed my 3 dogs turkey grease. Two day shit-fest ensues.
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> My dog got bit by something... can anyone possibly identify? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-11-29 00:08:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Species: Dog

Age: 9 years

Sex/Neuter status: Male/ Not Neutered

Breed: Black Lab

Body weight: 60lbs+

History: Never got treated for heartworm, so he's very swollen as it is. (we believe he's about to die.. slowed down a lot in the past few months) 
   
Clinical signs: I went to bring him inside today and noticed his left leg was swollen at the joint, but his opposite leg was not. Upon further inspection, I saw a quarter sized wound on the outside of his paw. Managed to snap a picture of that [Here](http://imgur.com/rQaWjbv). Adjacent to that on the bottom of his paw where the pad is, there is another dime sized wound. On the opposite side of the large wound, there is a smaller oval shaped wound. He doesn't seem to be in any pain, other than not walking on it. There is no visual bleeding. I flushed it out with peroxide and wrapped it in gauze. I talked to a vet tech friend of mine and she said it looks like a snake bite, which is odd since snakes aren't usually out around this time of the year.


Duration: Had to have happened in the early after noon today.

Your general location: Jacksonville, Florida </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> He's a Barbie Girl </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-09-15 09:31:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> He's a Barbie Girl </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-09-15 04:09:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
