<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject254</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-24 08:28:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Let them fast and only give them water.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-24 06:07:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [Why Does Coffee Make You Poop? - Video](https://youtu.be/JQO6VgqdM9I) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-24 03:05:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The mark was achieved Sunday night after a match that featured 2,357 people who took turns to keep the ball rolling during more than 120 hours. The score? A close 505-504. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-24 03:04:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> An Indian restaurant owner has been convicted of killing a customer with a nut allergy and sentenced to six years in jail. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-23 16:36:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> ...the Supreme Court of the United States held that a criminal defendant has a right to a jury trial not only on the question of guilt or innocence, but any fact used to increase the defendant's sentence beyond the maximum otherwise allowed by statutes or sentencing guidelines.   This invalidated the procedure in many states and the federal courts that allowed sentencing enhancement based on "a preponderance of evidence", where enhancement could be based on the judge's findings alone.

[Sentencing](https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Juries_in_the_United_States#Sentencing) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-23 12:59:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Looks like September in the UK </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-23 02:47:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  Danny explained: Thats a reality that there is a live show being thrashed out in Dougs head at the moment.   

But we are all up for it [and] have agreed to do it if Doug finally has the time to write it because at the moment he is post-producing 12 episodes of Red Dwarf, which takes three times as long as an ordinary show because of various effects. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-23 02:38:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [Reset!](http://dailysignal.com/wp-content/uploads/2009/03/reset_button090324.jpg)

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-02 18:09:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [Who Knew?](http://cdn.playbuzz.com/cdn/44f37cc2-0b9b-4811-8a3b-96fc2a02294d/6a788f5c-fdc4-4fc8-8486-149de77c3e34.gif)  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-18 17:34:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Apollo 13. 
The Right Stuff. 
The Martian.  


 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-18 17:25:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Relative to outside observers.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-17 06:54:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Carbon Credits  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-17 06:53:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The video shows two adult women bashing the young girl, but it is believed a third woman was also involved. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-11 23:56:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So if I don't have a new floodplain, just the old one, and I want to calculate areas it missed, can I do that with the tin or contours, or will I have to generate a new floodplain?     
 
My thought is to make the old floodplain a raster, buffer out the cross sections (BFE's) and then create a new raster that would show the buffer (as a raster) with elevations.  If I do this, and compare it to the old floodplain raster, would I get the results I'm looking for?  
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-08 22:55:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You mean for their *scientific research*?   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-08 16:43:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [Thinkin' Bee](https://youtu.be/LOofUNSAVp4) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-06 19:09:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I wonder how many more helmets have been discovered since this was written.  If so, if they vary much from the ones referenced in the article, as in surprise discoveries. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-03 15:06:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I would say ages 4+.   

While quite a bit is focused on middle school/high school, they usually do have  enough activities for younger kids to keep busy.  The Paper rockets, egg drop, popsicle stick catapults, tours, coloring, etc. seem to be favorites no matter how old.  With that being said, older children will probably find more to do, or at least enjoy exploring a bit more.


My thoughts on the time to allot based on age:  
**Ages 4-6 (2-3 hours)**  
**Ages 6-10 (3-4 hours)**  
**Ages 10+ (4+ hours)**  

If your child is competing in the preregistered competitions (i.e. Rube Goldberg), plan on 5+ hours. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-01 23:15:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Trump is 69, 70 in June. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-27 15:53:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Agreed about the source material. However, without subscriptions to professional journals, one is only allowed access to the abstract. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-27 15:06:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Guess you were right. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-26 18:40:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> A news story is not [/r/worldnews](https://www.reddit.com/r/worldnews) if it doesn't affect multiple parts of the world.  If the news only involves a country, region, city, or some other local place (relative to the story), it is not deemed worldnews and must be posted in the [/r/news](https://www.reddit.com/r/news) or other subreddit.  Threads can and have been removed for not obeying this.   [/r/news](https://www.reddit.com/r/news) is not just for US or UK news items either (so I've been told). </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-25 14:26:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  a dozen stab wounds

It's a miracle he survived.  I hope they catch his parents.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-25 04:24:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Agreed, especially when we're talking about dates **millions** of years ago. 
Our analysis of C. abyssinicus fossils reveals the ape to be only 8 million years old, younger than previously thought.  

[Source Article](http://www.lanl.gov/discover/news-release-archive/2016/February/02.16-fossil-analysis.php) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-25 01:03:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [Fete](http://dictionary.reference.com/browse/fete). 

noun, plural fetes.
1.
a day of celebration; holiday:
The Fourth of July is a great American fete.
2.
a festive celebration or entertainment:
The ball was the greatest fete of the season. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-23 21:06:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> There is a 3rd account somewhere in **The Twilight Zone!** </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-23 20:46:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Ignorance is bliss. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-23 05:12:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The article talks about three age ranges (progression) of the eagles that were found. Here is more information and visual on what they were talking about.[Bald Eagle Age Progression](http://www.onthewingphotography.com/wings/2011/02/16/bald-eagles-one-to-five-years-old/) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-23 01:48:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Mods wanted this reposted due to the original post using Time as the source. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-21 23:41:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Perhaps sources are in the book.  If there are any. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-21 04:00:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> All good reasons.  Surely they lose votes because of it.  I suppose those who are for a particular candidate do not necessarily have to watch or listen to the speeches.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-21 03:57:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> She's old enough to have trained Sylvester Stallone in [Over the Top](http://www.imdb.com/title/tt0093692/). </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-19 20:50:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Which one, I, II, III, IV or V? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-19 16:41:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You had better luck with your guesses than i did. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-19 16:25:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I didn't do as well as I thought I would.  My score:  **6** </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-17 14:49:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> His tweet right after that was pretty good too.  

[Judging from the misplaced repetition in my last tweet wicked strength lager indeed](https://twitter.com/CCfunkandsoul/status/699946632574590976) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-16 18:04:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thanks, I did come across that.  I should have said I was looking for the *.wav file. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-16 02:02:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> They're part of the X-Files </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-15 18:34:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Shootings in 2016 are more than double the same period in 2015, according to data kept by the Tribune. Killings are up 130 percent.  As of Sunday, at least 365 people have been shot in Chicago this year and at least 85 of them have been killed.

I think Chicago is trying to make it into the [Top 20 Most Dangerous Cities in America](http://kdvr.com/2015/05/08/by-the-numbers-here-are-the-most-dangerous-cities-in-america/)  
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-15 15:34:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Interning and being paid by what the law states is one thing.  You were getting paid about $3.1 Australian Dollars/hr.  

To compare, if we reverse it, she was getting paid 0.30/hr. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-15 14:47:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Doesn't matter if it was a franchise or not.  The point is, it looks like it's been an **ongoing and known problem**, and not much has been done to stop it, either by the franchise owners or by 7-11. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-15 07:51:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Kai Winn truly displayed arrogance to its perfection.  Even more so than Q, at least he showed humility and kindness a few times. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-15 07:48:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Interesting comment in the last paragraph:  
Rumours of several leopard spotting over the week led to 134 schools across the city shutting down </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-15 07:47:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> And some incompetent park staff.   

 the cage door was not properly shut. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-15 06:55:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Amazon did recently patent [Self Driving Delivery Trucks](http://www.autoevolution.com/news/googles-self-driving-delivery-truck-sounds-more-plausible-than-amazon-prime-air-104578.html). </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-15 06:09:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I agree, there is a vast difference between a a close/strong friendship compared to an intimate or sexual relationship.  I suppose when it involves the opposite sex, secret letters, covert meetings, or anything else, people's imaginations dive right into the gutter. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-15 03:24:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That ice killed the [150,000 penguins](http://www.cnn.com/2016/02/13/world/penguins-die-giant-iceberg-irpt/), this ice would have killed 150,000 people. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-13 06:36:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I wonder how many other countries have similar issues.  Is it safe to say most of the third world countries do? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-13 06:10:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Just wait until Trump hears about this. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-13 05:40:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> My guess is it's in line with their child safety seat laws somehow.
[Virginia's child passenger safety laws require all children under 8 to be properly secured in a child safety seat or booster seat, regardless of weight or height.](https://www.dmv.virginia.gov/safety/#programs/car_seats/index.html). 

 At least that's the only logical (for a government) and illogical (for the rest of the world) way of looking at it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-12 19:56:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> He was hoping for another Smokey and the Bandit movie. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-12 19:05:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I guess you can "eat" the meat, but you'll poison yourself with mercury.  
 [Burmese pythons in the Everglades contain some of the highest levels of mercury found in a living creature.](http://www.outsideonline.com/1794941/florida-officals-dont-eat-python-meat)  
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-12 18:51:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> According to [USGS](http://www.usgs.gov/faq/categories/9785/3262) there is no reliable estimate of how many Pythons are in the Everglades.  They can only say tens of thousands.  So let's take the low end... 20,000.   

So after a month long hunt, 102 snakes are killed.  Using the 20,000, that's only 0.51%.  
Chances are it's much lower than .5% of the total population.

We can probably safely assume more than 102 pythons were born during the hunt. From what the [Florida Fish and Wildlife
Conservation Commission](http://myfwc.com/wildlifehabitats/nonnatives/python/faqs/fast-facts/) reports:  
 A female Burmese python may lay 50-100 eggs  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-11 05:37:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Who said: *And may the Schwartz be with youuuyoyoy*? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-11 02:17:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What genre?  
I would highly suggest the [Wool Trilogy](http://www.hughhowey.com/books/wool/):  

Series Titles:  
[1. Wool](http://amzn.com/B0071XO8RA)  
[2. Shift](http://amzn.com/B00B6Z6HI2)  
[3. Dust](http://amzn.com/B00CYNGPTG)   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-11 02:02:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I don't think you can due to the dynamic zoom.   
Here is a link to someone that had the same question.  
[how could  make specific scales on google earth pro?](https://productforums.google.com/forum/#!msg/maps/NkTy5Focqi0/43DNtkhO2d4J) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-11 01:52:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Can they count each poach as an offense?  If so, then the first one falls under the bag limit, but the others would be felonies.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-11 01:50:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> They are banned from the ones that are part of the: Interstate Wildlife Violator Compact </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-11 01:41:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You should bring this up in class and get a class debate going.  Then let us know what your instructor thinks/says.  I'm interested in his take on whether he thinks the punishment was too low, or is their a particular reason they couldn't have a harsher sentence. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-11 01:38:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Sad that anywhere in the world, it can happen, just some places more than others.  

[Water is a precious commodity - Similar Photo](http://2.bp.blogspot.com/-T_8stHSD_Mk/VAtlmwwhc1I/AAAAAAAAB64/RaOkitOLi4E/s1600/Haiti-Children_Collecting_Water.jpg) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-11 00:29:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Looks good. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-10 23:38:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The states are:

Alabama, Alaska, Arizona, California, Colorado, Florida, Georgia, Idaho, Illinois, Indiana, Iowa, Kansas, Kentucky, Louisiana, Maryland, Michigan, Minnesota, Mississippi, Missouri, Montana, Nevada, New Mexico, New York, North Dakota, Ohio, Oklahoma, Oregon, South Dakota, Tennessee, Texas, Utah, Washington, West Virginia, Wisconsin, Wyoming

They are banned from the ones that are part of the:
[Interstate Wildlife Violator Compact](https://en.m.wikipedia.org/wiki/Interstate_Wildlife_Violator_Compact) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-10 20:56:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  The current fiscal year-to-date deficit stood at $160 billion, compared to a deficit of $194 billion at the same point last year. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-10 18:22:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  Two La Vergne residents have been banned from hunting in Tennessee and 43 other states after they illegally killed as many as 40 deer, and then took photos and videos mocking the animals, according to the Tennessee Wildlife Resources Agency. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-10 16:24:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  "The eighth story. Nineteen years later.
It was always difficult being Harry Potter and it isnt much easier now that he is an overworked employee of the Ministry of Magic, a husband, and father of three school-age children.
While Harry grapples with a past that refuses to stay where it belongs, his youngest son Albus must struggle with the weight of a family legacy he never wanted. As past and present fuse ominously, both father and son learn the uncomfortable truth: sometimes darkness comes from unexpected places." </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-09 17:24:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Where's the toy?  If it's untouched, McDonalds short changed her!  She should demand a refund. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-09 05:12:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Where did she learn to drive, Playschool?  
I picture them in an adult version of the [little tyke red car](http://www.elitereaders.com/adult-version-little-tikes-car/). </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-08 21:50:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [Boothby](http://www.startrek.com/database_article/boothby) would be proud.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-08 17:22:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> As 2009, there were some still in circulation:  
336  - $10,000  
342  - $5,000    
165,732  - $1,000   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-07 16:51:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I wonder if this underground community was all Christian. Did they live or worship there because of persecution or for other reasons? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-07 15:20:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Its because they are treated so well.  Free food, lodging, medication, TV, heat, ac, library, internet, etc. Then you've got the prison black market which makes some prisoners wealthy in their mini prison economy.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-06 23:11:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> At least she had some Data before she died.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-06 21:22:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Good call PhillyTaco

[Star Trek: TNG - Skin of Evil](https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Skin_of_Evil) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-06 20:22:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [The Blob](http://m.imdb.com/title/tt4381834/) remake is being release later this year.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-06 20:10:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If it was crude, oil companies would pay for the road to be moved and set up a rig.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-06 18:45:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I agree with the premise of the idea.  Tack on $25-50 upfront and you get it back when either you return and  recycle the new TV or old one you may be replacing.  It would easily scale for any electronic at all price points.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-06 18:17:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Here is a link to an article about the disks last month and about trying to retrieve the data.   
[How Star Trek creator Gene Roddenberrys words were freed from old floppy disks](http://www.pcworld.com/article/3018315/storage/star-trek-creators-lost-words-recovered-from-old-floppies.html) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-06 18:05:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Fixed </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-06 00:31:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> And no looking back. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-06 00:12:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I hope you get more up votes than I do this time around. You've got mine.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-05 23:38:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Sure does. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-05 17:44:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> After he had his [Uncle executed](http://worldnews.nbcnews.com/_news/2014/01/03/22156917-kim-jong-uns-executed-uncle-was-eaten-alive-by-120-hungry-dogs-report?lite) by hungry dogs, and recently killing [70  officials](http://www.usatoday.com/story/news/world/2015/07/09/north-korea-executions-officials/29899751/), who will he take out now?
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-05 02:56:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Gleason was also the creator and producer of the Honeymooners. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-04 20:52:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thanks, I just recently got the opportunity to check this series out, and already addicted to it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-04 20:49:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Season 2 is slated for 2017.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-04 19:46:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Sadly, Jackie Gleason  never made a dime off of it either.  At one point he almost sued for the mimicking and possible infringement of the Honeymooners, but Gleason didn't want to be thought of the one that killed off Flintstone.  

In the early 1990's, one of the creators admitted it was a rip off of the Honeymooners.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-04 03:07:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Reminds me of the Star Trek DS9 episode that Sisko used a Solar Sail.  


[Bajoran solar-sail vessel](http://www.startrek.com/database_article/bajoran-solar-sail-vessel) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-03 19:55:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's not weight, it's **mass.** </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-03 19:41:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Doubt it's Amazon's fault.  CBS wants to reign in their content prior to the new movies and new star trek show. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-03 19:31:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> CBS probably won't make an announcement of the start trek franchise leaving Netflix until it get's closer to the end of their contract. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-03 18:50:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It is definitely not the way to expand it's fan base. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-03 17:23:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If they did as good of a job on it that they did with the updated American History museum and the renovations of the Natural History museum, I'm sure it will be excellent.  I'm looking forward to visiting. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-03 16:48:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> My guess it is will coincide with the new Star Trek series that will only be available via the CBS subscription. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-03 03:06:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It wouldn't be so bad if there were genre subscription applications.  So instead of a generalized one like Netflix, Hulu and Amazon, it would be one focused just on ScFi, Drama, Westerns, etc.  I know there are already a couple out there for documentaries like [Curiosity Stream](https://curiositystream.com/lp?utm_campaign=S-Brand utm_medium=cpc utm_source=google utm_content=headline1 utm_term=curiousity%20stream gclid=Cj0KEQiAxMG1BRDFmu3P3qjwmeMBEiQAEzSDLqC9M2FeM-UFL4yosW9Y0h6B6SBvv2DfX1wNhyHK1HIaAo2h8P8HAQ). </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-03 00:31:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I remember seeing this a few times int he basement gift shop at the Air and Space Museum in Washington DC before they removed it a couple years ago.  It was always easy to see since not many people knew about the basement. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-02 23:10:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Standard by 2...Confirmed </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-02 16:47:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That or Blake's 7 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-02 15:38:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> 
I want to lie, shipwrecked and comatose, 
Drinking fresh, mango juice  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-02 04:26:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Season 1, first episode :)  There really are no bad episodes.  You'll enjoy them all, but the there really is a story line, and watching the beginning will help out later. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-02 03:44:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> My vote goes to **Orac**.  Witty, condescending, and downright intelligent were some of  his top qualities.  He was the perfect companion for *Avon*.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-01 23:44:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> At least they have groups ready to go for venting workforce.  Wait, do yahoo groups work as well as therapy? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-01 23:09:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Not sure if it was the new sets, or the HD, perhaps a combination of both.  But like you said.  
 it's still Red Dwarf   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-01 22:59:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Go is one of my all time favorite games.   

[Nature article: "The game of Go has long been viewed as the most challenging of classic games for artificial intelligence owing to its enormous search space and the difficulty of evaluating board positions and moves"](http://www.nature.com/nature/journal/v529/n7587/full/nature16961.html)
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-01 19:58:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I am smegging excited about this! I hope Dwayne Dibbley, Holy and Ace make appearances.  
From the previous post [Sneak Peeks](http://www.reddwarf.co.uk/news/2015/10/30/sneak-peeks/) there are a couple pictures with the cast with Dibbley teeth. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-01 19:46:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I wish I thought of that :) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-01 19:45:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Update:  "[Cops won't punish driver who pulled over Florida officer for speeding](http://www.foxnews.com/us/2016/02/01/cops-wont-punish-driver-who-pulled-over-florida-officer-for-speeding.html?intcmp=hplnws)" </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-01 15:27:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Totally agree. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-01 15:03:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I love his comment in the the [3rd video](https://youtu.be/p7Au42hxpYQ)...  Around the 36 second mark -  

Lady: "What's the emergency?"    
Cop: "Uh. I don't know how fast I was going."   
Cop: "But I can tell you this, I'm my way to work right now."  
Cop: "I don't believe I was speeding."  

Then the cops says "...then I pulled over, thought you had some kind emergency, is everything fine?"

How many times have people used the excuse about not knowing how fast they were going, or that they were on their way to work.  Guess it works for the cops, not fur civilians. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-01 14:31:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Best part is she recorded it all.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-01 06:03:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Something cute and fuzzy for the shelf or dresser.  A tribble, [or a family of 5 tribbles](https://www.etsy.com/listing/158436025/family-of-five-tribble-adoption-five?ref=market).  These little buggers are cross generational, showing up in both the original [Star Trek - Trouble with Tribbles](https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=p4wM5KvUGEc) and [Deep Space Nine -Trials and Tribble-ations](http://www.imdb.com/title/tt0708655/).  

This will also let her be a closet Trekkie, even when guests of family come and see the baby, it just looks like a little fuzzball.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-01 05:46:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I suppose only time will tell, and how fast the virus spreads.  

Here is an the [updated (January 2016) fact sheet](http://www.who.int/mediacentre/factsheets/zika/en/) from the WHO for the Zika Virus. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-01 05:17:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Whoops.  Good catch. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-01 05:10:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [Wikipedia: Pitcairn Islands](https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Pitcairn_Islands)  

"As of 2012, just two children had been born on Pitcairn in the 21 years prior" </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-31 00:42:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Sadly, the article doesn't suggest anyone came out to help either.  Kudos to Mr. Dueck!  All i know is if I saw an elderly person shoveling the snow, I would be out asap without hesitation to, at a minimum, help and bring coffee. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-31 00:30:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm pretty sure it's the GED Testing Service making the changes, not the Commonwealth of Kentucky. Definitely not because of Matt Bevin or any other politician (Independent, Republican or Democrat).  This is happening in multiple states across the board. Frustration should go to the organization (GED) who creates the tests and scores. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-30 21:44:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I can't imagine dealing with wear and tear on the body, let alone the jet lag.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-30 19:38:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> 21st Century Education </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-30 18:36:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> True, but it's good to see it can happen in impoverished nations as well. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-30 18:33:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm not a local to there, but came across it today and found it to be a fell good story.  One that puts a smile on your face. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-30 18:17:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That would have been too depressing for [/r/UpliftingNews](https://www.reddit.com/r/UpliftingNews).    :)  I wish they said what they named the lizard (unless I missed it). </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-30 18:06:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Was it [Chasing Mummies](http://www.imdb.com/title/tt1604096/)? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-30 17:46:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I guess when you can't increase the knowledge of the students, one lowers the test scores required to pass.  

We know that for individuals without a high school diploma or a GED, the unemployment rate is 5.4 percent higher and average annual income is $10,000 less than for those with these credentials, so these enhancements are game-changers for GED graduates"  

Soon the GED to employers won't mean much. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-30 17:01:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I also noticed small brick segments (nearly the size as the pyramid stones) as he climbed.  Are these shaft ends or vents? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-30 16:58:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Even by his own words, he didn't care.   
  
"At the half some people got attention on me and looked up. Thats how the police spotted me. They shouted something in Arabic I think but I didnt care and kept going while listening to music."   

It will be interesting to see if the authorities prosecute him, and if he gets the 3 years in prison.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-30 16:44:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I had forgotten all about this incident until I came across the update yesterday.  Imagine how [Zahi Hawass](https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Zahi_Hawass) would have dealt with it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-30 07:52:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Next he will insinuate the potatoes have feelings.  Making a million dollars off a victimized potato.  Go figure.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-30 00:48:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Seems like the refugees can't catch a break. It was reported today that over 1000 attacks on refugee homes in Germany alone in 2015. That was up 400% compared to 2014. 
[http://www.bbc.com/news/world-europe-35437873](http://www.bbc.com/news/world-europe-35437873) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-28 21:00:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I think we have to differentiate between accidents and injuries.  I think the article is stating that you may be more likely to have an accident wearing a helmet  (not referring to injuries).  I think everyone can safely say that it's ignorant not to wear a helmet, and one definitely has an increased chance of injury by not wearing one. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-28 18:19:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's similar to a [Self-fulfilling prophecy](https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Self-fulfilling_prophecy).  In other words... [Murphy's law](https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Murphy's_law). </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-28 18:17:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Whether it's 2 feet or **2 inches**, towns go crazy!  

[It's going to snow!](http://first2board.com/carolinatravelgirl/files/2014/04/Ice-Storm-milk-bread-snow.jpg) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-28 04:45:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Not sure about the deaths in cars, but over all there were 70 people who died due to the blizzard (not just Louisville).  
[http://fox41blogs.typepad.com/wdrb_weather/2013/01/remembering-the-great-blizzard-of-1978.html](http://fox41blogs.typepad.com/wdrb_weather/2013/01/remembering-the-great-blizzard-of-1978.html)   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-26 00:40:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Fair enough and good catch! The actual depth is (as you stated) about *220m*, still making it the deepest in the world.  
**Other Sources**  
[http://www.geologypage.com/2014/04/congo-river.html](http://www.geologypage.com/2014/04/congo-river.html)  
[http://www.livescience.com/29558-the-worlds-longest-rivers.html](http://www.livescience.com/29558-the-worlds-longest-rivers.html)  
[http://www.usgs.gov/newsroom/leads_pf.asp?ID=2160](http://www.usgs.gov/newsroom/leads_pf.asp?ID=2160)  
[http://www.destination360.com/africa/zambia/congo-river](http://www.destination360.com/africa/zambia/congo-river)  
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-26 00:12:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thanks, that did the trick.  With Face to face groups dwindling, what are the best online groups? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-25 22:37:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thanks.  Library has it via kindle download.  Going to check it out now. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-25 22:23:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Time to hire John Goodman.  If I recall, he has experience in exterminating spiders.    
[Arachnophobia](http://www.imdb.com/title/tt0099052/?ref_=nv_sr_1)   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-25 06:02:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Totally agree, sadly Han died long time ago.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-25 05:02:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Population Estimates:
London 1200AD: between 20,000-25,000
http://www.demographia.com/dm-lon31.htm

London 1100-1300 AD:  Population 15,000 - 80,000 respectively.
https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/History_of_London#Norman_and_Medieval_London_.281066_.E2.80.93_late_15th_century.29

Cahokia 1200s population about 40,000
https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Cahokia

Cahokia was a city that, at its peak from 1050-1200 A.D., was larger than many European cities, including London.  
http://www.livescience.com/22737-cahokia.html

Other sources:
http://www.atlasobscura.com/places/cahokia-mounds
https://sites.google.com/site/southernmostil/mississippian
http://traveleering.com/cahokia-mounds/
http://www.slu.edu/~amille75/LabPhotos/Persimmons.html

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-25 04:39:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's worth taking a sweater for sure, even in the summer.  If you're lucky in the late spring or early summer, with a small hike once you're at the top, you can find snow in the crevices and shadows.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-25 02:52:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Borg vs. Jedi </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-25 02:41:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Star Wars: Long time ago in a galaxy far far away. 
Star Trek: Semi-near future in our own Galaxy.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
