<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject5081</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-24 18:32:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yup I was excited to play horror games in VR but I don't think I can stomach them </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-24 11:40:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Same here. I screamed so loud like I never did in my life and I'm a grown ass man. 

I didn't finish the game after that scene. Too much tension :) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-22 15:17:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hey, thanks for saying you're sorry. 

I tried, and honestly, again, I have no problem in changing things - I really want only to help people understand and compare. If I missed something, or something is wrong, because we're both very invested in VR, please just help me correct it and make it perfect. I Think that instead of arguing with each other, you can help me polish the original write up. I'm really ok in being corrected, I just hate arguing :)

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-22 14:53:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Wow that's huge! Here comes the Matrix :) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-22 14:41:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You know what? I'm a reasonable person. If I am proven wrong, I've no problems in admitting it. 

What you did, instead of adding to the conversation with sources, or trying to correct the facts in a constructive way, was just plain arguing and attacking. And shame it's on me for continuing the conversation.

Both panels are from Samsung. The Oculus CV1 panel is not branded for their own reasons but it's same tech as the Vive one. The difference in size (stated even by iFixit in the range of less than 1.8mm) is not due only to form factors. 

So you could have just told me "Hey, there's actually a typo in your write-up, the ppi is slightly different, here are the sources! And thanks for taking the time of writing all up!". 

As a LPT, instead of criticising people, try to work together with them to improve the world around you - even if the improvement is really small. It's how you can actually make an impact - by helping people, not by cuddling in your own sense of entitlement.  

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-22 13:46:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Sure! Here's a very detailed analysis of HMDs screen latency: http://www.pcgamer.com/evaluating-vr-performance-and-latency-with-futuremarks-vrmark/ </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-22 13:44:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Exactly - different lenses yield different perceptions. But if you take the screen measurement for diagonal FOV, is the same. 

As I've stated in the beginning, the final, perceived effect is very subjective, and it's a sum of the factors. I'm only stating raw specs here, not passing judgement on which HMDs has the bigger perceived FOV. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-22 13:42:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  not very comprehensive and misinformative.

Dude. Seriously. Stop. 

My recap is the most comprehensive you can find so far, the one with least assumptions of all, and technically as accurate as one can be without physically accessing all the devices / blueprints. I work in tech and I'm fucking pissed off at people talking without real knowledge of what they say. Geez. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-22 09:58:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Raving fanboy </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-22 08:25:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If you actually read the article instead of just skimming you would notice that the first source states same panels for both. 

Same as the second - in the written article it states same panels, only in the recap column it gives one AMOLED and another one OLED. 

Plus honestly I took the time to write a comprehensive recap, checking sources and facts, and here I am arguing with strangers on the internet because X is better than Y. The perception of things is relative even for the same facts. Even if FOV by degrees is the same the lenses make the Vive perceived FOV bigger in my opinion. But that's not how you write things, not by opinions. 

I have a Vive and am happy with it, I love it. I wrote this because I was tired of reading 'Oculus is crap lolz', and because I wanted to explain why PSVR's quality might be good even tho on paper it starts with some GPU power handicaps. 

But no, people don't want analysis, they want to give in their confirmation bias. So be it.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-21 22:39:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yes. 

Source 1: http://www.pcgamer.com/tested-oculus-rift-vs-htc-vive-pre/

Source 2: http://arstechnica.com/gaming/2016/04/the-ars-vr-headset-showdown-oculus-rift-vs-htc-vive/ 

Source 3: http://www.flatpanelshd.com/review.php?subaction=showfull id=1467015168


 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-21 22:32:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Wow I didn't know that. Thanks, TIL

will correct the post accordingly. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-21 18:45:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  Oculus Rift and HTC Vive use the same panel, manufactured by Samsung.

The perceived effect might be different due to design choices but the panle tech specs and resulting FOV are the same.

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> A detailed analysis of the available VR HMDs Tech Specs: VIVE vs Oculus Rift vs GEAR VR vs PlayStationVR. May the battle begin. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-21 15:17:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hi guys,

having noticed a lot of misinformation on the current HMDs available, I decided to clarify and collect all the points that make each HMD different from one another.

*Consider that the final quality of a VR experience is given by the sum of the parts. Having simply a better resolution or better FOV doesn't necessarily means better VR*

Let's get this started!

**SCREEN TECH SPECS**

*HTC Vive*: Samsung OLED 21601200 (10801200 per eye), ~447ppi, 110degrees FOV (diagonal measurement of screen) , 90Hz 

*Oculus Rift*: Not-branded, Samsung manufactured OLED 21601200 (10801200 per eye), ~456ppi, 110degrees FOV (diagonal measurement of screen), 90Hz

*PSVR*: OLED 19201080 (9601080 per eye), ~386ppi, 100degrees, 120Hz (60Hz reprojected)

*Gear VR* (with a Samsung Galaxy S7): AMOLED 25601440 (12801440 per eye), ~540ppi, 90degrees, 60Hz


Let's analyse the screen raw specs. While the GEAR VR with a Samsung Galaxy S7 has a higher pixel density and higher resolution, the final result is of lower quality then of any other headset, partly because of a smaller FOV, and mainly because the mobile GPU doesn't really render at the given resolution, but upscales two square low-res images. The resulting image is of lesser quality then any of the images displayed on the VIVE/Rift/PSVR.

Also, HTC Vive / Oculus Rift / GearVR all use RGBG PenTile screens, while PSVR uses FullRGB screens. It has been proved that RGBG PenTile screens have a more noticeable Screen Door Effect, which is less noticeable on a fullRGB screen - this could be part of the explanation of why people that tried PSVR said that screen quality was very high.


**LENSES**

 **GEAR VR** uses standard +30 DPT lenses, which are the lowest quality ones in this list. **HTC Vive** uses custom-made fresnel lenses. Fresnel lenses are lenses that are cut in a certain way to reduce weight - this is what makes the "rings" effect when you look at a bright object against a dark background in your Vive.

The **Oculus Rift** uses custom hybrid fresnel/normal lenses, to cut weight but reduce the ring effect. While this custom lens reduces the ring effect, it augments the God Ray effect and a general blurriness of the edges when looking at bright objects against a dark background. 

**PSVR** is the most interesting of all, as Sony has a great history of building optics. They use an advanced multi-element optics (from what we've seen so far) which highly reduces any God Ray / blurriness. We'll have to wait until it's out, but it might be the HMD with the best optics around.

--

**GPU Power**

Of course, this doesn't depend on the HMD but on the GPU you're using. This immediately cuts out the GEARVR from the competition, as the Samsung Galaxy S7 mobile GPU has 36.8 GFLOPS of graphic power - which is 0.0348 TFLOPS (TeraFLOPS). A comparison of raw computational power:

**GTX 970** Stock is 3.9 TFLOPS

**GTX 1080** Stock is 9 TFLOPS

**PS4** is 1.84 TFLOPS.

Now, I've been wondering how the hell will Sony run the HMD with "only" 1.84 TFLOPS. The answer lies in the lower Refresh rate, lower FOV, and a rendering technique which Sony patented in 2014 called "VARYING EFFECTIVE RESOLUTION BY SCREEN LOCATION BY ALTERING RASTERIZATION PARAMETERS" = something something **Foveated rendering**.

*(also, thanks to /u/nmezib: "Foveated rendering isn't "FOVeated rendering" because the name doesn't come from FOV (Field of View) but rather from "fovea," which is the center of the retina where image clarity is highest.")*

For you who don't know, foveated rendering means that the GPU is rendering only the part of the screen you're looking at, thus minimising the impact on GPU. This is Sony's best kept secret so far, but I believe once the PSVR will be out, this will be confirmed officially. It's also a very similar technique to the Forward Renderer of The Lab.

Also, let's look at Refresh Rate. Both the VIVE and the Oculus Rift state that 90Hz (or, FPS) is the sweet spot for high-quality VR - which means, no nausea. 

There is a scientific explanation for that. Your brain will perceive 60FPS motion around you as smooth and life-like. But to perceive your movement as life-like, you need 90Hz (FPS). 

So, 60FPS is really the entry barrier for looking at content, and 90 is the barrier for interacting with content.

HTC Vive and Oculus Rift both ask to hit the 90FPS mark immediately, and have as a fail-safe respectively Reprojection and Asynchronous TimeWarp. Which one of the two is better only time will tell, but ideally they are both only there as parachutes when for whatever reason you don't hit 90FPS.

PSVR goes in a different direction. It will use 60FPS as a baseline and re-project to 120. Honestly, this might work very well for "spectator mode", but I have my doubts on high-paced action games where the player needs to move much (anything like Longbow, Hover Junkers, etc). Time will tell!

--

**TRACKING SYSTEM**

Last but not least, the tracking system. Everyone that experiences RoomScale and tracked controllers knows that this kind of interaction is what makes VR a jump into the future instead of a mere head-tracked camera. Also, a perfect, 0ms Lag tracking system is what separates nausea-free VR from The Vomit Inducer Experience which is so far any other VR system.

The **Samsung GEAR VR** has no real tracking system; your head movement is tracked internally by the gyroscope+accelerometer of the phone, which incredibly results in an acceptable experience with ~20ms lag.

We all know that **HTC Vive** Lighthouse tracking is incredibly good, with sub-millimeter precision and  ~11ms Lag. This is done by using two light-emitting base stations, which we call Lighthouses, while all the sensors are placed on the HMD and controllers. This is hands down the best tracking method around from a technical standpoint, and we all know how cool is it.

The **Oculus Rift** uses a tracking method called "Constellation" (latency  ~13ms), which consists of external infrared tracking sensors which optically track specially designed VR devices. So it's basically the opposite of the Vive; at the moment of writing, Oculus users have one tacking camera for Front-facing experiences. Once Touch is gonna be out, two cameras will be needed for a 180 degrees front facing experience. 

Oculus stresses that 180 degrees is where devs should focus their effort, and this sparked the debate "Is the Rift capable of Room-Scale"? The answer is still not certain, but a quick Google search will yield positive results. Also, it is worth noting that SteamVR supports Oculus and Touch controllers, and apparently, Oculus version of RoomScale with two or three cameras. The quality of this version of RoomScale is yet to be known. 

**PSVR** uses the PSCamera and Move controllers. The Move Controllers are tracked light points. I wont go into the whole dissertation on how hard is to track light points this way, and lets just assume that Sony knows what theyre doing. So PSVR will be capable of 60Hz ~18ms tracking of controller/headset. Since its a single tracking point, probably its gonna be a front-facing experience only, or with limited 360 degrees turns. Bonus: your PS4 standard controller is tracked in VR as well.



**CONCLUSIONS**

From all of that, and personal preferences aside, we can clearly state that from a pure capabilities point of view the HTC Vive is the HMD with the widest range of features, and the PSVR is the one with the most smart tech built in. GearVR is the HMD for an entry level VR. Oculus Rift is the most polished one, but only time will tell if Touch will be on par with the Vive wands, and if the RoomScale capabilities will be as perfect as the Vive.

Gaming and console history taught me one thing: content is key. The fact that we have more than one HMD on more than one platform is a great thing for content; the more the merrier. 

Only time will tell which HMD is gonna be more successful than the others, but one thing is certain: VR is here, and is here to stay.

What a time to be alive!


*All the informations contained in this write-up are factual - which means, there's no opinion attached to it. I tried to verify all of them, but if you find anything wrong, please do provide the source for the correction and I will modify accordingly*

**EDIT: corrected the ppi measurement according to iFixit teardown of both headsets**

**EDIT 2: adjusted the FOV measurement**
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> How many Elite Dangerous players are here and will switch to NMS? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-14 18:08:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Bonus question: I play E:D in VR and that's the only thing that will (probably) keep me from switching...

.. But if NMS ever gets VR support, I think it's a done deal for me.

EDIT: If I had time, I'd play both, but there's only so much time in my day! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> I wish No Man's Sky will have (one day) VR support. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-08 20:31:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I've been following the NMS hype train since its start and I'm pretty sure I'll buy the game because I'm a space junkie and procedurally generated Open World Space exploration with retro pop sci-fi graphic style? Sign me up!

However...

How cool is to fly your ship in E:D? That feeling is priceless. If NMS was my most hyped game, I am now afraid I'm not gonna like it if it's gonna be 'only' 2D. 

VR is a drug.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> GTX970 and E:D - looking for the best settings </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-07 09:30:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hi guys,

Elite Dangerous is definitely one of the killer games for the Vive. I'm a space junkie, but playing E:D in VR with my HOTAS is just mind-blowing. I didn't play it before VR because I wanted to experience the full immersion immediately and I'm glad I did.

Now to the original question: what are your best settings for E:D? I tried modifying some of the VR High settings because it was running fine - I only get stutter in busy spaceports- but then tried supersampling and boy everything looks crispier (apparently the original SS/AA I'm Elite doesn't really make a difference). 

So before I push too hard, is there any Commander out there with my same GPU that tried all the possible configurations and finally found the perfect balance?

I will play with configs myself and report back so others might benefit from my tinkering! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> PSVR has 29 full games coming down the line. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-16 12:39:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'll admit, I was a bit envious when I checked. 

Let's just hope that they're not gonna be all exclusives.

EDIT: here's the list: http://www.roadtovr.com/over-20-psvr-games-sony-showing-at-e3-heres-the-full-list/ </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> For me, traditional locomotion using a gamepad breaks immersion. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-15 15:33:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Before playing with the Vive, I thought that solutions like Virtuix Omni (treadmills) would be the answer to the locomotion for Open World games. But those solutions are bulky, expensive, and don't consider the various actions of crouching, dodging etc (I know there are some that will allow you to do so, but c'mon they're huge). 

I truly believe that Devs have to come up with creative solutions, like EdgeWalk by /u/SocialNetwooky or RIPmotion. Maybe a combination of the two.

But for me, having to play Fallout 4 and moving with a stick and not with my body would be a no-no.

For you? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> "I won't ever need more than 240GB Hard Drive". VR proved me wrong. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-15 09:25:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So I have only a 240 GB SSD for my PC. That's because with my limited time for playing games, I only have 2-3 games installed at all times usually to play through. I finish those, delete them, and make space for the next ones.

But then, VR happened.

I've more than 30 games/experiences installed on my PC, and only 5 GB left. 

Time to finish Batman: AK to make a bit of space, and to buy a 1TB 7200 RPM secondary drive... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> On the GPU requirements for VR in the short-to-mid term. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-13 09:50:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I have a MSI GTX970 Twin Frozr V with a Steam VR Test score of 8.6 (non-overclocked).

I can play every latest AAA title (The Witcher3, Batman:AK etc) with everything or close to everything set to Ultra @ 1080p 60FPS.

So far the only noticeable frame drops in VR have been in PoolNationVR (I can only play in Medium) and in the last mission of House of the Dying Sun (everything set to Ultra, AA8x).

I was thinking that maybe I will upgrade GPU around Christmas time. I thought to spend on a GTX980, then saw some benchmarks (I know it's early but) and decided, maybe a 1070.

Then AMD released the low-price great-spec card. And I started to think that yes, VR doesn't support SLI (yet), but maybe in the future it will, with one card per eye. 

Which means I might simply need another 970, until a next-gen headset is revealed with higher resolution (my guesstimate is at least 18 months from now, not for lack of quality screens but GPU power in the market).

What are your thoughts?


 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Played House of the Dying Sun. Now I want a proper HOTAS, but... </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-10 09:29:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So, HOTDS is a GREAT GAME. It's the best Early Access I've seen so far, and a super experience - piloting a ship in space? I'm sold.

I have an old, cheap HOTAS, and since the game supports binding, I spent the time to configure it and HO-LEE CRAP. I'm Captain Adama in my Viper. 

After having played half of the game, I went on Amazon to purchase a proper HOTAS (I can only imagine E:D in VR, or maybe - fingers crossed! - No Men's Sky). I was about to purchase a X52, but then I stopped. And you should wait too.

Because in 6/12 months, I'm SURE someone will com out with tracked controllers, HOTAS, the whole shenanigans. So you'll always see them in VR. 

The phrase I'm muttering the most lately is, What a time to be alive!

**tl;dr**: wait to buy HOTAS/wheels, as surely there'll be tracked versions soon! And buy House of the Dying Sun if you're into Space Dogfighting.

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Anyone uses Cortana to open SteamVR? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-09 15:06:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm in the office so I cannot test any shortcut and I'm a noob with Windows. Is there any way to launch SteamVR by using Cortana?

So I can show off and say, "Cortana, launch the Matrix"

:)
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Poor Nation VR - Performance thread </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-06 20:20:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hi guys,

just wanted to collect in one thread all the performance discussion around PoolNation VR. It seems so far the most demanding game out for VR.

I know it still needs "optimisation" and the devs are working on improvements every moment.

For me, I cannot play at higher than MEDIUM (with reprojection on). If I go on High I have serious stuttering and ULTRA is not playable.

my system:

- MSI GTX970 Twin Frozr V
- Intel i5 6400 3.2 Ghz
- 16GB DDR4 RAM
- SSD

Is that on par with the other people around here? 

See you later for a game of pool ;)



 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> VR is like diving [thoughts on first-gen VR] </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-01 13:27:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> There is an interesting conversation going on over /r/pcgaming : click [here](https://www.reddit.com/r/pcgaming/comments/4lx82u/if_youre_thinking_of_getting_into_vr_please_dont/)

Where people are going against Oculus (I understand why).

But, many "hardcore gamers" are still bashing the VR movement right now, because they are asking "can I play DOOM" and similar. Which is totally understandable.

Without entering the discussion, I came up with a simile and I wanted to share it.

VR is like diving, or space exploration. You need to strap yourself in plastic, wear a bulky thing on you, use other devices to interact with the environment. And much like diving, your FOV is restricted and your movements are limited, and things get blurry plenty of the time.

But the reward is to be there, in worlds you couldn't touch otherwise.

And much alike the first explorers, our suits are bulkier, our tech is limited; but our hearts are bigger and our minds travel afar, to push boundaries forward, for the love of exploration.
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Vive Demo night tonight for small group of people. Suggestions accepted! </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-31 12:32:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hi guys,

I've been demoing my Vive to quite a few people since I got it, but tonight it's gonna be my first group (4-5 people). 

So far I've demoed it to people who were not gamers nor tech savvy, so I went to the full tutorial FOR EVERY SINGLE ONE, and acted as a human chaperone to protect my TV, then put them into theBlu (which is mind-blowing). 

A request I've had is "I want to float into space" and even tho the solar system in the Lab is pretty cool, I'd like something more. Irrational Exuberance might cut it even tho might freak out some people. Suggestions welcome.

There is only one hard-core gamer tonight, so with him I'll skip the tutorial (he tried the Vive briefly) and put him into Space Pirate Traning, but as last user because it's gonna get sweaty.

That's my plan! how do you handle group demos? 

**EDIT: the demo night was good! People had fun, and wanted to try different things. As soon as they get the hang of it, I've noticed that people want interactivity - so it was tutorial first, the Blu second, and then Job Simulator. Two people tried and loved Unseen Diplomacy, and if there was more time, I am sure they would have tried everything (but Brookhaven Experiment ;).

Definitely going to get a VR cover for demo nights, and I need to reposition one lighthouse because we found a blinds spot.

Overall, I can say that introducing people to VR is part of the fun of being an early adopter! 

Bonus image of my Vive presentation pre-demo: http://imgur.com/728KbE7

Thank you all for the suggestions!**

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Cognitive Implications of Widespread Virtual Reality </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-27 14:46:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Cannot open the keyboard in VR anymore. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-27 14:35:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hi guys,

when I'm in Steam VR, and I try to search for anything, I cannot summon the keyboard anymore by squeezing the controller. I managed to do it just fine until yesterday. Random problems are the hardest to fix, but if any of you stumbled upon it and fixed it - well, any help is appreciated!

thanks!

**EDIT: Ok, so I opted-out of the Steam Beta (not the VR beta, the normal client beta! I didn't think about that), and after their reinstall, everything works fine! Hope that might work for you guys!** </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Two days in the Vive. I've got some questions. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-26 10:50:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hi guys,

I'll skip over the fact that this is the most incredible tech I've ever tried in my life (and I work for a tech company!), that AltspaceVR is a uber-cyberpunk experience, that my wife who is a tech luddite spent one afternoon giggling while flipping bacon in Job Simulator and telling me "just one more order and I'll exit" - let's go straight to the questions, since I didn't really skip the rest :)

- I connected my iPhone with the Vive. I get notifications but can't act on them. I am confident it's an iOS limitation but wanted to double check with Android users: can you reply to text messages while in VR?

- My playspace is currently 3.5meters x 2.9 meters. Lighthouses are ~5 meters apart. I have more space and can actually go 4x4.5 meters but this will give me a 6meters distance between the lighthouses. I know they can support it but am worried about tracking quality, so any real life experience would be appreciated.

- Is there any other Vive Spaces (like Museum etc)? I can't seem to find any.

- If you want to hang out in AltspaceVR (not right now!) come find me! I'll gladly say hello.

I'm very happy to be part of the early adopters of this incredible technology. The future is now guys, and it's up to us to spread the word! :)

bonus anecdote: I was in AltspaceVR yesterday and more than one guy asked me why I had "things coming out of my hands". They were my controllers. The guy owned a Oculus. He had no clue about the VIVE. More advertising for this might be good...

**EDIT: also, I wanted to buy different-colored wrist straps, so I can 1) easily identify right and left hand and 2) substitute the flimsy bundled ones. Any suggestion for the brand / direct Amazon UK link? Thanks!**






 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [Marketing] At the start of my promotional journey. Sharing my current situation, and asking for advice! </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-14 11:12:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hi guys,

After having finished my book 2 years ago, I never stopped writing, so finally I feel I have enough content ready to start promoting myself (1 book; 1 novella + short stories; Poems; Ongoing book). 
My plan is to publish the novella first (september?), then the poems, then in January 2017 the full book, then maybe the short stories in spring.

I have a very good understanding of marketing thanks to my job experiences, but I'd like to hear from more experienced writers.

My aim will be to self pub - because the industry as I see it doesn't promote talent anymore but only looks out for the next YA movie deal. Cormac McCarthy would strugge to find an agent. That's my opinion.

Before I get obvious comments: Yes I do have a stellar cover designer, yes I paid good money to editors to have all of my soon-to-be-published material shine. 

Now I'm at the audience building stage.

I have only 300 followers on twitter (~~https://twitter.com/subject508182~~ http://twitter.com/dariowrites), and I hate following people there because then it becomes a marketing masturbation party (buy my book! No! Buy mine! No! Buy mine! No!).
I use twitter to post aphorisms and links to my website (every time I post new content). It doesn't yield much and I'm willingly to change my strategy here, but honestly I don't see much twitter potential for those things.

I have a website (~~www.deadmennaked.com~~ www.dariowrites.com) where I am posting an ongoing thriller/news about my work when it gets published somewhere. The website has a very small following (40 trustful readers, plus the random ones, for a total avg of 150 visits per month since its opening in January). 

I didn't publicise it so far because I didn't have much content on it. Now that I'm in the middle of the story, I'm ready to publicise it (so people who arrive at the website will actually have more to read). I still have to understand how to best advertise it. Thoughts?

I am sending short stories out to Literary Magazines. So far I've been published in 3, with a fourth upcoming in May (yay! Ego boost!). I will keep writing shorts and trying LitMag because it's good for recognition (more than exposure I think). 

Yesterday I opened a Facebook page (www.Facebook.com/dariowrites). As I don't have a personal Facebook profile, I will have to manually tell people about it. Ideally I'd use the Facebook page as main outlet to build an audience (or potential audience), while linking my main website, and using twitter to blast out thoughts. How is still an ongoing question for me.

So my questions are really to the successful guys here (/u/michaelJsullivan, I'll wait for you :)). How did you promote in the start? I mean, practically, how did you get your facebook/twitter/website out there? did you go on other websites and comment? Did you asked friends to promote you?

Every suggestion helps guys. I've been on /r/writing for 3 years now, I learned a lot, I hopefully shared good insights, and if I haven't been active lately is because I wrote a shit-ton. 

Thanks for the time and help you're gonna give me, and sorry about the long post!

Dario.

(And yes, that's my real name)

**EDIT: Took immediately /u/jimhodgson 's advice and consolidated my brand. Thanks.**
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> A short story just got published [and I'm happy for a totally different reason] </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-25 15:37:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> ISIS-related message displayed by The Rock Radio (Cork City) </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-09-27 08:16:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Pitch Wars - where the unpublished author is mentored by a published one to win an agent. DEADLINE IS TODAY. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-08-17 14:12:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hi guys,

I discovered this yesterday. Might be useful for some of us. 

Here's the link: http://www.brenda-drake.com/2015/08/pitch-wars-submission-window-enter-now/

Happy submitting!

**NOTE: DEADLINE IS 11:59pm EDT today, 17th of August** </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> To Kane or not to Kane? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-08-06 12:52:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Simple as that guys. I can buy him in the next few GWs... but what if he jut blows everything away? Ownership is almost at 40%...

my team, for reference:

Boruc - Adrian

Francis - Prodl - Bellerin - Cedric - Huth

Walcott - Lens - Sterling - Depay - Mane'

Sakho - Rooney - Benteke


 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Is it normal not to receive feedback after a full MS request? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-08-04 08:55:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hey! Long time no see, r/writing! 

I've finally received the answer from the 2 agents that requested my full MS (4 months ago! Super quick market, huh?).

Negative.

Apart from the normal feeling of rejection, what really sets me off is that neither one of the 2 agents provided a feedback on the book. Just a "Sorry, we read it with interest, not for us". Heck, I've got better rejections to queries! 

I pinged the first agent and he never replied.
I pinged the second agent today, ~~so let's see~~ and she's been very nice in replying and giving a couple of pointers about why she didn't feel the right girl for the job.

I understand they're busy and all. But in my job, I reply to every single email I receive, even with just a one-liner - it's called being professional.

What is your experience? Did you get your feedback after a full request?

Thanks!

UPDATE: updated the second agent's reply. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Be sure to follow BookExpoAmerica! </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-29 13:59:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hi guys, 

the expo is HUGE and a lot of authors/agents are there.

here's the official link http://www.bookexpoamerica.com

There's a trending hashtag on Twitter #BEA15

Also, there's the official app. You can at least see who said what and so on. It's a nice insight into the "publishing world", and who knows, maybe you'll get the chance to virtually know some agents.... :) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Let's practice here for #PitMad [June 4th 2015] </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-22 10:07:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hi guys,

as per subject. Post you 140 characters elevator pitch for your novel, and let's polish it to have it ready for #PitMad.

Some pointers: you can also add your genre tag to help agents navigate it. Here are some of the most used ones:

- #YA - Young Adult
- #MG - Middle Grade
- #SFF - Science Fiction/Fantasy
- #F - Fantasy
- #LIT - Literary
- #UF - Urban Fantasy
- #MR - Magical Realism

and so on.



I'll post my elevator pitch here as soon as I'll figure it out! :)

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Do you know new agents that are building up their list? Post them here. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-21 15:35:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> As per subject. I will update every 24 hours the body of the post with the most relevant informations.

Here are some of the agents that are new to the gig / building their list:

[**- Eve Porinchak**, Jill Corcoran Literary](http://jillcorcoranliteraryagency.com/whowearejclit/)

[**- Lena Yarbrough**, InkWell Management](http://inkwellmanagement.com/staff/lena-yarbrough)

[**- Writer's Digest Updated list of New agents**](http://www.writersdigest.com/editor-blogs/guide-to-literary-agents/new-agency-alerts), thanks to /u/Luna_LoveWell ! 

[**- Cara Mannion**, Harold Ober Agency](http://www.haroldober.com/HOB-contacts.htm) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Nudging an Agent: The Know-how </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-21 15:19:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Here's the full article from QueryTracker: http://querytracker.blogspot.ie/2010/01/nudging-know-how.html

The highlights:

NEVER nudge on a Query.

3 Months for a Partial.

6 months for a full.

Of course those are guidelines (and far too long, in my opinion). 

What is your experience? Are you an author or an agent? Speak out. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> State of my query. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-21 15:13:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hi guys.

So far I've queried 43 agents. 12 of those 43 rejected my query (one actually did not reject, but so much time has passed I've lost hopes).

2 agents have my full manuscript - one has had it for two months, the other for 2 weeks.

1 Agent has a partial (50 Pages) since one month.

I'm biting my nails and composing drafts to those agents. "Dear agent. I hope you read my book and liked it. Why didn't you reply?". Cancel. Click.

"Dear agent. You have my 50 pages in your hand since one month. My 12yo son reads much quicker than you. Sincerely." Cancel.

"Dear agent. I am in incredible pain here. The urge to nudge is crazy. Do you realize that you have such power on us poor authors? Is your heart black and evil, to have you choose this job only to have that power on people? Looking forward to your multi-million offer."

I know I'm even "lucky" to have 3 requests. But man, the wait is crazy.

I'll share my basic query letter in a next post. I suggest you do the same.

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> New Subreddit for authors who are in the query process [/r/queryhell] </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-21 14:44:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hi guys,

being myself in the Query process for my book, I know how dreadful is the feeling that accompanies the process.

Some of the questions I've had in my mind:

- Is my Query Letter good enough?
- How do I know that's the right agent?
- Should I nudge after the query? (NO!)
- Well, should I nudge for a partial or full request?
- What are some new agents that are open to queries?

And many many more. I know there are websites and services that help authors with those questions, but there's nothing like reddit.

So I thought to found  /r/queryhell. It's a place for all of us who are querying and waiting. And waiting. And waiting.

We can share resources, opinions, help each other with the queries and support each other in the (very, very) long time from the submission of a query to the offer of representation.

I just started it, and immediately came here to give the good news. I will start posting useful things in the next few days (new agents accepting queries, articles etc) but I would love for it to be a community effort.

I hope you'll like it guys, and I hope we'll help each other there!


 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Manifesto </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-21 14:35:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> We believe that writing is not a hobby. 
Writing is a call. 

It is the blood that burns and the soul that crumbles and gets distilled in words. 
It is the solitary scanner upon the path of the souls. 

We believe there's no right amount of words for a book, but there's only just enough words to tell a story truthfully. 

We believe that our job is to write; to write truthfully, to write beautifully, to write without adverbs possibly. 

We believe that with the right story and the right writing and the right agent, our book will see the light. 


 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> You write to please yourself. You write for the joy of writing. And then your public reads you and it begins to gather around. [An Interview with Ray Bradbury] </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-11 15:34:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Can I have different agents for different countries? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-07 11:44:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hi guys,

I'd like trad-pub writers to help me out here. 

If I sign with an agent in the US, am I free to sign with another agency in the UK? Canada? Australia? Etc etc?

I suppose it depends from the contract you sign, but I'd like to know from more experienced writers what is the norm / best practices. 

Thank you in advance!  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [Discussion] The art of querying </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-17 10:55:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hi guys,

I wanted to talk about queries. I'm myself in the middle of the query process. To kick off the discussion around query styles, timing etc, I'll start by outlining where I am at.

First and foremost, I am not *heavily* querying for 2 main reasons:

1. I am *so* naive I am handpicking agents and agencies, hoping to find my perfect agent match * la Charlie Runkle*
2. I am not sure the same query works for every agency.

To expand on point 2: what works for Agency A won't work for Agency B. If you have a complex novel, which crosses over different genres, then you might have different way of pitching it.

To me it resolved (so far) in 3 types of queries' tone:

- **Lighthearted:** That's the first type I sent out to certain agencies. It follows the classic query structure - Introduction, synopsis, bio, closing paragraph. It looks more like a business letter than everything, with a more light tone of the prose to align with the agency and highlight that part of the novel.

- **Philosophical:** As my book touches various philosophical topics, I highlighted that part more. Using the same classical structure, I simply added to the synopsis my comments on the meaning of the parts of the book - an "extended version". Tone is business-as-usual, but it steers more towards literary, with accent on more thought-heavy parts of the novel.

- **Same-as-book:** If you're like me and read tons of thousands of queries and agents' advice, you know that one thing the agents ask for is to be able to get the book from the query. That's very hard of course - we wrote an entire book, now we've to cram it on one page. So I wrote the query with a more "experimental" angle. I wrote it with the same prose and pace of the book. It's more "literary" than a business letter, but I point this out at the very end - you wanted to see my book's style? Here ya go.

So far I've sent **12 queries in 2 months**. 5 of them "lighthearted", 2 of them "Philosophical", and 5 of them "Same-as-book". 

**2 rejections and 1 request of full manuscript so far.** Silence from the other agencies. First deadlines for "if you don't hear back from us then we're not interested" ends at the beginning of May.

So, that's me at the moment. I might develop other queries for other styles.

But let's talk about *you!*

How is your query process? Do you have different queries for different agents? Do you think a query should be "Classic" or are you getting creative with it?

And, for published authors: How was your query process? How long before you had in your hands the "perfect query" which eventually led to agent - publication?

Thanks, and sorry for the long post :)


 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [Advice] How long before an agent replies after having requested your manuscript? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-17 10:38:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hi guys,

Straightforward: I have an agent from a top-notch agency who has my manuscript. It's been in his hands for almost a month. 

I know it's not much. I know I should just patiently wait (and send out more queries, which never hurts).

But I am human, for chrissake. I am tempted to give a nudge to ask if he's liking it. Or something.

Thoughts? Advice?

Thanks! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Book Exchange \o </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-16 11:01:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> I need to 3D print a ring guard which full encases the ring. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-11 18:28:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hi guys!

I'm very very new to 3d print. I have a Silver ring which is a tad large.

I'd like to "encase" it into another ring - silicone, metal, you name it. Ideally, something I can easily swap in-out if I need, but it's not a priority.

I've seen ring guards on amazon but I wanted a full circle encase, with borders and whatnot - something that "shows" behind/around the ring.

I don't know if I explained myself well, but if some of you understood, can you help me figure out what would the best path to get one be?

many many thanks! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [WP] You are the first human being to receive a full body transplant. Your head will be implanted on a new body. When you wake up, you're not yourself anymore; the old owner of the body actually feels the new face is weird. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-10 15:14:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> inspired by np.reddit.com/r/technology/comments/323adn/30yearold_russian_man_valery_spiridonov_will/ </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> "I'm convinced that epublishing is another tech bubble, and that it will burst within the next 18 months." </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-10 14:44:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> I love you guys. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-02 19:11:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Should I remove my old first work from iBooks? [advice request] </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-31 16:37:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hi guys,

I have a short Novella self-published in some of the digital marketplaces (not Amazon, tho). 

I self-pubbed it some years ago, for free. It's 52 pages written when I was 20 in my mother-tongue language, and it's been downloaded 5000 times. The 2 reviews are very positive and it has an average score of 3.5 stars. 

I am now writing in English and the style is very different (and not just because of the language difference - also because I am a much more mature writer).

As I am pursuing the trad-pub route, should I remove this old piece of work? I don't recognize myself in it anymore honestly, but it gives me right as a Goodreads author - and kind of a small validation for future works. Maybe. I'm not sure.

What would you do?

Thanks!

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> "Somehow, to be helpful, an editor has to embody authority yet not become possessive or controlling." </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-30 12:57:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Some questions about Marketing, for Career Authors </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-10 17:17:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hi guys,

as per subject - this is really aimed at Pro Fiction Writers who marketed themselves (especially in the beginning of a trad-pub deal and/or at the beginning of their -successful- self-pub career). 

I will just shoot the questions here.

- What did you find useful to do (if anything) to market your book BEFORE its publication?

- How did you tackle previews and reviews, apart from the ones handled by your agent/publisher?

- Did you market *yourself* as well? Like social media, websites etc. Did you find it useful?

- Can you share some tips tricks? 


I appreciate all the kind replies you will want to leave here.


 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [QUESTION] Does ayahuasca consumption makes people more sensible to other substances? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-01 20:50:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hi guys,

I noticed that since I had ayahuasca I am more sensitive to other substances - even normal Marijuana has a "deeper" effect on my perceived self - It is easier to feel my consciousness expanding and recall the ayahuasca experience.

Is there any correlation between ayahuasca usage and permanent or semi-permanent sensibility to other mind-altering substances? If so, is it a change in brain chemistry (i.e. are there studies on it?) or it's a *perceptive* change (which, imho, is the same)?

Thanks to all of you who will share their insights!

edit: a word </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Do you guys know about the new Time And Oak product? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-09 15:56:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Here is their website: http://timeandoak.com

I was just wondering if any of you tried it / knows about it. The reviews on their website are ecstatic but of course I cannot possibly trust them all :)

As soon as I've understood how those things work I ordered their 5 flavor pack. Will keep you posted but if any of you already experienced it... please share! 

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [Request] What are the chances (for an aspiring author) of actually getting published? {x-post from /r/writing} </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-16 14:04:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> http://np.reddit.com/r/writing/comments/2sllge/what_are_the_chances_of_actually_getting_published/

Excluding the self-pub route, what would be the chances for an aspiring author to score a traditional contract?

Bonus question: What are the chances of getting published AND make a living out of it?

Thanks for your insight guys! This might solve a recurring question on that subreddit :) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Questions about dialogue structures. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-07 12:05:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hi fellas,

straight to the point: I am having some issues with dialogues. Not heavy ones, I just can't seem to decide which dialogue style would suit me best. So I'm asking your opinion as skilled readers: which style of dialogue do you prefer the most? Examples:

**Standard:**

"Hey you", said Joe. "Didn't see you there. How are you?"

"Not bad" replied Jane. "I always come here on Saturdays, haven't you noticed?"

"I thought it was only a one off," replied Joe.

"Nope. Here's the best to buy candies."

.

**Semicolon** (sorry about the Reddit Formatting):

- Hey you. Didn't see you there, Jane.
- Hi Joe. Why, I always come here on Saturdays.
- Oh, I thought it was just a one-off.
- No, that's my favourite place to bury bodies.

.

**McCharty/Bukowskian:**

Hey you, Jane.

Hey Joe. Long time no see.

Didn't see you, in fact. Whatcha doing here?

I always come here.

I never saw you.

That's because you never pay attention when I blow the horn.


---

Of course, some of them will inspire different dialogue styles - but my aim is to have a very natural dialogue way, without getting in the reader's way. 

Do you guys have any preference? Do you perceive the style much different, or are confused by some?

Thanks for all of you who will want to reply! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Where can I buy products like Beyone Meat, Daya etc in Europe (online shopping)? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-12-30 13:04:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hi guys,

basically the title summarises. I live in EU and it's really hard to find Vegan brands. The only commercial ones are Viana, Quorn (non-vegan) and Linda McCartney (non-vegan).

I am always envious when I see US choices. Days cheese is not the best, but it's a nice alternative. And Beyond Meat looks incredible.

Any help for a fellow vegan?

thanks!

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Can someone help me to try the Rift DK2? [Request][Country: Ireland] </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-12-16 14:29:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hi guys

as per subject. I never tried a Rift and I'd love to. It's totally out of curiosity and passion for the VR world. 

I live in Ireland at the moment!

Thanks!

**EDIT: Wow, thanks for all the replies! I just logged in. Will PM the closest one, but thanks all of you for your kindness guys!** </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> I remember the days when there was no such thing as self-publishing. [a rant, probably] </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-12-11 15:12:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> And I remember a lot of people complaining about the "Dark powers" of the publishing houses (in music, literature, etc). People complaining that Publishing houses were keeping talents at bay, just to sell the writers that could make them money. In total honesty, I thought so myself. I was dreaming of a world were PH would have no saying.

Well, I live in this world. Now everyone can self-publish. Everyone can save some money to hire an editor, a graphic designer, and create a decent product to sell. Amazon et cetera are the distribution channel. A curated twitter account is a good marketing channel - better than the old "book readings" from unknown authors.

So I look around, and I am looking for the new Joyces, the new Wallaces, the new DeLillos; all I find, in a sea of mediocre-to-terrible stuff and Rule-34 Porn, is some honest guy who wrote some ok stuff - and for as much empathy as I might have for my fellow writer, it's not enough. I have a list of thousands of books to read, by incredible authors, and I know I will never read them all. So why should I stop for the ok things? I aim for the best. 

And the promise that a world without publishers would have been a better world fell short; and like a cheating lover, I go back to the publishing houses, to ask for their guidance to find something more than decent in the sea of self-publish.

*TL;DR I am not so sure that self-publishing unleashed creativity of lesser-commercial writers, heightening the emerging of indie-cool stories, but actually flooded the market with crap. And Publishing houses still hold the keys to the kingdom of "Good Stories".*

**EDIT: Thanks guys for your points of view! I was asleep in my timezone and am now reading/replying where I can. The shared opinion is that yes, there's a lot of crap, but also very nice little gems. So I guess really the problem lies down with Vanity from the writers, lack of curation for the finished products, and lack of curated "lists" (reviews are not to be trusted unless they're many, many...many) by sub-genre that can help us navigate this monstrous sea of words.**
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [RMT] Hi guys, thinking of changing some players. Currently 80 points behind :( </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-11-25 16:16:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> London veggies, what's your favourite restaurant in the city? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-11-09 11:51:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hey guys!

I'm gonna spend my birthday in London with my wife and a couple of best friends. Before booking any restaurant, I thought I might ask Reddit for some tips... What is your favourite place?

thank you all!
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> I am at the end of my novel and I need advice from fellow writers. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-10-22 15:19:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hi guys,

It's been a while since I posted something here. I am at the end of my novel (technically the second, but it's really the first as I am writing after 10 years). I am probably anywhere between 5 to 20k words away from the "Grand Finale". 

I have the outline of the ending, the "message" I'd like to send and so on. But I feel that, to really understand and write this last part, I have to re-read everything I wrote (which will inevitably turning into editing). 

This is because the characters evolved (and devolved!) in the course of the 75000 words I wrote, and now I feel the urge to go back, re-shape them with what I know, and finally conclude the thing. Looking back, this is how I actually wrote the ending of my first novelette.

What would be your advice? Should I endure, resist the urge, and write the ending, leaving space for the final editing, or should I let the temptation win, start the first-editing, and then write the ending??

I know that any advice is purely personal - but that's what I am looking for; experience.

Thanks for all your help!

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The search for the perfect burrito. [x-post from r/vegan] </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-08-19 12:23:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I am usually a very good cook. I am creative, you see. I can make up amazing dishes and entertain my guests with A-grade appetisers. I know my wine as well; there won't be anything but the perfect glass together with your meal.


I see a dish, taste a flavour; they compose themselves, easily, in my mouth, without having to taste anything. I copy chefs, make their recipes better.


I have trained myself, in the coming of age, to the mastery of vegetarian cuisine, then vegan; no one of my guests ever felt the need of meat, and wondered at how did I make their mouth feel this.


But Burritos.


Seriously. I thought I was baking a kickass lil-donkey, until a wicked night of 2 years ago. I was brought by some friends to the magic place where burritos are born from Angel's laughters. "El Farolito" in the Mission, San Francisco. For you that live in the bay area, just drop everything you're doing and go there to have one.


Even if they are not vegan, their vegetarian option made me rethink my whole burrito-life.


Since that, I have been miserable. All my attempts have failed; my gift has gone. It seems like my rice is not as fluffy, my veggies not as grilled, like their released the sun they've used to grow. My guacamole, once exposed with pride, is put to shame, like a commercial counterpart, to the chunkiness of El Farolito. I am lost in an endless journey, burrito after burrito, towards that juicy perfection, the one, only amazing burrito that I tasted in a midsummer's evening, that rejoiced my soul.


So, I am asking you, reddit: what is your best shot at a burrito? The bar is high. Vegan would be my first choice, but I am willingly to go vegetarian for this one. Shameful, I know.


**tl;dr - tasted the best burrito of my life, I'm spending countless evenings trying to replicate it. Help me with you best recipe!** </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The search for the perfect burrito. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-08-19 12:09:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I am usually a very good cook. I am creative, you see. I can make up amazing dishes and entertain my guests with A-grade appetisers. I know my wine as well; there won't be anything but the perfect glass together with your meal.

I see a dish, taste a flavour; they compose themselves, easily, in my mouth, without having to taste anything. I copy chefs, make their recipes better.

I have trained myself, in the coming of age, to the mastery of vegetarian cuisine, then vegan; no one of my guests ever felt the need of meat, and wondered at how did I make their mouth feel this.

But Burritos. 

Seriously. I thought I was baking a kickass lil-donkey, until a wicked night of 2 years ago. I was brought by some friends to the magic place where burritos are born from Angel's laughters. "El Farolito" in the Mission, San Francisco. For you that live in the bay area, just drop everything you're doing and go there to have one. 

Even if they are not vegan, their vegetarian option made me rethink my whole burrito-life.

Since that, I have been miserable. All my attempts have failed; my gift has gone. It seems like my rice is not as fluffy, my veggies not as grilled, like their released the sun they've used to grow. My guacamole, once exposed with pride, is put to shame, like a commercial counterpart, to the chunkiness of El Farolito. I am lost in an endless journey, burrito after burrito, towards that juicy perfection, the one, only amazing burrito that I tasted in a midsummer's evening, that rejoiced my soul.

So, I am asking you, reddit: what is your best shot at a burrito? The bar is high. Vegan would be my first choice, but I am willingly to go vegetarian for this one. Shameful, I know.

**tl;dr - tasted the best burrito of my life, I'm spending countless evenings trying to replicate it. Help me with you best recipe!**  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [ADVICE NEEDED] Finger tattoo. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-08-04 16:14:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hi guys,

what is your opinion on fingers' tattoos? There is an arabic word which I really want to have tattooed on my ring finger but my artist was against it as he said Fingers tattoos go bad very easily. 

What is your experience/suggestion? Should I give up this idea?

Thanks!

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Analysis of a scene from a screenplay perspective. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-08-01 11:10:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> There are evenings where I can write an immortal poem. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-07-31 00:58:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> But the majority of them, I spend talking with people that have a better understanding of the universe than me, but cannot put it in words.
Thanks, you enlightened beings. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> People of Reddit, what made the last wedding you were invited to absolutely awesome? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-07-30 18:34:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I am getting married in a year's time and don't want to get trapped by the cliche weddings were people don't have fun. What is some things you've seen at a marriage you were invited / hosted that made the guests go "wow!!!"? 

**EDIT: Thanks for the early commenters, your advice is appreciated! I will check this back in a couple of hours!!** </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> SCRIVENER 20% Off for /r/writing !! </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-07-24 16:09:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> **UPDATE: Hey guys! Some Apple users noted that Scrivener is currently 50% off on the Mac App Store. This apparently does not apply to all the countries but only some. I suggest you check there first if you have a Mac!**


*I highly encourage linking this post in your favourite sub about writing. This way more people can enjoy the love! Please keep reference to this original post if you can so that our own /r/writing gets credit for it :)*

Hey guys,

I reached out the guys behind Scrivener, the famous software that many of us use/want to use.

They have been incredibly happy to hear there's so much love for their software, so much that implemented a nice 20% discount! I have no informations on how long this will stay in place. Here are their words:

Hello XXX,
We've implemented a 20% discount coupon code for the Reddit community. If
they now go to our web-store www.getscrivener.com and type REDDIT into the
obvious coupon code field after selecting their Scrivener 2.x for Mac OS X or
Scrivener for Windows *regular* licence, they will then benefit from a 20%
discount.

So I would suggest to all of you guys that are interested to avail of this! They also commented on their upcoming iOS app:

We're still working incredibly hard on our Scrivener for iOS release. We'd
love to get it out this year, but our schedule appears to be drifting into
2015. It's shaping up nicely though. ;-)

I hope the /r/writing community will appreciate that! :)


**EDIT - I don't work for/am affiliate in any way with the product Scrivener and the company Literature and Latte behind it. I just wanted to share the love for a product which I use extensively and believe is a great tool for writers.**

**EDIT 2: I am glad you guys appreciated that!** </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The Writer toolbox </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-07-22 14:12:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Seems obvious, but the device and the tools that you physically use to write have to be chosen according to your needs. A writer is not only the tormented artist who sits in a caf with his Mac and scribbles over a napkin. A writer can be a journalist, a tech writer, an instructional designer, a professor. Here is a list of some of the most used tools.

**LAPTOPS   DESKTOPS** - any will do, but here are some favourites:

*MacBooks (Air, Pro)* - lightweight, powerful, has access to some Mac-only tools. Lit-up keyboard. Expensive.
*Chromebooks* - lightweight, relatively inexpensive. The OS is a bit limiting and forces the use of Google Docs. There are guides on how to install Linux on them.

**SOFTWARE**

*Scrivener*

Made by a writer, this tool acts as a repository of all the content (scenes, ideas, research material, pictures etc). It is also very useful for outlining and plotting. There is a bit of learning curve and the interface can be daunting, but it is a star software. Two downsides so far: Mac Only, and lack of syncing with mobile devices as there is no App available.
Link here: www.literatureandlatte.com/scrivener.php

*Emacs*

Extensible, customisable text editor. It has a steep learning curve but it is highly customisable if you know how to get your hands dirty with code. It can handle document-specific dictionaries (not on a project level) which is useful when world-building. Open source.
Link here: http://www.gnu.org/software/emacs/


*nvALT (Notational Velocity)*

This is a great note-taking software. Simple and immediate. nvALT has an unusual interface. It only has three sections: A search line, a list of your notes, and an editing box. To create or find a note, you type in the search field and it narrows down the displayed notes as you type. Press ENTER to create a new note with whatever title you've typed in. The cursor moves to the editing window and you can start typing your note. It saves automatically. You can just open it (with a hotkey), enter your new note, and quit. Each note is saved as a separate text file in whatever folder you've set it to sync to. You can access and edit them in any program that will edit plain text.
Its simplicity and plain-text format allow the usage with any word processor. Mac Only.Link here: http://notational.net


*Notepad++*

Free notepad app. A step above the stock Notepad/Notes app, with multi-language environment, customisable GUI, Search/Replace, bookmark. Windows Only. 
Link here: http://notepad-plus-plus.org/download/v6.6.7.html


*Mac Notes App*

The stock notes app on any Mac/iOs device. Plain text. It made in the list only because it has automatic syncing and back-up to the cloud.


*MS Word*

Probably the most famous basic word processor. Remember to save often and back up your data.



**BACKUP / SYNCING**

Ok, youve written 2000, 10000 words. Great! Did you remember to press save? Do you have a fort-knox level vault where you store physical copy of your work? It does not matter how much you write - just remember to save!


*DropBox*

Everyone loves DropBox. It is a cross-platform syncing service, which means you can use Mac and PC and mobile. It also has a web interface, which means you can access to your files from anywhere - internet connection required. Basically every software that saves a file can be synced with DropBox - just save your work in the DropBox folder and it will be uploaded in their cloud, and synced across your selected devices. 5GB Storage free, more if you invite friends. 
Link here: https://www.dropbox.com


*Google Drive*

Basically, DropBox, but made by Google. Highly integrated with Google Docs, it allows you to online open/modify a Google Doc. Multi-platform and with 15 GB free.Link here: https://drive.google.com/


*GIT*

If you know the computer world, you know git. GIT is a distributed revision control and source code management (SCM) system with an emphasis on speed, data integrity, and support for distributed, non-linear workflows. Mostly used to write software and keep track of its changes, it can be a great tool to use for Backup, syncing and version control. Multi-platform and open source.
Link here: http://git-scm.com


*CrashPlan*

Backup Backup Backup. Never lose it. Back it up. Have I said it enough? Back up. There are many online services for backup, but Crashplan is probably the most professional one. Link here: www.code42.com/CrashPlan


*External Backup*

If you have an external hard drive, use it as a failsafe. Remember to back up the data often, or use an automated software (like Time Machine on Mac).


**OTHER SOFTWARE**


*Aeon Timeline*

If you like to visually plan down your plot, this is a great tool. With Aeon, you can divide your timeline into logical groups, projects, or concurrent arcs. You can model the relationships between events and people, places and ideas. Aeon calculates people's ages for you. And you can link your events with research material such as external files or images that can be displayed inside the application. Mac and Windows.
Link here: http://www.scribblecode.com


*MindNode*

MindNode is a iOS app which help you with mental mapping. Useful when jotting down complex ideas and need to visualise the correlations.
Link here: https://itunes.apple.com/us/app/mindnode/id312220102?mt=8



**EDIT: Thanks guys for the replies! it's evening for me now, so I will re-login tomorrow morning and rewrite this post with your suggestions. Keep 'em coming!!**

**EDIT 2: Goodmorning! I re-wrote the list adding your suggestions. If you have more or want to change something, please let me know.**
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Different books, different styles; when the author is perceived as cheating on his audience. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-07-20 13:57:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hi guys,

this should be more a question than a statement maybe. 

Most of us like an author for different reasons - may it be because he creates world that we love, or has an incredible pace, an exquisite prose, or compelling characters. 

JK Rowling founded her success on *consistency*; HP stories are a known world to the reader, and people love to dive into known waters. It is a sure bet. Now she is writing different things, and she chose a pseudonym. 
Same did our old friend Stephen King; he, the master of horror, when ready to publish his fantasy novel, decided to do it under a nickname. 

So it is safe to assume that once established in a genre, a style, a writer gains followers and audience that like him for what it is.

How bad is for you when your favourite writer broke his/her familiarity with something different? Did you forgive him/her? Did you like them more because they were more "rounded", like the characters we all try to breathe life into?

Looking forward to your answers. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What is the best self-publishing route for a short stories collection? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-07-19 11:27:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hi guys,

I have a small collection of short stories that I would like to self-publish in order to get to a broader audience and obtain some feedback. 

What would be your suggestion? Would you go and use a broker like Smashwords to be on all ebook stores, or would you go Amazon only?

Thank you in advance for your replies! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Editor needed for short story (5k). </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-07-04 14:17:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hi guys,

I wrote a short story for a contest and I would love to have it edited by some pro (or wannabe pro). 

I can pay in Amazon gifts :) just name your price for 5k! 

Thanks!

**EDIT: thanks everyone who replied! I prefer sending the PDF out via email so everyone has a copy - instead of a Google doc. Having said so, I will create a shareable doc so I can send the link out to all of you that asked for editing. Thanks again!!** </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> People of reddit, would you like to have the Upvote/Downvote count visible again? Comment here! </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-06-19 14:09:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> As per title. I believe that seeing the Upvotes/downvotes is actually a neat feature that helps me understand how split people are on different topics, and also helps the reddiquette to be sane.

What is your thought, Redditors? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Meat vs Hands </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-06-18 12:29:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> New to vinyl - bad, low sound from existing setup - HELP! </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-06-11 14:34:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hi guys,

me and my SO decided to enter the vinyl world. Disclaimer: we're on a budget so we want to start small and build up.

We bought a turntable (Auna TT931).
We have active speakers (Bose Companion 3 Series II) that provide good sound (I know, they're not the best for vinyl, but that's it). They have JackInput.

Now, plugging the turntable directly to the speakers through RCAtoJack cable produces the sound, even though not the best one; volume is really low, and basses are cut out completely. 

Being the speakers active, I supposedly thought I needed a Pre-Amp to pump the sound up. 
Wrong. 
The PreAmp jumps the volume up, but then I have a constant static buzz, and crackles, and when the music starts to get more intense, distortions and bad sound.

I know there are millions of things, and I know that the perfect setup would be GreatTurntable+PhonoPreAmp+Amp+PassiveSpeakers... but for the moment, do you have any suggestion? Do I have to ditch everything and start again?

Any help will be appreciated!

thank you all!

**EDIT: So I run some other tests. I discovered my Turntable does not need grounding, and on the manual it says "Just plug it to your Amplifier+Speakers". Which in my mind means it does not need a PreAmp.**

**With the current setup, Turntable + Active Speakers, I get a sound just passable, not even decent.
If I add the PreAmp (grounded), I get a boost in the sound, but a loud constant hum, and cracking noise as soon as the song that's plain goes a bit up in volume.
I tried with smaller, different speakers (active) and the result is more or less the same. I came to the conclusion that I won't need a PreAmp, but better speakers - possibly Amplifier+PassiveSpeakers.
Thanks for your reply, and if you have more suggestions, please write them down! :)** </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Skin Colour vs Muscles </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-06-11 10:28:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Money vs Time </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-06-10 13:58:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Great comment from /r/WritingPrompts </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-05-07 12:09:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Re-entering the US within the 90 days of the Visa Waiver Program </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-04-15 20:42:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hello travelers,

I have been one week in the US last week for work, and I am coming back next week for holidays with my girlfriend. 

At the entrance of the US border I have been granted a VWP permit of 90 days. Reading on the US embassy it states that I can re-enter the country with no problems (at discretion of the border agent) unless it shows I wanna try and stay there.

I have return tickets to my country of residence, where I work, and this should be enough proof even to skeptical guys.

My question is, do I have to show the border agent that I have already been approved a VWP permit? Or will they re-start it? 

It's the first time I travel so closely in time to the US and I have no clue! :)

thanks!

tl;dr Going in the US for the second time in a short period of time, don't know how it works with the VISA etc. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> How are the save games stored? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-04-14 23:47:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Vegan toddlers   kids - question about nutrition / supplements </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-04-04 12:10:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hi guys,

me and my wife are Vegetarians and transitioning into Veganism. 

*(funny part, I was a great meat-eater, swore never to give up meat, then turned vegetarian, swore never to turn vegan, and hey, here I am reading labels and not buying animal-derived products anymore)*

We are also planning to have kids sooner than later. 
When we started to be Veggie, we told ourselves that we would have not forced our diet on to our kids (still brainwashed at the time, huh). 

Now that we are aware of how incredibly healthier a Vegan lifestyle can be both for humans   environment, we are wondering to raise our kids (when we will be blessed with) on a Vegan diet. Of course if they'll ever want to taste meat, dairy, eggs, we won't stop them - they have to decide for themselves - but we will make them aware, in the most objective way, of everything they will want to do, without limiting their freedom (a lot of good will here eh?).

Finally, the question: did you raise your kids up Vegans? Was it difficult? Did you integrate in any way their diet (B12 et similia)? 

Please help!

**tl;dr Planning on raising a Vegan kid, trying to gather your experiences with any nutritional issue encountered. Thanks**



 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Why this subreddit switched to Comic Sans? Terrible, terrible, terrible!!! </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-04-02 17:43:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Can you please confirm translation? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-04-02 11:59:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hi guys, the following:

Should mean, "No clinging, No seeking".

am I correct?


Thanks!

**EDIT: Really? Downvoted? for what reason? This does not make sense guys. Downvotes are useful to dig bad stuff, not to disagree!!** </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> My First Class plane ticket has been downgraded to Business Class and now it's too late to choose my favorite seat. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-04-01 15:25:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Where could I find this exact faux leather Jacket from Charles and 1/2? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-03-24 18:00:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Best bottle I can find in European Duty Free? (London Heathrow) </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-03-17 14:32:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hi guys,

I'll be traveling to London and back for work. I am starting a whiskey collection (finally! Now that I can keep myself from drinking it immediately!).

Last time I've bought a Glenmorangie Nectar D'Or. Any recommendation? Avoid things like Tullamore Dew, Jameson, Black Bush, Kilbeggan... I can easily buy those things at home! :)

Thanks!

**EDIT: Rephrased last part to avoid misunderstanding.**
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> I need help - Guided meditation to deal with sorrow </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-03-12 18:04:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hi guys,

I am currently with my dad who is sick. Doctors says he needs a transplant or he will live only 1 year.

He has always been a strong man and seeing him dizzy and weak makes me angry, frustrated, and feels me with sorrow.

Meditation always helped me to calm my mind and emotions, but in the last days I am not able to do it. I'm restless and overwhelmed by thoughts. 

Can you help me deal with that? Do you have any guided meditation that works for you when you're restless and lost in thoughts and emotions?

Thank you all for your kindness.

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Help translating a simple phrase in aramaic! </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-03-04 14:19:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hi guys, that's for a friend who wants to get a tattoo. Before he gets something like "I am a dumb fart" on his body, can you help me translate 

"Never Surrender"

in Aramaic? 

Also, please don't ask why he wants to do it in Aramaic. I have already had this discussion...

Many thanks to all of you!!
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Vegan Elegant Men Coat wanted... as reward, link to an amazing Vegan Jacket. (originally posted in /r/vegan) </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-02-19 14:21:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hi guys,
I am recently renewing my wardrobe as my old non-vegan clothes are wearing out. I am searching for a Vegan coat. Possibly waterproof. Possibly "elegant". I don't care if cheap or not, it's an investment after all...

As promised, here's a great Vegan Jacket I've found. Good quality, great looking, affordable price!

http://www.wellensteyn-usa.com/SAN-DIEGO-at-Wellensteyn-PID8690-SAD202.aspx

I am looking forward to seeing your comments guys! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Vegan Elegant Men Coat wanted... as reward, link to an amazing Vegan Jacket. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-02-19 12:56:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hi guys,

I am recently renewing my wardrobe as my old non-vegan clothes are wearing out. 
I am searching for a Vegan coat. Possibly waterproof. Possibly "elegant". I don't care if cheap or not, it's an investment after all...

As promised, here's a great Vegan Jacket I've found. Good quality, great looking, affordable price!

http://www.wellensteyn-usa.com/SAN-DIEGO-at-Wellensteyn-PID8690-SAD202.aspx

I am looking forward to seeing your comments guys!

**EDIT: Thanks all of you so far. Keep post in in the comments if you find something worth sharing. For all of us, here are the links collected so far. I will keep updating them.**

[Vegansaurus collection of links](http://vegansaurus.com/post/273389902/mens-winter-coat-guide)

[Hoodlamb Jackets](http://outlet.hoodlamb.com/index.php?cPath=38_45)

[Vaute Couture](http://vautecouture.com/collections/men) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> I was in a discussion with a meat-eater and he kept saying that I eat always the same things. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-01-24 15:32:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So basically his argument was "I can eat beef, pork, chicken, fish... what do you eat as you cannot eat anything?"

I chose simply to face palm.

EDIT: Thanks guys, I just wanted to have some fun :) your replies are my same ones. And I'll adopt the "pocket lint" one immediately! :) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Questioning the utility of Reality Checks. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-01-16 16:42:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Last night I was dreaming (non-lucid). I had to go to an appointment and I was late, so I told myself "I'll never make it by foot. Let's fly there". So I start flying just by waving my arms like a bird. Midway to my arrival point, I look down, stop waving arms, and say to myself "Wait, that's impossible. I am dreaming!!!" excited for the revelation, I decide to take a reality check to confirm, and then do whatever. As soon as I try the nose blow, I got a false negative (no air passes) and I think "Shit, it's reality. I better avoid to fly on that lake then in case I fall".

First: I laughed myself off when I awoke. 

Secondly: I'm doing meditation every day, RCs between 5-20 per day, and am studying Dream Yoga to practice ADA. 

In the dream yoga there's no reference for the need of reality checks. You just really need to be focused in recognising your current state (awareness). 

I'm starting to think that RC are overrated, and ADA and Dream recall/journaling are the best way to go there.

Before starting to study LaBerge (which is in my book list), I wanted to ask the community: what do you think of RCs? Where the practice of RCs come from? Would you think that reaching lucidity is not strictly connected with RCs?

For me, RCs work great when doing FILD but the subsequent LD is usually not vivid, low-light ambient etc.

WILD, never managed to reach lucidity with it.

DILD, I managed to get lucid twice.

So far, apart when FILDing, my RCs have always been false negative in my dreams, thus preventing my lucidity.

I'm looking forward to hear your thoughts. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> How do you cope when discovering a published book with a similar idea to the one you're actually writing? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-01-15 10:34:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm in the middle of writing a book with some weird premises (there's a touch of supernatural in there). 

Yesterday wandering around Amazon I found an author which is published and had a similar base-idea as mine.

I keep telling myself that it does not matter - story   plot   characters make the book - that it's like writing YAB on zombie apocalypses, but I still wanted to share with you and hear your comments.

Shoot.

**EDIT: Thanks guys, you confirmed my feelings and thoughts!!** </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Writers of Reddit, give me your opinion about agents. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-01-07 14:08:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I live in Europe so for us agents are not really that "big" like in the US. But thanks to internet now it's easy to reach out to agents. 

Do you think agents are important/fundamental? How is your experience? How did you find one? Can you suggest tips/tricks or agencies?

Share share share! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> How would police react if I call and tell, "there's my best friend dead in my bathtub?" (hypothetical question for a book scene) </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-12-31 09:52:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> originally posted in /r/Writing

I am writing a scene of my book where the main character wakes up drunk and finds his best friend dead (by natural causes, meaning that there is no visible sign of fight, shots, blood etc) in the bathtub. After the normal shock he calls the police and waits for them in his apartment.

The scene I wrote is a really "quiet" one, meaning that 3 people arrive at the apartment, 2 go them check on the body in the bathroom and the third questions the Main Character about what happened. No violence, no gun drawn etc. A friend that read the scene told me that this would be "unreal" in his opinion as he believe police will come into your house, be more "physical" in making sure you're not harmful, and then question you in the station and not in your house. 

Thankfully it never happened to me :D but I believe that if I find my best friend dead in my bathtub and call the police explaining what happened, they will come to my place relatively calm, without creating too much of a mess - am I wrong? 

Help is appreciated!!! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Need advice for a scene where Police is involved. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-12-31 09:28:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hi guys, I don't know if there's a subreddit for that or I have to move to /r/AskReddit. Please let me know.

I am writing a scene of my book where the main character wakes up drunk and finds his best friend dead (by natural causes, meaning that there is no visible sign of fight, shots, blood etc) in the bathtub. After the normal shock he calls the police and waits for them in his apartment.

The scene I wrote is a really "quiet" one, meaning that 3 people arrive at the apartment, 2 go them check on the body in the bathroom and the third questions the Main Character about what happened. No violence, no gun drawn etc. A friend that read the scene told me that this would be "unreal" in his opinion as he believe police will come into your house, be more "physical" in making sure you're not harmful, and then question you in the station and not in your house. 

Thankfully it never happened to me :D but I believe that if I find my best friend dead in my bathtub and call the police explaining what happened, they will come to my place relatively calm, without creating too much of a mess - am I wrong? 

Help is appreciated!!!

**EDIT: Thanks to all of you guys, your answers have been really, really helpful. I might contact some of you in private for further informations!!!** </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Is it just me or Tofu is terrible? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-12-18 15:44:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I've gone vegetarian 2 years ago and never looked back. In the beginning it was just meat-substitute (Quorn et similia) but now I can cook vegetables and use meat substitutes practically never. 
While I love Seitan and make incredibly gorgeous Seitan Gyropita or Kebabs, I hate tofu. Consistency is terrible, flavour is plastic-like.
I tried different brands, cooked, grilled, marinated... nothing.

So my question is: is it me, or Tofu is just nearly-unedible?

EDIT: Thanks for the replies guys!! I'll try and read / reply to them tomorrow :)
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Aurora, the dream-enanching headband </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-12-16 12:15:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Project live on KickStarter: http://www.kickstarter.com/projects/iwinks/the-aurora-dream-enhancing-headband?ref=category

I am not in any way related to the Aurora team, but as a trainee in Lucid Dreaming I thought that this was worth sharing.

My take: Technology can be a great help, but in my personal opinion is that the way to master Lucid Dreaming is a way to master your inner self. The whole training of recognising DS, Meditating, WILD etc... the whole experience is worth the training. 

What are your thoughts?

tl;dr a headband that can help you LD. Worth it? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Afraid of SP   letting go my body </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-12-12 14:40:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Ok I've been trying to LD for a month now. I managed to reach lucidity only once with FILD.

I'm trying WILD now as I feel I can manage this more easily (and I can also learn to meditate). Point is, every time I reach SP and my REM starts, I am afraid of seeing scary things (after all the SP stories around) and wake myself up on purpose. 
Do you have any advice on how I can learn to "let go" of my body and abandon myself to the dream world?

Thanks in advance!

tl;dr Everytime I reach SP, I purposely wake myself up as I'm afraid to let go and dream. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Long Hair, which product to use? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-12-05 15:40:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I've long blonde hair - always had on and off for a while - and now they've grown a lot, I'm catching up with my girl ;) 
At work I wore them tied up with a band or a hairstick (I've got a cool, handmade hairstick from Etsy). 

But I'd love to have the same "look" of Mr. Brad Pitt with his hair long. They are shiny and I suppose he's using some kind of oily product to keep them in shape/separate the various strands.

Any clue/help? Thanks! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Dreamception (aka dreaming of lucid dreaming) </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-11-28 12:27:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I believe I dreamt of lucid dreaming. 

I started to keep a dream journal a week ago, doing my ADA, and my favorite RC is to close my nose and try to breath - if I breathe with my nostrils closed, I'm dreaming :)

Also, I started to try FILD every night, with mixed results. It happened to me twice to recognise I was dreaming, and immediately waking up from excitement. Not last night. 

So i was trying to go lucid using FILD.  First attempt of reality check, I realize I was dreaming!! This time no panic, I do not wake up, try immediately to visualize something (I was in total darkness). This does not work and I feel the lucidity is going away, so I simply try to focus and stabilize. So as I realize I don't have full control over the dream, I try to "trick" my brain to obtain informations. So I shout a question "what's the purpose of life and all?" And suddenly a green field appears, very lovely place, with my grave. I don't feel scared - it's a dream - and anyway I'm constantly exploring my 'fear of death' so I kind of know it's one of my greatest fears. At this point I feel I have more control, and try to fly. I float up 5,6 feet, and then everything turns blank and the dream ends... And now what makes me think I was not really lucid: instead of waking up at the end of the dream, I dream that I'm in reality! I do my checks and they work, so I believe I'm real and I'm walking down the street. I decide to do a "deep" awareness moment, and suddenly I walk in slow-motion and "feel" everything around me - people, sounds, the sidewalk. It was a great sensation and told me that LD will bring me more awareness of my real world.
Maybe I did LD and then slipped into a normal dream. After the "reality" dream, Then I slipped in a second dream that involved enemies and guns and bazooka.

Scary thou that my mind led me to believe that a dream is reality. This can mess you up long term I believe.

tl;dr - I'm not sure if I LD or dreamed of lucid dreaming, and then I dreamed that my dream was reality.





 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> You won the geek contest. Prize is 5000$. What would you buy? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-11-22 21:54:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Only rules are, you can only buy geeky gadgets or brand new technology. Like Nest Thermostats, Cube sensors, SmartThings etc. 

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Reddit bodybuilder, help me define my next workout routine. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-10-13 12:29:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Once I found a website where you can check if the corporations were investing in illegal business. People of Reddit, do you remember the site? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-07-04 10:39:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> There is no direct evolutionary motivation for an AI to be friendly to humans.  </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-07-02 14:38:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> I'm a European (unpublished) writer. Reddit, how do I get published in the US? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-06-29 15:41:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So, here's the deal. I'm a writer and I'm gonna write my first book in english soon. It will be a big, huge challenge, as English is not my native language. But I want a broad audience to have more chances to be published. 
I'll try in my country first (which is English-speaking) but as is a small one, I want to try in the US as well.

Writers around here, how do I get published in the US?

{NOTE: Please spare comment like "write a good book" etc. I know I've to write something good to have the chance, the question here is more technical!} </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> I'm home alone today. Which movie (pref. on Netflix) do you suggest me to watch, Reddit? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-06-24 12:35:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> To help you understand my tastes, here're some of my favs:

Blade Runner.
Lord of the Rings.
Matrix.
Star Trek (the next gen).
The Exorcist.
Pulp Fiction.
From dusk till dawn.
The night of the living dead.
The hitchhiker's guide to the galaxy.
SpaceBalls.
Frankenstein Jr.
Back to the Future.
Indiana Jones.
(this is getting fun actually).
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Reddit, do you think Apple will eventually unveil a proper TV?  </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-06-22 16:38:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> And, if so, what would be the game-changer feature? Broadcasters partnerships?

I think that the killer opt would be the chance to play REAL games on it as well. That would be the perfect device to buy; good for the father, to watch sports   check internet; good for the mother, to use Facetime and chat with friends; and good for the kids, that will be able to play directly.

What's your opinion, Reddit? What are the features that you would like in a "Smart" TV? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The Strange Sounds in the sky... Explained. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-06-22 14:17:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Redditors,
you know that strange sound that people hear, coming from the sky, which freaks them out? You know that some of them thinks it's God, some others think it's some kind of super-secret weapon (like the HAARP), while others think it's an alien sound?
Well...

It's the Schumann resonance. 

*(from Wikipedia: The Schumann resonances (SR) are a set of spectrum peaks in the extremely low frequency (ELF) portion of the Earth's electromagnetic field spectrum. Schumann resonances are global electromagnetic resonances, excited by lightning discharges in the cavity formed by the Earth's surface and the ionosphere.)*

When the sun strikes a flare, it creates an electromagnetic storm that will reach the Earth. Usually this storm has no impact on our everyday life, but sometimes it can be so strong that make communications cease, or cause black-outs. Some other times, it reaches a certain "frequency" (we are talking about waves) that matches the frequencies of the ionosphere cavity of the Earth, making it... sound. It's an amazing thing, it's like our planet and the sun talking together. 

Nikola Tesla calculated this frequency and said it was about 8Hz. Schumann frequencies are between 3Hz and 60Hz, so when the sun strikes at 8Hz its magnetic storm... Earth sounds like a diapason.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The Strange Sound people hear around the world... explained (I hope). </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-06-22 13:52:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Which strategy games on Mac, Reddit? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-06-19 18:44:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm looking for a strategy game on Mac. I am undecided between Civilization V or Star Wars: Empire at War, but as I'm long outside the gaming world, I accept suggestion! Only limit: it has to run on Mac! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
