<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject9815</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-27 19:47:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Radio guys talking about Springer taking a bigger lead off first. Hopefully he worked on his baserunning.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-27 19:44:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Lance Berkman, Craig Biggio, or Jeff Bagwell to DH/teach everyone but Altuve how to hit.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-27 19:32:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Well damn Tyler GIDP to kill my excitement of checking in for the first time.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-27 17:47:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Don't we have battles for 4   5? or are we assuming Morton at 4? Keuchel, McHugh, and LMJ are locks.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-27 17:23:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> * Trying to work on making my Letter of Intent for Grad School more personal. 
* Finally and absolutely done moving. Praise be. 
* I'm going to have to go with bears.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Astros Rank 3rd in Baseball America's Organizational Ranking! </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-27 17:19:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-27 16:52:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I read the Hobbit as a kid but I remember the first chapter being the hardest to read. I'm debating picking it up this year.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-27 16:51:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Just finished **Born to Run by Christopher McDougall** and I know some people have a problem with his journalistic style, but it really reminded me why I run, and that I should run more. Highly recommend. 

Working slowly through **The Queen of the Night by Alexander Chee** it's so well written but I don't care for the story at all.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-27 15:35:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I was trying my best to be inconspicuous but I think I just awkwardly drew more attention to myself. I wanted to shout "I'm not being a pervert I have tights under!" but thought that would be worse.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-27 15:34:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> running tights. I'm not quite there yet in running in just tights. Plus they have a little hole in the inner thigh area.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-27 15:21:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Wasn't Swanson basically on par with Bregman? (and I would never put Bregman up there with Correa) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-27 15:02:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I forgot my running shorts at home. So I have to find some during my lunch break or just run in tights. This plus shocking a local teen by taking off my pants in a bus shelter (I had tights under!) makes me feel like I should just wear shorts everywhere and at all times.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-27 04:25:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Carlos Beltran? But he's back. So it ends now.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-27 02:09:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Jason Castro would've been my answer last year. I'll stick with catchers and say McCann. Although Gurriel could intimidate his team into success with his troll hair  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-26 02:44:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I use more than one. Its really how much effort you want to put in i Guess. Strava is a fan favorite  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-25 20:09:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Maybe the wrong Edison Frias showed up and everyone just went with it  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-25 06:03:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Is it impressive its expected?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-25 03:15:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm not sure if other people have already mentioned this to you but I don't buy the argument that people voted not because of xenophobia and riled up fear but somehow because restricting immigration is more pragmatic than corporate regulation because if you think building a multi billion dollar wall that will absolutely disrupt local ecology with some insect extinction or endangerment possible, remove access to our own water supply, increase the death rate of border crossers, and cut off access to irrigation and farm land for American farmers AND at the same doubling down on the belief that we can't regulate corporations by voting for a business insider who wants to repeal Glass Steagall and already has more ethics violations that most presidents and is making bank on his presidency all while inflaming racist beliefs with Muslim bans than you are going a long way to delude yourself. At least Hillary proposed actual education plans for out of work laborers in dying industries, wanted to regulate excessive and predatory bank practices, and believed in the repeal of Citizens United.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-24 19:12:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> * sleepy. always sleepy.
* HM training hopefully. Realistically just more apartment packing up. 
* I used to think Raskolnikov but then figured that made me a psychopath. My other go to and guilty pleasure growing up was Ginger from As Told by Ginger  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-24 18:00:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I wonder if Harris goes back to being used as the stats-backed LOOGY and everyone slides back into their roles from 2015 (with Giles as the Closer). The only exception I have to your list is that Feliz is completely missing. I think he's still the clear fire man http://www.chron.com/sports/astros/article/Michael-Feliz-has-a-leg-up-on-winning-an-Astros-10944228.php </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Astros' Collin McHugh: Wins arbitration hearing </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-14 21:24:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> 950XL battery replacement </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-02-11 19:12:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Just stopped into the microsoft store in Manhattan and was directed to the b2x app for support. Even though I have complete until December it tells me im out of warranty. MS offered me a swap to the Idol or X3. Should I take it or can anyone offer a good third party battery that definitely works? My original plan was to wait until the last month of my complete and then swap out </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Donald Trump filed for Reelection on Jan 20 2017 </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-30 17:48:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Bagwell HOF jersey </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-19 17:17:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Does anyone know if these will go on sale again? https://instagram.com/p/BPbHwB-ALR8/ preferably online. I don't remember or wasn't paying attention to the Astros store for Biggios HOF induction </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> McHugh, Fiers, Harris,   Marwin still unsigned </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-14 07:46:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Per the [Chronicle](http://m.chron.com/sports/astros/article/Astros-avoid-arbitration-with-Dallas-Keuchel-10856074.php)

 Starting pitchers Collin McHugh and Mike Fiers, reliever Will Harris and infielder Marwin Gonzalez remained unsigned after Friday's deadline for teams and the agents of arbitration-eligible players to exchange desired salary figures. Cases that aren't settled in the coming weeks are heard in February by a three-person panel, which decides on one side's proposed number or the other's </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Writing Prompt: Los Dos Invisibles </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-15 04:40:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> www.reddit.com/r/WritingPrompts/comments/5icun0/wp_overnight_the_united_states_of_america/db78j4x

Reynosa, Mexico

Israel stares out into the new ocean. Rio Bravo to Mar Bravo. A tempestuous monster that taunted those brave enough to attempt the crossing, the whispers of better wages, a better life. His mother had been lucky, receiving a visa to do low skilled labor, but what else did she know, traveling across the Rio every day and coming home with a little extra money. American dollars, green and crumpled with her sweat. 
Papa woke from his bed, hungover, drinking since the disappearance. His voice croaked and he beckoned Israel closer. 

Israel, dame agua, he wants water. Israel pours some from the faucet wondering now what will happen to their water supply. Millions of gallons of fresh water consumed by the Atlantic and Pacific oceans as they mingled violently in the Mar Bravo. 

The news went from bewilderment to passive acceptance. If an entire nation had disappeared, overnight, in the middle of the day, whenever, there would have been a large wave accompanying the loss of mass, a rushing of water to fill the void. Reynosa would have been destroyed, flooded by a tidal wave too high to understand, they would have disappeared with the United States. Instead a beach formed where people started getting used to the loss of the silt rich river water, for the stinging salt water. 

Nadia cambio? his father asked. Has anything changed. 
Israel and his father avoided their neighbors after the empty stares, those who knew what it was like to lose a family member, and those who wanted to offer their condolences without understanding the weight of it. 

Israel of course had the messages in his bottle. Three had come since the disappearance. Three letters that held his mother in an imagined land, each day forgotten by those in the world who wanted to pretend that there never had been an America, just the drifting peninsula of Mexico, and the cold island of Canada. 

But what about Alaska? Israel wondered. 

But what about my mother? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Writing Prompt: My Time as the Only Adult </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-13 22:49:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [continued](https://www.reddit.com/r/WritingPrompts/comments/5i467o/wp_a_virus_has_swept_the_world_killing_everyone/db5c86w/)

"What the fuck is your deal," she said, full of anger and resentment.

Flustered, "Excuse me? I just, what are you getting at?"

"What do you do," she continued.

Before I answer that there are some things I've discovered while living amongst the children. I'm not Jane Goodall observing these children recreate society, and frankly I don't want to know very much about how things are going. What I do know isfrightening to the only adult survivor of the over 10 disease. I said that I didn't want to think about pregnant children, but really it happens. You see some 6 year old waddling around and you think about how she's going to spend 10 months of her short life carrying another children, and you get depressed, and then you run to chase away that depression with endorphins. As a result of the disease, which I can speculate affected the DNA of everyone alive, as in your cells telomeres get long enough and then just give out. That's a speculation based off high school AP Biology, so that probably means nothing. Gestation periods seem to have shortened from 10 months to 3 months, and that's all I know based off observations and guesses. The other obvious question is how do children that are less than 10 years old maintain the utilities of society? Electricity, running water, reddit? Yeah I've been on reddit, that's the Jane Goodall part I was referring to. I'm not smart enough to know anything about this new society I just stole it off some public post on the reddit front page before deciding the internet wasn't for me anymore. Somehow in a process I'll never be able to explain, knowledge is passed on from generation to generation, and there is a boost to learning ability. 
What is not passed on is emotional maturity or any kind of physical development that allows these post disease children to be miniature adults. So I live with extremely knowledgeable but vindictive and bratty children, who know to keep me at a distance until they've decided if looking into the adult-ing process is worth investigating. 

So this productive member of society, without a grasp on her volatile emotions, was getting in my face, about what I did, "I'm chief counsel." 

"You run around town," she said.

"I'm training for a marathon," I responded quickly.

Because of the lack of physical development, they didn't place any importance on exercise, much less endurance training. 

"That's not conducive to our society," she said. "I've been your neighbor for a quarter of my life, and I've seen you waste hours running from your home to who knows where. I think it's time Town Leader reevaluates your importance to us." 

Punishment in town didn't really exist because of the short lifespan. Yes some people did get put away in prison for extended periods of time, but sentences were whimsical and soon forgotten. I could not imagine what her threat was, this miniscule matron. 

"I've had some talks with Chuck," she started, "and it he's thinking about how best to approach your unique situation. But, because he likes meand I shouldn't tell you this but I may be next in linehe's leaving the decision up to me."

She paused and tied her hair up with a hair tie from her wrist. 
Her eyes squinted and she scrutinized me before emitting a low chuckle that was mostly exhaled air. I wished, seeing these short humans dominating the world, that I had a background in sociology or a science. 

"I am willing to let these idolatry slide," she said, "if you'll do something for me." </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> New York City's Hardest-Working Bands of 2016 </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-12 22:49:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> 2017 ZiPS Projections  Houston Astros </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-09 17:47:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Projecting Yesterdays Rule 5 Picks </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-09 17:35:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Tri City Valley Cats: The (Front) Office parody </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-08 01:41:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Five for 5: Rule 5 Draft names to know </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-07 16:28:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The Book of My Lives by Aleksandar Hemon </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-05 21:45:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Just finished this memoir by Hemon yesterday. Hemon is so adept at driving emotional daggers into reader's hearts, and concludes with the previously published [The Aquarium](http://www.newyorker.com/magazine/2011/06/13/the-aquarium) in which he details the hospitalization of his 9 month old for a tumor. 

While I bookmarked many many pages, it's this paragraph that I keep thinking about today

Much like Ella, Id found myself with an excess of words, the wealth of which far exceeded the pathetic limits of my own biography. Id needed narrative space to extend myself into; Id needed more lives. I, too, had needed another set of parents, and someone other than myself to throw my metaphysical tantrums. Id cooked up those avatars in the soup of my ever-changing self, but they were not methey did what I wouldnt, or couldnt, do. Listening to Ella furiously and endlessly unfurl the Mingus tales, I understood that the need to tell stories was deeply embedded in our minds and inseparably entangled with the mechanisms that generate and absorb language. Narrative imaginationand therefore fictionwas a basic evolutionary tool of survival. We processed the world by telling stories, produced human knowledge through our engagement with imagined selves.

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Will Jennings v. Rodriguez shape Trump's Immigration Policy? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-01 16:05:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The Supreme Court began hearing arguments in [Jennings v. Rodriguez](http://www.scotusblog.com/case-files/cases/jennings-v-rodriguez/?wpmp_switcher=desktop) which will primarily determine if detained unauthorized immigrants are apply to apply for individual bonds. Per [NPR](http://www.npr.org/2016/11/30/503902528/supreme-court-tests-whether-detained-immigrants-have-right-to-hearing) the court is divided along ideological lines. 

Does a ruling in favor of bond hearings, and therefore potential release of unauthorized immigrants awaiting trial rile up the anti-immigration feelings? Or does Trump avoid talking about it unless the outcome is in his favor?

Additionally what are the repercussions of detention without hearing for non-citizens? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Advice for soon to be stay at home dad? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-30 23:35:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So my wife and I weird the options and NYC daycare is just too expensive to justify both people working,  especially as it would make my life more challenging and stressful and I don't love my job.  Any pointers for transition to being a stay at home? I'm also fearful that finding work later will be impossible </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> How will Chao contribute to Trump's infrastructure spending plans? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-30 00:20:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Donald Trump has announced Elaine Chao as his Secretary of Transportation. http://nymag.com/daily/intelligencer/2016/11/trump-picks-elaine-chao-for-transportation-secretary.html?mid=facebook_nymag

Chao has experience both in presidential cabinets and in the department of transportation.  How will she help implement Trump's infrastructure plans? 

How will her marriage to Majority Leader Mitchell McConnell effect future legislation? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Latest On Market For Rich Hill : Astros Still In on Hill </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-29 23:23:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Is political pay for play the new normal? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-19 22:13:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Per the [Washington Post](https://www.washingtonpost.com/business/capitalbusiness/2016/11/18/9da9c572-ad18-11e6-977a-1030f822fc35_story.html) foreign diplomats are rushing to book stays in Trump hotels in the off chance of currying favor in the Trump administration while Trump hotels held raffles to other properties and encouraged diplomats to see what his business had to offer.  Earlier Clinton was criticized for her use of the Clinton Foundation  as a means for foreign operatives to gain access to the State Department.  Is this an established and acceptable norm of operating the federal government?  Ie were Trumps claims of impropriety against Clinton political posturing?  Or will we see an increased exposure and vigilance by the press and an anti establishment populace? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Astros Newest Carolina League club reveals logo, uniform for 2017 season </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-18 19:20:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Astros still want OF Carlos Beltran </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-18 17:05:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Statehood case for DC </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-09 22:44:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Astros Offseason: What if Jason Castro Already Rejected a Deal? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-31 16:46:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Photos folder duplicating and reappearing after deletion. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-27 20:48:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So I'm having this problem where a folder labeled Pictures will reappear after deletion with one neon wallpaper. Over the course of the day the wallpaper duplicates until there are around 100 per day in the same folder. Deletion doesn't solve the problem. I turned off camera uploads to onedrive. Any other possible solutions? I'm stuck.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> (spoilers) A Little Life, Jude St. Francis   Jude the Obscure </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-26 20:43:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I just finished A Little Life and was pretty devastated. The ending was probably only the third time I've teared up over a book, and while I guess I could have seen it coming it was still pretty awful. What's worse was the death of Wilhem and Malcom. 

What kept reoccurring to me though, was just how awful Jude's life was and the obvious (I think) reference to Jude the Obscure. Now I haven't had the pleasure of reading Jude the Obscure (though I have read Tess of the d'Ubbervilles so I feel like I have some context) but I kept coming back to a quote by Stephen King in which he describes situations where the characters are so down trodden, so maligned, and abused by the writer that his situation becomes almost comical. While I'm not suggesting that I laughed at Jude's misfortune in A Little Life, it did begin to feel a little absurd when after being mistreated by Brother Luke, he was then placed in a group home where he was abused, ran away, and ended up with a doctor who continued to abuse him. 

In such a heart wrenching book in which the character was constantly in some place of misfortune how does Yanagahira avoid making Jude's life absurd with tragedy? 

I'm still digesting but I'm really interested in what everyone else thought of the book. 

EDIT: [Interview](http://www.liljas-library.com/showinterview.php?id=34) where King mentions: "every now and then I think of what Oscar Wilde said about The Little Match Girl. He said that its impossible to read about the little match girl without weeping tears of laughter and...you know something that is so sad its actually funny." I know he better discuss it in the introduction to *Blaze* but I can't find that online.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Animated Tribute To The Hard-Partying 1986 Mets </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-25 21:18:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The Cubs Curse Is Now More Likely To End Than To Continue </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-21 19:16:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Audiobook running </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-20 23:03:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I've been working through A Little Life by Hanya Yanagahiara while I run. It's about 24 hours of book. I'm finally closing in on the finish (and it's been a journey). Now I'm debating whether or not I should just finish it normally or save 2 - 3 hours for my HM in November. Any thoughts on running with audiobooks in general? Or suggestions on finishing it in training or during the race?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Bullpen Usage is Destroying Offense This Postseason </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-19 20:08:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> In Baseball, October Is Reliever Season </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-18 17:17:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> SSS: OF Ramon Laureano is batting .444 in the AFL </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-18 17:09:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Through 5 games Laureano in the Arizona Fall league 






AVG .444 | G 5 | AB 18 | H 8 | 2B 8 | 3B 2 | HR 2 | BB 2 | SO 1 | OBP .476 | SLG .778 | OPS 1.254

    









This after a great season split between Lancaster and Corpus. 
http://mlb.mlb.com/milb/stats/stats.jsp?pos= sid=l119 t=p_pbp pid=657656

Prospect Report: http://www.todaysknuckleball.com/al/houston-astros/astros-prospects-ramon-laureano-garrett-stubbs-earn-promotions/

I was talking with an Astros prospect guru the other day, and he asked me for a comp to Laureano. Because of their similar builds, my mind immediately went to the Astros superstar second baseman, Jose Altuve. But looking past the statistics and surface-level stuff, Laureano is that type of player. Hes involved in everything on the field, hes an aggressive, scrappy, smaller guy, and he has a surprising amount of pop despite his unassuming stature.

Astros seem to be stocking up on Jose Altuve type players. 







 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Francis Martes to make his first start for the Glendale Desert Dogs: 10/13 @ 7:35 PM CST </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-13 18:55:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Might this be the canceled Microsoft Band 3? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-12 20:08:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Microsoft no longer offering complete on phones. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-04 06:01:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Went in today to get my 950XL swapped since I shattered the screen this morning. Manager told me complete is no longer being offered but they'll still obviously honor any complete that's already been purchased. The good news is my deductible was $50 instead of $100 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Regina Spektor releases Remember Us to Life today 9/30 </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-01 03:49:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Pre ordered this off Amazon. Listening now with my wife and kid. It's good but im not sure it'll be on heavy rotate like Begin to Hope </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Carlos Correa, Playing Through Injury, and True Talent </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-28 18:44:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> CBS Sports gives our Wild Card SP job to Fister or Fiers </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-21 15:13:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Season ends for JetHawks with 7-2 loss to Mavs in Game 4 </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-14 15:26:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Altuve hits homer #24 and ties the game 1-1 </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-14 03:38:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> ValleyCats to host 2017 New York-Penn League All-Star Game </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-13 23:00:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> 9/13 Game 4: High Desert (2-1) @ Lancaster (1-2) 6:35 PM PT </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-13 22:54:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> http://www.milb.com/scoreboard/index.jsp?sid=t491

Lancaster SP [Jose Hernandez](http://www.milb.com/player/index.jsp?sid=t491 player_id=664353#/career/R/pitching/2016/ALL)

High Desert SP [David Ledbetter](http://www.milb.com/player/index.jsp?sid=t491 player_id=641780#/career/R/pitching/2016/ALL) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Hooks Among Attendance Leaders </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-13 22:44:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Microsoft Band's future in doubt; efforts to get it running on Windows 10 reportedly canceled </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-13 21:20:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Spikes score New York-Penn League title </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-13 18:12:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Astros' Dallas Keuchel pushes back his return to throwing again </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-13 16:13:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The Making of Zombie Wars by Aleksandar Hemon </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-13 06:21:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The Dividends of Alex Bregmans Non-Adjustment </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-12 16:18:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> JetHawks rout Rancho 21-6, advance to South Finals </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-11 03:37:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Grouplove release "Big Mess" </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-09 17:58:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Their first album since Spreading Rumors in 2013. I saw them headline a Prospect Park show one summer and they just blew me away, definitely one of the best bands I've seen live. I'm excited to listen to this on repeat.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The Case for Jose Altuve for American League MVP </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-06 18:24:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Astros MiLB Season Overview </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-06 18:15:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> **Fresno Grizzlies**  (73-70) The Grizzlies miss the playoffs and finish in 3rd place in the PCL Pacific Northern Division. 



*Top Hitters*

Danny Worth SS/UTIL AVG .303/OPS .955

Jon Singleton 1B AVG .202/OPS .728 led the team in HR with 24

Derek Fisher RF AVG .290/OPS .852 (split time at AA)

Chan Moon 2B AVG .309/OPS .753 (split time at AA)



*Top Pitchers*

Brady Rodgers 12-4 2.84 ERA/PCL Pitcher of the Year/ 1.15 WHIP 2 CG 1 SH

Cesar Valdez 12-1 3.12 ERA 1.13 WHIP 1 CG 1 SH



**Corpus Christi Hooks** (85-55) The Hooks finish with the best record in the Texas League and advance to the playoffs. The 5 game division series against Midland begins on Sept 7th. 



*Top Hitters*

Garrett Stubbs C AVG .325/OPS .918 

Alejandro Garcia OF AVG .270/OPS .661

JD Davis 3B lead the team with 24 HR



*Top Pitchers*

Francis Martes 9-6 3.30 ERA 1.20 WHIP 131 SO

Keegan Yuhl 8-3 3.04 ERA 1.21 WHIP 75 SO

David Paulino 5-2 1.83 ERA .91 WHIP 72 SO (finished his season at AAA)



**Lancaster Jethawks** (77-63) The Jethawks finish as the Second Half Division Leader and will play a 3 game series against Wildcard Rancho Cucamonga starting Sept. 7



*Top Hitter*

Kyle Tucker OF AVG .339/OPS 1.028 20 H in 16 Games for Tucker

Jason Martin CF led the team with 24 HR



*Top Pitchers*

Joshua James 9-5 4.81 ERA 1.45 WHIP 121 SO

Dean Deetz 6-5 4.24 ERA 1.40 WHIP 86 SO (Got called up to AA where he went 2-0 0.00 ERA .71 WHIP 17 SO in 12.0 IP)


 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Astros calling up Brady Rodgers from Fresno </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-02 17:28:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Astros extend PDC with Triple-A Fresno </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-02 17:05:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Astros will send seven to the Arizona Fall League </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-01 21:21:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Scrappers' Aiken earns first win as a pro </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-01 20:10:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Will the Trump/Pea Nieto meeting improve Trump's image as possible future world leader? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-31 22:38:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> http://www.foxnews.com/politics/2016/08/31/trump-agrees-to-meet-with-mexican-president.html

Just watched the press conference. It didn't really seem to come to much in terms of what their meeting was about and Pea-Nieto reiterated that he has the interest of Mexicans living anywhere as his priority. I thought was interesting that Nieto stated he invited both candidates to discuss inter-nation relations, and Trump was the only one who responded.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Astros' Brady Rodgers Named PCL Pitcher Of The Year </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-31 21:25:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Astros' Brady Rodgers Named PCL Pitcher Of The Year </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-31 21:21:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Evolved NY-Penn League Charm Nostalgia Batavia May Soon Face Final </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-31 15:26:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Extra Winnings: Signed Juan Minaya   Tommy Shirley baseball </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-29 22:49:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Best tempered glass screen protectors for Lumia 950 XL </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-29 20:17:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Here Are the Aces Who Should Make Up the All-Time Astros Pitching Staff </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-29 16:24:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Shot with LG V20 </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-26 23:28:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> 8/25/16: Grizzlies launch four homers in offensive affair with Sacramento </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-26 16:18:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Cesar Valdez Baffles Sacramento </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-25 19:02:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Cesar Valdez Baffles Sacramento </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-25 18:39:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Fayetteville council says yes to Astros baseball stadium agreement </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-24 18:25:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The LG V20 will come bundled with B O headphones. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-24 16:40:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> New LG V20 Renders Show Phone to Have Dual Cameras Front and Back </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-24 15:26:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> More Instagram shots from the V20 </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-23 21:31:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Joe Musgroves Weird One-Seam Sinker </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-23 16:29:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> LG V20: Google gives us our first look at Nougat-powered phone </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-22 22:07:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> LG V20 New Teaser </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-22 15:29:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Rumor: Subway Confessions about Microsoft Band 3 and Surface Phone </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-18 20:18:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> LG V20 Gets First 3D Video Render, Based on the Online Leaks (Video) </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-18 16:29:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Does every Minor league affiliate have a food related alt? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-17 21:38:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Just picked up [this](http://shop.brooklyncyclones.com/coney-island-franks/coney-island-franks-cap/) Cyclones cap last week 

The Fresno [Tacos](http://grizzlies.milbstore.com/store_contents.cfm?store_id=17 dept_id=1 product_id=67911) are one of my favorites

And I just discovered the Staten Island Yankees are also the [Cannolis](http://siyanks.milbstore.com//store_contents.cfm?store_id=94 dept_id=-1 product_id=82566) 

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> LG V20 Details Leak on Reddit, Includes Pricing and Preorder Information for T-mobile </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-15 22:08:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Jose Altuve approaches 1,000-hit milestone </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-15 18:35:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Jose Altuve approaches 1,000-hit milestone </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-15 18:27:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> TCB Interview with: Teoscar Hernandez (2014) </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-12 18:17:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Gold Medalist Simone Biles Throws Out First Pitch for Houston Astros </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-12 17:00:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The Astros Chris Devenski and Large Velocity Gaps </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-12 16:22:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Topps with the Throwback set honoring Ichiro's 3000th hit </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-12 05:18:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> So You Want to Try to Salvage Carlos Gomez </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-11 16:20:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> 2016 Front Office Confidence Ratings, Midseason Update </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-09 20:32:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Ken Giles, Josh Fields, and pitching under pressure </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-04 18:58:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Brooklyn Cyclones: Wilmer Flores "Tears to Cheers" Bobblehad </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-29 19:25:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Lance McCullers Jr. comments on the Top 100 Midseason List </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-29 16:26:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Astros Yulieski Gurriel is one of the best players in Cuban history </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-28 16:34:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> MLB Games Are Slow Again, And Its Helping Older Hitters </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-28 15:57:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Should Your Team Buy Or Sell At The MLB Trade Deadline? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-25 21:44:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Scouting Astros Call-Up Alex Bregman </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-25 16:39:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Truecaller won't setup on W10M </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-22 22:57:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Is anyone using Truecaller for W10M. I'm on the most recent production release. After inputting my world code and telephone number the continue button disappears with the keyboard.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Confidence, Command, Health, and Lance McCullers </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-22 16:34:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> July 19th Fresno Boxscore </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-20 17:24:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> MLB Trade Rumors: Astros Trade Needs </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-15 03:19:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> King of TOOTBLAN: Jose Altuve </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-16 15:16:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> NYCRUNS Spring Fling 5k/10k </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-17 20:50:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Anyone else running this Saturday? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> First round of Spring Training cuts </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-11 16:17:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Running with my Mutt </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-22 17:24:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Any advice for training my mutt to run with me? He's a 40lb pretty low to the ground possible pit bull mix. We put him in training for petsmart for all the basic essentials so he's pretty good at commands (especially when treated). When running though he has started tugging at the leash during the first steps or he'll shoot out in front and then get distracted and start veering not paying attention. Any advice for the leash tugging? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Switch 4G/LTE on </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-02 02:42:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Just purchased an ATT variant for my wife. I use W10 personally and my wife was coming from an iPhone. I can't figure out how to enable LTE on her phone. I've tried opening the phone information with the *#*4636#*#* etc string but it says information isn't available for the phone. Any help is appreciated </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Groove Scrobbling </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-26 01:39:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Has anyone found a way to scrobble to last.fm from groove on mobile? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
