<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject8367</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Convict criminologists have all done time in prison and this firsthand experience now informs their research and teaching. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-11 15:19:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-10 17:34:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [Pit bull label for shelter dogs may triple length of stay](https://www.researchgate.net/blog/post/pit-bull-label-for-shelter-dogs-may-triple-length-of-stay) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Pit bull label for shelter dogs triples their length of stay </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-10 17:33:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-08 14:30:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> 1. [Japans monkeys wash their potatoes and ride deer like horses](https://www.researchgate.net/blog/post/japans-monkeys-wash-their-potatoes-and-ride-deer-like-horses)

2. [Social network and decision-making in primates: a report on Franco-Japanese research collaborations](https://www.researchgate.net/publication/287805563_Social_network_and_decision-making_in_primates_a_report_on_Franco-Japanese_research_collaborations)

3. [Interspecies sexual behaviour between a japanese macaque male and a sika deer female](https://www.asp.org/IPS/meetings/abstractDisplay.cfm?abstractID=6543 confEventID=7434) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Japanese macaque monkeys are able to wash their potatoes and ride deer like horses </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-08 14:29:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> An antibiotic has been discovered in human boogers that can treat even antibiotic-resistant forms of Staph, a Nature study describes </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-27 19:00:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> To protect yourself from malaria sleep with a chicken next to your bed </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-21 11:50:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Parasite Lives inside cricket growing to take up most of its body until it forces the cricket to drown itself and then comes out </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-13 15:21:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-13 15:15:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Haha exactly  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-12 18:20:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Warrior also lost Shield maiden :) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-12 17:44:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I have had a very similar experience with this deck. I'm waiting to get to the warrior farming but so far only getting aggro. I'm patient though. It will happen. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-12 17:17:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  Luca Santini, a biologist from Sapienza University Rome, is trying to answer some of the many unknowns surrounding climate change and the impact it will have on the environment. He and his team built a predictive model to estimate how quickly mammals can spread from their native habitats and whether they will be able to outpace the rate of climate change. We talked to him to find out why his estimate is likely to be conservative, and what we can do to mitigate the negative effects climate change could have on animals.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-01 16:52:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  A financial crisis is preventing the state from honoring its commitments to the Olympic and Paralympic Games, the governor said. That crisis is so severe, he said, it could eventually bring about a total collapse in public security, health, education, mobility and environmental management. The authorities are now authorized to ration essential public services and the state is eligible for emergency funds from the federal government. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Brazils Olympic Catastrophe - Can Rio pull off the Games with only weeks to go? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-01 16:52:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-01 15:27:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This is fantastic! I really appreciate this. I also loved the pie chart gif. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-01 15:22:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thank you kindly for your answer anyways! I will have a go at this deck </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-01 14:29:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What do people actually think of that RenoLock list with N'Zoth?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-01 14:24:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> When making a data visualization, do you know you have chosen the right graph if everyone understands the information being presented? Or is there any other considerations beyond just conveying meaning?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> 20 years after Australia's gun reform there have been no mass shootings and a decline in intentional firearm deaths, JAMA study finds. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-22 17:03:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-22 16:27:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Which CW list do you think is the most commonly played on ladder ATM? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-22 16:16:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I played a few games here but Boom on 7 almost every time still kills me. I think I need a few more months.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-17 14:18:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Full text: http://www.cell.com/cell/fulltext/S0092-8674(16)30730-9 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> New Cell study finds that the dietary addition of a single species of gut bacteria reverses autism-related social behavior in mice </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-17 14:15:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> TIL one of the most successful pirates in history was a Chinese former prostitute. She commanded around 80,000 men in the early 1800s </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-09 15:54:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-09 11:18:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Haha yeah but these guys are the suspected ancestors but they need more information before they can confirm this. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
