<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject4616</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> PSA - Hardback copy of Amazing Spider-Man: Spider-Verse is currently pre-ordering for 17 (x-post from /r/comicbooks) </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-07 01:33:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> David Fincher discusses the matured, "settled" Peter Parker he'd have featured in his take on Spider-Man, and its rapid, operatic opening sequence. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-03 03:17:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Teenage Mutant Ninja Turtles concept art featuring Bebop, Rocksteady, and Krang. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-03 03:05:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Lettered Preview: First look at Amazing Spider-Man #12 </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-01 17:50:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Right so, how are we all? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-12-14 05:24:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> How've we all been keeping? People feeling good about Christmas, fairly neutral, or is there something about the season of good will not sitting well? Be sure t'share, and throw in a suggestion for your breakfast, that new cereal cafe place has me hungry just reading about it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Euphoria-OS: The ROM Formerly Known as Mahdi hits 5.0 Lollipop. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-12-13 19:55:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Managing Twitter - Advice for the Overwhelmed </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-12-07 01:34:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Irish government retroactively legalizes GCHQ surveillance revealed in Snowden docs. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-12-07 01:00:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Meet Cublic - The Personal Artificial Intelligance Assistant with Personality </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-12-05 22:34:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Spider-Man film franchise internal discussions leaked following Sony hacking fiasco. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-12-05 01:20:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> TIL brain cells "shrink" during sleep, forming a lymphatic system which allows the brain to clear waste such as beta-amyloid, a peptide implicated in the development of Alzheimer's disease. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-12-02 01:23:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> "Santa Claus" on a coffee break in Tramore, Co. Waterford, Ireland. (x-post from /r/ireland) </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-11-29 22:41:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Sinkhole appears in Killarney, Co. Kerry. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-11-24 16:24:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Driver Theory Test - Recommended Apps? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-11-20 22:30:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I was wondering if anybody has any particular recommendation for a DTT app. A cursory search of Android's Play Store brings up a dozen options, and I'd imagine the iOS and Windows Phone platforms are similar.

If anybody could recommend an app specifically for tablets, so much the better. Many thanks! :-) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Suggestion - Move swipe for sidebar(s) slightly away from the edge. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-11-20 12:00:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [POSSIBLE SPOILERS] Is this the plot to Josh Trank's Fantastic Four reboot? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-11-18 00:24:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Trinity College dormitory evacuated due to Goldsmith Hall bedbug infestation. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-11-17 15:29:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Aunt May: The Movie - Could Sony be planning to explore May's pre-Peter spying career? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-11-11 17:23:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> So there's a water economist giving his spiel over on /r/IAmA (ctrl+F Ireland...) </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-11-11 17:06:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> LED Lightbulbs - Advice on converting the gaff... </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-11-10 00:04:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Pretty much what the title says, really. Has anybody converted (or, more realistically, partially converted) their home lighting to LED? If so, how did you go about it? More importantly, has it brought any side effects? I know they had a reputation for being "colder," as they say, a number of years ago, but that problem is largely behind us, no? Perhaps most importantly, has the investment paid off? Aside from the bulbs lasting longer, have you noticed a decrease in your electricity bill?

Finally, any advice on where best to source the bulbs would be great. Online ordering would be preferred, although I wouldn't be opposed to visiting a brick-and-mortar store if anyone can recommend one.

Many thanks in advance folks, I'm looking forward t'hearing your suggestions soon. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Looks like Big Boss's photography skills made the top post on the front page... </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-11-09 17:49:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [feature request] Have we a way of delaying a comment until the appropriate thread shows up? Example inside... </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-11-02 01:53:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So I finally bought myself a Nexus 7 tablet, and I've come up with a *lot* of questions while flashing custom ROMs and tweaking the settings of various kernels, so many that I should have a list as long as my arm by the time the usual Moronic Monday thread shows up on /r/android. It'd be a really amazing implementation of the [RemindMeBot](http://www.reddit.com/r/RemindMeBot/comments/24duzp/remindmebot_info/), for example, if I could ask a question somewhere here in RES and have it post to the relevant weekly thread once it shows up, all I'd have to do is wait for a post to my inbox.

I appreciate that this has pitfalls - I've managed to solve half my issues myself since encountering them, original research should be strongly encouraged when a problem first arises - but I feel that the benefits definitely outweigh the advantages. Responsible use of this feature (i.e. editing a question yourself if you've found an answer, for example) could also be strictly enforced where possible.

What do we think? Is this a feature we could see implemented at some point? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> "There are no strings on me..." - Now available in T-Shirt form! </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-10-26 01:48:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Gifferific cover to Amazing Spider-Man (1963) #33 </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-10-25 20:02:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Bomb threat in Aras an Uachtarain forces presidential evacuation. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-10-25 18:45:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> An Android equivalent for iOS 8's Instant Hotspot? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-10-19 17:25:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Spider-Verse Team Up #1 variant cover art by Dave Rapoza (x-post from /r/comicbooks) </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-10-19 00:20:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Spider-Verse Team Up #1 variant cover art by Dave Rapoza </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-10-19 00:19:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Visualisation of Global Android Activations (Oct 2008 - Jan 2011) </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-10-17 19:47:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Silk also getting her own ongoing - by Robbie Thompson and Stacey Lee </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-10-13 02:05:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Superior Spider-Memories - Sequart Magazine's take on the psychology behind Otto/Pete's mind swap. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-10-12 20:58:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> So we made the front page... (x-post from /r/worldnews R.E. Water Protests) </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-10-12 17:10:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Personal Finance Apps - Y'know, for Irish banks? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-10-01 20:29:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I became very interested not too long ago in Mint.com, and was thoroughly disappointed to learn that it isn't compatible with our banking system, due to a lack of available APIs or some such.

I was wondering if anything had changed since then, and what we're using to manage our money online. I've been investigating [BillGuard](https://www.billguard.com/), but I haven't had much luck finding anyone with home I could compare notes.

Any information is useful, hopefully we can initiate a useful discussion. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Big Boss and Skull Face - Handling their Soldiers. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-09-26 19:08:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I noticed in the E3 2013 Red Band trailer that Skull Face was quite light handed, for want of a better way of putting it, in approaching his soldiers. I imagined that this was just an aspect of the character, the appearance he'd created for himself, until I saw Big Boss himself moving in a similar fashion in the recent *Quiet but not Silent* trailer. I've included the two below, earmarked at the relevant times, for your consideration:

[E3 2013 - Skull Face's movements.](http://www.youtube.com/watch?v=NL4ZxDWLwpM#t=6m51s)

[*Quiet but not Silent* - Big Boss's movements.](https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=B94LZ1a-3To#t=1m40.73s)

There seems to be a similarity with how delicately each man approaches his own soldiers, and I was wondering if this was some kind of technique. Obviously neither man wants to startle anyone who's armed, right?

Please feel free to post any possible theories/explanations below, I'll be happy to read through them all. :-) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Three Quick Questions - The Dot View Case... </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-09-21 02:28:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hi all,

As the title says, I've three quick questions I'm hoping can be answered briefly:

1) Does the case in question hinder the famed Boomsound speakers? If not, is there a way for interacting with music via said case? I'm open to suggestions that involve Xposed/other root options.

2) Does the case interfere with the camera in any way? I've imagined that a vertically opening flip case would be a much more ergonomic idea than the current horizontal one, but then again the opposite case is likely true for people who typically flip their phone horizontally for photographs.

3) Has anybody experimented with wireless charging? For example, would a Qi receiver fit neatly between the phone itself and the case's back, or is it likely to protrude?

Many thanks /r/htcone, I'm looking forward to hearing if anybody can answer my questions! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Right, it's Sunday - How have we all been this week? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-09-21 01:11:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You folks know the drill, what's been going on? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Silent Hills P.T. Concept Trailer - Was a MGSV:GZ model re-used @ 0:26? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-09-18 18:35:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Leap Card via Mobile Phone's NFC? (x-post from /r/Android) </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-09-15 17:14:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm wondering if anybody's used the method outlined [here](http://www.reddit.com/r/Android/comments/2ge7x3/44_emulate_transit_cards_using_nfc/) to enable their phone to emulate their Leap Card. It seems like a logical step forward for Leap, but given how long it took the system to come into effect in the first place we probably won't see it officially supported for some time.

Anybody got any commentary? What would Network Noel have to say? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Les Enfants Terribles: Big Boss, Eva, and the Kids - by Zarla Sheenaza </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-09-09 18:00:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Guardians of the Galaxy - So who exactly sought what? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-09-07 02:20:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hi all, quick question.

In *Guardians of the Galaxy*, we presume Thanos sought The Orb for the Infinity Stone contained therein, and we also assume that he seeks the other five. As Ronan was in his employ, we know that Ronan sought The Orb for Thanos, in order to fulfil his part of their deal.

This presents two questions:

1) What did The Broker want with The Orb? Who was he tasked with acquiring it for? We know it wasn't Ronan, although it may still have been Thanos. Whether or not he knew it held an Infinity Stone is still unknown.

2) What did The Collector want with The Orb? He knew it held an Infinity Stone, that's for sure, and he's also in search of the other five. This makes it unlikely that he sought The Orb for Ronan, but he may still have been in league with Thanos.

It's been a while since I've seen the movie, so bear with me if some details have eluded my memory, but any theories or debate on the query would be more than welcome. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Twitter desktop and mobile clients - a couple of quick questions. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-09-06 23:15:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hey all,

I've never been what you could call a serious Twitter user, but I'm hoping to change that soon.

My question mostly concerns desktop Twitter clients; I understand Tweetdeck is a shadow of what it was, but is it really my best option? Is there an alternative which could rival Tweetdeck's glory days?

If not, that's no problem, but I would like to know if there's a way for me to create a column which feeds me relevant hashtags from a given region; ultimately, I'd like to select:

 Add Column - Trending - Trends: United States of America - City: New York

And stop there, without having to select a hashtag specifically trending in New York. I feel like this would be a great way to give me a good overview of what's trending in New York City, with another column for, say, Dublin, Ireland beside it. This would be a great way to get a general overview of the city, and I'd be better able to keep up with friends who have gone abroad.

Secondly, I'm wondering if the official app in Google's Play Store is really my best option for mobile tweeting. I'm happy to wait if a dev is rumoured to be in the running for more tokens, and if so any guidance would be appreciated. Many thanks.

Finally, I'm curious as to what this news is about a "filtered" feed? Is this an experiment similar to what Facebook performed recently? Or a move away from a chronological timeline of events in my feed? Many thanks for any explanation.

Thanks again for taking the time to read this post, I'll be looking forward to hearing any advice seasoned Twitterers can offer me.

subject4616. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Bag Question - Peter Quill's from Guardians of the Galaxy </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-09-05 21:08:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hey all.

First time posting here, so I'll get straight to the point; I really liked the look of the shoulder-chest bag Chris Pratt's character, Peter Quill/Star-Lord had in *Guardians of the Galaxy*. It looked comfortable, practical, and stylish, basically everything I've been looking for in a satchel/messenger bag but have never been able to find. I wondered if anyone could provide me with any information as to what bag this was? I've included some photos - they mightn't be 100% movie accurate, but they should hopefully be enough to jog the memory of anyone who may be able to help.

1) [This](http://marveltoynews.com/wp-content/uploads/2014/07/Star-Lord-Hot-Toys-Accessories-MMS255-e1406129291314.jpg) is probably the best image, it shows him wearing it to the right and the bag itself to the left.

2) [This one](http://2.bp.blogspot.com/-OJs4io-ROis/U8s32Pasm-I/AAAAAAAAjgY/PDtZBx6qPCE/s1600/San+Diego+Comic-Con+2014+Exclusive+Guardians+of+the+Galaxy+Star-Lord+Hoodie+by+Marvel.jpg) is also quite good, it's based on a hoodie Marvel is releasing.

3) There's also [this one](http://1.bp.blogspot.com/-EIWrMqzv6wk/U5ZyjZoCPnI/AAAAAAAAJEo/bzdzlprK6OM/s1600/IMG_4061.JPG), a good overview of the bag closed. The blasters would be a welcome accessory, but aren't necessary.

4) Finally, [these](http://www.gq.com/images/copilot/entertainment/201408/1406910558573_01-chris-pratt-peter-quill.jpg) [two](http://4.bp.blogspot.com/-tzHqqHzBFt0/U9-tzBoXDhI/AAAAAAAAHXw/D8jxUAtTcjA/s1600/140801113451-guardians-of-the-galaxy-chris-pratt-082014-story-top.jpg) are screenshots from the film itself, although they don't appear to show the second strap, which is a feature I quite liked.

I'm looking forward to hearing if you can guide me to either this bag itself or something reasonably similar. Many thanks in advance /r/malefashionadvice. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Light House Cinema now recruiting ScamBridge interns - "Third level education preferred" </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-08-11 15:30:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> OTTO. IS. BACK! SSM #32 Lettered Preview. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-08-01 13:23:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Right so, how's everyone been this week? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-07-13 13:15:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I didn't see the usual thread, so I figured I'd take charge of it. Go ahead /r/Ireland, how've we all been keeping? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Finding 6tag photos on phone? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-07-10 11:58:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hey all, quick question.

A number of months ago I was using a Lumia 720, WP 8.0, and began to experiment with Rudy's excellent 6tag. i was very pleased with the first image I took, but never posted it to my Instagram account due to initial confusion over sharing with other social networks, followed by a battery drain.

Having used Instagram's official Android app since, I see that completed images are saved to the device before upload, and was wondering if this was true for WP 8.0 too. Does anyone know of a way I might retrieve this image from the phone, or indeed whether there's any possibility that the image is still on the device? Any information at all would be helpful, as I would really love to have this photo back; the associated memories are beyond precious to me.

Many thanks in advance, /r/windowsphone. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> "A computer virus that mimics FOXDIE..." - Ocelot, MGS2 </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-07-07 04:50:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What exactly is meant when Ocelot says this during the climax of *Sons of Liberty* [here](http://youtu.be/k1G2XA2Xz6w?t=4m37s)? I'm not entirely sure how the virus should be accepted as a mimicry of Snake's FOXDIE, can anybody offer an explanation?

Many thanks in advance for the discussion! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Finding 6tag photos on phone? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-06-17 00:26:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hey all, quick question.

A number of months ago I was using a Lumia 720, WP 8.0, and began to experiment with Rudy's excellent 6tag. i was very pleased with the first image I took, but never posted it to my Instagram account due to initial confusion over sharing with other social networks, followed by a battery drain.

Having used Instagram's official Android app since, I see that completed images are saved to the device before upload, and was wondering if this was true for WP 8.0 too. Does anyone know of a way I might retrieve this image from the phone, or indeed whether there's any possibility that the image is still on the device? Any information at all would be helpful, as I would really love to have this photo back; the associated memories are beyond precious to me.

Many thanks in advance, /r/windowsphone. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> "In everything, do to others as you would have them do to you; for this is the law and the prophets." - Matthew 7:12 </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-06-15 22:13:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hi all, curious Christian (Catholic) here.

I came across [this collection](http://imgur.com/gallery/7s1BB) of different versions of the Bible verse quoted in the title, and I was disappointed not to see some fitting line from the Bah' writings. I wonder if anybody could direct me to the most appropriate text, as I'm sure there are several.

Many thanks in advance; here's to hoping that we'll see the most popular suggestion included the next time the linked images are shared. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> /u/Echono explains what Comcast is trying to do to the Internet, using electricity as a simple analogy. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-05-17 21:27:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> PushBullet and Chrome Full Screen... </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-03-30 06:23:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hi all,

Just started using PushBullet this evening, it's an amazing app with incredible potential for me. I have, however, a small question: I use Chrome in Full Screen mode on my Macbook, and while I hear a notification to alert me to a mirrored notification, I can't actually see anything in Chrome. This problem seems to be exclusive to running Chrome in Full Screen mode.

Clearly this robs the app of a great deal of its potential, and if anyone can recommend a fix that'd be hugely appreciated, many thanks in advance. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Moto X Just Arrived! Post-root recommendations, anyone? [x-post from /r/Android] </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-03-26 01:42:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hey all,

Okay, I exaggerate a little, it came late last week, and while I've yet to activate the sim, I've rooted the device and installed the Xposed Framework. Apart from that the unit is fresh out of the box, and I'm hopeful that you wonderful and informed people can offer me any further advice or knowledge before I finally make my first Android device my daily driver.

Any particular apps you might recommend? What about Xposed modules, or specific GravityBox tweaks? Any other tips, tricks, or hacks that I should be made aware of?

Reading through this post is thoroughly appreciated, and I'm hugely grateful for any advice that any of you can offer.

Thanks in advance! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Moto X Just Arrived! Post-root recommendations, anyone? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-03-26 01:30:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> MFW I see someone else in public using Windows Phone... </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-03-07 17:07:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Google Now Always Listening - Nexus 5 vs Moto X </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-03-05 17:15:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hi all!

I'm a little confused about the Always Listening feature of Google Now, and it's been keeping me on the fence regarding the two phones above. I was under the impression that the Moto X shipped with an low-power core used exclusively to listen for commands. The reason the Nexus 5 didn't have this, as I understood it, was because it lacked such a core, and enabling any sort of Always Listening for the phone would ramp up processor use, and therefore battery consumption.

I'm now reading that the Nexus 5 *does*, in fact, possess such a core, which changes things entirely.

If anybody could offer a clear and concise explanation as to what, exactly, the reality of the situation is, I would be most appreciative. Any further input on the two phones mentioned above would also be helpful, specifically in reference to ergonomics - I've heard great things about the Moto X, but having held a Nexus 5 for the first time today I'm quite impressed...

Many thanks once again,

subject4616. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Have there been detailed studies concerning how different users perceive the World Wide Web? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-03-02 23:53:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hi all!

I've been thinking lately about how the Internet, originally designed as a robust communications system, may well be dividing society at large, due to inherent societal behaviour. With Google monitoring users to "improve" feedback, how great is the divide from one individual to another thought to be?

I'm also interested in studies which identify social media usage as such a dividing factor. For instance, sharing content via Facebook/Twitter may seem like a way to break down barriers formed by Google's habits, but is it likely that those users are isolating themselves based upon their own social stratification?

Any material, simple or complex, will be of great interest, and I thank you in advance for your time. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Inceptor - The Dream Based Board Game! [x-post from /r/gaming] </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-02-27 02:52:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> "Breathe Like a Boss" - Poster about the negative effects of Febreze Air Freshener. Can we get some more of these? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-02-24 21:40:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> So my mom did some baking yesterday... </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-02-22 19:48:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> So the Keeper learned Headbutt... </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-02-20 13:14:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The only answer to the Anarchy/Democracy debate... </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-02-19 00:12:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Coffee Run. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-02-02 23:03:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Dad's response to a simple grocery shopping request... </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-01-11 15:51:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So my dad was heading out to the supermarket, and wanted to know if there was anything we needed. I mentioned that we'd no teabags, but he went to check anyway. He picked up the box, and informed me that we had a whole box. My brother and I looked at him, wondering if he hadn't felt the weightlessness of it.

"I never said we had a whole box of tea, but we definitely have a whole box! There are no holes in it!"

Much rolling of eyes followed... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Hideo Kojima to direct a Silent Hill game? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-01-08 20:49:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Razer announces new wearable - The Nabu </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-01-07 23:12:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> HDMI Passthrough and XBMC </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-12-28 06:32:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hey all, quick question as per the title.

I'm wondering how nicely XBMC plays with HDMI passthrough. For example, if I'm running XBMC (either in Windows/Linux or as a standalone Linux-based OS) on a HTPC, with a HDMI leading into it from the HTPC and out of it to the television, will I be able to select to play the PS3 via XBMC? If, for instance, the PS3 is left in standby mode, will selecting it in XBMC wake it up?

Sorry if this question comes across as unclear, I'll be happy to clean up any inadvertent confusion, and I'm grateful in advance for your input and assistance.

subject4616. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> I knew science was cool, but never dreamed it was THIS cool! </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-12-21 19:50:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> I've been going through some stuff lately, and Googled "Never Give Up" for a quick shot of inspiration. This was one of the top results. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-12-16 06:07:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Amazon running a sale on everything you need to build a PC! </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-11-19 18:15:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> MISSING PERSON - Last Seen in Rathfarnham </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-10-22 01:41:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Iron Spider - Suit Up! [Went down well over at /r/spiderman, thought I'd share here.] </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-10-22 01:04:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Iron Spider - Suit Up! </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-10-19 01:32:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Now let me go... </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-10-18 22:52:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Baconography, this is unacceptable... </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-10-15 22:38:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> So I found this sub... </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-08-26 14:44:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Early Avengers animatics reveal what might have been, including Wasp! </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-08-25 14:35:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Recording lectures/conferences on a Windows Phone 8 device... </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-08-16 22:57:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hey all!

My question's in the title, really. I'm wondering what hardware/software combo you knowledgable folks would recommend for the aforementioned task. Obviously I'd require something with decent recording quality, but the battery life of the unit in question would need to be fairly heavy duty. Aside from recording several hours straight, it'd also need the stamina to receive push e-mail throughout the day. Basically heavy use for twelve hours at a time, really.

Finally, if there are specific apps anyone could recommend for the task of creating quality audio recordings I'd thoroughly appreciate the advice. Free is preferable, but I'm willing to pay for the best experience, if necessary.

Many thanks for your input, I'm looking forward to reading all of your responses. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> "Liquid and Solid hunted down Big Boss, trying to sever the tie that bound them to him" - Solidus, *MGS2* </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-07-14 01:00:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> http://www.youtube.com/watch?v=KqOZ2aC2hXs#t=56s

So at 0:56 Solidus explains to Raiden that Snake and Liquid both sought out Big Boss, but when? Okay, we could argue that Snake "hunted" him in *Metal Gear* and *Metal Gear 2: Solid Snake*, even though he was already working with the man at that stage, but what about Liquid? When did he hunt Big Boss?

Is it possible that we'll see Liqiud's pursuit of BB in *MGSV*? At the very least, this line lends credence to the "Eli = Liquid" theory floating about... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> David Hayter adapting Image Comics series The Sword </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-07-08 21:49:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> "Ocelot - A Rival living a Lie" </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-07-02 01:39:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So we see Ocelot at [6:57](http://www.youtube.com/watch?v=XVUYdPkFuMY#t=6m57.5s) in the latest trailer, and he's described as "A Rival living a Lie." Okay, the capitalization seems a little random, but has anyone wondered about what the text actually means?

Whose rival is he? Why is he living a lie? I mean, he's working alongside Big Boss, the only man he's ever actually been true to in his loyalty. I know it's difficult to keep tabs on Ocelot due to his nature as a double/triple agent, but the one ultimate truth throughout the whole series about the man has been his loyalty to Big Boss.

Apologies if this has already been discussed to death, I was away during the initial trailer reveal and I can't seem to find the search button with the new (and thoroughly beautiful) layout, so if anyone could point me in the direction of further discussion that'd be much appreciated. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Cold War era spy equipment (x-post from /r/pics, see if you recognize anything!) </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-05-11 12:48:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> WINTER SOLDIER issue #18 preview, the origin of The Electric Ghost. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-04-28 15:44:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> At some point in *MGSV*... </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-04-16 01:16:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> ...we'll discover we've been playing a portion of the game as Decoy Octopus.

You read it here first! :-P </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Possible explanation for Hayter's absence? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-04-01 00:42:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Okay, I was thinking about Big Boss's extensive career, and I briefly wondered how he had managed to escape any symptoms of radiation poisoning. I mean, c'mon, maybe you could downplay his involvement in Bikini Atoll, but the guy's since been exposed to large doses, and hasn't seen any negative effects. Or has he?

A symptom of radiation exposure which BB himself mentioned is thyroid cancer. Some of his friends from Bikini Atoll went on to develop this illness, as mentioned in the second paragraph of [this](http://metalgear.wikia.com/wiki/Big_Boss#Early_years) article. A symptom of thyroid cancer may include [changes in voice](http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Thyroid_cancer#Symptoms)...

How extreme are these changes? I can't say for sure, but a quick glance at the literature seems to indicate that it may become [hoarser](http://www.endocrineweb.com/conditions/thyroid-cancer/thyroid-cancer-symptoms) and [cracklier](http://csn.cancer.org/node/190723), and [tired more easily](http://blog.voicewize.com/2011/08/18/minimally-invasive-thyroid-surgery-voice/).

Whether this would be enough to warrant Hayter's replacement is unclear. I mean, I didn't think you could get much growlier than Hayter without going full Christian Bale. I mean, if Kojima *did* want to work this into the story, I'm sure he could do so with DH on board. 

I'm a firm believer that we'll see (hear?) Hayter in *MGSV* (and it'll be about as surprising as Konami's involvement with *The Phantom Pain*), but in what capacity is anyone's guess. 

Anyway, the floor's open to discussion, so feel free to pick apart my theory, I'm looking forward to hearing your feedback! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> There... there is not title for this... </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-03-17 16:50:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Interview tips for a biochem grad? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-03-10 03:42:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hey all! 

So I've an interview on Monday morning with the P.I. of a clinical bioinformatics lab in a nearby university, and I really want to make it work. I graduated last year with a biochem undergrad degree, and while I do have some experience in bioinformatics (via both taught and research routes), as well as a working knowledge of and thorough interest in computers, I know very little about programming. I am willing to learn, of course.

I've examined much of the material on the lab's website, in terms of both the lab's overall goals and the research interests of individual personnel, and I'll been invited to meet these other researchers over lunch following the interview. I'm wondering is there any practical advice that /r/bioinformatics could offer? Are there any particular topics I should mention, or any that I should avoid? I'm extremely excited at the prospect of obtaining this position, and I'd also appreciate advice on how I should organize myself in the first couple of days (provided I actually get the job!), first impressions being what they are and all that. 

Any additional reading material or well-wishes would be much appreciated, and rest assured I'll be back to let my new favourite sub know how it all went. 

Many thanks in advance! :-) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Cambridge Consultants develops indoor tech to pick up where GPS drops off </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-03-08 16:57:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> All this 90s nostalgia reminded me of this... </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-03-07 20:48:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What's the most useful phone app you have? [x-post from /r/askreddit] /r/windowsphone represent! </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-03-01 19:31:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Zero Allies - Piano Cover </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-02-27 23:46:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Iron Man 3 concept art leak... (POSSIBLE SPOILERS!!!) </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-02-23 18:15:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> If you say so, Supes! </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-02-17 23:09:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Awesome MGS1 Foxhound wallpaper I found... </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-02-08 19:58:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [TOMT][Webcomic] Snowmen brought from a detention camp to a mountain, then flattened for skiers... </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-01-21 00:44:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I saw this a couple of times in the last month, and wanted to send it to a friend who's going skiing in a couple of weeks, but haven't had any luck finding it.

Basically it starts out with a group of soldiers visiting a detention camp filled with snowmen. They march the snowmen into trucks, and drive them to a mountain, where they unload them and proceed to savagely beat them with their batons. The snowmen are flattened into piles of snow, leaving a very picturesque mountain, and the following day skiers arrive and hit the slopes, none-the-wiser of the atrocity committed just the previous night...

So yeah, if anyone could help me out here that'd be great! :-) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Metal Gear Mk. II case mod. Pictures aplenty! </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-01-15 18:26:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Proposed merger with /r/metalgear? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-01-14 17:31:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Anybody think we should merge with/r/metalgear? They're a much smaller and far less active subreddit, we could absorb them quite easily. I see no reason not to, really...

Edit: Okay, so there's been a hugely positive response to this idea from you folks. Meanwhile, over in /r/metalgear, the submission hasn't even been seen. If anybody needed convincing that a merger was required, that's it right there, y'ask me. In the interest of fairness to the other sub, however, I'll wait until 24 hours has passed since making this suggestion, and then I'll get onto the mods of both subs concerned.

Edit 2: Alright, well I've sent each of the two subreddit's mods the following message:

 Hi there Killerzeit/mezzism/SnakeLinkSonic/Deadlypuf/Yen24/Ganonsfoot/dbarts21/DOOMz_illa!

 I'm contacting you regarding an idea I proposed in [/r/metalgearsolid]...(http://www.reddit.com/r/metalgearsolid/comments/16k2hf/proposed_merger_with_rmetalgear/) and [/r/metalgear](http://www.reddit.com/r/metalgear/comments/16k2e4/proposed_merger_with_rmetalgearsolid/) to overwhelmingly positive response; users are interested in the possibility of merging these two subreddits. Specifically, we would like to see the former absorb the latter. 
/r/metalgearsolid would be renamed /r/metalgear, but keep its present look, with the possible addition of crimzind's redesigned subreddit logo as well.

 Users have brought up concerns regarding who the moderator duties should fall to, but I           personally feel that this would be a good opportunity for certain mods to reconsider their interest in the role, and for us to appoint new blood if necessary.

 Please see the discussion [here](http://www.reddit.com/r/metalgearsolid/comments/16k2hf/proposed_merger_with_rmetalgear/) for  more information, and feel free to contact me with any additional questions you may have, I'll be happy to field them.

 Yours sincerely,

 subject4616

It's all in their hands now, but the fact that this post received over 120 upvotes and nearly fifty comments, and the identical post in [/r/metalgear](http://www.reddit.com/r/metalgear/comments/16k2e4/proposed_merger_with_rmetalgearsolid/) wasn't even seen says a huge amount, I think. Also, I've glanced the activity of each mod, and found /u/Deadlypuf's appointment to the position to be most curious, considering his/her overall activity...

Anyway, many thanks to everyone who replied for their input. It's in the mod's hands now of course, but I'll keep you all informed as to any changes as they take place...

Edit 3: I've been invited to become a mod of /r/metalgear... Since we'll hopefully be running that show soon, I just wanna ask; d'you guys accept me to moderate that subreddit? I'll only take the job if you guys would be happy t'see me in the position, otherwise I'll turn it down, no questions asked. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Proposed merger with /r/metalgearsolid? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-01-14 17:30:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> /r/metalgearsolid just seems like a much more active subreddit, I'm this one could be absorbed and integrated into it quite easily. Really, is there any reason not to? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> How society reacts to new ideas... [gif + comments] </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-01-12 15:51:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Transporter: the peer-to-peer social storage solution </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-12-07 19:03:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Wii Mini confirmed - Canada exclusive until 2013, priced $99.99 </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-11-27 18:20:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Gray Fox skin coming to MGR: Revengeance via GameStop pre-order </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-11-22 18:35:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Gadgets! Charge 'em if you got 'em! </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-10-29 21:59:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Here comes Hurricane Sandy: Charge 'em if you got 'em [xpost /r/android and /r/apple] </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-10-29 01:54:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Mind blowing Ben Howard cover - Keep Your Head Up. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-10-18 14:47:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> So reddit, we've read WAY too many threads on people cheating on their SO, tell us about the sheer levels of loyalty, devotion, and love you've witnessed in a relationship. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2011-12-08 11:46:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> DAE think Apple should get Paul Bettany (who voiced JARVIS in the Iron Man films) to provide Siri's voice? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2011-10-06 00:45:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Amanda Knox cleared of Meredith Kercher murder </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2011-10-03 21:55:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> So I've just finished reading Paul Pope's Batman: Year 100... </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2011-08-13 02:14:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I enjoyed it, and I'll certainly be revisiting it before long to digest the artwork and further examine the story, but I'd like to hear the opinion's of other Batfans, and this is certainly the place get them!

For those who haven't read it yet, I'd certainly recommend you pick it up, not immediately, but when you get the chance. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Response to Whynne's request [first post, true story!] </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2011-07-16 19:27:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> One for every occasion! </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2011-07-11 15:07:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Philosoraptor chimes in on the riots in Vancouver (crosspost from /r/adviceanimals) </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2011-06-18 04:08:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Illogical Douchebag Rioter (crosspost from /r/adviceanimals) </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2011-06-18 03:08:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Piracy at college: share your stories, Reddit! </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2010-08-05 01:51:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Just wondering if anybody has any interesting tales of file sharing from their college years. What kind of setup did you have, how did you go about implementing it, and did you ever get caught? If so, what were the consequences? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Piracy at college: share your stories, Reddit! </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2010-07-31 23:57:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Index of /album, just a small collection of random (SFW) images, still thought it was worth sharing though. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2010-07-30 20:30:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Index of /garbage, mostly images and MP3s, as well as some videos. Bon Apptit! </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2010-07-18 15:52:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Adding your content to an existing torrent? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2010-07-13 19:03:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> In an effort to increase my ratio on a number of well known private trackers, I've been considering uploading my own DVDs/CDs. However, many of these are already available on said trackers, but they have very few (if any) seeders.

What I'm wondering is would it be possible for me to make my personal copy of this media available as part of an existing torrent?

Chime in with your suggestions/solutions, I look forward to your advice, Reddit! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> TIL that the asterisk beside a Reddit comment means that that comment has been edited! </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2010-06-15 02:08:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I was enlightened when a fellow Redditor questioned another Redditor as to why they needed to edit a one line comment, and I noted that the comment in question had an asterisk beside it! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Howdy Reddit, any advice on giving an old laptop a new lease on life? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2010-06-08 21:33:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So Reddit, I'm currently operating from a five year old notebook, packing a 1.73GHz Intel Pentium M processor, 512MB of RAM, Intel GMA 900 integrated graphics, and Windows XP Professional SP2. It's in good condition, but I'm hoping to replace it soon with a more portable solution.

Thing is, I've grown quite attached to the laptop, and I see no reason to retire it to a lifetime of gathering dust when it's still in such good condition. I've been thinking about how I might utilize it, and have come up with a couple of possibilities:

* A network-attached storage server, using FreeNAS in a virtual machine to manage a few terabytes spread across several external HDDs.
* A bittorrent box, to manage the seeding and leeching of all of that free, libre, and open source software! ;-)
* A personal SSH server, to bypass the ol' work filter that foolishly attempts to keep me from my Reddit!
* An XBMC Media Centre.

I'd also consider adding a distributed computing client to it (such as Folding@Home) and possibly Asterisk, the open source telephony project. Upgrading the current laptop isn't out of the question, for example maxing out the RAM, installing a low capacity SSD, and possibly adding an external graphics card

Absolutely any advice on achieving/maintaining my desired setup is welcome, as well as tips about what else I might be able to pump out of the machine. Ideally I'd like to enable Wake-on-LAN, so that the machine isn't wasting too much power when not in use, so if anyone could advise me in that regard it would also be appreciated.

One more thing Redditor's would be qualified to advise me on is what to replace the notebook with. I'd consider a netbook ideal, but feel free to promote your Macbooks, iPads, Dell Streaks and anything else that you think would suit.

Thanks so much in advance, HiveMind, I'm sure you won't let me down!

Edit: Formatting... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> You'll never look at Dugtrio the same way again... </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2010-06-03 00:54:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> STOP! Hammer Time!!! </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2010-05-19 15:58:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
