<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject3591</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-12 17:40:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm kind of scared of that Uni. (second from left middle row)
Can you eat that? It just looks so un-edible. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-12 17:32:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So, there was a local 4x4 Tacoma in the paper for $9999.  205,000 miles.  How does that happen? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-12 16:31:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So, the magnet holds the piece to the wheel while the grinder comes down and you turn it to get the cross hatch? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-12 16:18:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah, I was going to say this looks like a brake rotor for a ski lift.  The one I saw recently was for a high speed quad detachable and was maybe 40" </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-11 00:13:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Well, I didn't realize that it was an album with additional photos.  Oops, looks great! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-10 23:58:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Well, first off there's nothing double about it except there are two and each one has two slices of tomato and maybe two slices of cheese over the tomato. One has two rings of raw onion, the other three.  Then we get to the bun.  I looks good, and if you made it yourself, congrats.  No one would buy it though.  Maybe next time try some egg wash or butter and sesame seeds for a more even finished look.  The only other things about it is the patties are too small and they look like Jimmy Dean sausage. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-10 23:22:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I think OP has dysleia. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-10 22:59:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I've got a thinner one coming to my plate soon.  Going to do a bit of reverse sear, and it's pretty large so thinking to cut the bone off and roast it separately with the potato.  Good job! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-10 04:48:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yes, plus their seeds drift with the wind and water and then they sue small farmers for patent violation! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-10 04:41:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> When we first got Mercedes engines in snow tractors the starter was $1800 brand new from Germany.  In fact, they probably still are a whole lot from the dealer. Alternators were even worse.  They're really close to the Unimog 24v, but I've had terrible luck with the chinese ones.  Like the thing won't spin, the fan isn't stuck to the shaft, stupid stuff. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-10 04:34:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I had to buy an exhaust manifold for an old (think '86 350) Chevy engine (Ford fleet) once a few years ago and found it at Autozone.  Well, it had to come from the manufacturer or a distribution center or something.  Somehow it was there the next day (rural) and they didn't even charge me for shipping.  Not sure if f*ck up or usual service. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-10 04:21:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I guess no one cares about Palisade peaches, but one of these days it will take off. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-10 03:27:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> visited the website, very nice. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-10 02:52:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> heh, frog legs anyone? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-10 02:36:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Looks great especially for takeout.  Dunno how much pasta I could eat after all this. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-10 02:21:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Does OP photo shop these, the dog and table and the rest are always the same lol </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-10 01:53:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> the restaurant ran out of rice. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-08 02:48:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Also good to add quarters of onion to the simmer.  You can put them on the grill also afterwards. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-07 02:52:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's important to get them good and black, steam them in a bag and peel those chiles right away because the peel is a lot thicker than a jalapeno or anaheim.  It comes off clear/charred. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-07 01:45:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> that chop is the best looking I've ever seen.  Did you use a flame torch on it after the sous vide, because in a pan you can't get that coverage all over? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-05 19:50:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I had an 86 944 base model.  67k miles.  It had a newer set of wheels than these, and got 27 mpg.  It was a great car till some jerk t-boned me driver's door 10 weeks later. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-05 19:34:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's a headlamp housing.  How is it possible to call it a klingon?  http://www.ebay.com/itm/International-head-lamp-housing-2512518C91-/162129560670 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-04 22:27:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It ain't no thing but a chicken wing. A service mechanic told me once he worked for years and didn't use a drain pan when servicing logging equipment.  Probably the same for construction. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-04 22:14:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hey, that lift table is really nifty. I'm going to show this picture to my boss as we totally fubared the table we have. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-04 21:20:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I've had a few great dealings with LKQ. One call does it all. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-04 21:17:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I got a sweet t-shirt from Napa for one of the contests I entered. I think it was regarding a cruise to the Bahamas. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-04 21:11:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> My boss won a contest for golf course supers. You have to know a lot about grass (lol), and be a member of the institution and get lucky on the draw. We got a brand new utility truckstrer from Toro, and he got to go play in a tournament and who knows what else (hookers and blow). </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-04 21:04:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Why do we use copper nuts on turbochargers?  I'm sure it has to do with heat, but some of the nuts are steel. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-04 20:55:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I heard someone say that the average life of a traffic cone is 30 minutes.  Its an exaggeration.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-04 20:31:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Wow, I did not know that. Top of the line. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-04 17:30:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That
's
nice
but why
not
put them in order 
sweet to hot? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-04 17:27:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I like the portion sizes! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-04 17:16:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Caulichos! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-04 17:15:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I just picture that time that Guy F did the same on DDD and the juices were coming out all over, the owner was giving him dagger eyes. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-04 17:07:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Looks fun. Maybe add the potato and steak first, the rest later? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-04 17:03:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Is pork knuckle the knee joint then? I've never seen it here in USA, maybe they ship them all overseas. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-04 16:39:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Ooh, that would be good with sausage also. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-04 16:32:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Fennel or Anise is the main flavor with other herbs/spices.  The hot version adds crushed pepper flakes. The sweet version features basil. http://www.johnsonville.com/lines/italian.html </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-04 16:28:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Ah, so the filling is hot but you need to warm up the beans, cheese and salsa.  It should have salsa! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-04 16:16:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Seems like a good way to survive a hurricane massacre. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-04 16:14:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That album makes me want to buy a sous vide, vacuum machine, bunch of bags, binder clips, steal some spoons from work.  Oh, and a steak, stupid expensive package of rosemary and head of garlic. Some butter and a potato. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-04 00:59:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Ok </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-04 00:57:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So if I handed you a cold one when you're hiking in the desert, you'd need to go sterilize it under 170 degree f water? There's a reason that you have an immune system. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-04 00:53:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Had fish with cottage cut fries yesterday.  I thought it was ok, but my brother didn't like the "chefy" tartar sauce. He's like, how can you f-up tartar sauce.  I didn't even notice. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-03 05:21:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> so sad.  I've got to lighten the mood.  I once heard a story about a paraplegic who got a few million in a settlement regarding his injury.  So hey, I'm young why not try to make some more money in this new bungie jumping industry? They buy some equipment, and he wants to test it out. So, they weigh the investor, calculate the number of bungies, go to Utah, put him in a rig, jump off a bridge, and the bungies break. They have a boat below of course, but there happens to be another boat closer that goes into rescue mode. They get close and call out "wholly cow are you OK". Bungie jumper says "I can't feel my legs!" </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-03 05:10:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> No, just had to run the "clean" function on the oven. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-03 05:08:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> There's a whole 'nuther future, just two hours or so ahead. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-03 04:50:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Here's a tip: I genuinely don't care. I'm not your momma, your spouse, or your priest. Don't waste my time and endanger your health spewing bullshit. Whatever horrible twisted thing you think is too shameful to talk about, I promise you, I've seen worse.
Sometimes you are the priest.  See that lady that couldn't get her IUD removed in network while she was bleeding!  found it: http://abc7chicago.com/health/woman-claims-doctor-refused-to-remove-iud-for-religious-reasons-/1480333/ </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-03 01:23:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> just disconnect the rest of the spark plugs and turn it over on the starter till the rest of that plug jumps out, /s </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-03 01:08:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> jeez, that really looks great.  I need to get my chicken noodle on soon.  I like it with those Kluski noodles. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-01 05:22:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Good job! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-01 05:18:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Looks great, chef here tried to make it for employee lunch and it was with fries. Turned out too salty, and not a good enough cut of meat. I was interested though and learned a bit about the dish. Saw it on DDD also. Could eat a lot of it right now. Good job with the options. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-01 05:14:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Looks fairly healthy for a takeaway. They must really love you. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-01 05:04:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> No, who would create something like that and then put crab all over it?  You're food costs would be through the moon. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-01 04:57:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I've done these *(this cut) in the oven low and slow.  It usually doesn't turn out awesome. But they are cheap, and edible.  Some parts might want some sauce.  Smoking probably gives it flavor, but time doesn't seem to loosen the juices in portions of the cut. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-01 04:45:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> No kidding, that, I want it!  Is that a Matzo ball underneath? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-01 04:44:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> 10/10, would pay for this </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-01 04:42:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I found a bottle in Denver at a specialty meat purveyor.  It's a little sweeter than A1.  Also more brown like Heinz 57.  Just go for which ever one of those you like.  Maybe add a touch of Worcherstershire. cough </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-01 04:32:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Pre-delivery Inspection? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> TIFU by baking a potato </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-01 03:35:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So, I turned the oven on and put a potato in a hot oven at 400f/200c. I used a higher temperature than usual in order to get it done quicker. Then I went and drank a few while watching some TV.  Well, a few turned into an hour fifteen minutes.  When I remembered the potato I went to the oven and opened it up.  The potato had exploded violently because I neglected to pierce it first. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-01 02:10:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Well, how is it untypical? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-01 02:01:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Is that the turbo on the top right of your engine picture?  Seems a weird shape to me.  Like a scroll turbo?
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-31 06:45:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>   be sure to send a few to timken ..

I don't see why you're computer tech would be in trouble because that is obvs work related.  But I'd like to have a contact at Timken that knew anything about 50 year old ski lift gear boxes, lol.  Just kidding, I have a contact at ZF  axle. I should send them a Christmas card this year. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-31 06:31:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I thought that was a "drop bear". </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-31 06:28:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It still has 14.7 psi.  That's more than my lawnmower or bicycle. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-31 06:25:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> floor mats and front overcoverclear are more expensive and add more value imho.  But parts guys can't install those, so you are awesome. fuck the $50 ashtray.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-31 06:17:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> One of the guys at work.  His wifey is buying a Subaru Crosstrek.  She insists on a manual trans.  There are three coming into the state in 3 weeks.  My ex and I did the same thing with a 2006 Corolla back in the day kind of.  We bought it from the only dealer that had one.  Thankfully John Elway didn't add wheel locks.  Anyway, bought a set of steelies and winter tires mounted and balanced for under $600 iirc back then.  They were the Hakkipiletta with walnut shells or some such mixed into the rubber.  edit: added info about winter tires. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-31 06:12:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I guess the car I saw might have been older or the model above.  It wasn't the Diamante.  But the front grill stuck out an inch or so in the center, just around the logo.  The rear was pretty bad also, and the paint?  not grey not green, not silver.  STUPID. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-31 06:05:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It looks like that would help keep a person with the key from stripping them also. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-31 06:03:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Get them from 4 different places in order to be more secure. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-31 06:02:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Oh, the huge manatee </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-31 05:59:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah, maybe the "news" inflates it.  I'm sure they do.  I heard on the "news" once or twice that your tires lose up to 10 psi every time the temperature drops below zero or something.  Complete B/S, it does that all winter long, every night even. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-31 05:55:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Also the TPMS requirement.  If you don't notice when your tires aren't inflated you need to check your stance. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-31 05:49:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> maybe put some small wooden pieces under the gloves. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-31 05:48:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> build a special cage and wear two welding gloves when you clip the farking hose clamps. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-31 05:45:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I run a lot of ski-doo (same company) snowmobiles and feel that they are really engineered well.  The Spyder does look weird though.  Never seen one on the freeway, how fast can they go?  I don't know, but I guess when you turn the handle bar the front wheels tilt into the turn.  The rear wheel looks widish.  I guess you have to ride it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-31 05:39:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Maybe the wifey is more comfortable/secure? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-31 05:32:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> When I first started my job in the summer a H-D towing a trailer broke down on the highway right outside the shop.  Well, it turned out that the leaf spring for the trailer was welded directly to the axle.  He said he only had to make it to Santa Fe or something and someone welded it back on.  I think he gave the guy $100 or more. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-31 05:25:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Really, I saw a Mitsubishi Galant on the freeway yesterday.  I wonder how much they pay for those. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-31 05:23:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah, my driver's side window failed in the up position thankfully.  The switch felt flaky, but that wasn't it.  It's been over a month and haven't diagnosed it.  2k Blazer. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-31 05:18:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Maybe it depends on how much you contribute to the sheriff's campaign fund. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-31 04:53:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah, like this one: http://i.imgur.com/GUOMvCG.jpg </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-31 04:10:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Wow, the picture looks like something you could hang on the wall.  A 3D piece of fish even.  Compliments to the artist. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-31 03:56:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> this recipe is how we do it: http://allrecipes.com/recipe/97621/foolproof-rib-roast/ </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-31 03:07:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Missing jealous dog.  Otherwise perfect.  I saw that pig ear episode of DDD, where they cooked all day in a crockpot and were all floppy and stuff.  Couldn't believe Guy ate that. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-28 16:56:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This seems so easy, I don't know why those frogs would attempt it differently. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-28 16:50:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Shop name checks out. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-28 16:13:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> lol, good job.  Here's a book: http://cdn.inquisitr.com/wp-content/uploads/uncat/cooking-your-dog.jpg </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-27 03:48:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Needs catsup.  And sausage. Parsley sprig would be nice. As well as an orange wedge. If you want a tip, I want a proper napkin. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-27 03:36:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I like the fact that some more of the images seem to be posted inline instead of as a link today.  Is there a way to make multiple pictures a link, and single images right in the comments? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-27 03:29:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I've only made it fresh once, but we utilized a multitasker and hung them off of the edge of a ironing board at rental condo.  or just laid them flat. maybe flip them later. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-27 03:19:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah, but their Interstate Highways go nowhere! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-27 03:18:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Peanuts is a dog, right? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-27 02:33:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Why doesn't the upgraded sandwich include extra cheese.  In USA, it only includes 50% extra meat?

Also, what would happen if I ordered 50% extra meat on a meatball subway? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-26 03:09:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=0Ex0Eye_cA8

ice cream! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-26 03:08:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Just think, you could do that pasta in the cheese wheel thing every night! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-26 03:04:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I've never had curry.  But I have had beef stew, 'murica! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> test trying to figure out why links to the picture aren't in every thread </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-03 20:33:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Avalanche danger is pretty high, don't do this tomorrow </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-26 07:59:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> So, I finally opened the bottle of Oy Vey teriyaki sauce </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-03 02:18:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's probably at least 6 years old, and there were a lot of solids right up near the top after I got the plastic and cap off.  Even though I shook it a bit.  So, I put the cap back on and shook the bottle harder and longer.  Well, that seemed to clear the neck of the bottle of those solids, but right away the liquid in the bottle started expanding and flowing out of the top of the bottle!  There's no stopping it, so I let some flow onto my salmon, got it stopped up and washed the outside of the bottle.  So, I cooked the salmon and ate it last night.  Am I going to die?  Also, can I eat the rest of the teriyaki sauce? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> cooking advice </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-01 00:37:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
