<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject2154</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-01-03 14:18:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> obviously I don't know for sure but it spread to every place I put the ointment.  I had an outbreak (and still do on occasion ) in places where I never had it the previous twenty-something years.  It could be a coincidence or the virus reaping revenge.  I just didn't want to chance it again and I get the same results with the treatment plan I have now. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-01-02 23:58:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I have no doubt we've all come up with our own ways to deal with this calamity. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-01-02 23:10:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I suffer from these, for over thirty years now, contracted as a child in the hospital from some awesome person who didn't wash their hands.  My first outbreak covered the entire left side of my face when I was in second grade.  

I used to get a "normal" outbreak a dozen times a year, always in the same area.  I've had two additional outbreaks that were large and covered big sections of my face.  As I've gotten older, I seem to have outbreaks less often, maybe once or twice a year now.

I completely sympathize with how it makes you feel.  I truly hate it, especially that tingling I get when I know its about to surface.  I just feel crummy altogether...its indescribable.

I used Abreva when it first came on the market and for me, it made it spread.  The small outbreaks used to only occur on the corner of my mouth.  Once I used Abreva it spread to to the corner and the side of one nostril.  I'll get it there on occasion now.  That may not be the case for everyone but it was for me and I'm too afraid to try it again.

Funny enough I use Carmex and if I begin to apply it right as I feel the tingle, it will either not show up or be rather small and only last a week at the most.  I keep it within reach at the house, in my desk drawer and in my backpack. Any trip away from home I have it with me, usually several containers to be safe.  It's probably just a placebo affect but I'm pleased with the results.

I've been prescribed meds, both oral and topical, previously but they didn't make a difference for me.  That was some time ago so I may revisit that in the future.

I'm most nervous that when I get old and crust, my kids will ship me off to an old folks home and then I'll have an outbreak and it won't be treated properly...how sad is that.  :) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-12-31 21:04:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> We "cut the cord" years ago and if you still want to have cable internet service you can use Internet Nebraska.  If you use them you will also get "ESPN3" (or whatever its called now) so you can catch the ESPN broadcasts online.  If you have a Xbox 360 you can use the ESPN channel on there with that too.

We use an antenna for over the air, netflix, hulu, I subscribe to MLB TV for my baseball fix (can watch baseball on my roku or xbox in HD) and use ESPN3 for anything else.  If I have to I can hit the bar of a friends house for a Husker game airing on any other station.
It took us about 6 months to get used to but then you seriously won't want to go back.  My wife through a fit when we did this change and recently I asked if we should consider going back and she said "no way, never"! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Wife and kids always get me exactly what I want! </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-12-25 18:14:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-12-20 20:05:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> it is a phenomenal game and well worth the normal price.  I highly recommend it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-12-20 19:57:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> yeah, its really short and it was the only thing I could find so I wanted to share.  Hopefully the Library of Congress can provide more insight. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-12-20 15:21:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> you have nothing to apologize for...this is just a game, not worth your health or sanity.  Thank you for enjoyment you have given so many and be thrilled with what you have accomplished.  Best of luck to you sir and happy holidays! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-12-20 15:10:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Is this it??  http://www.britishpathe.com/video/animal-hotel.  Shows a small clip of the film at least...good work @Inflorescence . </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-12-20 03:51:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> the wrapper from a band-aid I put on my two year old's toe, after she finally decided it was the big toe on her right foot that hurt. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-12-18 21:55:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I've been eagerly awaiting this movie as it was not released theatrically where I live. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-12-18 02:22:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm originally from Rockford and lived in Chicago for a few years after college...may need to spend a week back home in 2016. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-12-17 16:38:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I just ruined a keyboard and perhaps my monitor, thanks for the laugh! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-12-16 21:19:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> yes, that is a good point, his comments were pretty unexpected and insightful at that time. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-12-16 20:20:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> omg please do...i really didnt think anyone would see this. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-12-16 20:18:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Its not about liking or not liking the quote...I think often folks do not give any weight to words unless they are from a famous person.  If you or I typed that, no one would give it a second read...but if OMG Justin Beiber said it, then it must have more value.  It wasn't the words it was that it was supposedly by someone famous so we must share it 100000 times.  :) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-12-16 20:03:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> oh snap. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-12-16 19:56:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> i must have misread that on FB </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-12-16 17:05:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> haha its alright, its just one of those funny things about facebook.

"all celebrity quotes on facebook are true"

-Orson Welles </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-12-16 17:00:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> lol so true. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-12-16 16:59:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [Link to hoax](http://www.inquisitr.com/440462/morgan-freemans-newtown-statement-almost-definitely-a-hoax/) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-12-16 16:59:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [Link to hoax](http://www.inquisitr.com/440462/morgan-freemans-newtown-statement-almost-definitely-a-hoax/) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-12-16 16:23:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> as a former resident from before blue tooth...its not blue tooth.  :( </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Got tired of seeing this quoted by nearly everyone on facebook. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-12-16 16:18:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-12-15 16:04:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I think you may want to read this:  [Gizmodo](http://gizmodo.com/5968532/stop-pretending-you-dont-look-at-porn-online)

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-12-15 15:58:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> this is it exactly...lol... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-12-15 02:49:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What Dell was saying in your article is they are shifting their focus to enterprise, not only focusing on the existing PC market.  Here is a quote from Dell in the article you are citing: "Anderson said that the company would continue to invest in PCs, citing the success of its premium XPS line of consumer laptops and desktops."

HP specifically stated they were considering spinning off or selling their PC business.

"HP today announced that its board of directors has authorized the evaluation of strategic alternatives for its Personal Systems Group (PSG), including the exploration of the separation of its PC business into a separate company through a spin-off or other transaction."

http://www.hp.com/hpinfo/newsroom/press/2011/110818xb.html

======

What Dell was getting at is they are going to focus on enterprise solutions to offer with their hardware solutions.  If you look at their acquisitions over the last 3 years you will understand they have focused on that strategy and want to be thought of as more than a PC maker but a solutions provider.

Key Acquistions:

* Perot Systems (now Dell Services)
* Secureworks
* SonicWall
* Wyse
* AppAssure
* Quest migration software
* Force 10
* Compellent
* many more...

They've used one of those acquisitions to build Dell Cloud Services as well.  This is why they are trying to emphasize the focus on more than PCs...not that they are leaving the PC business. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-12-14 22:23:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> /eyeroll </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-12-14 22:10:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Nebraska leads the nation in Academic All-Americans:  [link] (http://www.huskers.com/ViewArticle.dbml?ATCLID=205821488 DB_OEM_ID=100).

College Football as ranked by academics: [link](http://higheredwatch.newamerica.net/blogposts/2012/the_2012_academic_bowl_championship_series-75177).

The only reason we were removed from the AAU is because our Medical Center is under a different administrative umbrella so it's research dollars do not count towards the AAU requirements and a large portion of our grants go towards Ag and so a large chunk of that amount also does not count towards the grant dollars total.  We are a small school and it wasn't academic based, it was research dollar totals based upon some crazy requirements.

Just a silly uniformed statement. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-12-14 21:43:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I think Paul Rhoads is an exceptional coach and I hope he gets to keep on doing that at Iowa State...I really saw him taking a high profile job down the line but major kudos to him for remaining there.

-edit...I misspelled Rhoads...the horror. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-12-14 14:27:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> no that was HP. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-12-12 21:47:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> when my apartment got broke into years ago, my landlord tried to charged me for the front door and jam because they were damaged during the break-in.  I told him he could collect the money when we met in hell. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-12-11 04:39:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> will all these be new mail accounts?  If so you can have multiple addresses on a single gmail/hotmail account. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-12-11 04:37:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The only thing I would add to the above is to also verify that you're mail gateway solution doesn't offer bounce verification.  Cisco Iron Port does and it would be great to use along with the suggestions above.  There is no need to accept or deliver mail to your server for addresses which are not valid. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-12-11 04:34:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> which mail gateway solution do you utilize? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-12-09 18:16:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> those refueling tankers take off from the airport right out my window every day...they are doing their touch and goes right now.  cool stuff... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-12-07 01:45:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> every year we hear the same crap...its not true, not going to happen...some random blog-o-iwishiwasasportswriter put this crap up to get the page hits from the husker fans.  He's only been a head coach five seasons and across two different conferences, it takes time. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-12-05 20:30:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> he may be that one special player we need to get our program on an upward trajectory. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-12-04 22:51:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> just takes that one guy to get the ball (so to speak) rolling and get a program moving forward.  I think this guys could be one of those guys. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-12-04 21:44:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> word is he signed and is coming for certain...woohoo! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-12-04 04:59:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> that's great!  I know the commit from Australia/New Zealand (can't remember which) was supposed to be at this game...let's hope he signed his papers! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-12-04 04:55:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> As a parent of three great kids...this is a heartbreaking story.  My heartfelt sympathies to Isaiah's family...what a brave young man.  

My son and I wear our Team Jack shirts every weekend...let's hope one day that children won't have to fear such things. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Ultimately, it's just a game.  Especially for family   friends that lost much more this weekend. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-12-04 04:51:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-12-03 16:21:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I am just as mad/sad/angry/pissed/depressed/etc as the rest of the fans.  As an Alumni and a citizen of Lincoln I want our team to be great on and off the field.  I don't measure great by number of wins as much as I do the quality of the student athletes and how they look on the field of play.

Coach Bo has succeeded at the off the field and in the classroom aspect.  I also think he is a kind and loyal friend.

In order to take things to the next level, he needs a new O Line coach and a new D coordinator.  Just my opinion, and I could certainly be wrong.  I also think our offensive coordinator has bad games but I believe he will improve.  (Offense can control the tempo and they failed to do that at all on Saturday...everyone knows the weakness of the Wisconsin offense but we often tried to run it up the middle instead or three quick throws...terrible play calling at critical times.)

We also need to evaluate our special teams coaching and reinforce ball security as a major focal point this off season.

I don't want Bo to leave, as far as I know he's a good coach, good person and a good leader.  He just needs to realize this isn't Coaching U, and although the staff is a great bunch of folks, we just aren't improving as would be expected.  We don't have time for a 34 year old to learn on the job.  

I don't mind losing...by 3 or 7...this is football, it happens all over the country, every week...but losing by 40...just inexcusable...when that happens, something has to change, somewhere. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-11-28 15:20:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Wisconsin you have a good coach...there will be up an down years, especially when you had to replace a QB that is now starting in the NFL.  Remember the games you lost this year were close ones...BREATH...it will be ok. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-11-27 16:59:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I would agree but our team likes to spot the other team at least 14 through fumbles, interceptions or muffed punts.  I hope both teams play a complete game and best of luck to your team. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-11-27 15:36:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Soldier Field or Lambeau would rock but I can see why they would want this a the DOME. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-11-27 14:31:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> have a great time, it will be an incredible, hard fought game. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-11-26 22:36:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> lol yeah, same for me...and then I never wanted to touch the damn game again. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-11-23 08:31:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> U.S. here, purchased at $22.50 no problem using the code in the subject.  Thank you, this is the one game I was waiting to go on sale. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-11-21 17:50:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Our two biggest challenges with families and holidays are:

-They serve "the meal" at odd times, like at 7 or 8 pm.  This may be fine when you are just dinning with adults but children, especially small ones, don't adapt well and it causes them to get fussy and act up when they may not normally.  If you give them a snack to tied them over, then they may not eat at the meal...which elicits comments.

-They like to give the kids a lot of junk food, soda pop and ask us to let them stay up, all because they don't get to see them often, then comment on how they are misbehaving the next day, all directly related to these factors.

but you roll with the punches because life's too short. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-11-21 17:04:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> yeah, as Voytrekk says, im hoping to see it on Steam...its about the only game I haven't picked up from the last few sales. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-11-21 04:54:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> one of the craziest plays ever: https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=OvTaN1uplS4 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-11-20 20:58:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> "Nebraska is the polite kid your parents would want you to be."

LOL that's awesome, I love it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-11-20 18:48:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> that's awesome, you should be proud to wear that! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-11-15 22:59:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> LOL...OK, how about:

[First Half](http://media.huskerlocker.com/files/5/blog/48ff443be6e8b/tn_510x510_Baby_sleep.jpg)

[Second Half](http://hackworthless.files.wordpress.com/2008/09/post-340-12201768611.jpg) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-11-15 22:10:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> completely epic and true.  Although I'd swap the first half pic with a sleeping old lady. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-11-15 14:22:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thank you for sharing, will have to squeeze this into an especially busy weekend. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> This is what it's been like putting my 2 1/2 year old to bed the last few days. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-11-14 16:07:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-11-13 21:08:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Coach Solich is an incredible guy...there is still immense hatred for he whose name shall not be spoken...as well as his supposed replacement for Solich. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-11-12 17:21:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> As a Husker fan I did want to tell the Penn State fans that holy crap, your team looked great, disciplined and I think you have a really special coach.  I have a good friend who is a Penn State Alum and I know many folks were not happy about O'Brien at first, but, he's going to do great things.  

I'd rather not have any "controversial" calls or injured star players because then "your team really didn't win"....but teams can only play with those around them and we certainly don't have any influence on the refs, especially when Bo is screaming at them most of the time.

A lot of Husker fans point to the 1 second put back on against Texas in the Big 12 Championship in 2009 and scream conspiracy but they often forget that the drive started with a kick off out of bounds and if memory serves, a penalty at some point.  Remove those two things and they aren't in field goal range and the 1 second may become meaningless and Nebraska wins...or Texas could have scored on a hail mary...who knows.  It's part of what makes any sport exciting and frustrating and I'm sorry that it didn't go your way.  I think it was a TD as do all fans I have discussed it with...there was 8 minutes left so who knows what would have happened...it wasn't a TD with 1 second left sort of situation.

In any event, before this game, I think on a league and national level the Nebraska vs Penn State "rivalry" seemed forced and now it has a purpose and will be a fun to watch for years to come.  

Best of luck on the rest of your season. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-11-11 15:05:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That's a superb question but it came out in 2003...and to be honest I don't remember enough to answer that thoroughly.  What I remember was a great story and I loved managing the squad.  It was one of those games that really stood out to me and like a great book, I was sad to see it come to an end.  

I've been playing games since the early 80's when my dad bought an Atari at Sears and there will be certain games that will stand out in my mind as something special, and to me, this was one of those.  I'm about to move in a week and perhaps I'll come across it.  If I do, I fire it up and see how it stands 9 years later. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-11-10 15:37:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [Freedom Fighters](http://www.giantbomb.com/freedom-fighters/61-10853/)!

I loved this game.  It was well executed, unique and I was really expecting a follow up.  I hope that we may one day. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-11-10 01:49:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> in any event, if its 2 x the full game, just let me know and I'll give you 2x DOTA.  I am about to go grab dinner so let me know or else I'll came back a bit later and we can deal then. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-11-10 01:27:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'll give you 2 DOTA for the 2 Killing Floor...one for me and you can gift the other to my brother?  Game?? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-11-09 20:31:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Dave Matthews Band cover the Cosby Show theme... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-11-09 04:27:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I loved the book...this doesn't look like the book...but man, it does look like it could be an exciting film.  I think I would have enjoyed it more if they stayed true to the book and did it like Band of Brothers were it was episodic on like HBO.

The reason I read this book is that I was returning [The Good War](http://www.barnesandnoble.com/w/good-war-studs-terkel/1101302815?ean=9781565843431 itm=85 usri=ww2+books) by Studs Terkel and the older librarian suggested it.  Great read...both of them are. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-11-08 19:22:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> looks like the updated the original story now, he is taking another position...i.e. he cant stand by his commitment to his constituents. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-11-08 18:29:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Does anyone know if this was expected or what happened.  I was really quite surprised. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Adam Hornung is expected to resign from the Lincoln City Council today. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-11-08 18:28:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-11-07 18:20:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> sorry, my very first reddit post and I put the URL in where it said, I failed somehow.  Here is the link I thought I submitted:

http://lovedrunkstudio.com/HTML/uuvvwwz.html </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-11-07 18:14:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Found it in an article on the Journal Star website (want to give credit where due).  Thought it was a great way to promote our thriving music scene in Lincoln/Omaha/Nebraska.

Here is the link I somehow failed to submit:  http://lovedrunkstudio.com/HTML/uuvvwwz.html </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Lincoln band UUVVWWZ filmed a "single take" video in Mayor's office. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-11-07 18:12:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Filmed by Love Drunk.  This was Love Drunk's 100th one-take video shoot. The independent music video production team from Omaha has shot all over the country.

http://lovedrunkstudio.com/HTML/uuvvwwz.html </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-11-06 18:14:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> thanks for the details. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-11-02 22:54:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I still have my 3500 with video in/out dongle in a box somewhere...sweet stuff. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-11-01 22:09:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This was a game I really enjoyed but haven't played for quite a bit.  Good for them, it's quite an accomplishment to publish any game and congrats to their team. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-10-30 22:17:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> well personally I get excited by independent development instead of something churned out of a big studio.  A few guys dedicated 8 tireless years to make something great, I think it warrants additional attention, but that's just me. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-10-30 22:15:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I was going to post the same thing in your forums..."guide and lead not demean".  That's my slogan. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-10-30 22:14:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> its no problem, thank you!  You can send to my email, Jacob.Crabb@Gmail.com.  Thanks again, that is extraordinarily cool of you to do that. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-10-30 19:09:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> purchased 7/19/10... :)  Congrats and I wish you all great success! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-10-30 19:07:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I purchased mine on 7/19/2010.  Been a long time coming...enjoy! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-10-30 14:36:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> it's an incredible game from an independent developer.  Show them your support. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-10-25 02:06:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> there was a just a system wide announcement in game that they are pushing out an update, or something, which they believe will address most of the CTD issues. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-10-25 01:10:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> yes, same here.  constant crashes...today was a bit better, some times as long as 15-20 minute before I would CTD.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-10-23 14:50:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I also have a 9 year old.  Here are some suggestions from what my son enjoys as well as my friends 9 year old daughter.

-Portal/Portal 2...if they are smart and like to solve puzzles, they both love this game and they think it's funny.
-Sam   Max games...good adventure games and you can catch them on steam sales all the time
-Angry Birds...I think you can still get that free through the Chrome web browser store...kids are crazy for this game, I guess everyone was at some point.
-King Arthur's Gold.  Its like Terraria, sorta...its more online, red vs blue, building and defending.  My son loves it and it's also prob my favorite game right now and has been for the last 6 mo or more...and im playing XCOM, Dishonored, NS2, GW2 and PS2.

That's what my 9 year old likes right now...if you asked me to pick 1 single game, I'd recommend Portal 2 b/c they can build new levels which can be incredibly rewarding for them as well.  If I think of something else, I'll update here.
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-10-23 02:17:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Someone contacted me shortly after my post and traded me for the same but then Reddit crapped the bed so I couldn't respond.  Thank you though! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-10-22 18:22:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'd love the PS2 key.  All I have is LA Noir to offer..sorry already gave my NS2 gift to my brother. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-10-19 14:42:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> ....Valve...*tear drops*...I love Valve...congrats on that, that's great.  I used to do mod work back in HL 1 days.  Our little group of level designers ended up creating quite a few official DOD maps. A few from our group went on and did some work for Valve as well as my buddy "Waldo".   I also did stuff for countless other mods, released and unreleased.  

There used to be another level designer from Lincoln who did stuff for the NS1 mod and did some work for 4D rulers when they were still around, not sure if that's you or you knew him...I think he went by Squirrel something...something...can't remember anymore...not important.

I credit Valve for my current career path.  I wanted to play Team Fortress Classic so bad so I built my first computer which led to a tech bench job.  12 years later and a ton of hard work and I'm in a high skill IT job.  I wouldn't have discovered my passion for this field if it wasn't for starring at the back of the HL box and wanting to play TFC.  That journey began just after receiving my arts degree from UNL so quite a shift.

I believe the business model created by Gabe and Co and the ultimate results were monumental to the gaming world.  How they cultivated and supported the mod community, often gave them work later on...and don't forget Steam which has changed gaming forever.

If any event, if you see Gabe, tell him big thanks for me.  Also, a strange request.  I have been trying to put together a (sort of) sleeve for a tattoo and was actually going to write Gabe about this.  I saw in some pictures in the Valve lobby that there is a glass wall with lots of tiny icons/logos/symbols or whatever and was wondering if they had close up pictures of that.  I thought it would be neat concept to incorporate into some of the items I already want to use.  

Ok...well...I've gone on long enough.  Maybe next time I come to Seattle you can help me apply for an official tour.  :)  Take care! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-10-18 16:44:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> they are wonderful and something unique for our town...you are to be commended! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-10-16 18:20:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I did find it interesting and surprising that they endorsed Obama, as they had endorsed McCain 4 years ago.  What was more surprising was all the outrage and threats to cancel a paper subscription because of this.  What is the point of reading/listening/watching only sources of information you agree with.  All along, these readers spent money supporting the paper and must have agreed with most of what they said up to this point.  Now that the editors have come to a consensus on who the believe would be the best choice of the two candidates, which some readers do not agree with, they get all butt hurt?  If it was the other way around, they'd be sharing it on Facebook and high five-ing correct?  I guess I don't understand why the one conclusion is given more weight then another.  It's really just a few people's opinions.  Take from it what you can and move on, right?

Additional endorsements that caught my attention and likely caused a little backlash:

Winstom-Salem Journal endorses Obama, first Democrat since 1964.

[LINK](http://www2.journalnow.com/news/2012/oct/14/obama-best-choice-president-ar-2689120/?referer=None shorturl=http://bit.ly/RWM6Lg)

Sarah Palin's hometown paper endorses Obama (edit, this is from 2008, just imagine though):

[LINK](http://www.adn.com/2008/10/25/567867/obama-for-president.html)
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-10-16 15:15:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thank you for the recommendation, I do see them on West O but it's difficult to know the quality when you are unfamiliar with them.  I will check them out this weekend. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-10-16 01:18:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Here are my favorites:

http://www.stmonicas.com/get_involved/volunteer.html

http://www.peoplescitymission.org/index.php/get-involved

http://lincolnbikekitchen.blogspot.com/p/get-involved.html

Thank you for contributing to a better community.

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-10-04 17:51:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> thank you sir! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-10-04 15:15:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That's great and congrats.  If you don't mind, do you have a copy of the comic panel that is on the top inside of the box?  I've been trying to find a nice batman panel for a tattoo and that looks like it might be the layout im looking for.  Thanks! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
