<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject516</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-07-10 07:31:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This might be the best thing I've read today.  I feel terrible for laughing, but every sentence in your story is pure gold. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-07-10 07:19:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> After what seemed like years of begging, my parents broke down and got me [the $100 Lego castle set](http://www.classic-castle.com/sets/images/OOP/1995/6090.jpg) that I wanted.  I remember building it to be 95% correct and then destroying it for some stupid reason.  Alas, the Lego set of my dreams was never finished.  *Just like my childhood.* :'( </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-07-10 07:14:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> THOSE EXISTED!?

God, my parents must've really fucking hated me if they made me go through all of the agony of separating those 2x1 flats.  God damn it, Ellen. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-07-09 07:12:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Way to dash my hopes of becoming Aquaman one day :( </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-07-08 18:29:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That's hardly creepy, now a days.  That's basically the equivalent of a handshake to our generation hahah. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-07-08 18:16:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I have nothing to add besides that I loved Helen Mirren in Caligula!  Well, I love that she somehow has a career still :P </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-07-07 19:10:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm honestly surprised by how many people seemed to have missed 0bsesshun's awful, awful song reference.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-07-07 10:37:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  I talked to him about an hour before he passed. He was almost blissful. He told me that he could see everything really clearly, and that it was all about love. That's it.

Fuck. 
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-07-07 10:34:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This really hit me.  I'm a 21 year old gay man and to think I could've died within the last year, without my parents by my side, and being treated like a leper scares me.  RIP Andy and a lost generation; I promise that I will never have unprotected sex again in part due to remembrance, and also fear.  Life's too short to have it end at 21 due to carelessness and I just wish our community had more stories like this to educate the youth.  :( </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-07-07 06:52:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The alternative idea is that cats were simply tolerated by people and gradually diverged from their 'wild' relatives through natural selection, as they adapted to hunting the vermin found around humans in towns and villages.[4]

Fun fact: cats are actually believed to have domesticated themselves.  That's from the Cats wikipedia by the way. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-07-01 22:22:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The would be the best ever episode of Intervention. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-06-28 02:12:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I use one of those for work.  I am so, so sorry.

Note:  a bit of background; the screen's awful, the keyboard is annoying, and don't get me started on that touchpad.  Go for the UX31A or just wait until the next gen of ultrabooks.  This one is pretty annoying to use. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-06-27 07:40:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Ugh, I'll never "get" the BBT... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-06-27 07:39:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [We already have those.](http://www.youtube.com/watch?v=IlN_yu96Ygo feature=related) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-06-20 08:09:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> *lets </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-06-18 07:12:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Imagine all of the lurkers lurking at the party! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-06-18 06:18:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I guess douchey was a bit of a bad word to chose, so I apologize.  I guess the word "vain" might've applied better, but that's not to say you yourself are vain. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-06-18 02:21:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Oh my God, why does it matter to you if she was looking at clouds or not?  Jeez, it's a nice photo, and while it's a little ~~douchey~~ vain to post a nice photo of yourself, that doesn't make the photo any less of a "nice photo of a human."  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-06-17 23:57:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> God damn it, reddit just continuously proves to me how nice people are.  Your LEGO creations are awesome dude, and seeing so many supportive strangers really brings tears to my eyes.  Keep your head up; the best days of your life are yet to come, I promise! :)  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-06-17 03:27:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> PUG ASS-BITCH </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-06-16 09:50:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> No, I'm originally from Ohio.  May I ask why? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-06-16 09:37:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Heh, thanks, looking at your submissions, we would totally bro out together.  Here's to Archer, Crown Royal, and Mad Men! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-06-16 09:34:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Ah, this must be the answer on what happened; thanks!! :) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-06-16 09:33:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Oh baby, my buffers are overflowing.

And we're done here. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-06-16 07:48:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Do you have a link to that thread? I'd like to see what they're saying about it </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-06-16 07:35:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Well, I'm more of a gay CS nerd than anything.  So if talks about the benefits of object oriented programming get you going, we'd be in business haha.  Either that or a nerding out session over Doctor Who or 30 Rock :P </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-06-16 07:32:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I've never been on 4chan, so I imagine someone reposted it there. Also, stop taking the internet so seriously; you'll never make it out alive. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-06-16 01:14:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I, erm, thank you, sir or madam.

EDIT:  Clicked your account, nice to see a fellow gaymer here!  Huzzah! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-06-16 00:14:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [You get a slider for scaled HiDPI resolutions.](http://www.anandtech.com/Gallery/Album/2078)  I got the machine to show its native resolution using an application called [SwitchResX](http://www.madrau.com/download/latest/latest.html). </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-06-16 00:07:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> My laptop does png but I imagine I changed it because the jpg's are what appeared when I did a screen shot on the new MBP.  So either Best Buy/someone changed it or it's the default setting.

Either way, I apologize to everyone's corneas. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-06-15 23:49:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You mean a front page post on reddit doesn't count as a personal thank you?  Huh.  I guess I just don't get etiquette then. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-06-15 23:21:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Sorry about that, it's what OSX defaults to when using the screenshot function and I wasn't about to really go through Best Buy's laptop's settings
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-06-15 23:03:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Also, I just thought I'd add that using it at this resolution was almost dizzying for some reason.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-06-15 22:37:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> SwitchResX worked even without the admin password! :) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-06-15 20:52:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Seriously, the whole "touchscreen controller" would work *perfectly* as a pokedex.  As of right now, I'm having a hard time understanding any other real use for it beyond this.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-06-15 09:38:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I feel like it would be more comforting than anything in that situation.  There's nothing worse than a parent outliving their child, but knowing that their son or daughter's death meant someone else could live at least makes it seem like it wasn't all for naught.  Sure, some might say that it's "unfair" that their child passed while the other person could live, but a situation where they die without any actual benefit would hurt much more, I guess.  I dunno, I've never been in this situation and my heart hurts more and more as I type :( </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-06-15 08:59:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Every time someone uses that term, a SSD crashes.  Or, y'know, a puppy dies or something. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-06-14 23:38:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I sear Apple dropped support for Carbon in Lion/Mountain Lion, but I guess I'm wrong.  If/when Apple decides to do that, Microsoft will be in big trouble, right? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-06-14 22:45:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> No matter what comment you make, there will ALWAYS be a combative response to it.  You could post "The sky is blue!" and there will be four comments about how wrong you are and that you're an idiot.  When did reddit gets so angry and needlessly defiant?  :( </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-06-14 20:25:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This comment made me sad.  I'm not missing the sarcasm, but you're absolutely right; Microsoft is so large and has so much money that they should be able to pump out a Cocoa build of Office in (relatively) no time.  Hell, the CS suite is Cocoa now, why can't Microsoft get their act together on this? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-06-12 19:05:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thank God.  Though, it took them being kicked off the platform to come to that stance, which really leaves a bad taste in my mouth.  Seriously, they had control over the Google Maps app for iOS and even said Navigation would come to it when it was first announced for Android, but they did jack with it just to leverage Android.  Sure, it's a smart move, but it only hurt iOS users/consumers. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-06-10 18:50:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I mean, I was just telling you why people screenshot tweets, not why that one specific person did.  I'm not a sociologist, I just have my PhD in Twitter Meltdowns. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-06-10 18:33:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Well, if you're linking to a tweet like "Holy shit, Jennifer Love Hewitt is having a total mental break down on twitter right now!!!" there's a good possibility it'll get deleted soon.  So, a screenshot is a way to make sure everyone gets to see her go nuts. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-06-10 03:35:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This video is 2 years old.

Down vote, next. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-06-10 02:22:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> IIRC, it was a FYE class :( </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-06-09 22:25:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Heh, I can tell you're possibly into more networking stuff?  I rarely see anyone spell out ASCII characters with ':' in between them :P  Though, that could be my limited experience and awful convention of writing 0x4865792C......  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-06-09 22:00:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thank you kind sir, have an upvote from a thankful CS enthusiast :) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-06-09 21:42:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Any idea who that girl is?  Sorry, I'm a little late to this gif-overuse party, I guess haha. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-06-09 08:55:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I've never actually heard anyone say, "You're my little snowflake, and all you need to do is sleep on a couch and you'll be a millionaire!"  Though, I've heard people *believe* others say that on reddit. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-06-09 04:34:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I was wondering that earlier.  I feel like every generation's parents told their kids "if you work hard enough, you'll make something of yourself."  Sure, that's a bit more than "15th place gets a trophy, too," but it's still instilling a belief that hard work will always pay off.  So, if you're 60, how did your generation deal with this belief? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-06-08 23:15:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This is why we shouldn't let religion dictate the use of science.  Seriously, this is amazing news!  :) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-06-08 23:05:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Also, the point of keg stands are that they're supposedly fun (I've never actually done one).  What's the point of buying alcohol for a party if you're going to worry about the quantity of it over the amount of fun you're having with it? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-06-07 22:43:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Upvoted for The Cool Kids :) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-06-07 08:09:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Derferman is streets ahead. 3 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-06-07 08:08:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Pretty sure that's all there is atm.  Just have to wait :) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-06-06 12:41:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I missed this yesterday, but [her real date is apparently behind them.](http://www.reddit.com/r/pics/comments/umnub/went_to_prom_with_the_prettiest_girl_from_school/c4wrl0n?context=3)  Also, that girl is gorgeous.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-06-06 12:29:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I once said that the sexiest thing about going down on a girl is "that you can control her pleasure," which apparently made a girl say "that's so creepy, no no no, stop.  I don't want a man 'controlling' my pleasure."  Sigh... I didn't mean anything misogynistic with it, but I feel like some people just like to look for things, I guess. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-06-06 07:19:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Insert meme:

If you're going to go camping with your mother

You're gonna have a bad time </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-06-05 21:05:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I hate to be *that guy* but that's the life you chose.  You could've easily dropped out of school, decided to be a bartender, and worked at a local bar the rest of your life. Hell, you could've taken up acting at an early age, moved to Hollywood, and maybe got rich doing that. 

This is all beyond the point.  Being a "first world" country has nothing to do with your personal happiness or your situation.  You have running tap water.  You have a job.  You have income.  You have a family.  You have a means of transportation.  You have shelter.  You have clothes.  Our country isn't any less of a developed country because people are unhappy while others are happy.  Also, the millionaire business men and engineers don't exactly sleep all day.  They have to work, too, and presumably harder than most; you can't just wake up one day at the top of the corporate ladder.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-06-05 13:42:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> While I agree for the most part, being a successful employee is 20% skill and 80% people skills.  You can be the most intelligent guy in the room, but why hire you if you won't share/help the other team members?  What if they needed you to go to HR and argue with them about something?  You can't just say "I know this stuff, give me a job" because anyone can go to college/buy a book and learn things.  You need to demonstrate value as a person, too. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-06-05 13:38:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I have an internship in a few weeks with one of the largest tech companies in America and I asked (for #5) "Honestly, do you enjoy working for [NAME]?"  I think it was a great question because it showed that I was truly interested in *how* it feels to work there rather than just wanting to work there.  Plus, the guy seemed excited to be able to talk about his point of view on where he works.  Would you say this is a good question?

It really isn't that hard to be charismatic or engaging; just ask people about themselves.  If you allow someone the opportunity to share *their* experiences with you, I've found they'll like you 100x more than if you talk about yours. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-06-05 12:25:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Oh c'mon, that's not true.  The simple fact that you're saying we're not a first world country on an article about a *video game studio* closing its doors shows you that the US is in a much better place than you imply.  Yes, the megarich are hurting the country, but to say it's not a "first world" country if you're poor is wrong.  Even if you're poor, you have access to more food, water, power, clothing, and shelter than 90% of the world. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-06-05 06:31:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I think you mean Urban Fervor. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-06-04 14:37:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> "If you're straight, that's something I could get behind." </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-06-04 08:10:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Damn it, I just spent the last hour watching an episode of Cosmos.  I mean, that's never a problem, but I wanted to go to sleep awhile ago.

Oh, who cares.  Learning about Flatland *never* gets old! :) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-06-04 03:37:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Am I really the only one who thinks the mustache looks stupid?  No offense, it's just more of a gag than anything you should want 24/7. Though, the hair looks good, especially with the beard.  Just trim the 'stache, man. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-06-04 03:08:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Really though, you should get [Reddit Enhancement Suite](http://redditenhancementsuite.com), it allows you to easily do all of this AND provides a Live Preview (I think that's from RES and not normal reddit, right?) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-06-04 01:23:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Honestly, even better. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-06-04 00:46:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's probably more like a year and 3/4 now, but still.... Also, wuddup Cantion?  I was born and raised in Beachwood! :) (Assuming you're from Canton, Ohio) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-06-04 00:02:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Wow, this is proof that I have been on reddit for *wayyyyyyy* too long. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-06-03 19:19:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Here's what I said about the deleted comment:

It was originally like "Yes, tell that to every poor person in the crappy areas that try hard but can't help being poor and in shitty areas." Though, much more vulgar. He then responded to me with a lot of ramblings about how many people aren't individuals, how the American Dream is stupid, and then quoted Oscar Wilde (the irony was lost on him, apparently). Though, once again, he was much more vulgar.
I'm tired of people being too combative and litteral on reddit. 

Every quote here WILL NOT apply to everyone. Also, there will always be poor people trying to get out, but can't. It's sad, but detracting from other things because of it is a waste of time. I wonder if the original commenter hated his birthday because AIDS is prevalent in Africa? Hell, why celebrate Christmas when the housing market is in shambles?
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-06-03 19:17:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It was originally like "Yes, tell that to every poor person in the crappy areas that try hard but can't help being poor and in shitty areas."  Though, much more vulgar.  He then responded to me with a lot of ramblings about how many people aren't individuals, how the American Dream is stupid, and then quoted Oscar Wilde (the irony was lost on him, apparently).  Though, once again, he was much more vulgar.

I'm tired of people being too combative and litteral on reddit.  Every quote here WILL NOT apply to everyone.  Also, there will always be poor people trying to get out, but can't.  It's sad, but detracting from other things because of it is a waste of time.  I wonder if the original commenter hated his birthday because AIDS is prevalent in Africa?  Hell, why celebrate Christmas when the housing market is in shambles? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-06-03 08:43:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> They also dumbed down Troy like no other.  He used to have child-like wonder, now he's just a child.  Old Troy wouldn't have eaten the candy cigarette (though that was very funny). </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-06-03 08:39:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yes, because *every* quote has to apply to *every* person without *any* exceptions.  Jeez, you seem like a great person to invite to a party. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-06-03 08:33:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What an idiotic post.  Alright, we'll call you when one woman fixes *everything* that's wrong with America right now.

Oh wait, this is the same ignorance that people have now when it comes to Obama and how he "didn't fix all of the problems in 4 years; what a failure!!!"   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-06-02 19:23:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thank God.  Community is my favorite show, but we don't need a *fourth* episode about paintballs.  The pillow fort/fight episode were much better than anything they could've thought up with another paintball episode, IMHO. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-05-31 18:44:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That's great, but maybe that's why you're not an extremely well-paid higher up at one of the world's largest corporations.  People in business, especially higher ups, tend to put their jobs before anything and everything.  If he truly didn't want to go, he could've said no.  Sure, there would've been repercussions, but that's a result of not doing what needed to be done as a higher up. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-05-31 15:49:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The coworker *chose* to go.  Tim Cook asked "why are you still here" and he just got up and went straight to the airport.  He could've said, "My daughter's recital is tonight, I'm sorry, I just can't," but he didn't.  This is business here, this isn't some low level employee working in a cubicle being told to miss his parents funeral to do paperwork.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-05-31 09:00:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Seriously, it reads like the OP is almost disgusted with Cook, but the article read like he has a commanding presence and really knew what Apple needed to be saved at that time. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-05-30 21:44:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Then you sound like a Bostonian saying "Potzis" </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-05-30 21:43:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I thought Oregon was a pretty liberal place?   :\ </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-05-30 12:48:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [Can you paint me, like one of your French girls?](http://i.imgur.com/X163L.jpg)

Note:  This is totally unrepresentative of what I look like; it's from three or four years ago and is a senior picture.  I now rock a beard and have grown a hump. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-05-30 09:58:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Oh, good point :(  Well, you all are campus treasurers for providing food for drunk/high kids to eat.  Thanks 3 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-05-30 09:55:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [You think that's sexy?](http://media.washingtonpost.com/wp-srv/liveonline/images/celebritology/10/young_colbert.jpg) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-05-30 09:53:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> James Franco is the sexiest man alive and I've never once thought of of Christina Hendricks naked.  Enough proof? :) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-05-30 09:52:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I think it was a joke. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-05-30 09:51:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Jimmy John's on 15th?  You people do the Lord's work on Friday/Saturday nights from 11pm-3am </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Don't tell your parents! 3 </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-04-29 16:34:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Alright internet, that's enough. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2011-12-23 22:10:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> ELI5: The differences between a bank and a credit union </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2011-11-14 16:24:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Also, why should one choose a certain one?  Thanks!

Thanks for the really awesome responses! Another question, as asked below, how's a credit unions fraud protection? I would love to support "the little guy" but if they can't protect my money, then I can't switch :( </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Quick question:  When would you use heap spraying if not for ASLR? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2011-11-03 14:56:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This is one of those times where I've learned about these techniques but never had to use them on my own accord.  A simple answer is enough to suffice, thanks RE! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> My gripe with every programming book I've ever owned  </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2011-10-16 20:07:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I love reading programming books; it's so easy to go to a Half-Price Books and buy a C++ book for $6 and absorb it's information in a few days time.  In fact, I have around 25 books thanks to this, but it just seems like every book I buy always has 7 intro chapters on an "if" statement and what a String is, it's ridiculous.  Is there an easier way to learn other programming languages without having to deal with this?  I just sat down to read my new Assembly book (which I paid $60 for... sigh) and apparently the first 200 pages are about the theory behind assembly, computers, programming, and more without even getting to a Hello World.  It's just a little ridiculous that I paid so much for a book that's one third basic knowledge. 
/mini-rant </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Where to learn OpenGL? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2011-10-10 07:08:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hey guys, I know C++, Java, (ARM/x86) assembly and more but I'm trying to learn OpenGL now.  Does anyone know of a good book that is helpful and not too dry/simple?  Amazon recommends the Super Bible but it seems that the 5th edition only teaches you the author's own framework with dealing with OpenGL..  Any help would be amazing, thanks! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Sears now selling iPhoney 4! </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2011-06-16 19:10:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> My MicroSD card slot's busted, any ideas? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2011-06-14 09:15:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It won't hold the card anymore and I have no idea why, any ideas?  I'm not above putting tape over the slot, but nothing I've tried seems to hold :(  Any help is greatly appreciated, thanks!! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> I guess the architects of my local Time Warner Cable building have the same opinion as me </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2011-05-08 22:17:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Dear /r/Apple, is there any way I can make my partition extended to the free space?  I just erased my other partition and I didn't foresee this... </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2011-04-20 21:56:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Dear Andreddit, should I get the G-Tablet? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2011-04-19 05:22:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm a broke college student who has a Kindle for books and text books.  While it's an amazing little device, the small screen size makes textbook reading a huge hassle.  So, I could sell the kindle for ~120 and I have the rest (I'm not THAT broke haha) and then buy the G-Tablet for $280.  Now, my question is, is it worth it?  It's extremely cheap for a Tegra 2 10" Android device so I'm wondering about quality.  I know the screen view angles suck but is it enough to say the device is worthless?  I would love to start hacking it and then eventually putting HC on it when the source is available :)  Though, I'm afraid the dev community might not be that active?  Any thoughts would help!  Thanks guys! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Engadget Review of XOOM.  tl;dr: 7/10 </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2011-02-24 03:32:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Anyone know of a good local media streaming server? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2011-02-08 02:52:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> One burn book to rule them all! </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2011-01-31 22:51:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Hey /r/trees, if you want to watch an epicly trippy video, check this out! </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2010-12-22 20:20:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
