<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject7911</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [WP] You wake up in a dark cavern, dizzy and uncomfortable. You see two wooden doors with bronze knobs ahead of you. One is labelled past and the other future. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-25 11:29:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-25 11:24:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> i get it. I t says "wake up" </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [WP]A highly intelligent species in on a mission to destroy everything beautiful in their star system which has nine planets. They have already destroyed one planet and are planning to destroy the next one which is closest the one destroyed, Mars. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-25 11:17:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The destroyed planet is earth and the one they are planning to destroy is Mars.
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Date Night </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-24 20:41:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I was excited to meet him. I was going on my first date after moving to this new town. It has been three months since I have moved to this town. I got up early, even before the sun, I love the dark city in the morning and also at night, the silence, and also because I was excited to meet Anthony.

I had bath and my breakfast and was ready to go to my boring same old job.

I was thinking about the date the whole day, about the dress which I specially bought three days back for tonight. I didnt know the answers for the various questions that rose in my mind. But I surely did know it was going to be a fun night.

My shift was over, Danny came to his shift to replace me, and I was happy to leave that place and head back home to get ready for the date. I took the bus, it was filled with all kinds of people and all of them were engrossed in something, books, and phones.

I reached home. I quickly had a bath and wore my red gown. I reached the restaurant where we decided to meet. I saw him, waiting for me with his hands behind him. I saw him and he saw me. My heart stopped for a second, he was beautiful, a really nice smile he had and he also had a really nice figure, an athletes. His hands were thick and muscular, he seemed quite strong and like a person who takes personal fitness seriously. 

I went to him.

He stares at me and is stunned to look at me just like all the other men before who I have met.

I dont know what people think of me or my personality but I was pretty sure that I was a beautiful woman.

You look pretty, beautiful. Anthony said slowly and with a nice smile, with his hands still behind him.

You look handsome too. I said.

After a second of exchanging stares with each other, he pulled out a bouquet which had purple, yellow and red flowers which smelled entrancing. I took it from his hands and my fingers touched the back of his palm. I thanked him for the bouquet and we went in. We took our seats, had a lovely dinner and a talked a lot.

After that, he asked me whether I wanted him to drop me at my house in his car. I didnt refuse.

We reached at my house. I got out of his car and started walking towards the front door of my house. As I went more and more away from the car I felt him pulling me towards him, towards his body. I didnt want to leave him. So I stopped and turned around. He was still there, in his car, looking me go away.

Would you like to come in and have some coffee? I asked Anthony.

Sure, he replied and got out of his car. We went in.

It was surely not for the coffee but what came after it.

He waited for me on the couch as I was preparing coffee for him. I brought him his cup. I wanted to be done with the coffee as soon as possible. I cant wait to take him to my room. I was literally burning from inside.

He took his first sip from the cup and after a few second he started to feel a bit dizzy. I saw him fall unconscious on the ground with the cup. I wasnt surprised, the pills were working. This is what I was waiting for. Finally, the moment was here where I could take him to my room. I dragged his unconscious body to my room and on the way his head hit a few corners. He was heavy, bulky and I liked that because its so much fun cutting open a muscular body. I was sweaty and thirsty after all that dragging, so I went to the kitchen to cleanse my thirst with some water and then to the basement to get my axe which I had bought three days back after I had bought my new dress. A spark of energy bolted within me as I touched the axe, it made me more excited. I returned to my room where Anthony was still lying there with half life on the floor
. 
Smack! I hit the axes blade on his thigh and blood flew on my red dress.

Smack! 

Then his arms. More blood.

Smack!

Then the face. More blood.

With every drop of blood that spurted out of him, I got happier and happier. I dont know why but I loved this. This is what I did to Ian, Sam, Nathan and every other man I have met before. I loved cutting up men. It felt like an art to me.

My daddy used to abuse my mom, beat her. I didnt like it, so one night I drowned him in his own blood. It all started with my dad.

After Anthonys body was in eighteen or so pieces, I decided to end the fun. I got a huge plastic bag to put in the pieces. It was 1 am in the morning. 

I took the bag to my backyard. I dug up a hole with a shovel. I didnt want to bury the pieces while in the bag, if they pieces were buried without the bag and just in the dirt they would decompose faster. I emptied the whole bag with Anthony into the hole and also threw in the axe, just like I did for Jackson, Henry and Mathew. I filled the hole again with mud and back in my house.

I was tired but I did enjoy it a lot. I took a bowl of chips and saw some TV, my hands were still strained in blood but it didnt matter much.

TWO MONTHS LATER

It has been two months since I have moved to this town and I was excited to meet Barry tonight.


 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
