<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject2930</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> This Nifty Tool Helps You Create Nutella-Stuffed Bananas </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-08-13 19:06:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Make An L.E.D Illusion Mirror! </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-08-12 18:35:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-08-06 23:03:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That's a Lyft car.  https://www.lyft.com/
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Push For Pizza, The Easiest Way To Order Pizza Ever. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-08-05 20:51:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What do you get when you cross a bad marketing idea with a classic childhood candy? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-07-21 18:03:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-07-18 09:11:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So odd, I did it again with the same search words still nothing about canceling service, but I did get some other search results. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-07-17 23:37:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thanks for the feedback.  Yeah, I made sure that it's 24 months at the price, no contract.  I have a few friends over there that took care of me so I'm not worried.  I'm just looking forward to a service that is up to date in the decade.  Comcast hasn't change their shitty UI in like 10+ years. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-07-17 23:32:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thanks for sharing the positive experience.  I just hope that after the recent media about the experience that guy had it will be at least a little easier for people to cancel if they want to.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-07-17 23:19:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Well I'll be calling them on Saturday to cancel.  I plan on recording it just to see what hoops they make me jump through.  AT T U-verse here I come!  current Comcast bill $245, U-Verse for 2 years at $120(more channels and faster internet) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-07-17 20:12:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah that's true, but they don't even give that option when you search.  This what I got when I searched AT T http://imgur.com/Gdwvc2F
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Search results for "cancel service" on Comcast website </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-07-17 20:04:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
