<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject1493</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-11-14 02:35:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> He probably buys his drugs from a guy in a hummer </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-11-13 19:41:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Juice pouches trigger me. You stab an obviously phallic straw into a vagina -like pouch, it's basically a rape pouch. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-11-13 18:45:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [:(](http://imgur.com/WjR6LkV) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-11-13 17:14:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I honestly think it started as justification for keeping the slaves. I'm not a historian by any means so my opinion should be taken for next to worthless on this subject but I don't think racism was the huge driving force behind slavery. Slavery was a fact of the time, has been for longer than naught, it was just an easy source of free labor. It's also inhumane and horrible, so there wasn't much way to justify it morally to the populace. Unless the people you were enslaving are less than human, or not worthy of humane treatment. It's much easier to justify enslaving a dehumanized entity then one who thinks and feels the same way we do. It's what Hitler did to the Jews, made them out to be sub-human, something dangerous and worthy of destruction. It was easier to convince white Europeans and Americans that Black people were subhuman because they were physiologically different, came from a more primitive country, and couldn't communicate with the populace (at first, they learned eventually). Over hundreds of years, this justification turned into a more innate social racism as children were taught that black people deserved to be treated in such a way. People grew up knowing no different, they were taught racism and so racism festered. Until people who were not taught such things saw how disgusting it was and decided it needed to be ended. Again, I'm not historian and this opinion may be woefully wrong in regards to the real historical context so make what you will of it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-11-13 16:48:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That was the lost city of Atlanta, not Atlantis, big difference there's no Coca Cola plants in Atlantis to turn everyone into merpeople.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-11-13 16:40:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [Mahogany!?](http://www.youtube.com/watch?v=14D5wKSVlXg) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-11-13 16:31:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Well this dates back to the Greeks, who were possibly the most comfortable society has ever been with nudity. They took pride in the male form (sometimes to crazy extents) and saw no need to exaggerate the size of genitalia. They also, as a culture, celebrated youthfulness, nature, and the use of brain as the ultimate sign of masculinity. So if a Greek sculpture or artist created a man with a ridiculous schlong, not only would everyone call bullshit (because everyone was naked at least part of the time) they wouldn't have found it attractive or appealing since that isn't what their society deemed desirable. It would have been seen as a barbaric simpleton and not a learned Greek warrior. 

Renaissance era artists like Michelangelo were referencing the Greek artistic style when creating things like the Statue of David, or the Sistine Chapel (small dongs on that too). Today's culture is actually extremely prudish in comparison to the Greeks. We shame nature, nudity, and sex. So is it really any surprise that when what comes naturally is shamed, we come up with unnatural and unrealistic expectations of it? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-11-13 15:38:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Semantic Satiation, is the term for that. If you say something enough times you begin to doubt it's meaning. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-11-12 21:17:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yes by order of the Turd Reich, the Gestapoo will arrest all who dare defecate. No longer will the Poo menace sully our great nation. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-11-12 20:31:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Good thing it's a fox and not a person. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-11-12 19:37:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That too, didn't mean to imply they couldn't.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-11-12 18:52:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Its more just White People = Rich   Priviledged to them, facts dont really matter I think. They probably assume people like Vincent Van Gogh, Edgar Allen Poe, and Oscar Wilde were rich and priviledged even though they all died penniless.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-11-12 18:17:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's like being a policeman. Some join because they want to do good in their community, and help people in need. Others join because they enjoy being powerful and having dominion over normal citizens. And some join simply because it's a paycheck. You can't realistically say "all cops are bad" but you also can't say "all cops are good", there's just too much nuance to reality. I respect good soldiers like I respect good cops, denying that bad ones exist (not to imply that's what /u/Nozphexezora was saying) is just harmful though. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-11-12 18:02:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I could definitely see why some would, there are some very fair skinned people out there and since inter-race relationships are now pretty common it's not all that surprising. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-11-12 17:40:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I really don't know actually, Al-assad and Ghadafi are really the only ones who look kind of white (Maybe Hussein?). I've never heard of Asians self identifying as Caucasian though, not that it doesn't happen. A lot of these people were and are nationalists, and more than a couple hate the west and it's influence, so i couldn't see many identifying as white over the more indigenous races of the countries they rule. Anyway the point being humans do shitty things to other humans, race is not a prerequisite for evil, as i'm sure you're aware. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-11-12 17:21:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> And Mao also happens to be white, as well as, Pol Pot, Idi Aman, Saddam Hussein, Muammar Ghadafi, Genghis Khan, Osama Bin Laden, Bashar Al-Assad, Emperor Hirohito, Kim Il-sung, Kim Jong-il and Kim Jong-un, Robert Mugabe, Than Shwe, Sani Abacha, and Ayatollah Ali Kha. Why are white people so mean? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-11-12 16:49:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's odd because I have feeling people like this would be quick to call us racist if we had to point out the color of accomplished people as proof of some innate racial superiority. Bringing race up at every chance only further serves to make it an issue, which is probably what some people want (so they can continue to use the race card). Seriously, it will stop being such a big problem when people stop injecting it into every goddamn conversation and issue. Sometimes arbitrary melanin count just isn't part of the issue and it's really ironic because these people (SJW's and such) are supposedly against racism when they themselves seem to think that race is a big deal when it comes to dealing with people. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-11-12 16:20:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Well if they had to judge an idea based on it's merits they'd actually have to think, and form a cohesive argument, which we know the majority is incapable of. It's much easier to look up the person who authored it on wikipedia and launch Ad Hominen attacks until the other person has no interest in furthering the discussion. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-11-12 04:16:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What If paramedics were able to save one or both of Bruce Wayne's parents. Would he have become a doctor instead of Batman? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-11-11 18:00:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I believe he's talking about less quantifiable things, the changing of ones habits, lifestyle, thought process, and sometimes social circles. The effort involved with changing your entire life and outlook on life can be a hell of a lot more difficult than expected. I've experienced weight loss first hand and it is more than it's bare-bones components in that it requires a lot from a person, mentally, physically and habitually. One could say that driving a race car is simply just going fast and not crashing, and while they would be correct there is a little more nuance to it.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-11-11 16:13:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Did the exact same thing man. Even weirder still, I have one of his videos opened in another tab right this minute </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-11-10 17:29:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> "Oh no it looks like we have a technical rape on the field, the refs are stopping play" </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-11-10 17:12:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thanks for sharing the update, It seems like they got what was coming to them. I normally feel bad when the internet launches personal attacks on people. Not that it isn't deserved in some cases, it's just that I always advocate for the use of proper legal channels since the likelihood of the internet misfiring and jumping on innocents is pretty high (I guess i just don't support vigilantism in general). This though, this seems like a community letting these fuckers know that their bullshit has consequences. And I'm pretty conflicted as to whether that's better than vigilantism or not. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-11-09 19:12:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I like your idea better, she'll lose weight that way.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-11-08 17:44:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> A burner is a phone or something bought specifically to use a couple times then ditch. It's to make it harder to find you or harder to have illegal activities linked to you through the device. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-11-08 16:32:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So, one guy gets searched by an over-zealous (To say the least) cop, and all of a sudden cops everywhere gain the legal authority to start randomly stopping people and searching their phones?

Where did you get that from? I said that if cops can anally probe a guy over nothing, then them searching phone contents isn't all that unlikely. I never said whether it was defensible in court, or whether they had the right to, simply that it certainly seems possible given how far certain cops are willing to abuse privacy. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-11-08 14:24:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Well I mean there was that guy who got anally probed multiple times over a routine traffic stop because the officers thought he had drugs in there. They found nothing yet tried looking multiple times based on nothing more than the way he got out of his car or something. If shit like that can happen, downloading phone contents doesn't seem all that unlikely. That being said it's still a flagrant abuse of one's privacy rights. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-11-07 21:50:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> A fair point, never actually thought what would happen if I really needed to fap in an emergency situation. Assumed it would be something like [this](http://youtu.be/pQWCAvmZBcw?t=43s). </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-11-07 21:44:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Isn't that what the internet is in a nutshell, one big porn collection and a couple other sites? I mean who has a physical porn collection anymore? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-11-07 19:20:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I rolled over on to my right side, seeking optimal comfort under the oppressive softness and warmth of my heavy comforter. Letting out a sigh of content I curled up tighter, trying to squeeze every bit of warmth from this unforgiving room. Winter nights have always been the worst in this house. The draft that permeated the upper floors was almost unbearable at times, prompting the purchase of the extra thick bedsheets. One would think that there must be some sort of problem with the top floor, perhaps a lack of insulation, or improperly laid venting. The problem here is that I've had the house inspected several times by various different people. From furnace and duct work specialists to general contractors and so far no one has found anything of note. It was frustrating to say the least but luckily everything else about the house is great. I should probably just invest in a space heater and stop complaining to be honest. 


As the thoughts of of my house slowly wound down into peaceful nothingness, the hands of the sandman carefully wrapped around me, dragging me ever more quickly into his realm of slumber. Biology seemed to have a different idea though, and with my consciousness waning my bladder made a desperate plea. "Seriously?" I thought to myself "Always at the worst times, I swear". I grumbled audibly as I tentatively removed myself from my wonderful cocoon and stepped into the frigid landscape that was my bedroom. I grabbed a sweater that hung from the door and slipped it on, already shivering in the pale moonlight. Glancing at my alarm told me it was 12:26 am. I had been tossing and turning for nearly 2 hours. I've suffered from mild insomnia for years, so this wasn't anything new to me. However it didn't make it any more easy to leave my thermal sanctuary. 


As if sensing what I was doing my bladder let out an even more desperate cry, forcing me to nearly duck waddle as I made my way down the dark hallway to the bathroom. I flicked the light switch on, blinding myself in the process. Through squinted eyes I was able to make out the toilet and begin my business. My eyes had adjusted by the time I was finished, so I took a moment to inspect my face in the mirror as I washed my hands. My eye's were those of a man who was far too tired and cold, nearly dead in their stare. If I they weren't mine I'd probably be scared of eyes like this. I took a second to inspect the thin scar that ran across the bridge of my nose, a remnant of my childhood. I had apparently done battle with a coffee table when I was 5 and the coffee table won. "I got a cool scar out of it at least" I thought to myself.


I finished my hands and flushed the toilet. This is my least favorite part of late night wanderings. I stood in the doorway, took a deep breath and turned off the bathroom light. Now I'm not a superstitious person, I'm not paranoid, I'm not one to jump at shadows. For some reason though, standing in total darkness waiting for my eyes to adjust, has always terrified me, even in my own home. When i was younger It was a real problem. I'd never go to the bathroom at night unless i absolutely had to, to the point where wetting the bed was a more preferred outcome. As I became older it did get better but even now at 23 i still get freaked out about late night lavatory visits. They say that the fear of the dark is simply the fear of the unknown and i believe that holds true. I'd imagine it's a primeval thing, dating back to when a shadow in the dark was likely a predator trying to eat you. The lack of predators in the urban sprawl doesn't comfort me though. When my eyes finally came into focus I started to make my retreat towards my downy fortress.


My eyes deceived me though and i managed to stub my pinky toe, on the unseen door to the laundry room, which had been left slightly open. The pain was bad but i was too tired to do anything but grumble and shuffle back to my room. Slipping the sweater off, I crawled back into bed. I was beginning to drift off again when i heard it. A single muffled bump. Normally this wouldn't have really bothered me but I was already on edge from my recent expedition. I decided It was probably nothing until I heard another one a minute or so later. It was strange but likely just an animal on the roof. But it continued and my sleep deprived mind went to thoughts of Jeremy. This is what got me out of bed. Slowly standing up, I donned my sweater once more and stepped into the dim hallway for a second time. 


I made my way slowly down the hall, my eyes already keen in the darkness. I didn't want to turn on any lights lest I lose what night vision I had. I made it to the bathroom and listened. I heard the bump again, it definitely wasn't on the roof like I had previously thought. It seemed to be coming from downstairs. My stomach jumped into my chest. I lost all sense of self preservation and ran downstairs not caring who was listening. I made it to the second door on the left and swung it open, flicking on the light as i did so. 


What greeted me was extremely relieving. "What are you doing Jeremy? Whats the matter?" I asked. My son looked at me, a rather terrified and confused look on his face and then he ran over and hugged my leg. I picked him up, and held him tightly as he tried his best to explain what was wrong. He was a decent speaker for 3 but he seemed to be trying to say a couple different things at once. I calmed him down and eventually found out that he had heard a monster making noise upstairs. He said he didn't want to go up there so he tried banging on his wall to get attention. I smiled at that, which prompted and even more quizzical look from my son. "Don't worry I was just up there, and If there were any monsters they must have run away scared". Jeremy seemed relieved at that, but still seemed a bit shaken up. "Do you want to sleep in our bed tonight?" I asked , i got a small nod in answer. I carried him upstairs, showing him the lack of monsters firsthand, which calmed him down immensely. By the time i laid him in between my wife and I, he was already sound asleep. My wife rolled over a gave me a look, to which i responded "Don't worry about it, just dealing with some monsters". I climbed into bed pecked my wife and son on the cheek and drifted off.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-11-07 17:40:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [I'll take that $9 now, thank you very much](http://imgur.com/gCAw2hn) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-11-07 16:13:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Honestly I'm surprised China even had a somewhat valid argument for the women, heels really are not good driving shoes. I actually would have expected a more Saudi Arabian approach, in that they would just say women are inferior drivers for being women and that they can't drive cars because it hurts their uterus (although sitting in the passenger seat doesn't effect it for some reason?). Have to give credit to China for at least trying to have an actual reason and in a country where female babies are still considered inherently inferior, it counts for something i think.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-11-06 19:03:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I watched as the streetlight flickered above me, a dancing flame in the cool night. I observed, as it illuminated the darkness for a brief second and then stole it away, only to bath the recesses in light another time. My mind tried to grasp at a pattern in the intermittent flashing of the dying bulb, but there was none to be seen. I continued to search for repetition or some way to predict what would come next. It was fruitless though, some things follow no pattern. Yet, I find myself searching for these illusive sequences in everything i do. Most of the time I don't even realize it's happening. Until someone asks why I've been staring at a dripping faucet for 5 minutes. If I had to guess I'd say it's a fear of the unknown if anything. I just feel comfortable in routine, in predictability, leaving things to chance has never sat well with me. 


"Yo Danny, what's good my man?" A voice from behind me said, breaking me from my trance. I felt a hand pat my shoulder a few times. 


"It's all good Spence, how you been?" I said standing up and turning around to greet the reason I was sitting on the curb at nearly half past 10 on a Wednesday.


"I'm doin good bro, making flow. Been pretty quiet around here lately"


I looked around at the deserted houses, detritus strewn along their yards and spilling on to the street. The colors were faded, the windows broken, graffiti was on nearly every available spot. It was sad more than anything. Those houses once held families, they were once places of comfort to many people. Now they're either deserted or used as drug dens. Watching this street die was painful but thinking about the lives involved is even worse to me.


"Ya it's a real ghost town around here" I said focusing back onto Spencer. "We should probably hurry this up before we get some unwanted attention" 


"Relax man, no ones gonna bug us" Spencer said looking from one end of the street to the other. "You want your regular I'm guessing?"


"You know it" 


I pulled some cash out of my wallet, the last I had to be honest, and handed it over. What I got in return was a small plastic dime-bag. 


"Thanks dude, take er easy. I'll probably hit you up tomorrow" I said fist bumping Spence and taking my leave. 


I could hardly contain myself as i left the deal, I nearly ran back to my apartment. Clutching my prize the entire time, as if it would fly away if I weren't careful. I went up the 2 flights of stairs to my room and quickly went in and locked the door behind me. There was trash littering the floor, old pizza boxes, bills, and candy wrappers for the most part. It didn't bother me though, I just walked around it or kicked it out of the way as I went to my bedroom. The bedroom was no better than the rest of the apartment. The bed smelled and was unmade, the sheets were stained and grimy. Again didn't bother me, although i should wash the sheets soon. I sat on the edge of my bed and pulled out something from under it. It was an old cigar box, dark red and about the size of a football. It had my father's initials engraved on the top as well as some fancy design or something. It was one of the few things of his that I kept after he died. It had once housed a couple of Cuban cigars that my dad would puff on every once in a while. Usually for a celebration of some sort. Now it held a tourniquet, spoon, lighter and a few fresh hypodermic needles. 


My hands made deaf work of the spoils, quickly heating it and getting it prepped. Though, even with practiced hands I couldn't go quick enough to stop the shakes, and by the time I had found a vein they had started to become quite violent. I finally managed to get it in after a few failed attempts, injecting it gently into my bloodstream as the shakes continued to worsen. I removed the needle and laid back in my bed, the opiate quickly speeding through my body. I closed my eyes and let it happen, basking in the drug induced glow and contemplating my situation. 


This is one pattern i can reasonably predict. My penchant for substance abuse. I'm aware of what it's doing to me, it's effect on my health both mental and physical. The drain on my finances, my relationships and yet I find it hard to care. Because in this moment as my high begins, as the shakes wear down, as the struggles of the day to day shrug off me like many heavy chains; I am home.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-11-06 17:05:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> He hasn't been in power that long so I can't reasonably expect him to have completely fixed the church by now (there is a lot to fix). I do have to give him credit for trying though, and I'm interested to see where he'll take the CC. Nobody could be worse than Ratzinger... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-11-06 16:42:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm all for the CC doing good things and adapting and all that but i don't think we should start giving out tons of brownie points to the pope or the church for being decent human beings. Don't get me wrong I don't unconditionally hate the CC (i do admittedly dislike it though) it's just helping the poor and being humble are things they've been preaching for centuries. I don't feel the pope should be praised for doing things they have been telling others to do for close to 2000 years. Again progress is good, i'm happy that they're at least trying to move forward but they still have lots of ground to cover in my eyes.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-11-06 16:23:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> We had a chose to fight the Axis with love.


Maybe Hitler just needed a hug?


We had a chose to share the land.


Maybe Stalin could have given a hand?



We had a chose to fight on D-Day


Maybe France wanted Germany to stay?


We had a chose to fight Japan with peace


Maybe the emperor just wanted a treat? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-11-05 17:57:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Because the man was a dissenter and needed to be punished. All power to the great and mighty Micky D's! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-11-05 17:46:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Well that's different you see. Men don't have sex because they enjoy the company of women they do it because they hate women and want to rape them. So heterosexual males are all misogynistic and because of that any sex they have is really just violent rape. This is different to a glorious woman hating the people who imprison her, that's her right and being attracted to men means they are just oppressing her super hard. Therefore the only real misandrist's are the women who have realized they are being horribly oppressed and have opened up their true free lesbian as it is meant to be.

(Just pulled this out of my ass. Who knew making up illogical arguments was so easy?) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-11-05 16:21:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Goddammit Chris Hansen, this is the third time this week, either i'm really bad at judging age or you just can't wait to see me again. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-11-05 15:32:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'll bet you every publicized thing she's ever done was at the instruction of her handlers. I think it's way too formulaic to be anything but, I mean controversy is what every artist goes to when they start to drop out of the public eye. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-11-05 15:27:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  pretty much they're a bunch of fucktards.

tumblr SJW's in a nutshell. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-11-02 13:25:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You're a little off, It's entirely debatable and actually would be pretty easy to disprove. It's part of the beauty of science, any and all theories can be challenged or argued and it's necessary that they are. When we start claiming there's no arguing with the current explanation we create dogma. The only thing evolution deniers need is evidence, a fossil in the wrong spot from the wrong time period or a transitional species that doesn't fit the current model, anything besides belief to prove their position. If they find one of those, write a peer reviewed study on it and can argue it effectively then we'd have no reason but to consider their position. The fact that they've found none of those in the hundred years or so the theory has been around is pretty telling however. We just need to keep in mind that it's possible for science to be wrong, and not shirk away from admitting it when it happens, something that religion might never do, and part of why science consistently gets results. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-11-01 19:07:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You tell me edzachary what you're talking about! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-10-31 16:56:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It may be different in other places but [in Ontario, it's up to you to get the money](http://www.attorneygeneral.jus.gov.on.ca/english/courts/scc/small_claims_court_brochures_EN_Jan_11.pdf), although there are several court options that can be used in the case of a stubborn debtor. If the debtor isn't paying or the creditor wants a more structured payment plan (enforceable under the law) he/she can file for an examination hearing which examines the debtors finances and ability to pay. After examination the judge can then order the debtor to pay on certain dates if he see's fit. If the debtor does not pay, then there are 2 options left, garnishment of wages and seizure of land and property. Both require further paperwork and fee's, plus the seizure process is quite long and complicated. Basically if it's a relatively small amount and you have a really stubborn debtor it can very well end up costing more than the settlement itself.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-10-31 16:20:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> "It hurts my feelings to know that my actions have consequences"

It really is such a childish mentality, the shrugging of personal responsibility. Yes your fat, yes it's largely your fault, and yes it could kill you. They can ignore it all they want but when their pancreas explodes, their heart clogs shut, and their limbs start dying one by one, it's not going to matter whether they've accepted their body or consider themselves healthy.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-10-28 19:26:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Exactly, if someone tells me they feel uncomfortable with certain things and also doesn't feel comfortable explaining it, I'll just be a bit more mindful around them. This guy seemed to be flirting with her if anything, which is technically rape i guess. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-10-28 18:41:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hey man thats cool if you believe in something that strongly, im not saying that no one should stand up for their rights if that is what they choose. However, "Dead men tell no tales", what good can my corpse do? Id rather live and try to make the best of it, possibly effect change from within. If that means i have to play pretend for a couple hours a week so be it. Though, if one would rather die in protection of their rights, than be a pacifist. Thats their choice and all the power to them.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-10-28 17:10:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yep, my disbelief isn't worth becoming a martyr in my eyes. Sure if you believe there is a heaven being a martyr may make sense but me pretending to like Allah is much more appealing then being dead. Does that make me a coward? Probably. Does it mean I can live another day and possibly better my existence? Seems like it.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-10-28 17:05:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Nah we beat em with hockey sticks to tenderize them, the brain is then pan-fried and served with fries, cheese curds, and gravy. Ol' Dick isn't close to Canadian, although It wouldn't hurt him to be more polite (at least as far as I know).  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-10-28 16:26:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yah screwing up once can be attributed to many different things, incompetence, nurse could have been having a bad day, patient could have been stressed, the nurse could have made an honest error and read it wrong. But repeating the same mistake (or even less likely, different mistakes that cause the same outcome) consistently is just not likely in the slightest. 

  It'd be like a sports team that get's a penalty or something. The first one can be blamed on the ref, or an accident, or anything. The second and third could still be accidents, or the ref just doesn't like them. However, if this team is getting 2-3 penalties (assuming that's not ordinary for that sport) every game regardless of the refs, the blame almost certainly falls on the team itself, or more specifically it's management.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-10-28 16:14:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Wouldn't put it past her, these people treat weight like, well, treats. And everyone knows you can't have too much of a good thing^teehee! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-10-28 16:04:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Ya why should she have to explain how innocent gestures of human companionship trigger a childhood experience that no other human being could possibly know happened unless she specifically tells them. That shitlord should have used his patriarchal scrying stone to communicate with the ghosts of patriarchy past and determine she had already been oppressed enough before he tried to push it any further. The nerve of these men* is so triggering sometimes.

*(read: "Poopy Prince") </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-10-27 15:40:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yep they probably hate that our justice systems take on innocence is that "We'd a rather a hundred guilty men go free, then one innocent be jailed". </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-10-25 20:29:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [It's an edited commercial for La Sirena](http://www.youtube.com/watch?v=014JUEHxtzM) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-10-25 17:26:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [What he's referencing](http://www.youtube.com/watch?v=r9eS8PtfmRg) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-10-25 16:40:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> God that's depressing, thanks for sharing some insight into their culture. I'm both surprised and not that this kind of attitude still exists in the modern age.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-10-25 16:31:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> "It's necessary to have a gay in the group, wouldn't want people thinking we're prejudiced. See our gay is sitting over there by the black, we're a very diverse group in case you can't tell." </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-10-25 16:26:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Sex sells, there's not much more to it than that. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-10-25 16:19:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Which is ridiculous because the vast majority of males are under 6 feet, a small percentage is 6 foot or over and an even smaller percentage is over 6'5'' (like less than %2). Us guys are supposed to be accepting and understanding of things like weight, things that a women *can* actually change, but god forbid if we don't grow past 5'8''.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-10-25 15:57:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> And feels, nice chocolatey feels. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-10-25 15:54:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I remember reading somewhere that glandular conditions at the more extreme end can only account for around 25lbs of extra weight. Not saying medication won't be necessary in some cases, but it doesn't account for them being 150+lbs over the healthy weight. It really is as simple as eat less (and more healthy), move more in most cases, although as someone with a biological hindrance ([CFS](http://www.cdc.gov/CFS/)) I know it's easier said than done. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-10-24 17:59:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Wow, just wow. I'm so glad there was a happy ending to this, it was getting rather depressing hearing about how terrible people can be for such inane reasons. No one deserves to be treated like you were, like your not human, it's disgusting and anyone who acts that way has absolutely no right to claim moral superiority. 

Again very happy that you got out and that you've found some stability. It's a horrible reality that this kind of thing often breaks those involved, lesser men (women, trans, whatever) might not have had the determination or coping ability to do what you did, and hopefully stories like yours will stand as evidence of greener pastures to those poor unfortunates. 

Ever forward never back

Alone along a beaten path

Horrors long on horrid past 

Fearful not, free at last

(sorry you brought out the amateur poet in me) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-10-24 17:34:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I could perhaps see the news writing about it in more liberal leaning countries like Canada or the UK. Actually scratch that I could definitely see it becoming common place here in Canada, even though the country is one big cultural melting pot we do tend to take stupid measures in the name of equality.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-10-24 16:31:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Honestly at some point it stops being the parents fault how their child turns out. She's 22, her actions are her own now. Maybe her parents weren't good and started her off on a shitty footing or maybe they did everything as right as a parent can. We don't know but i think regardless of all that any decisions she's made, any stupid things she's done, are her own and should be treated as such. Her parents are only responsible for so much, she chooses to party, she chooses to abandon her daughter, she chooses not too pursue any kind of meaningful existence and she should be held accountable for it in full, at least i think so.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-10-24 16:15:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I think he only lost the tips of his fingers </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-10-24 15:44:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> "THERE IS NOTHING HERE, WE NEED TO TALK ABOUT GUNS AND GAYS NOW!" Thank you Arnold, that leads us to our next topic "Are gays making you shoot* people?" more on that in a minute.

Edit - Stupidity </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-10-23 20:11:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Dawkins* Now i feel stupid. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-10-23 18:05:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That it is my friend, that it is. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-10-23 17:55:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> She deserves a letter of gratitude from the agency for Patriarchal Education and National Institutional Security (PE-NIS). If more women self-identified as crazy there would be less time needed for educating and more time for oppressing. Hopefully when the Center for Unisex but Mostly Female Assimilation and Repression Training (CUMFART) starts up there will be more like her. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-10-23 17:34:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thank you very much! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-10-23 17:30:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> \Implying a women who willingly bleeds everywhere is in a "right state of mind"

\Implying her mattress isn't already a vile unsanitary mess

\Implying people would willingly go to her home let alone sit on her furniture

My issue is that it's pretty dangerous and unfair to people around you to be leaving bodily secretions (blood at that) every where you go. Sounds like a great way for disease too spread, or at the very least make a janitors job that much more unpleasant. While i support her right to do as she pleases with her body, I do take the stand that she should do so in the privacy of her own home. Simply because there is no one alive that wishes to be subjected to that. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-10-23 17:14:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The ["Streisand Effect"](http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Streisand_effect) if you will. Happens to SJW's a lot from what i can tell. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-10-23 17:00:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Reminds me of a debate i saw with Hitchens, Dawkings, and Grayling (IIRC) on the topic of "Is religion bad for society". Dawkings (or Grayling) spoke first for the atheist and brought up historical and current examples of theocratic evil, listing only places that start with the letter "b". His argument basically pointed out that religion has had hundreds of chances to be good for society and has failed (rather horribly in some cases) almost every time. 

The speaker directly after him was a Rabbi who's entire argument was "My synagogue does charity work, and we're all really good people, and there's no bad that comes from religion because my congregation does good things so that's proof that religion only does good things." Pure feelsy anecdotes to counter Dawkins exposition about the very real things religion has done when it has power. She essentially undermined the entire position with her little sermon about feels and ignoring larger contexts in favor of happy anecdotes.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-10-22 17:34:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Not sure about the Americans but i've always used "spoiled" in Canada. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-10-22 16:39:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Warm compress to bring it to a head and then pop it. Alternatively you could wash it daily until it goes away but where's the fun in that? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-10-22 15:21:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> They do it here in Canada as well </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-10-22 15:14:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You should be proud of yourself for losing weight, it's an accomplishment, one that isn't always easy to get. There's nothing wrong with being proud of the body you sculpted, you earned it, just don't rub it in peoples faces all the time :P.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-10-22 14:46:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Well they obviously weren't there before the people already sitting at the front so what are they complaining about? That white people shouldn't get first come first serve seating even though they were there first? How do they not see the blatant entitlement behind that?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-10-22 14:18:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Same here bro, not sure why they would bother coming here but who knows. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-10-21 16:17:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It keeps them busy and out of the streets, so there's that i guess. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-10-20 17:05:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Afrocentric


afrsntrk/


adjective

    

1. regarding African or black culture as pre-eminent. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-10-20 15:49:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> that are fat because of legit conditions. 

Glandular problems can account for 25 lbs extra at the most. I don't think there's a condition out there that makes you fat (and certainly not obese) if you are dieting and exercising properly. Even if you physically can't exercise, if you eat accordingly you won't get fat.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-10-19 02:41:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thank you for expanding. The book that i got this regimen from detailed a food plan as well. I dont have the book on me atm but to summarize it said much the same thing: complex carbs, low fat but also all good fat from things like yogurt and nuts, plenty of protein from lean meats (and nuts again), high fiber, tons of vegetables (leafy greens especially), fruit but not a lot. 

The book really stood out to me because its incredibly sensible in its principles and 
extremely comprehensive. Its really worth a read now that im thinking about it. The approach it gave me to eating and exercise is really great. When i get it back ill read over it and refresh my memory see if anything else might help people. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Diet and CFS </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-10-18 17:50:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So /u/Kromulent thinks my choice of diet is deserving of a post here. Now i can't take credit for this diet plan, as it's tenants were outlined to me in a book called *The New Abs Diet* by David Zinczenko (editor-in-chief of men's health). The book has nothing relating to CFS in it but the diet it set forth produced interesting results for me. 


Basically eating healthy is obvious for most of us. Good food = more nutrients and essentials = good functioning body. What surprised me was that the strictness of times for eating had the most impact. The way the diet is setup is as follows.


You eat 6 times a day, 3 meals (400-500 cal), and 3 snacks (200-300 cal) at specific times. An example of what this might look like (starting time should be just after you wake up) is: 8 am meal, 11 am snack, 1 pm meal, 4 pm snack, 6 pm meal, 9pm snack. The goal is too have 3 hours between a meal and a snack and 2 hours between a snack and a meal. 


It seems pretty anal, and it really is but I noticed that my body adapted really quickly and I'm at a point where I'm almost only hungry at the times I'm used to eating at. The interesting thing though, is that my energy is more stable and constant than before, i crash less frequently and not as severely. I find keeping a level amount of food in the body prevents energy spikes and subsequent troughs, or at least lessens their impact. The routine part of it also allows for the better planning of meals and i find it's a good framework for other pre-planned daily tasks, it just feels less stressful when you know when to do certain things.


I'm not sure how this will effect other people but i've had success with it and it's not a pill or anything drastic. Which means anyone can give it a shot and i'd say it's worth a try at the least. I wish the best of luck to everyone, i hope this helps in some way. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-10-18 17:13:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> A Canadian stand off if you will. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-10-18 15:46:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Huh well not sure how i missed that, I stand corrected. She must be pissed off 24/7 at all the misogynistic door holding that goes on here. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Aesop Rock -- Big Bang [Hip-Hop] (2000) </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-08-17 18:50:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [Meta] Musings and contemplations of fat-logic. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-07-23 15:45:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I've gotten to thinking lately about causes and factors at play within the mind of a planet. I'm no psychologist but i have theories as to some of the various delusions winding their way through a hammy mind. These are simply theories and in no way are scientifically viable. I just see these as common factors (at least one) in all FPS's. 

1.) Confirmation Bias

This is a big one and very common in TiTP and other people who believe in "fat oppression". Confirmation bias is when one harbors a preconceived notion and in turn looks for confirmation of it in everything they do. A great example is fatties who get offended when a skinny person looks better in a dress. With the bias the fatty doesn't see a skinny person with a nice dress because they feel like wearing it, or want to look good. No they see a skinny person *trying to show them up*. In their mind they've already come to the conclusion that you are oppressing them and thus will grasp at any straw no matter how thin and then take it the most offensive way possible. They then hold up their delusion as fact of their oppression.

2.) Self Victimization

It's hard to tell what is a bias and what is "Playing the victim". Porkers always seem ready to spin a tale so that they are the ones being hurt. I think that playing the victim is simply a means to an end though. I believe that it's necessary for them to maintain their bias, their delusion. If they were in the wrong, then they aren't being oppressed. They've already confirmed in their minds that they are oppressed and therefore the story in their head takes shape as them in the right. Every. Time. Now it could also be the inability to accept personal responsibility and in which case they aren't playing the victim, they legitimately think they *are* the victim. It could also simply be a condition of their psyche, some people get off to being a victim. I think in most cases though it's a reaffirmation of an already made up mind.


3.) Protagonist delusion (delusions of grandeur/entitlement)

There's probably a word for this but I'm going to call it "Protagonist Delusion". It's a personal delusion in which ones self is considered to be the main character of the story that is life. That one is more important than another because in their mind the story was written for them. This is a universally human delusion that i feel effects everyone to a certain degree. My theory is it's because you can only experience your own life. You have no possible way of feeling through the eyes of another person. You have no reference point but yourself, and other people aren't you. Critical thinking and empathy would dictate that another life is just as valuable (or invaluable depending on your thoughts of the species) as your own. Those lacking these skills though, may dismiss everyone else as "background characters" thus leading to a sense of entitlement. A good example is Hammies thinking that everyone should be attracted to them, or that they should get special treatment, or just that general air about them, that they think they are better than you. It may stem from a need for attention, it may also stem from a disconnect from reality. I don't know the cause but the effect is there.

4.) Self esteem and confidence

Or the reason HAES is so popular. Gas giants would like you to think they are unaffected by society or biology and it's bias towards health. For some they probably aren't, but most i feel at some level know they are being disgusting. I think this leads to a lot of the lashing out that planets seem to do. They are hurting a lot but instead of trying to get over it they blame others and internalize it. It also causes them to seek out constant self-reassurance in their delusions. If that takes the form a 50 year-old outdated and dis-proven study than so be it, it supports their reality. 

5.) Rejection from society (real or imagined) 

I have no doubts that bullying of fat people exists. It's just that the root factor is more than likely not their weight. See bullies don't care who or what you are if you have any kind of weakness, anything about you that might be embarrassing. They will find it and they will exploit it. They make fun of weight not because they hate fat people (most of the time, im sure there are some people who just hate fatties) but because it hurts you. If they couldn't draw a reaction from it they'd stop it and move on to something that will. Now it could also be that the person is just an asshole and people are mean to them because they are just genuinely unlikeable. Regardless, a person who's bullied (or feels they are) is in a very vulnerable state of mind. It would be fairly easy for them or someone else to convince them it's not *them* but their *weight*.  It's comforting to think it's just some stupid superficial thing and not that they don't like you or that somethings wrong with you.  I think this thinking leads to a confirmation bias, and ultimately to fat logic.

Let me know what you guys think. Do you think im close with some? Or is the beetus actin up again and makin me write nonsense? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Basic Cable - Aesop Rock </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-07-17 03:24:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [Progress] I think I made it. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-07-12 15:54:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> First, pics:

[Before](http://imgur.com/xPAjqDj) 6' (183 cm), 230lbs (104kg), mostly fat (not the best pic but the best one i had right before i started losing weight)

[After](http://imgur.com/VIFgWII) 6', 172lbs (78kg), mostly muscle

I suffer from a condition called [Chronic Fatigue Syndrome](http://www.nlm.nih.gov/medlineplus/chronicfatiguesyndrome.html) so for a while i considered exercise too strenuous. It took too much of a toll on my body. The outcome of such a mentality (coupled with my eating habits) is no surprise; I became fairly overweight. I ballooned up to my highest of ~230lbs right around the age of 14-15, I.E the beginning of high school. So i spent most of my first year trying to hide my body, generally feeling uncomfortable in any clothes i wear and scared of social situations. That summer though everything just kind of clicked. I decided i was going to do something about it. 

I got my mom to help teach me about nutrition and I started scouring the web for information and a workout routine. I started with some generic bodyweight/light dumbbell circuit training and i began restricting calories and food. As you can imagine it was a bitch at first, as is common. However, as the months went by my body became more and more adapt to exercise. I still ached and felt like crap a lot but i was seeing results and goddamnit i wasn't giving up now. Around the 5-6 month mark i had hit my initial goal of 195lbs. I could have stopped there, goal accomplished, and it would have still been a success. I found a love in fitness though, I wanted to see just how far i could make it. Another 3 or 4 months later i was at 170 lbs, almost under weight, something i never thought would happen.

Since that time more than a year ago, i've been adding muscle+definition, and working on my cardio (which i admittedly  neglected for most of my weight loss). I've changed routines lots of times but i've returned to a circuit training routine for the last couple months to get rid of any and all excess fat. 

More important than my weight loss though is the skills i've learned while doing it, things i never knew that i had in me. Discipline, self-control, self-motivation, self-determination, structure, routine, organization and more. These are things that are desperately needed to survive with a chronic illness and i'm thankful everyday that i decided to change myself. I really feel that fitness has saved my life or at least certainly enhanced my ability to enjoy it. 

For those wondering my weekly routine as of now goes like this

Monday: Full body circuit training with an ab circuit to begin

Ab circuit: Upper abs (Crunches), Lower Abs (Pulse Ups), Obliques (Side crunches), Transverse abdominis (Plank), Lower Back (Seated Good Mornings) 

Full body circuit: Squat, Bench Press, Pulldown, Military Press, Bent Over Row, Tricep Pulldowns, Leg Extensions, Bicep Curls, Leg Curls. 

Tuesday: 3km interval style run

Wednesday: Ab circuit with different exercises to hit the same body parts. Then same full body workout as Monday. 

Thursday: 3km interval style run

Friday: Leg day, no ab circuit but a slightly different full body circuit.

Leg day circuit: Deadlifts, Bench Press, Pulldown, Weighted Lunges, Military Press, Bent Over Row, Weighted step-ups, Tricep Pulldowns, Leg Extensions, Bicep Curls, Leg Curls. And i sometimes go for a run after.

Saturday: Ab circuit

Sunday: Off

I'll answer any questions to the best of my ability. If this isn't the place to put this let me know and thanks for reading!
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> I caught a picture of her mid-yawn. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-07-10 17:50:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> F2F - How I prevented the genesis of a Hamplanet </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-06-29 15:42:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> EDIT:Very sorry for being an idiot and not reading the posting guide. All further posts will fall in line with those rules, again my apologies.
TL;DR I lost lot's of weight after i got fed up with myself.
Greetings my fellow whale watchers. I'm new to this site and FPS is by far my favorite subreddit since i started reading a couple days ago. I have seen several stories of people who were motivated from this site. I'm not one of them, but perhaps I can serve as an inspiration. For you see i've been on the magical journey towards fitness and have been quite successful (IMO). So perhaps my story might resonate with some of you lusciously curvy individuals out there. 

So to begin some back story is needed. I grew up in a mid-sized Canadian town. In school i was an average kid, weight and height wise, until about Grade 3 (9 or 10 years old) when i started showing symptoms of what would later by diagnosed as Myalgic Encephalomyelitis (Chronic Fatigue Syndrome). To complicate things I had a major growth spurt the year after, i shot up to 5''8' or so which took a toll on me. My eating and exercise habits up to this point had peen poor at best. Lot's of quick meals, lot's of snacks, no real control on portions and the CFS made exercise harder since i never felt like i had the energy to do it. Add that all together and I was a Hamplanet in the making. 

Fast forward to Grade 9. I was just under 6'', 230lbs+ and gaining. I had started playing football the year before to try and combat it (I was pretty good, surprisingly, but it always took a lot out of me). I played in high school and noticed moderate improvement on my cardio and lung capacity but I was still gaining weight. During that season i suffered further injury to an already bad shoulder to the point where i had to quit because i could cause lifelong injuries. So here i am, overweight, self-conscious, and now without my only source of exercise. The hammy cosmos were rejoicing that day, having made preparations to admit me into the Interstellar Hamplanet society. 

Now here's the part where most people get lost. That summer, coupled with the new social hierarchy posed by HS, my self esteem was at an all time low. I wasn't the fattest but i had really unsightly rolls, man tits, stretchmarks, and like most overweight people i never felt comfortable in or out of clothes. One day (couldn't tell you which) i decided to change myself. This is where people have a hard time. "But subject1493 what do you mean nothing inspired you to lose weight?", "It can't be that simple subject1493" Oh but is. It just clicked one day, I'm doing this to myself. I had blamed my circumstance in the past. My genetics, my condition, but i realized that I wasn't exactly doing anything to help myself. I had been sitting on my butt upset with myself for years because nothing was changing, but what the hell was i doing to change it? This is where my real journey began.

My mom has been overweight my whole life. Not hamplanet size, more of a small moon but not a fit person. However she learned a lot about health and fitness because of her medical job. 
So she was making efforts to be healthy, and took full responsibility for the way her body looked, there was no fat logic to be found (sorry guys). This is where i learned the fundamentals of a healthy diet, which admittedly she had been trying to teach me for years but i never listened. As for exercise i just looked up some random full body MMA circuit workout. Thus began my transformation. In the months following i struggled to get a routine in order. I worked out 2-3 times a week, and began to restrict what and how much i ate. My goal was to be 195lbs, i would be more than content to be 35lbs lighter. Nothing much happened at first but i began to see minor weight loss, a few pounds or so, enough that it could be chocked up to a loss in water weight. I took it as a sign to try harder, lo and behold a month or so later i was down 10 lbs. Couldn't blame that on water, I was seeing success! 

I kept this pace for around 8 months. Improving my workout and diet as often as possible. It wasn't easy, a lot of days i had to force myself, others i was just physically incapable, I never stopped completely though. I would do something small, anything, my motto during that time was simply "something is better than nothing". 10 push-ups is better than none etc. I couldn't believe what had happened though. Nobody really could. As the dust settled my feeble goal of 195lbs had been shattered beyond recognition. I was 170lbs, I had lost 60, over %25 of my body mass. I honestly couldn't believe it, I still barely can. The only reminder i have of my former self is the stretch marks that litter my body, slowly fading as my skin readjusts. The boost to both my confidence and self-esteem in that moment was palpable, it was as if i was going Super Saiyan.

Since then my fitness efforts have only increased. I've gained around 10 lbs of muscle in the year and a bit since i lost the weight. Old friends couldn't believe their eye's, I had a near constant smile for the first few months until the euphoria wore off. For someone who had not been comfortable with themselves since they were 11, being able to take my shirt off with confidence is just indescribable. My entire life has changed, things look so much better for me. CFS no longer tolls me the way it did since I fined tuned myself, I can play soccer or something with friends without stopping to catch my breath every 5 minutes. Plus my new favorite activity is running, which I consider a big f-u to my former immobile chunky self. 

Thanks for reading everyone and I really hope this doesn't sound like me bragging. I'll answer any questions to the best of my ability. If this is the wrong place to post this let me know. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
