<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject713</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-23 04:19:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> For sure!  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-23 03:34:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm aware. I'm buying a tank and all that tomorrow.

Update: Contacted the previous tenant, apparently he escaped about 10 months ago... I'm amazed he has survived that long.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-23 03:33:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I just found him ... I'm buying a tank off Craigslist tomorrow. Found out the hard way they are an incredibly aggressive species.

Update: I was able to get this together today. Now we wait, he is very shy and I don't want to poke him out,  

[The Setup](https://imgur.com/gallery/i2vWZ) 

Still haven't caught him... he is ultra elusive and I also discovered he climbs INTO the fridges components. I'm assuming because it's warm up there. I've got a proper lamp and all, but he seems to dig the fridge. 11/28/16

Sad news. 11/30/16

The gecko has passed away. I didn't seem him since our encounter and I had a suspicion he was somewhere in the workings of the fridge. I looked and never saw anything. I noticed a smell last night and I knew it was him. I dissembled the bottom of the fridge and he was living  between the fan and the compressor. Lots of feces and bugs, must have lived there for a long time. It's sad.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> I recently moved into my apartment and found the previous owners abandoned gecko. He lives underneath and behind my fridge. He lives off the occasional bug. He is currently shedding his skin. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-23 03:12:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What we should really have been worried about </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-09 20:20:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-07 18:44:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Calling her back </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-07 05:18:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Most overrated thing in Europe.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-07 04:21:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Just goes to show how misinformed I was. Are the North African refugees from the Arab Spring or is their arrival more drug related? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-06 18:10:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Then my beggar wasn't Romanian. He was much darker skin.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-06 15:27:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Awesome man, thanks. I guess I was amazed by the intense cultural diversity. Before I went to Europe I was ignorant enough to think that countries had a single identity with minor differences. 

I had a similar realization when going through France. Specially with Paris vs.  Rest of France.

I was told they hop and trains and when they land in the train station that they become marooned there. I'm not sure what Romanians look like.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-06 15:11:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I was amazed with how similar Bavaria was to Texas. Bavarians are incredibly proud like Texans. Their mentality is "I'm Bavarian before I'm German." It was interesting to see Munich compared to Berlin. Not sure if that's the actual mentality expressed by them but it is what I observed. 

Also, I was in the Berlin train station for a few hours waiting for a train to Prague and there was a TON of refugees begging. They are the most aggressive beggars I've ever encountered. They gave the guys beneath the Eiffel Tower a run for their money. Really put the crisis into perspective for me.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-25 21:42:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Do not touch at every museum ever </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
