<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject2323</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-28 13:50:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So I ended up buying this fan (against all advice of not buying aftermarket). It was 1/3 of the cost of OEM and the reviews are very positive, it arrive in 2 days and fit like OEM. we will see - https://www.amazon.com/URO-Parts-17-561-757/dp/B00BQS7BJS/ref=pd_rhf_yaod_p_img_3?ie=UTF8 psc=1 refRID=7JQKZCJXG606A0SC4NJS </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-24 17:11:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> the one closest to the engine. Thank you for the price range. Do you have a part number? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-24 16:42:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> its a 2002 e46 325CIc - sports package </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Your index finger is always a bit smaller than your nostril </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-24 14:45:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-24 14:40:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'll see what AAP has and let you guys know. Thanks! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-24 14:39:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I haven't checked that - worried about overheating but I will try today. Thanks! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> ELI5: what UK leaving EU means to the average UK citizen </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-24 14:31:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-24 14:15:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I tested and there is ~12v at the connector and small voltage at the signal wire. The fuse is good and no check engine light. I would like to just go buy it at a store instead of ordering it.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-24 13:55:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> i don't agree - I feel Reddit is a safe haven for people to express themselves without having anger hurdled at them by the troubled youth </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-24 13:47:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> save you the clicks: https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=nBB2bPwKWVg </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> TIL Moby's song 'Extreme Ways' was used at the conclusion of all four of the Bourne films </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-24 13:45:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-24 13:18:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I use Mobil 1 0w40 for over 100k - Can't complain </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-24 13:03:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I have a 02 325 Cic - I agree with you - the car is constant work (160k) but still puts a smile on my face! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Radiator Cooling Fan not turning on - Car overheating </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-24 13:02:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I got my E46 325CIc back from getting Thermostat, Coolant hoses, Water pump, Thermal expansion bottle, and radiator replaced and now it over heats in traffic or waiting at a drive thru. I noticed the Radiator fan does not turn on. Since it is easy to remove (Manual Trans) I inspected the connections and all looks good. Any suggestion on next step? Or where to buy a quality, long lasting Radiator Fan? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-24 13:00:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I got my E46 325CIc back from getting everything above replaced and now it over heats in traffic or waiting at a drive thru. I noticed the Radiator fan does not turn on. Since it is easy to remove (Manual Trans) I inspected the connections and all looks good. Any suggestion on next step? Or where to buy a quality, long lasting Radiator Fan? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-24 12:55:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I found the same broken wire! the brown thin wire. fixed and now folds as before...If anything BMW's are consistent - Thanks guys! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-23 13:13:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I think I have the same issue. Here is when my fault happens:
When Top is Up (closed) the red light blinks as if not closed completely and will not move in any director by pressing button.
I can manually put it down (i got a small auto-driver with an allen)
When top is Down (open) I can press close button, it will go up half way (looks like the picture) and just stops.

I did read there are position sensors in the harness, and if 1 goes bad it stops. I haven't tried to fix it. Anyone have a solution? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-21 13:24:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I knew nothing about LCD but my GF was adamant we see them and I am glad I was part of the experience. Being a fan of the EDM scene I appreciated their electronic sound and impressed that it was all generated on stage, not by a track playing in the background. My GF kept referring to James Murphy (front man) as a god...I will say his presence on stage was captivating and dare i say god-like </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-15 15:46:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Kanye did nothing to be forgiven for! This totem is a reminder to the haters that they should just let go of the undeserving bashing  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-15 15:40:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I got such a bad sneeze attack (and nose dripping and coughing) during Pearl Jam that I had to leave  :(( missed the fireworks and pink floyd cover - heard it from the car </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-14 20:40:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thank you! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-14 13:04:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I have a video - not sure what the best way to share it since youtube is taking everything Bonnaroo related down </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-14 13:03:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Sorry - still learning how to use Reddit here --- http://imgur.com/NNHz0J7  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-14 13:03:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> http://imgur.com/NNHz0J7  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> So during the Judd Apathow comedy show in the Comedy Tent at Bonnaroo, Eddie Vedder came out and sang a tribute song to Gary Shandling, while Judd read Gary's old jokes...This actually happened --- http://imgur.com/NNHz0J7 </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-14 12:56:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-14 12:53:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So during the Judd Apathow comedy show in the Comedy Tent in Bonnaroo, Eddie Vedder came out and sang a tribute song to Gary Shandling, while Judd read Gary's old jokes...This actually happened --- http://imgur.com/NNHz0J7 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-10 11:20:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Its 5:18a in Boston - I am running around with my head cut off trying to pack (and doing my morning ritual by ready Reddit)...I will see you there!!!!  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-09 13:04:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> for comparison: http://imgur.com/gallery/4xAQypN/ </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-09 12:58:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This island in PR has thousands of wild horses that behave like wild dogs...just roaming the streets eating grass. Beautiful Place </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Wild Horses on a Beach in Vieques, Puerto Rico </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-09 12:58:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-09 12:42:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This island in PR has thousands of wild horses that behave like wild dogs...just roaming the streets eating grass. Beautiful Place </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Wild Horses on the beach in Vieques, Puerto Rico </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-09 12:40:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-08 13:14:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If you are a young Republican, there is a good chance you were raised in a strict household. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The older I get the more I realize Sex is a Job that is required to keep a woman happy in a relationship...and it is a lot of hard work! </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-24 11:57:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-13 13:05:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This is a fake: No TSA employee past or present would know a complex word like 'flabbergasted' NONE! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-11 12:38:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> ~Said Justin Bieber </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-30 12:31:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I am in a similar situation...but I really like this girl. Is there no other way? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-30 12:29:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> my GF is recognizing she has mental health issues (I tried pointing it out but coming from me it sounds like i'm just calling her crazy) she signed up for a therapist and after 2 visits she feels he sucks. All he kept telling her is she is normal and everyone goes thru this. After she got a bill for $400 (two visits with insurance) she is discouraged from going to a different one. Can you recommend what I can do to get her proper treatment?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-17 01:50:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> at 30 my hangovers are more than just a small headache...its now a terrible self loathing, questioning my existence experience. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-15 05:31:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> coincidentally, 1 hour ago i watched the final episode..GF never seen the show and we just binged all 5 seasons in 2 months....what a show..... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-11-21 14:33:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Do you mind rattling off some of those shows? I don't have the patience to 'give shows a try'. I like complex, sophisticated shows with high level of cinematography quality...like the Leftovers (HBO). </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-11-21 14:30:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I want my gf to stop being crazy 15 out of the 30 days a month </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-10-29 11:47:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The Book was soo much better...after reading it, I found the movie sanitized and boring. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-10-14 13:22:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Black Rock...Burning Man...Lightning in a shape of a man burning...I get it.... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-10-11 14:20:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What are your thoughts comparing the movie to the book? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Did anyone else think 'The Martian' movie did no justice to the book? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-10-10 17:17:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> After finishing the book, I went right to the theater to get a visual representation....and felt like I watched sanitized cliff notes. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-08-14 13:47:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> IMO he played the same character in both movies...just one was motivated by money the other by hate...thoughts?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-02 14:53:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I recommend a black shirt over the eyes. When you have a dream you know mission accomplished
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-28 16:58:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Soo.....Mission Success? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> SpaceX - CRS-7 Launch explosion - Video [ Funny Ending ] </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-28 16:57:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
