<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject1230</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-28 02:14:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> When are people going to figure out that prohibition doesn't work?

Alcohol, other substances, technology...it's all prohibition. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-28 01:58:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  That Bitcoin is good enough (once the blocksize thing is resolved).

I'm starting to think this is a very big *if*, and it pains me to say that. :-( </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-28 01:50:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> How are you supposed to create these coins, with machines, or can I just use a normal computer?

'You' are not really supposed to create coins, or at least you cannot do so effectively with a normal computer, but you can try if you want. The mining market is dominated by people and companies with Application Specific Integrated Circuits (ASICs) that are much more powerful and efficient than a CPU or GPU in a normal computer.

What is "mining" exactly, and what does it mine?

Mining is a computationally intensive process by which miners put transactions permanently into the blockchain. They are rewarded for doing this by the new bitcoins that are 'mined' and given to them.

Is it expensive to do?

Yes, unless you have cheap electricity or are just doing it on a very small scale as a hobby or learning experience.

If you want to buy bitcoins, I recommend services like Coinbase.com or Circle.com for newbies. You could also meetup with people in person and pay cash through LocalBitcoins.com or Mycelium Local Trader.

For your own Bitcoin 'account', I'd recommend using Electrum on a normal computer, Mycelium on Android, and BreadWallet or AirBitz on IOS.

I hope this helps and I'm happy to answer any other questions. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-28 01:37:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Remember everyone that almost all of us really want the same sort of things.

Bases on their actions for over a year now, I no longer believe that Adam Back and Blockstream/Core want open, permissionless innovation. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-27 03:45:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This may not be popular in this sub, but...

Just pay for a legitimate copy of Windows.

I feel like $100 to $120 is well worth it to get a copy of Windows that you *know* doesn't have all sorts of rootkits in it.

(well, at least only Microsoft and USGovernment approved rootkits) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-27 03:07:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If Bernie's not on the ballot, I'm probably voting for Gary Johnson or Jill Stein.

Or fuck it, even John McAfee.

Mainstream Democrats and mainstream Republicans in no way represent me.

It's like, should I:

* vote for a 'Democrat' party member for perpetual warfare, expansion of the surveillance state, continuation of the war on drugs, and unbalanced budgets?
* vote for a Republican party member for perpetual warfare, expansion of the surveillance state, continuation of the war on drugs, and unbalanced budgets?
* Not vote for candidates that don't represent my interests? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-27 01:46:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It'll go to the Supreme Court. Fo sure.

FBI fooled *you!* (and me)

They just pretend it was no big deal and never happened and now they'll find more subtle ways to spy on everything everybody does. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-27 01:44:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> **We have always been at war with unencrypted disposable phones.**
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-27 01:15:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> 'We', as in the general population, lose wealth via taxes and money printing to support endless warfare.

This is wealth being taken from us that is used to destroy infrastructure and kill brown people on the other side of the world and to also enrich our domestic 'defense' industry.

[George Orwell](https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/George_Orwell) wrote [a book largely about this](https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Nineteen_Eighty-Four), including [a chapter focusing almost exclusively on it](https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/The_Theory_and_Practice_of_Oligarchical_Collectivism). </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-27 00:47:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah, I'm very confused here.

I'm currently only seeing 316 total votes for Bernie and 83 total votes for Hillary with 72.5% of precincts reporting.

Anybody know what's going on here? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-25 18:24:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> TIL Bernie Sanders will replace Cash for Clunkers with Karma for Krap when elected.

But only if you upvote this dank ~~shit~~ krap, yo.

#\#KarmaForKrap </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-25 06:56:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> "and I took an Ambien." </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-25 06:55:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Coming, you say? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-25 06:35:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'll leave this here:

http://www.wordfind.com/ends-with/ted/ </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-25 06:33:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That just for JEB! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-25 06:32:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> ADULTERA**TED** </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-25 06:25:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> 2creepy4u, pussy.

I was just, like, uh, saying it was scary so I would know who to call a pussy, pussy.

/s </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-25 06:11:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That's like some Silent Hill level nightmare shit. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-25 06:05:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> MARK IT ZERO!!! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-25 05:45:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thank you. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-25 05:33:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> **Gets the lotion** </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-25 05:22:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> !poop! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-25 05:22:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> poop </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-24 22:22:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> *ASSIMILATE!* </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-24 21:23:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thank you! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-24 21:09:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Awesome article dude. I really like the differences between projections and realities, especially the color coding.

Just one pointer because it made my eyes hurt: it's very difficult to read the text in the dark blue/purple cells. Maybe use a grayish color that shows up well on both light and dark backgrounds? Or some other color scheme?

I don't say that to take away from the article. It's extremely high quality. Keep up the good work!
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-24 20:53:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thank you /u/GTFErinyes! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-24 20:51:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> ...and Windows Snipping Tool and Microsoft Paint. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-24 20:47:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  The only problem is that you'll never get the same exposure as being positively portrayed in millions of people's living rooms, as Clinton has had the privilege of doing.
 
 The cable news stations should not only give fair time and fair balance to Sanders, but should disclose their corporate ties which contribute to Clinton's campaign. They should do that every time they mention either of their names.

I've been telling my dad how there's an agenda behind everything on television. He normally doesn't want to hear about it.

But he was bitching recently about a segment on Star Wars that was on Good Morning America (ABC) and that he doesn't give a crap about Star Wars.

I asked him who owns Star Wars and who owns ABC. He correctly answered Disney.

Now he's sort of getting it and grumbles that the news *used* to be mostly just presentation of facts. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-24 20:41:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This is very true, though I believe it does give a good indication of what types of individuals are supporting each candidate.

Maybe a PAC graph will be my next project. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-24 20:40:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Well thank you!

Happy Thursday to you as well! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-24 20:38:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The raw data is available at http://www.fec.gov/disclosurep/pnational.do and includes a break down of each donation made and the name of the person making each donation.

So it could be easily parsed. I've got other work to do right now, but I might try to do it tonight or tomorrow.

Or you can do it and probably get a good chunk of internet points. :-) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-24 19:09:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Created using Microsoft Excel. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-24 19:02:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Microsoft Excel.

Thank you. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-24 18:57:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yes.

Thank you. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-24 18:55:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thank you.

The maximum individual donation amount is $2,700.00. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-24 18:03:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Source: http://www.fec.gov/disclosurep/pnational.do

Inspired by:

* /u/Schwa142
* /u/_prototype 
* /u/dreamsplease
* /u/Janube

in this thread: https://np.reddit.com/r/politics/comments/4bdwzf/hillary_clinton_says_her_campaign_depends_on/d18lp7x?context=2 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-24 17:58:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Source: http://www.fec.gov/disclosurep/pnational.do

Inspired by:

* /u/Schwa142
* /u/_prototype 
* /u/dreamsplease
* /u/Janube

in this thread: https://np.reddit.com/r/politics/comments/4bdwzf/hillary_clinton_says_her_campaign_depends_on/d18lp7x?context=2 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-24 17:58:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Source: http://www.fec.gov/disclosurep/pnational.do

Inspired by:

* /u/Schwa142
* /u/_prototype 
* /u/dreamsplease
* /u/Janube

in this thread: https://np.reddit.com/r/politics/comments/4bdwzf/hillary_clinton_says_her_campaign_depends_on/d18lp7x?context=2 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-24 17:55:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Source: http://www.fec.gov/disclosurep/pnational.do

EDIT: Inspired by:

* /u/Schwa142
* /u/_prototype 
* /u/dreamsplease
* /u/Janube

in this thread: https://np.reddit.com/r/politics/comments/4bdwzf/hillary_clinton_says_her_campaign_depends_on/d18lp7x?context=2

EDIT 2: Created using Microsoft Excel.

EDIT 3: ...and Windows Snipping Tool and Microsoft Paint. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-24 15:40:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What's the source on this?

All I could find was 

http://www.cfinst.org/pdf/federal/president/2016/M2/Presidential_M2_Table2.pdf

which goes through January 31, 2016.

EDIT: Nevermind, looks like this is it

http://www.fec.gov/disclosurep/pnational.do </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-22 16:45:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> lol </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-22 16:41:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Your ban was justified in accordance with Infallible r\Bitcoin Supreme Law. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-22 16:15:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> /r/Glitch_in_the_Matrix/ </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-22 15:50:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> First commenter appears to be shadowbanned. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-22 15:04:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Copy that. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-22 15:03:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Copy that. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-22 15:00:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hey man. Thanks for commenting. I have no problem with sidechains. I think they're awesome and I encourage solutions built on top of (or to the side of?) Bitcoin.

Bringing up 'evil Blockstream' doesn't seem totally relevant here, beyond using RootStock as an example of why sidechains are a good thing.

But while we're bringing up unrelated topics, may we continue the conversation we were previously having? (https://np.reddit.com/r/Anarcho_Capitalism/comments/4b06de/request_to_remove_rbitcoin_from_the_sister/d16v5m8?context=3)

vakeraj:
r/btc is such garbage. They merely practice a different for of censorship: downvoting all pro-Core comments or anyone contradicting their Blockstream conspiracy theories to oblivion. Now they're bringing the fight here because many ancaps might not follow the minutiae of the blocksize debate, so they're easily swayed.

subject1230:
Oh look, another BlockstreamCore defender getting downvoted on a non-Bitcoin subreddit.

First /r/technology, now /r/Anarcho_Capitalism.

Those /r/btc sock-puppets and shills are just *EVERYWHERE!*

vakeraj:
This thread was started by a frequent poster at r/btc, and is being brigaded from r/btc.

Also, that thread in r/technology you were referring to was also started by a frequent r/btc poster, and brigaded from there.

Classic supporters mindlessly view this as a war that has to be won, instead of taking a deep breath, stepping back for a moment, and calmly looking at the issue.

subject1230:
that thread in /r/technology you were referring to was also started by a frequent /r/btc poster, and brigaded from there.

Are we referring to this thread with 2,400+ more upvotes than downvotes? https://np.reddit.com/r/technology/comments/48zggz/a_behind_the_scenes_look_at_how_bitcoin_core/

With this top comment at 1,000+ more upvotes than downvotes? https://np.reddit.com/r/technology/comments/48zggz/a_behind_the_scenes_look_at_how_bitcoin_core/d0nx0h7

Started by /u/champbronc2, who in his last 1,000 or so posts, has 656 posts and 2,137 karma in r\Bitcoin and 6 posts and 116 karma in /r/btc? http://snoopsnoo.com/u/champbronc2#by-subreddit </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-22 04:39:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> `beep boop beep boop`

`Moderation is not censorship, and /r/Bitcoin is not Core.`

`beep boop beep boop`

`At the current rate of growth, we will not hit 1 MB for 4 more years.`

`beep boop beep boop`

`Technically, Blockstream is my customer, not the users or miners.`

`beep boop beep boop`

`Evolutionism is still no more credible than it has ever been. By the way, the Sun really orbits the Earth, not vice-versa.`

`beep boop beep boop`

`Claims of censorship in /r/Bitcoin seem to be nothing but FUD`

`beep boop beep boop`

`Manipulating public opinion is not censorship`

`beep boop beep boop`

`The concensus of scientific research seems more in favour of the geocentric theory`

`beep boop beep boop`

`Essentially they (/r/BTC, Bitcoin.com, "Bitcoin Classic", et al) want to establish a government for Bitcoin.`

`beep boop beep boop` </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-22 04:14:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> RemindMe! 2 days Sweet sweet karma courtesy /u/dreamsplease </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-21 15:39:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The easiest way to support classic is probably to run a full node.

You can download full Classic node software at https://bitcoinclassic.com/ and clicking on the "[Download](https://github.com/bitcoinclassic/bitcoinclassic/releases/tag/v0.12.0cl1)" link that goes to GitHub.

They have builds for Windows, OSX, Linux, and ARMs. I believe the ARM build should work on a Raspberry Pi. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-21 14:40:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Just write to Ben Lawsk....oh wait, he created an over-burdensome cryptocurrency regulatory framework and promptly resigned to start The Lawsky Group (http://www.lawskygroup.com/about.html), which describes itself as follows

The Lawsky Group specializes in helping companies, boards, and individuals manage their most complex, emergent and dynamic challenges. The firm provides in-depth counsel and strategic advice on financial services regulation, cybersecurity and cyber-risk, new financial technologies, compliance, consumer protection, privacy, anti-money laundering controls, crisis management, and investigations in the banking, insurance and other related industries.

But to answer your question, this (http://www.dfs.ny.gov/consumer/fileacomplaint.htm) is probably what you're looking for. The "General Questions about Financial Services" section might be the most appropriate option. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-20 23:01:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I do agree that a hard-fork is not backwards compatible and it would take time to deploy.

In that regard, how do you feel about Classic's 28 day activation grace period?

* Is a grace period a good way to help deploy a hard-fork? If not, what are other good options?
* If it is a good option, is 28 days enough? If not, how long would be enough?

Regarding simplicity (or lack thereof), I realize there's a little bit more to increasing the maximum block size than just changing a "1" to a "2", but the impression I've gotten from perusing through the Classic code a little bit back is that it's about 15 more lines of code to make sure everything goes smoothly. Am I misinformed here? (---genuine question, I haven't delved through every single line of code or considered *every* angle).

What hangs me up is seeing something like SegWit (which I have no problem with in itself), which seems to be a fairly fundamental restructuring of the blockchain, being promoted, while changing a "1" to a "2" and about a dozen more lines of supporting code changes being called too complicated. I'm not following the logic there, but maybe I'm missing a part of the picture.

I have to head out right now, but I'll do my best to get back to any responses later tonight.

Thanks for for the discussion. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-20 20:27:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Probably Circle or Coinbase then.

https://LocalBitcoins.com/ or Mycelium Local Trader could be good too if you'd rather meet someone nearby in person and exchange cash. Just be safe.

https://LibertyX.com/ might be useful too. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-20 20:02:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I would reformat the new phone for security purposes, even if Bitcoin wasn't a factor here.

For the transfer, personally I'd just make a new wallet on the new phone and send the coins over from the old wallet on the old phone because I think it'd be simpler, but transferring the original wallet to the new phone shouldn't be difficult either, especially if you use your 12(?) word seed. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-20 19:57:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> As far as *easiest* goes, I'd say Circle or Coinbase.

But you might get better responses if you name your country. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-20 19:33:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> what happend since then?

I suspect money, but I have no proof.

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-20 19:27:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  stop the infighting.

I strongly suspect that if Core were to change:

`/** The maximum allowed size for a serialized block, in bytes (network rule) */`
`static const unsigned int MAX_BLOCK_SIZE = 1000000;`

to

`/** The maximum allowed size for a serialized block, in bytes (network rule) */`
`static const unsigned int MAX_BLOCK_SIZE = 2000000;`

a vast majority of the infighting would stop. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-20 19:16:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Like, they really have to crap all over people doing something to improve their lives? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-20 18:27:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  intel lost as far as i am concerned.

I'm not disagreeing with individual use cases, but market share data may indicate otherwise:

http://static.cdn-seekingalpha.com/uploads/2012/3/6/1007049-13310482568458378-Helix-Investment-Management_origin.png </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-20 18:15:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> +1, shit man. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-20 18:08:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> that thread in /r/technology you were referring to was also started by a frequent /r/btc poster, and brigaded from there.

Are we referring to this thread with 2,400+ more upvotes than downvotes? https://np.reddit.com/r/technology/comments/48zggz/a_behind_the_scenes_look_at_how_bitcoin_core/

With this top comment at 1,000+ more upvotes than downvotes? https://np.reddit.com/r/technology/comments/48zggz/a_behind_the_scenes_look_at_how_bitcoin_core/d0nx0h7

Started by /u/champbronc2, who in his last 1,000 or so posts, has 656 posts and 2,137 karma in r\Bitcoin and 6 posts and 116 karma in /r/btc? http://snoopsnoo.com/u/champbronc2#by-subreddit </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-20 17:44:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm also thinking sociopath possibly. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-20 17:42:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Perhaps he's had a financially inspired change of heart. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-20 17:32:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I think he thinks you're suggesting you were banned on one account and then made a second account to get around the ban. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-20 17:20:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The government itself does not care if the currency is devalued as long as it keeps printing more money for itself.

The population is forced to suffer devaluation of the money they already have because the government keeps printing more money and giving this money to itself.

Simplified Example:

* The total quantity of all Venezuelan Bolivares in existence is 1,000,000.00 Bolivares and the people (not the government) hold all of it.

* The government decides to print 99,000,000.00 more Bolivares and give it to itself.

* The total value in terms of Bolivares is now 100,000,000.00 Bolivares, but the total value of these 100,000,000.00 Bolivares in terms of purchasing power is still the same as the original 1,000,000.00 Bolivares.

* Due to inflation (the printing of 99,000,000.00 Bolivares), the original 1,000,000.00 Bolivares owned by the Venezuelan people is now worth 1% of what it was worth before the printing.

* The Venezuelan government has effectively stolen 99% of the cash value that was previously owned by the Venezuelan people. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-19 12:36:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's my opinion that that /r/Buttcoin often has surprisingly insightful points of view, even if they're jerks or trolls about it sometimes. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-19 12:35:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> For the record, I think The Daily Decrypt is great and /u/The_Daily_Decrypt does an excellent job.

I also think /r/Buttcoin is often better than many of us at being objective about Bitcoin, even if they're jerks about it some of the time. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-19 05:16:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> https://archive.is/VbArf

Full thread:

https://archive.is/https://www.reddit.com/r/Anarcho_Capitalism/comments/4b06de/request_to_remove_rbitcoin_from_the_sister/ </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-19 05:12:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm actively diversifying. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-19 05:05:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I was banned from r\Bitcoin for 90 days for 'Brigading' when I linked to r\Bitcoin from /r/btc without using an NP link.

I suspect it was really just an excuse to ban me for making rational and civil arguments that did not support your personal views. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-19 04:52:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I also request to remove /r/bitcoin from the "Sister Subreddits" on the sidebar.

Or at the very least add /r/btc or add a note saying that r\Bitcoin is under heavy censorship. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-19 04:43:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Uhhhhhh....THAT'S NOT WHAT YOUR MOM SAID! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-19 04:23:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Because the Venezuelan government is printing so much money that their currency is rapidly losing value, and the government is forcing 'official' exchange rates that are wildly out of tune with free market exchange rates.

Any other currency that holds value better than the Venezuelan Bolivar is a way out of this for the population.

In particular, Bitcoin and cryptocurrency are useful because they are easy to transport and difficult to detect in transport. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-19 04:12:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> "Bolivarian Intelligence Service" and "administration of the ministry of Popular Power for Communication and Information"

Orwellian much? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-19 03:58:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> https://archive.is/xG6Zt

And the full thread:

https://archive.is/https://www.reddit.com/r/Anarcho_Capitalism/comments/4b06de/request_to_remove_rbitcoin_from_the_sister/ </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-19 03:51:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  Bitcoin's natural anarchism

/u/luke-jr and BlockstreamCore: Self-anointed king's of Bitcoin's natural anarchism.

Praise be to /u/luke-jr and BlockstreamCore! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-19 03:47:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Oh look, another BlockstreamCore developer/defender and censorship denier getting downvoted on a non-Bitcoin subreddit.

First /r/technology, now /r/Anarcho_Capitalism!

These /r/btc sock-puppets and shills are just *EVERYWHERE!* </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-19 03:22:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I second this, /r/Buttcoin and altcoins subs are great for getting out of the Bitcoin echo-chamber.

Edit: Aww, come on guys. I'm a huge Bitcoin supporter. But we all know we get pretty overzealous a lot of the time. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-19 03:19:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Oh look, another BlockstreamCore defender getting downvoted on a non-Bitcoin subreddit.

First /r/technology, now /r/Anarcho_Capitalism.

Those /r/btc sock-puppets and shills are just *EVERYWHERE!* </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-18 17:19:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I prefer sending PM's to individuals in r\Bitcoin. Even more so now that I'm banned. :-)

I've found what's even more effective is to just help them out with whatever they're talking about. Eventually they'll ask why you're not responding in the thread in r\Bitcoin.

Though I guess sending PMs doesn't do anything to reach out to lurkers. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-18 17:16:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Oh, I didn't actually give you the gold. Just that I think it got your post the attention that led to someone else giving you gold. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-18 15:57:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I agree in concept, but it seems obvious (to me at least) that this is a preemptive move to prevent people from finding out about things that don't support their continued control of Bitcoin. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-18 15:52:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> *Oh*, it starts with a few jokes and some slurs. *"Hey, denty!"* Next thing you know you're saying they should have their own schools! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-18 15:49:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I realize the word 'Agile' has been turned into a management/marketing buzzword, but I still think it's extremely valid and applicable. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-18 15:47:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yes sir, gotta get me that sweet internet karma.

And get you some sweet internet gold. ;-P </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-18 05:58:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> BlockstreamCore devs be like: [It's Like I'm Walking On Sunshine!](https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=H6TW6v39_kQ) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-18 05:48:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Obligatory GIVE ME GOLD, ASSHOLES. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-18 05:41:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I am *not* an *anti-dentite!* </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-18 05:23:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's alright

You're ready for the night

Of your life

Stars will shine so bright

They say

We're dancing the stress away

(Hey hey) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-18 05:02:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You shut up! You're not really Satoshi's sock-puppet, you damn dirty sock-puppet! /s </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-18 05:00:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> And [page 4](http://8btc.com/thread-30703-4-1.html). </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-18 04:59:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> classic classic </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-18 04:56:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [Manifesto for Agile Software Development](http://agilemanifesto.org/):

**Manifesto for Agile Software Development**

We are uncovering better ways of developing

software by doing it and helping others do it.

Through this work we have come to value:

* Individuals and interactions over processes and tools

* Working software over comprehensive documentation

* Customer collaboration over contract negotiation

* Responding to change over following a plan

That is, while there is value in the items on

the right, we value the items on the left more.

[Open-source software development methods](https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Open-source_software_development#Open-source_software_development_methods) (emphasis mine):

It is hard to run an open-source project following a more traditional software development method like the waterfall model, because in these traditional methods it is not allowed to go back to a previous phase. In open-source software development, requirements are rarely gathered before the start of the project; instead they are based on early releases of the software product, as Robbins describes[4]. Besides requirements, often volunteer staff is attracted to help develop the software product based on the early releases of the software. ***This networking effect is essential according to Abrahamsson et al.: if the introduced prototype gathers enough attention, it will gradually start to attract more and more developers. However, Abrahamsson et al. also point out that the community is very harsh, much like the business world of closed-source software: if you find the customers you survive, but without customers you die.[5]***

Alfonso Fuggetta mentions that rapid prototyping, incremental and evolutionary development, spiral lifecycle, rapid application development, and, recently, extreme programming and the agile software process can be equally applied to proprietary and open source software.[6] One open-source development method mentioned by Fuggetta is an agile method called Extreme Programming. ***All the Agile methods are in essence applicable to open-source software development, because of their iterative and incremental character.*** Another Agile method, Internet-Speed Development, is also suitable for open-source software development in particular because of the distributed development principle it adopts. Internet-Speed Development used geographically distributed teams to work around the clock. This method is mostly adopted by large closed-source firms like Microsoft, because only big software firms are able to create distributed development centers in different time zones. Of course if software is developed by a large group of volunteers in different countries, this is being achieved naturally and without the investment needed like with closed-source software development. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-18 04:35:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This?

http://www.ic.unicamp.br/~stolfi/EXPORT/projects/bitcoin/posts/2015-06-10-my-sofa-is-a-sidechain/main.html

This is fantastic! Though he did lose me at:

For my sofa, the relevant digital artifact is the integer 418 in 16-bit unsigned binary notation. Its controller, by definition, is the real number sqrt(pi); a fact that can be trivially ascertained by any cryptographic method. So, the integer 418 is an asset, by definition (2). </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-17 16:53:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Paging /u/jstolfi for being awesome. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-17 16:27:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Understood. Thank you for the excellent response.

I would encourage you to make this into its own post.

:-) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-17 15:24:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm familiar with the Agile Manifesto, but I'm not fully seeing the connection.

Can you elaborate? Are you saying this behavior from Blockstream/Core does not conform to the Agile Manifesto? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-17 15:18:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Intro (emphasis mine):

It's a mystery that has evaded the best minds in archeology for decades: the unknown fate of a beautiful queen who ruled over ancient Egypt at the height of its power.

But Nefertiti may be hiding in plain sight, [according to a recent theory](http://cnn.com/2015/10/01/africa/nefertiti-tomb-egypt/) that's set the Egyptology world buzzing.

Adding credence to that theory, Egyptian Antiquities Minister Mamdouh El Damati announced Thursday that based on preliminary findings from a radar scan of King Tut's tomb site, ***experts are 90% sure they found two new chambers behind the walls of Tut's resting place***.

 [British archaeologist Nicolas Reeves](http://edition.cnn.com/2015/08/11/africa/nefertiti-tomb-tutankhamun/) speculated in August that Nefertiti was buried in one of those chambers. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-17 04:52:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thank you. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-17 04:39:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [Zune](https://www.reddit.com/r/Zune/) Master Race. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-17 04:21:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This @satoshin?

https://twitter.com/satoshin </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-16 20:56:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> * **Strengthen Family Outreach and Engagement**

 Families are the first line of defense in keeping youth safe from violent extremism. High schools should develop outreach and engagement programs that educate families about the 
various forms of violent extremism and ways to identify at-risk youth or concerning behaviors and communications. In fact, many of the most fruitful and positive leads 
reported to authorities have come from concerned family members or community leaders. It is very important that schools engage the students families through PTA or other programs as a vital step to preventing the mobilization of possibly radicalized students.

...

* **Educate Faculty About Bystanders**

Less than half of the individuals witnessing activities or behaviors that can lead to early intervention report their observations to community members or law enforcement. Encouraging increased reporting and intercession by third parties could improve the success of efforts to curb extremist acts in the U.S. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-16 20:48:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Is the document posted in the article legitimate?

https://info.publicintelligence.net/FBI-PreventingExtremismSchools.pdf

Anyone have a source directly from the FBI? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-16 20:44:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What's the source on this?

Where are these screen shots pulled from? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-16 20:34:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Welcome back! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-16 20:26:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's convenient for traders who are quickly going back and forth between BTC and other currencies.

It's also convenient for people who can't be bothered to learn how to use Bitcoin for themselves, which was and still is a large number of people. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-16 20:00:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Correct.

You control your own private keys with Mycelium.

People with coins in mtgox did not control their private keys. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-16 19:13:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It depends what 'enough' means for you.

Someone could still hack into your device and figure out a way to steal your coins.

If you have any amount that you consider significant, you may want to figure out some sort of air-gapped cold storage solution. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-15 17:46:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> As soon as one of the agents handling this software realizes the truly gargantuan amount of money he or she could make from selling it on the internet, he or she will figure out a way to do so. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-15 17:39:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> https://i.imgur.com/hvNzkRc.jpg

[*The Twilight Zone*: The Odyssey of Flight 33](https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/The_Odyssey_of_Flight_33) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-15 16:29:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hey man, I agree that this was very heavy-handed.

That said, repeatedly dropping the f-bomb and otherwise taking a confrontational tone really doesn't help anyone to act in good faith.

Keep up the high quality content /u/aquentin; I hope to see you back soon. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-15 16:22:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Assuming the modmail conversation posted [here](https://np.reddit.com/r/bitcoin_uncensored/comments/4aetng/banned_from_rbtc/d0zumkn) is accurate, can we please let /u/aquentin back in immediately?

I realize modding sucks some or a lot of the time and decisions need to be made, and I very very much appreciate what /u/SouperNerd and all the other mods do here, but this seems pretty extreme, especially for someone who contributes so much to this subreddit.

This just seems like a crappy situation caused by two good guys with maybe not-so-great communication by both parties.

EDIT: switched the link to NP </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-15 15:41:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [Best response completely nails it](https://twitter.com/a3456gf/status/709501337222963200):

[@austinhill](https://twitter.com/austinhill) You are a hypocrite. Downvotes are not censorship. It's a signal that the Bitcoin community hates you. You should get the hint. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-15 13:31:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> (   ) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-15 13:07:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If you hold the private keys, you'll own coins on both chains after a fork.

If you don't hold the private keys, it'll be up to the party holding your coins if they give you coins on both chains (or any coins at all, but that's always the case if someone else holds your coins).

TL;DR: Use your own wallet, not a 3rd party wallet.

Also, 'BCC' and 'BC' might be confusing to people: BitCoin Classic? BitCoin Core? BitCoin? Blockstream Core? BlockChain? BitCoinChina? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-14 13:31:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Disagreement on the maximum block size limit.

But it's reached the point of being more about governance of Bitcoin rather than the maximum block size limit itself.

And on top of this, heavy-handed censorship on r\Bitcoin and condonement of said censorship by several Blockstream/Core developers is making the whole situation much more divisive. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-13 22:31:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  It couldn't be more plain that we are in trouble, that we caused it, and that we as a species have to be as proactive as possible doing something about it.

As long as there are massive short term profits to be made and regular people have their bread and circuses, very little will be done.

Change will happen when the pain of staying the same is greater than the pain of changing.

:-( </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-13 20:35:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [6,000 x 4,000](https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=dQw4w9WgXcQ), not JK. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-13 16:08:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> *ahem*

[He's a troll](https://www.reddit.com/r/btc/comments/4a60hc/rbtc_seems_to_have_lost_its_way/d0y8rx0?context=1). </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-13 16:06:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> ***Engage with the above individual at the expense of your own time and sanity***

FYI guys, /u/smartfbrankings is known for 'hooking' rational people with inflammatory comments, and then acting like he is open to having a rational discussion.

He then will waste your time in a 10+ comment thread that gets buried in which he repeatedly shifts goal posts, finds new things to argue about, uses all sorts of logical fallacies, and generally doesn't actually offer any sort of position or stance or suggestions and just disagrees with everything you have to say in what appears to be a concerned manner.

And he's damn good at it. I'd call him a master concern-troll.

Engage if you want, consider it an in exercise making sure you fully understand your beliefs. But do not assume he is engaging with you in good faith.

And no, I'm not responding to you /u/smartfbrankings. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-13 16:00:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  you...spin...bullshit

:-) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-12 14:11:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So congress could unite on hate? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-12 14:02:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Fucking Steph Curry. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-12 06:31:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> ***Engage with the above individual at the expense of your own time and sanity***

FYI guys, /u/smartfbrankings is known for 'hooking' rational people with inflammatory comments, and then acting like he is open to having a rational discussion.

He then will waste your time in a 10+ comment thread that gets buried in which he repeatedly shifts goal posts, finds new things to argue about, uses all sorts of logical fallacies, and generally doesn't actually offer any sort of position or stance or suggestions and just disagrees with everything you have to say in what appears to be a concerned manner.

And he's damn good at it. I'd call him a master concern-troll.

Engage if you want, consider it an in exercise making sure you fully understand your beliefs. But do not assume he is engaging with you in good faith.

And no, I'm not responding to you /u/smartfbrankings. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-12 06:22:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I was banned for 'Brigading' when I linked to r\Bitcoin from /r/btc without using an NP link.

Or maybe it had to do with all the times I civilly and logically pointed out nonsense over there. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-12 05:58:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You mean r\Bitcoin?

:-) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-11 16:01:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You're welcome, it's my pleasure!

Looks better already! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-11 14:51:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I think it's cool and the site is awesome.

That said, here's feedback from my perspective:

* The 'popup that takes up the whole screen' method really puts me off. My immediate thought is to just close the page because 'screw this' (like I do with Forbes and their welcome screens, Bitcoin.com and their popups, or just obnoxious ads in general).

* The popup also makes me question the credibility of what the popup has to say and the contents of the whole site. "If this site feels the need to force this message upon me, are they just pushing an agenda?"

* The **NOTICE** looks like a seizure notice, a DMCA take-down notice, or some other type of error and at first glance makes me think there is something wrong with the site.

My suggestions:

* Make the popup slightly less obnoxious, at least not nearly the entire screen as it is now. Make it so readers can see more than just a giant black and white popup **NOTICE** and that there is actual content behind the popup.

* Maybe use less dimming on the background behind the **NOTICE** so users can more easily see the actual page behind it.

* Spruce the notice up a little bit! Add some color or design, maybe something a little more descriptive than just **NOTICE**, it could be framed as a PSA meant to help and inform Bitcoin enthusiasts. Hell, even the FBI and DEA make eye-catching take-down/seizure notices.

Maybe I'm different from others visiting the site or I'm not your target demographic, but these are my thoughts.

I hope this helps. Keep up the excellent work. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-11 12:54:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  reasonable

Keyword here.

But really though, objections are objections, reasonable or not.

Just look at how XT got picked apart for having other changes besides an 8MB block size limit.

At this point the debate is about more than just the max block size or other improvements, it's about governance of Bitcoin.

Though I imagine at some point in the future thin blocks will be merged, regardless of how this debacle turns out. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-11 06:00:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [Dont Talk to Police](https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=6wXkI4t7nuc), and definitely don't confess. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-11 05:56:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> They're both de facto forms of governance/control.

One has a greater degree of perceived legitimacy. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-11 05:44:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> #WAKE UP ~~SHEEPLE~~ BEEPLE </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-11 04:56:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Exactly this.

No need to give any further potential for objection to Classic.

2MB vs 1MB.

That's it for now. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-11 04:52:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [Seeing this complete bullshit on there is depressing.](https://np.reddit.com/r/Bitcoin/comments/492jbs/bitcoin_is_on_the_front_page_of_rtechnology_again/d0oj89j)

[Especially seeing all the "BlockstreamCore" conspiracy retard posts.](https://np.reddit.com/r/Bitcoin/comments/492jbs/bitcoin_is_on_the_front_page_of_rtechnology_again/d0oj89j)

[Are people now trying to make Bitcoin look bad in the public eye out of spite? Now that Classic has failed and has little support, are the tx spam attacks and reddit posts trying to damage Bitcoin by feeding outsiders bullshit stories what they are doing now because they want to damage the reputation of Bitcoin?](https://np.reddit.com/r/Bitcoin/comments/492jbs/bitcoin_is_on_the_front_page_of_rtechnology_again/d0oj89j)

[Seeing their political strategy shift to one that's going negative on Bitcoin towards outsiders/mainstream non-Bitcoin users it makes me wonder what the point is, and what their next step is going to be. Classic has failed, and trying to pull down Bitcoin doesn't make a lot of sense unless they're planning on competing with it. So what's the next step here, altcoin? Is this the transition strategy to try to create the new narrative that Bitcoin has failed, here's our new solution?](https://np.reddit.com/r/Bitcoin/comments/492jbs/bitcoin_is_on_the_front_page_of_rtechnology_again/d0oj89j)

[They know it requires consensus within Bitcoin to change anything. This new political effort isn't the type of thing that's going to help Classic gain any sort of consensus with the people who know what's going on in Bitcoin(the people who matter and make up the economic and technical consensus). So other than pure spite, what's going on?](https://np.reddit.com/r/Bitcoin/comments/492jbs/bitcoin_is_on_the_front_page_of_rtechnology_again/d0oj89j)

**/SARCASM** </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-11 04:44:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> FWIW, IMHO Bitcoin.com *feels* pretty scammy, but actually has a ton of good content.

Paying to promote wallets immediately strikes me as scammy.

As do popups that take over my entire mobile screen.

These are two things that, from my point of view, immediately detract from the credibility of Bitcoin.com. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-11 04:39:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> OP is a Redditor for one day... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-11 04:32:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hai! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-10 17:58:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What about /u/RegurgitatedCumBuble s? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-10 17:56:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I came too. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-10 17:54:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You say to-may-to, I say to-mah-to. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-10 17:53:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Are you related to Michael Buble? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-10 16:40:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Practice test, practice tests, and more practice tests, from lots of different sources.

And when you see anything you don't know on a practice test (whether you get the question right or wrong) look it up and take some notes on it.

Also, Mike Myers' and Professor Messer's videos are fantastic. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-10 16:31:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [Telescreens](https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Telescreen) are becoming more and more real everyday.

Good thing [Big Brother](https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Big_Brother_%28Nineteen_Eighty-Four%29) will keep us safe. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-10 16:19:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Check your finger privilege, shit lord.

**\#AllSurfacePatternsMatter** </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-10 16:16:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> He's with the lord now. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-10 16:09:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I think the issue is that some people within our community are not admitting to their vested interests.

Or at least that's what others suspect. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-10 15:50:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hey Adam, replying again because it looks like the pitchforks may be starting to come out:

Thank you for coming over here and initializing a civil conversation. I have some strong disagreements with you on certain topics, but discussing the economics of mining is not something I feel warrants anything less than civility.

Am I correct in interpreting your comments as follows?

I think what Adam is saying is that the 'switch on price' is a lot higher than a 'switch off price' because to initially switch on requires a relatively significant investment in initial mining infrastructure.

I imagine there is also a 'switch back on price' that is equal to or just slightly higher than the 'switch off price' for miners that have switched off. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-10 15:46:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I think what Adam is saying is that the 'switch on price' is a lot higher than a 'switch off price' because to initially switch on requires a relatively significant investment in initial mining infrastructure.

I imagine there is also a 'switch back on price' that is equal to or just slightly higher than the 'switch off price' for miners that have switched off.

Yeah, I do see the irony in what might be a misapplication of the term 'sunk cost', but he's here trying to have a civil conversation about the economics of mining. As far as this conversation goes, I see no need to get out pitchforks or otherwise be even slightly less than civil. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-10 15:42:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I understand sunk cost is a fallacy and I think Adam is just slightly misusing the term.

I think what Adam is saying is that the 'switch on price' is a lot higher than a 'switch off price' because to initially switch on requires a relatively significant investment in initial mining infrastructure.

I imagine there is also a 'switch back on price' that is equal to or just slightly higher than the 'switch off price' for miners that have switched off. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-10 15:40:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I understand sunk cost is a fallacy.

I think what Adam is saying is that the 'switch on price' is a lot higher than a 'switch off price' because to initially switch on requires a relatively significant investment in initial mining infrastructure.

I imagine there is also a 'switch back on price' that is equal to or just slightly higher than the 'switch off price' for miners that have switched off. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-10 14:26:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  There is a huge difference between the switch on price (what reward per GH you'd need to see to make a mining investment) and the switch off price (what reward per GH you'd switch off at because it is below electrical efficiency break-even).

Assuming all things stay the same (mainly price though), won't the halving significantly increase the switch off price for many miners?

My understanding is that it is based on:

* The miner's cost of electricity
* The miner's mining efficiency

Meaning miners with some of the higher costs of electricity (or lower efficiencies) may have to turn off?

Is it correct to say that it's hard to know exactly what will happen as none of us know what future price movements will be? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-10 06:26:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'd recommend [Coinbase](https://www.coinbase.com/) or [Circle](https://www.circle.com).

Or [LocalBitcoins](https://localbitcoins.com/) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-10 06:24:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> There's a lot of nuances to what may or may not happen, but the important thing from a practical aspect is to make sure you control your coins with your own private keys (e.g. don't use a 3rd party wallet like a webwallet).

* If there's a fork and you control your own private keys, you will then have coins on both forks.
* If there's a fork and you do not control your own private keys, you're at the mercy of the 3rd party who may or may not give you coins on both forks. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-10 06:12:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If you just want to learn what you're doing I'd say get something tiny like an [AntMiner U3](https://www.bitmaintech.com/productDetail.htm?pid=00020141017110427977rQGR3pcf06BE) before you make any serious investment.

 (A copypasta will be over in /r/bitcoin, please don't flag it.)

/r/btc would be happy to help as well. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-10 05:36:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Get a good night's sleep.

Don't drink too much fluid before the test.

Poop before the test.

Pass. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-10 05:22:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You're on your own from here.

This is something I'd feel way more comfortable with doing in person.

Good luck to you. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-10 05:21:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This is what bothers me. He was one of the few semi-reasonable people over there.

I understand he is pointing out that there are shenanigans, propaganda, and poo-flinging on both sides of the debate, and I fully agree that they exist and I applaud him for trying to point it out in a rational manner.

But when someone says

 [No /r/bitcoin mod will likely respond to this, since you guys have proven that you will just censor any reply they make](https://www.reddit.com/r/btc/comments/49nf9e/mods_of_rbitcoin_why_did_you_censor_information/d0tc22x)

then implies that downvoting is the same as censorship (and makes no mention of massive amounts of actual deletion on r\Bitcoin)

 [But the mods of this subreddit are not the real problem, so discussing them is besides the point. The real problem is the culture of downvoting that the people here have. A /r/bitcoin mod could reply to every single complaint made in this subreddit, but 90% of the users wouldn't ever know that they did. They would get the wrong impression that the /r/bitcoin mods were ignoring them. This just feeds back into itself to form a never-ending cycle.](https://www.reddit.com/r/btc/comments/49nf9e/mods_of_rbitcoin_why_did_you_censor_information/d0th9wu)

I have a problem with that and in my eyes it greatly lowers his credibility. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-09 19:43:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Sweet. See if you can set the router to 802.11n as well then. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-09 19:21:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Or were just memeing it up because we're on Reddit.

But sure, let's use a single humorous comment to write off an entire group of developers, 3.7% of hashpower, 1,900 nodes, 13,000 /r/btc subscribers, and many many others. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-09 19:14:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thank you. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-09 17:53:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Luke should really just delete his Reddit account. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-09 17:50:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Lets dispel with this fiction that core devs dont know what they're doing. They know exactly what they're doing. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-09 17:46:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah, I'll elaborate.

You said your WiFi is at 5% of 1Gbps, which is about 50 Mbps.

802.11a and 802.11g both operate at a maximum speed of 54 Mbps, but 802.11a is not that common, so I assume you're on 802.11g.

That means your WiFi adapter on your laptop and your WiFi router are both operating on 802.11g.

However, each of them may be capable of operating at 802.11n or 802.11ac.

It may be worth checking their specs to see if they can operate on 802.11n or 802.11ac.

802.11n has a maximum speed of 150 to 600 Mbps.

802.11ac has a maximum speed of 150 to 6,934 Mbps (I think, you may want to double check this upper limit if you care to.)

But yeah, I'd imagine that the built in WiFi adapter in a 2 year old high end laptop would support 802.11n and probably 802.11ac too.

Your WiFi router could be the limiting factor here.

Or just plug your laptop directly into your modem and/or router and bypass WiFi. :-)

I hope this helps. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-09 17:25:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I hear what you're saying, but most of the people here have been banned or otherwise censored on r\Bitcoin. There's a serious axe to grind, and frankly, I think that heavy-handed censorship by a single person who owns 3 of the major Bitcoin forums is a major issue that people need to be aware of, and apparently want to discuss.

It can really be a serious eye-opener when someone who's only been reading r\Bitcoin comes to /r/btc and sees 13,000 subscribers and about 40% as many active users and sees a bunch of topics that are rarely if ever seen on /r/btc.

When censorship is less of an issue, upvoted posts will reflect this.

So that all said...

Dear OP and others, please consider using r\Bitcoin when discussing the other subreddit:

* It implies that r\Bitcoin is backwards.
* It does not link to r\Bitcoin. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-09 17:16:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  How sad, Core devs cannot comprehend that the 1MB limit became an attack vector and limits the potential of the network.

Lets dispel once and for all with this fiction that core devs dont know what they're doing. They know exactly what they're doing. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-09 17:14:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Dear OP and others, please consider using r\Bitcoin:

* It implies that r\Bitcoin is backwards.
* It does not link to r\Bitcoin. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-09 17:10:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  censor

There's a big difference between deletion and downvoting.

Some people have actively chosen to make no distinction between the two while using the word 'censor'.

FYI, I did not not downvote this because I want more people to see this, but I did not upvote this because I feel that the way some people are using the word 'censor' is disingenuous. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-09 16:59:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [Amazon Best Sellers in **Laptop Computer Network Adapters**](http://www.amazon.com/gp/bestsellers/electronics/13983731)

I can vouch for one of these personally.

/pushing products </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-09 16:46:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thank you for posting this. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-09 15:05:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Upgrade from 802.11g?

802.11n and even 802.11ac are pretty cheap. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-09 14:44:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thanks guys!

FYI, it looks like someone is shadowbanned and it's not /u/xeroc or /u/chris4210. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-09 14:39:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thanks guys! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-09 14:34:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Haha, that's hilarious. Thanks for the link.

I especially liked the part at the end where he blows up a wall with laserbeams out of his eyes, but then he has to protect his face from the explosion debris. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-09 05:26:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Someone kindly explain the reference? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-09 05:25:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Is it possible to leave the 1MB vs 2MB+ graph along with the 0.12 graph? I found it to be quite insightful.

I tried going to http://nodecounter.com/#nodes_1mb_vs_2mb but it looks like all the code is commented out.

In any case, thanks for everything you do for Bitcoin! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-09 05:14:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> ELI5? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-09 05:12:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  When mainstream media start to realize what is going on with Bitcoin and its community (with all the censorship), shit will hit the fan really hard.

*If* mainstream media cares about or even wants to bring any attention to our corner of the internet. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-09 04:58:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thank you. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-09 04:58:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thanks everybody! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-09 04:56:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thank you everybody for the help! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-08 18:27:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Gotcha, thank you for taking the time to explain. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-08 18:13:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thank you very much as well. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-08 18:12:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thank you very much. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-08 17:52:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Why the 14th? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-08 14:51:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> From https://letsencrypt.org/about/

Lets Encrypt is a free, automated, and open certificate authority (CA), run for the publics benefit. Lets Encrypt is a service provided by the [Internet Security Research Group (ISRG)](https://letsencrypt.org/isrg/).

The key principles behind Lets Encrypt are:

* **Free:** Anyone who owns a domain name can use Lets Encrypt to obtain a trusted certificate at zero cost.
* **Automatic:** Software running on a web server can interact with Lets Encrypt to painlessly obtain a certificate, securely configure it for use, and automatically take care of renewal.
* **Secure:** Lets Encrypt will serve as a platform for advancing TLS security best practices, both on the CA side and by helping site operators properly secure their servers.
* **Transparent:** All certificates issued or revoked will be publicly recorded and available for anyone to inspect.
* **Open:** The automatic issuance and renewal protocol will be published as an open standard that others can adopt.
* **Cooperative:** Much like the underlying Internet protocols themselves, Lets Encrypt is a joint effort to benefit the community, beyond the control of any one organization. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-07 14:33:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> http://www.nodecounter.com/#nodes_pie_graph

https://coin.dance/nodes/share </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-07 05:09:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So make sure javascript is disabled and turn security to high? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-07 04:49:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I understand what you're saying.

Time/space and a blockchain could be considered similar in that they both appear to be (semi-?)deterministic conclusions of everything that has come before. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-07 03:57:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> How the heck are actual bitcoin users who want a p2p currency with cheap transaction fees supposed to have any input?

With their feet.

It's that simple.

:-(

You can also vote by mining or running a node, but I believe your feet are the loudest vote. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-07 03:51:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Okay, valid point. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-07 03:51:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The connection goes even further if you keep digging. :-) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-06 20:26:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [@sysmannet](https://twitter.com/sysmannet) sorry, we will continue mining empty blocks. This is the freedom given by the Bitcoin protocol.

[@JihanWu](https://twitter.com/JihanWu) sorry, users will continue moving to other cryptocurrencies. This is the freedom given by open-source protocols.

:-( </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-06 20:14:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I must not joke. 

Jokes are the mind-killer. 

Jokes are the little-death that bring total obliteration. 

I will face their jokes. 

I will permit them to woosh over me and through me. 

And when they have gone past I will turn the inner eye, but not see their path. 

Where the jokes have gone there will be nothing. Only I will remain. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-06 19:19:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Until the next one. :-( </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-06 19:18:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Nah bro it's fine, just don't worry about it and everything will be okay. /s </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-06 19:13:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Melange_(fictional_drug) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-06 19:09:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Melange_(fictional_drug) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-06 14:37:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> For anyone wondering what this wish of /u/theymos is:

https://np.reddit.com/r/bitcoin/comments/3h9cq4/its_time_for_a_break_about_the_recent_mess/

https://archive.is/Lfvw0

If 90% of /r/Bitcoin users find these policies to be intolerable, then I want these 90% of /r/Bitcoin users to leave. Both /r/Bitcoin and these people will be happier for it. I do not want these people to make threads breaking the rules, demanding change, asking for upvotes, making personal attacks against moderators, etc. Without some real argument, you're not going to convince anyone with any brains -- you're just wasting your time and ours. The temporary rules against blocksize and moderation discussion are in part designed to encourage people who should leave /r/Bitcoin to actually do so so that /r/Bitcoin can get back to the business of discussing Bitcoin news in peace. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
