<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject4860</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-07 10:14:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Let's see here - the possibility of voter fraud, a gigantic DDOS attack that came from the internet of things, and everything else?  I'm thinking we need to move things AWAY from the internet, not towards it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> October DRAM price surge </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-07 10:07:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> New US Robotics Roadmap calls for increased regulations, education and research </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-07 09:57:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> is their any way for marketing a product on reddit? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-03 09:10:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Infant deaths during home birth often tied to delivery problems </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-03 08:52:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-03 08:34:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I hope there's not too much damage   minimum casualties  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Asia stocks subdued, dollar slips on U.S. election tension </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-03 08:23:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Somali pirates free 26 hostages after nearly 5 years </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-25 09:25:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-25 09:05:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> China is illegally laying claim on a large part of North-Eastern state and along Northern border with India, which is conventionally and historically well demarcated. Significantly they are not ready to settle the border issue ever and keep it pending for so that land hungry China may lay claim on more areas in future, besides what they are occupying in PoK, gifted to them by their friend Pakistan. Ironically China don't recognize the Mc Mohan line of border demarcation settled by the British Indian government. But they recognize the dotted line of their border on the water bed of South China Sea. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Alert level raised for Alaska volcano after explosion detected </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-25 08:30:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
