<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject4680</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-02-05 21:26:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That's a great idea! Thanks! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-02-05 21:24:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah. My only problem with Dark Sun is it seems to focus on removing elements as opposed to adding them, which is just plain annoying. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-02-05 21:23:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Sounds like a great starting point for a campaign. I'll keep that in mind.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-02-05 21:23:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Oh. Good to know. I didn't think about books and such. Thanks! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-02-05 21:21:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Seems pretty credible! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-02-05 16:55:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Well, I'm planning on playing 4e, and my party is about split. Two of them are slayers that just love fighting anything and everything, and the other two are thinkers that like a good mystery.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Dark Sun or Eberron? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-02-05 16:39:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm starting a new campaign for a group of my friends, starting at level 1. I'm not the most experienced DM, but a very capable one. I'm trying to decide on a setting, and I'm torn between Dark Sun and Eberron. Any suggestions? Also, if you know of a good campaign arc for either, I would love to hear it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Someone asked me why urban legends happen. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-02-04 16:41:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> I don't get many opportunities to look clever during the Super Bowl... </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-02-04 03:34:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-02-03 03:26:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Downvote, just because confession bear. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-02-02 03:52:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hmmm... I don't know. I was kinda hoping that plot line works out. I love the Followers, personally. Best faction in the game, and the best companion too. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-02-01 21:21:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You realize you can get them to form a pact with whoever you join, right? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-02-01 16:52:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You could try a sorcerer with the dragon character build. If you have the Player's Guide 2. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-02-01 16:27:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> : O holy shit. That's the best idea I've heard all year. Probably because we're still pretty early in the year, but I applaud you, good sir.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-02-01 16:26:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thanks! That's very helpful. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-02-01 04:18:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Well, I would do that, but these are players from different circles that don't care much for the other. The people in the first group play mostly to hang out with each other, and I doubt they'd like to play without each other. I know ten players is over any good limit, but we make it work, even if combat takes an eternity. Thank you for your suggestion though.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> How to get new players interested? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-02-01 02:22:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I have a current game going, and am just getting out of my beginner stage myself as I learn more and read more of the rules, but I have encountered a problem. I have two friends that have heard I play, and are interested in starting out, and I would allow them to join my current campaign, but it already has about ten players, and that's excluding the DM. I would gladly get a new game going for this different group of friends, but that gets me into a new problem. I would like at least three players for a well rounded party for me to DM so they enjoy the game to its full capacity. I have a couple friends that I could potentially get to join, but there's a huge change they'll dismiss it as hugely "nerdy" the second "D D" comes out of my mouth. How exactly could I propose the idea to increase the chances of them being interested? If you actually read that entire thing, I applaud you, by the way.

TL;DR: How can I get people to join my campaign that would enjoy the game, but might dismiss it and laugh if I don't present it well out of fear of it being too nerdy? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-01-31 03:33:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Well, I'm a student at a fairly small school, and this might seem odd, but the students gossip with the teachers more than often. It goes from anything as serious as students being suicidal to as petty as "so and so like so and so". So the teachers, at least at my school, are fully aware of it, but as I said, I go to a very small school, and it's almost always dealt with quickly and effectively.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [Utah] Looking to exchange. Any takers? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-01-31 03:25:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm a high schooler in Utah. This sounds cool, and I'm in. Anyone willing to exchange? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-01-31 00:11:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You got it! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-01-30 04:09:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Pronounce Tyranny "correctly". I pronounce it "Tie-Ran-Y" Because dang it, that's how it's done.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-01-29 22:06:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> A girl loses her head. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-01-29 22:03:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> High schoolers disobey school rules. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Truly Terrible </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-01-28 16:45:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-01-25 21:23:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That's certainly problematic. Sorry to hear it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-01-25 21:22:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Well, I always start all of my cities with a monument, and than focus on getting production and food, than to all out on wonders. Legalism in the Tradition tree makes this automatic in first four cities, and if your playing cultural that would mean more than all of your cities. 3 to 4 cities can work, but I ideally play with two. This means you have to know how to play REALLY tall. This means you need a lot of food, and production in these cities to make them power houses that can fuel all of your needs.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-01-25 02:54:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah. Moving up takes a lot of practice.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-01-25 02:36:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Well, in the early game that sounds great, but it takes a long while to make. I would make sure you have an adequate production before you make it, as not to fall too far behind too early.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-01-25 02:20:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Wait, are you playing G K? I play that, and I don't care too much about faith (mostly because I'm not very good at it to be honest) so I typically ignore stonehedge. I think The Oracle, Sistine, Sydney, and Cristo Redentor are absolutely necessary though. I typically attempt to get as many other wonders as possible, but they take second place compared to cultural buildings, and having a functional military.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-01-25 01:59:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Well, at this point, it seems your in quite an emergency scenario. I only play on prince (4) so far, but sometimes, in scenarios like that you just have to put everything else on the back burner for a minute and get as much tech and production as you can for the moment, without causing any long lasting damage. With techs, until things start going your way, rush it to the best military units you can get your hands on, and than quickly catch up once your done with the war.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-01-25 00:43:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Personally, and I could be wrong, I would say Egypt. I would say wonders are one of the most important things in a culture play-through, and the bonus from Egypt gives you a huge head start on their production times, and building them in general.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-01-25 00:42:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Well, personally, I think city state bonuses are amazing during a cultural victory, but city states are tricky, and you need to focus more on building up culture than gold. So, focus on building up your own culture, and if you have the extra stuff, city-states add a huge bonus.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> I'm willing to help with cultural victories! </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-01-24 21:44:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I know a lot of people struggle with cultural victories in Civ 5, but they come very naturally to me. If you would like any help with this victory type, please ask me anything you'd like to know. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-01-21 17:49:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Wow. That's a really great turn of events. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-01-21 17:47:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That's certainly impressive. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-01-21 07:38:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Ha! That's even better! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-01-21 07:37:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That's great! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-01-21 07:35:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> x D My friends to critical fails too. I love that rule. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-01-21 07:34:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That's an epic comeback. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-01-21 07:32:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I've heard a lot of epic moments from my friends (they play a lot), but that takes the cake by far! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-01-21 07:29:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That's amazing. That is... Amazing. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-01-21 05:56:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That I talk REALLY load. And people ALWAYS have to point it out to me. I seldom realize everyone in the house can hear me when I'm trying to have a discrete conversation.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-01-21 02:57:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That's certainly exciting. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-01-21 02:56:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That's pretty great! I don't know many DMs that do plot twists that great.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-01-21 01:03:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> x D Well done.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-01-20 23:48:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That's great! That's both victorious and a failure at the same time. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What's your greatest defining moment in D D? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-01-20 23:17:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What's the greatest moment that just stuck with you that happened during D D? It might be a memory your greatest victory, or maybe your worst defeat, or maybe something different entirely! I haven't been playing for very long, so I don't really have one yet, but I'd like to hear what you have to say. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-01-20 17:55:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That's pretty great. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-01-20 03:55:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Well, I have a friend that continuously tries to intimidiate his way out of any scenario. At first I would let him do it without consequence, but I eventually got mad and after he intimidated a king. Guards swarmed him and he ended up in the hardest fight of the campaign.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-01-19 07:15:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Angel Beats! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-01-17 00:15:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That's probably true.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-01-17 00:14:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Huh. Maybe it was just our session or something that was weird.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-01-17 00:13:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thank you. That's very interesting. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Am I the only one that has trouble with rolling 1's way too often on roll20.net? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-01-16 04:56:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I played an adventure on roll20.net with my friends the other day we once rolled five ones in a row! We rolled ones probably 30-40% of the time. Am I the only one with this problem? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Thank you! And an update on how my game went. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-01-15 02:56:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I recently asked r/DnD for advice on the campaign I was about to start. I just did the first game of it yesterday, and it went very well, mostly due to all of you who gave me advice. Thank you very much!
The player's enjoyed the game, but said I need to make combat a lot shorter and faster (one fight lasted the majority of our three hour session), but everyone enjoyed it nonetheless. 
The setting worked, but I would like to hear some input on how to improve it. The current setting is in a massive city called Blackburn with a really nice area and a ghetto. Different sections are ruled by different dukes. The city is overrun with disease and the players discovered that one of the dukes is a wererat in charge of a Lycanthrope army. They thwarted his plans and kicked him out of his thrown, but he is still alive, and likely to make a comeback.

**TL;DR** I was wondering two things on how to keep improving this campaign:
1. How can I improve the setting, and what should I add to it?
2. What is a good way to make combat faster? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-01-14 21:27:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Well said.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-01-14 03:07:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> How do you feel about the 53 lego related deaths in history? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-01-12 22:09:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I don't think that's possible for anyone that isn't a robot. Are you a robot? How did you get past the thing that makes you type in the letters you see? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-01-12 21:47:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thanks. I'm playing 4e, by the way.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-01-12 21:45:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thanks. I'll be sure to look over my rulebooks again. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-01-12 21:44:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Holy crap that's amazing, and, even better, it fits exactly into the campaign pieces of plot I had already. Thanks! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-01-12 06:11:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I will keep that in mind. Thanks! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> I am a relatively new DM starting my first campaign. Any advice? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-01-12 05:44:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I am new to D D. (I've played about 5 times, DMing about three). I asked my friends that I play with if I could DM a full campaign. I'm not a superb or even great DM by any standard, but they agreed. I really need advice on how to do this. I only vaguely have a world made, and only vaguely have a plot. Your help is greatly appreciated.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-01-12 04:37:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah! I love RPing as a Tiefling so much!  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-01-12 01:52:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> My group always makes it so a nat 1 does damage to YOU or your allies. This isn't taken very seriously and often leads to hilarious situations (like an orc launching its sword at it's Kobold friend.) It's also one of the best moments to see the look on your friend's face as you roll a damage die to see how hard you hit them.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-01-12 01:21:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm a Teifling Wizard with a really bad past, and a nasty habit of doing things rather questionable, be it killing innocence to achieve a goal, or "accidentally" striking my teammates. 
There's a Half-Elf ranger who the DM loves to have monsters be "swooned" by, which drives her nuts. All in good fun, of course.
There's a Human Warlord that has a rude manner, and is always looking to get in the NPC's way, even if it's a friend. 
Finally, there's a Dwarf Fighter that chargers into battle and never looks back. Has no regard to strategy, most rules, or any premade plan.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-01-10 21:41:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I am an American considering living in Japan when I am older. I am currently a high schooler, and I went there for a week last year. Is it a good place to study abroad? Would you recommend living there? I don't speak any Japanese, but I am fairly good with languages. Is the language particularly difficult? (sorry for all the questions in one) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
