<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject1503</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Just coming back to the game and looking for a guild/server to play on. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-11-23 17:51:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> As the title says, I'm just returning to the game after quitting about 4 months after release.  I have a level 50 Shadow on the Prophecy of Five server in Champion/early HM gear from back then.  I have no idea how my gear stacks up now, but I'm looking for a friendly group to help me re-learn the ropes and perhaps see some end game content. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-10-31 17:43:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm not going to the Billings show but I'll be driving to the Spokane show on the 10th.  I'll be sure to take pictures and post.  For reference its the same distance to Spokane as it is to Billings for me since I live in Helena. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-08-31 23:53:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Honestly I don't know.  I'll be curious to see just how well the Griz do this season.  I do think that it was good that things finally came to light with them over the off season though. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Griz Football starts tomorrow and my office is ready! </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-08-31 22:48:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-08-31 16:38:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I could possible be persuaded to drive to Billings from Helena for this  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-08-03 19:02:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm here to say two things.  First you seem like an incredibly awesome individual (4 languages excluding English??? WOW!).  Second, there is some debate over whether larger cats can purr since we don't know exactly what the mechanism is when cats purr.  

Generally though larger cats "chuff" or friendly growl instead of the standard purr noise.  Some scientists have theorized that the larger cats would be purring but due to their size it comes out as a "chuff" instead.

*Edit for spelling </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-08-03 16:36:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm also a new rider with about 2 months on my Ninja 250r and this subreddit has been super helpful for me. It helped me make the decision to buy the bike I did, and I've received great feedback on pictures I've posted of where I've gone here in MT.

Thanks for taking the time for this subreddit, I enjoy hanging out here. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-08-03 16:25:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I am a Korean adopted male with an adopted younger sister, and while growing up I don't ever remember her dating an Asian guy.  Honestly I still don't think she has ever dated an Asian guy, she is always with a white male.

My sister is not racist in any way, shape or form, but I've always wondered why she's never dated another Asian.  Part of the reason may be that we grew up in Montana where the population of Asians is smaller at best, but when she went to Hawaii for college, she still never did.

I've never asked her what the reason for this might be, but perhaps I will now this post has me thinking about it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Trip to Gates of the Mountains in MT </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-08-01 19:24:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Way to nice of a day to not go riding with a friend in Montana! </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-07-30 01:31:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-07-29 08:10:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The helmet is there more just for the photo, I normally never leave it like that. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Beautiful day to take a drive in Montana </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-07-29 08:00:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-07-12 00:23:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> "Chief Tim Barkell said she was naked, and tried running off into traffic."

Yep,sounds like Butte, MT.

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-07-07 23:42:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I was in the AF.  I separated as an E5 back in 2010 from Hill AFB in UT.  You must be stationed at Malmstrom though? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-07-06 21:42:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I will also say, if this post is even months old feel free to message me. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-07-05 20:48:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> When you say "wingman out!" I picture this http://senorgif.memebase.com/2010/08/17/funny-gifs-up-up-and-away/ </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [27M4F] Asian in MT looking to meet some new people! </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-07-05 19:27:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Well as the title says I'm 27, Asian, and living in MT.  I'm 5'8", brown eyes, with the typical Asian build. 

I left college in my junior year to enlist in the USAF and spent four years having a great time.  Upon separation in 2010 I moved back to my hometown for financial and family support reasons.  Now that I'm back I've been disgusted and disappointed with trying to meet/date people here.

I'm not necessarily looking for a relationship, but I'm open to wherever things lead to.  Don't care how far away you are (accents are awesome) PM if you're interested in chatting! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-06-28 03:04:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> An upvote for you as well Thracks! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> My first bike!  Quick question about paint costs. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-06-27 21:20:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I just purchased my first bike a 99 Ninja 250r

http://i.imgur.com/dNpOl.jpg

I was curious if anyone knew around how much it would cost to get the color changed to black?  I know that these costs can vary depending on area and vendor, but I was trying to get a ballpark figure. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-06-27 19:29:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm now confused as to why I'm being downvoted :-( </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-06-27 19:22:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thanks everyone for the great advice.  I am still on the hunt, and possibly now just looking at buying a new Ninja 250 :-P </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-06-27 19:20:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Was my first thought too.  Loki btw is the one that looks innocent in the corner.  I know that he has framed his brother! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Walked into my study to find shredded paper towels and this.  Meet Thor and Loki </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-06-27 18:47:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Meet Thor and Loki </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-06-27 17:40:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-06-25 18:58:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thanks for the great information!  I know the seller wants as close to 3k as he can get so he can purchase a quad, so I get the feeling he's not going to come down very far.  I will definitely ask about the valves and how longs its been sitting.  He mentioned that he was holding onto it for his fiancee but she has no interest in riding.

I also just found another bike of interest, a 99 Ninja 250r.  He's asking 1900 and I know that's a bit high.  Bike has never been tipped, and the picture looks fairly good.  Any thoughts on what a good counter offer would be? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What would a 2007 Ninja250r be worth with just over 2k miles? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-06-25 18:23:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm looking at buying my first bike and I've found one that I'm interested in but the seller is asking at least $2600.00 for it.  I did some price checking and it seems that this is almost the MSRP for it.  

Is this a decent price or should I try for lower?

For reference I live in Montana (not sure if that affects price) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Time to vote Montana </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-06-05 21:25:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Seriously, I was just down at the polls and its empty.  EVERYONE needs to get out and vote! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-05-08 18:53:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm a 1300 rated AD carry and I come with one of the better support players I've met. Look us up.  Zaniel and Tskrian respectively. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-02-06 22:21:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Therwild/Therwild </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2011-11-10 21:30:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Upvoted good sir. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2011-11-10 20:10:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Apparently wedding photos are pictures of "tools" </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2011-08-22 23:14:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Absence make the heart go yonder! KQ1-6 = AMAZING! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Our Universe the inside of another universe's black hole?...? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2011-08-18 23:48:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
