<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject6914</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-10 17:18:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It seems to me this is good for the 'digital divide': broadband is expensive.  So it might not be as good as paid access, but it is affordable to all. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Salem considering city-wide free public Wi-Fi (buildout this fall) </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-10 16:09:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Vatican accuses woman at heart of leaks trial of calumny </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-31 23:46:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-20 13:49:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> **Submission statement**
We often think of slaves as passive, but hundreds of thousands of them over the years tried to escape from their masters.  They didn't leave evidence behind themselves - but their masters' did, in the form of ads they placed in newspapers across the US south. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> In a digital archive of fugitive slave ads, a new portrait of slavery emerges </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-20 13:48:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-20 13:46:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I know you're joking, but I have a brother on a waiting list for a kidney transplant, and the shortage isn't funny.

Giving one kidney really is quite safe, and life-changing for the recipient.
http://www.hopkinsmedicine.org/transplant/news_events/media/transcripts/kidney_pancreas/what_kidney_donors_need_to_know.html </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-19 13:40:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hope I'm doing this right.
Sitzpinkler: a man who pees sitting down. The noun is a compound of Sitz (seat), pinkeln (to pee), and -er (a male-specific suffix). This word is part of a series of lighthearted wuss definitions, which includes Abschiedsheuler (a man who wails at farewells) and Sockenfalter (a man who folds his socks). </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
