<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject8211</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-21 21:03:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This thread is more prudish than an amish nun.

That said, the edit suggests he's willing to live and let live. Which makes the decision of dealing with him vs being short is all yours. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-21 05:17:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I also have the same issue with unspecified, random players. In fact I'm probably more cynical than you. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-21 04:59:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The mere exposure to this ungodly level of stupidity is taking years of my life. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-21 04:31:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Why not both? :D </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-21 04:30:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> One of my favourite classes and mechanics.

The system is very versatile, the fluff is very flavourful and there are many different builds and shenanigans you can pull off. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-21 02:50:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I did the same thing. They did.

Took a 3-month vacation abroad.

It was glorious. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-21 02:40:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Next up: **"The Prince"**. :) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-21 02:39:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Mechanically, he's the arbiter.  
Narrative-wise, he's the stage upon which the play unfurls.  
Meta-wise, the DM has no stake in the campaign.  

So it depends on your viewpoint. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-20 02:34:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I have a different solution - if he wants to play adversarially, you and the rest of the party as people, sharing a common competitive activity, MAKE HIM PLAY BY THE RULES.

Competitions have rules. Force him to stick to them.

If I was in a bike race and another competitor ran past me on a motorcycle, me and the rest of the competitors sure as hell wouldn't take that lying down. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-20 00:54:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> For prettier graphics and a more general explanation of the concept, one can watch the recent QM-related video series on [PBS SpaceTime](https://www.youtube.com/playlist?list=PLsPUh22kYmNCGaVGuGfKfJl-6RdHiCjo1). </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-20 00:47:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> 1. Ability to abstract.
2. Critical thought.
3. Diverse interests.

2 and 3 are essential, but good lord, is #1 **critical**. Its lack is literally the source of 95% of all problems on the table ever. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-20 00:39:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> https://imgflip.com/i/1awjgx

Statistics nerds probably jizzed. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-20 00:01:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yet another reason why lasers are so awesome.

The "crispness" of the models is astonishing. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-20 00:00:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Psion.

They're versatile, powerful, flavourful and I love the fluff. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-19 17:48:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The pervasive stupidity born out of wilful ignorance and learned helplessness and the culture of offence. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-19 04:04:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The *Conrith* episode reminds me of Max Payne.

Also, I'm totally stealing that Ogol technique. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-19 01:59:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I've played Fallout(the old ones) with a stupid character. Does that count?  
Int 2, Luck and Cha to max. It was fun. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-19 01:57:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Misleading title led me to not expect genuine story, but the usual 4chan twist.

No twists in this one, just a bad DM story.

It's sad sacks like that one that give D D a bad name. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-18 21:28:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I could use some help with some creation myths for my campaign. Do those sound fun to you?

I already have a fairly elaborate cosmology, which I now need to grind through the lens of the ages to get some nice cultural mythology out of it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-18 21:21:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I believe the name you are looking for is "Blibdoolpoolp". </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-18 21:20:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> IMO, yes, yes it is.

Even past my personal distaste for such hokum, it just get soooo overplayed in low-quality fantasy. It's one of those tropes that get so boring and bland due to oversaturation.

Obviously that is going to vary depending on the type of content a person has been historically exposed to, but for me at least it's too much. But it is going to be novel and exciting for someone out there. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-17 19:33:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> TB doing the good work. Getting me my much-needed SC2 fix. So hard to find good dealers these days. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-17 19:31:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Reminds me of Malcolm. :) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-17 16:21:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This looks awesome. Very good design.

I've been wanting to do something similar, but for 3.5.

Is there any particular reason you use Knockout over React? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-17 04:52:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I regularly somehow manage to produce such intractable problems, not even stackoverflow can help me. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-17 04:07:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Exactly my point. Taking away cool shit from your players, just so you as a DM can be a lazy bastard is reprehensible. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-17 02:28:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It is partly because it is one of the most obvious and easy to understand problem.

I'll assume you're aware of the existence of anti-matter. Well, when the universe was very, very young(unknown, but we're probably talking less than a second here) its energy density was so great that normal particles(or laws of physics) didn't exist yet.  
Then when it inflated, it cooled down/spread apart - enough for its energy density to drop to levels where the existence of particles was a theoretical possibility. In general creating particles from energy creates a matter and an anti-matter particle - you know, equal quantities of both, preserving all sorts of symmetries. Except, as you are well aware, just by being aware... we're missing some of that anti-matter. (Cuz you know, if it was here it would annihilate with matter and go back to being energy, thereby making you dead.) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-16 23:56:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> http://www.schlockmercenary.com/2011-05-28

Also... step up. Characters are supposed to get flight at some point - even permanent flight. Have other things fly too. Get creative with spells and equipment. Nets, web, magical bindings, paralysis, etc. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-16 21:49:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I merely have different interests. :) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-16 18:30:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Aren't we all? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-16 18:29:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's weird. This is sort of somehow their "natural order". </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-16 18:25:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> ~~The same thing we do every night! Try to take...~~

Travel.  
Make a game.  
Get a physics degree.  
Finish my D D setting.  
Play in that setting.  

Not necessarily in that order. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-16 18:17:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> 90% of it. Literally.

Pick something popular. 90% of those guesses I couldn't give a flying fuck about. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-16 18:15:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The textures are horrific. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-16 18:12:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I myself am partial to the Baryon asymmetry problem. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-16 18:07:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  Reddit is a fickle beast.

That's like saying that the asteroid that wiped out the dinos is a firecracker. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-16 17:55:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> For some reason this is inordinately amusing, even when you know it will happen. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-16 15:20:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Vindictive DMing at its best. How delightfully juvenile. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-16 15:10:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I feel like roll20 would be worse in that regard, just because of the "it's online gaming" thing. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-16 05:01:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> He's a pushover, vanilla-style. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-16 04:42:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Boy, as a web developer does that see use.

However, I actually explicitly don't use it for porn, because I want to know what porn I've seen, so it needs to be in the history for the links to be purple. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-16 04:36:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Starter pack: Get the books, throw them away, get a premade module. Run it.

Advanced start: Read the books. Figure out what kind of campaign you wanna run, what your players want from it, some kind of abstract main conflict and get to worldbuilding. A month to a year later play the game. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-16 00:48:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> TL;DR: If you have to ask, the answer is no.

To play a DMPC effectively, you need to know the pitfalls. To know the pitfalls, you have to be an experienced D D player(as in psychology, the idiosyncrasies of the game, system mastery, etc.). If you were, you wouldn't be asking. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-16 00:38:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The kind of answer you hope for does not exist.

You know the obvious one. You have 2 DMs and 9 people. The math isn't hard.

If the obvious one won't happen... well, you're out of luck. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-16 00:28:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> As you can see, you can't really have a discussion in this sub. Reddit is for circlejerking. For actual discourse, you need to try one of the forums, like GitP or enworld.

***
Here's how the design process breaks down:

1. The designers need to present both simple and martial ranged options to players.
2. Game design wise, better performing weapons should require harder to obtain proficiencies.  
 The designers chose to play on what a layman would find to be a reasonable assumption - bigger = better. And also on the familiarity of the weapons(almost everyone is aware of the existence of longbows and shortbows). This is a case of the ["Reality is Unrealistic"](http://tvtropes.org/pmwiki/pmwiki.php/Main/RealityIsUnrealistic) trope.
3. Mounted combat DOES NOT perform the same role in D D as it does in real world.  
 In real life it is a tactically significant combat style that brings to a battle capabilities that cannot be achieved in the same manner in any other way. In D D it is a fringe character option, rarely used due to the mechanics of the system. It is by necessity reductionist in its combat rules, and mounted combat is one of the options that suffer. In addition to that factor, there is magic, which changes warfare in ways we usually only scratch the surface of.

**TL;DR** Due to the fringe status of mounted combat, but the familiarity of the general public with the terms "longbow" and "shortbow", they chose to redirect the differentiation between both from what was significant in the real world to what was significant in the game mechanics. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-15 15:39:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> For first time players the answer is most likely no. Dealing with real drama requires experienced players, players who know how to "handle their shit". </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-15 03:34:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'mma borrow this if you don't mind. It fits uncannily well as a city I was planning on fleshing out these days in my setting. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-15 01:32:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Well... they have stations all over the globe and so many satellites spewing tons data constantly. They probably need that shit and more. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-15 01:17:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This is strong in a horror or more gritty game.

D D, as a highly mechanical game makes it easy: Have high stats in the relevant abilities and a class that utilizes them fully. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-14 20:13:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  I run 2e


 TPK's happen

No need to repeat yourself, we got it the first time. :) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-14 19:52:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  ~~Why I don't allow evil characters (a story)~~

FTFY: Why I don't allow inexperienced players.

Despite the whole *"everyman's game"* attitude towards D D, it is also possible to create games, which do require a certain expertise that actually very few players and DMs possess.

This is one of those games.

I'd give an arm and a leg(the character's) to play in such a game, which is why it makes me doubly sad it died over some hissy fits. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-14 18:19:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I use Civ4. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-13 02:53:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> FFS. Just read the actual rules I linked to instead of making shit up.

5e drops ability damage as a mechanic, so doesn't explicitly deal with low ability scores, which for that edition technically makes it a house rule, but a pretty authoritative one. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-13 02:39:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That was a very short rant that will achieve absolutely nothing, even though we all want it to with all our hearts and upvotes. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-13 02:32:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The one I am writing now.

The campaign starts off small and sandboxy. PCs are free to follow their passions. It has a very simple premise: **The rabbit hole is *always* deeper.**

The setting is also pretty generic: Classic high fantasy.  
Save for the fact that I intentionally subvert many of the tropes of the genre and of D D in particular. Mostly by virtue of me introducing the concept of common sense, both in and out of game.

My life's goal as a DM is to see the end of that campaign. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-13 00:01:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I assume PW2 cuz feats. Combat Wizard 2 might have been a better fit with Primordial giant.

I'd go for sublime chord. L9 casting ain't nothin to sneeze at. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-12 23:54:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The number you are looking for which describes these conditions is **[0](http://www.d20srd.org/srd/specialAbilities.htm#abilityScoreLoss)**.

Also only int 1 is unplayable because animal. Others are valid.

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-12 23:42:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Otherwise known as d20 Modern. There is an SRD. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-12 23:41:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Also, 3.5e DMG2, chapter 1 (player archetypes/motivations). </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-12 23:30:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Someone's been reading the 1e PHB again. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-12 14:22:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's funnier when you're also from Bulgaria. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-12 02:59:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Define **"good"**.

What do you wanna do with them? There is an enormous range that goes from ROT13 all the way to modern-day crypto. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-11 23:57:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's not even about the bad rolls, it's about the rolls period.

"I take 10" is a 2-second statement, which you utter and you're done. Rolling a trio of dice and extracting a result is not a trivial action in comparison.  
This is the "compromise" part I was referring to.

The "important mechanic" part is that the player can rely on a his character possessing a certain ability. For example, if my character has +15 to Climb, I *know* he will be able to climb a generic wall every time. Players work to get that good. Taking that away makes you look like a bastard DM.

So, while much greater verisimilitude is maintained with the bell curve roll, the "take 10" mechanic is substantially superior game design. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-11 16:38:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Taking 10 is both a compromise and an important mechanic.

And you're misunderstanding what "active involvement" means.  
It's the ***decision*** that's the active part. Rolling the dice is passive.

If a DM imposed this rule in a game, I'd just make him roll all the dice every time I decided to take 10. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-11 06:49:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's not what he did. It's what he didn't do.

Saying **NO**. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-10 23:56:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Sidebar does good work.

Choosing the edition based on the story you wanna tell would be your best bet. For example, I'd not choose 5e for epic fantasy, just because you can't mechanically represent the growth from chumps to champions. But for awesomeness-to-time-invested-prepping 5e can't be beat. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-10 23:43:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Familiarize your DM with the concept of a bell curve.

Also, creatures with 1 int are not playable characters. I repeat, NOT PLAYABLE. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-10 23:42:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I have a char with 18, 18, 17, 15, 13, 11.

The nature of chance is... it will happen to someone. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-10 23:40:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Neverwinter nights are as faithful and as current an adaptation as you're probably going to get.

Have not played DDO, but I've heard it more MMO-y than D D. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-10 00:10:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> DMC man... there's no competition here.

The first DMC performance I ever saw was C2C's 2005 and I was blown away. That's when I learned what true DJing is. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-09 23:42:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I've seen a couple of the feats from that book before, but it might also have been on the previous site, so who knows... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-09 23:14:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That burger does a good popcorn impression. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-09 23:05:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> While for others, the older you get, the harder it is NOT to stay up till the birdies. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-09 22:58:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Half-elves are pretty good this edition, yea. But for ranger straight elves or halflings are better. Besides, most of the time spells are more fun than straight sword-and-board.

Also, points for the username. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-09 22:44:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Darkstalker still allows a Spot check, it just forces it for abilities that would normally allow automatic detection. Skill checks are generally easy to boost, so just use enough spells and items to overcome the DC.

Touchsight or Mindsight flat out defeat darkstalker.

The shadow-based Hide in plain sight that Shadowdancers(among a few others) get is always an Su ability, therefore does not work in Anti-magic field. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-09 22:22:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Cthulhu eating ye. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-09 22:19:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Nothing we couldn't already with 2.

Heck, our lovable kobold overgod needs only 1. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-09 18:45:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> We're live. :) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Kiss [Prywinko] </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-04 03:13:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Can the past be reconstructed? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-11 02:02:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If you were to have access to perfect information, could the exact state of the universe at all past moments be extrapolated from the present?

If not, why not? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [bug] Filter *still* not working </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-04 22:09:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> *What's the problem?*   
  And by **still** I mean, I went and built from source(as you see by the version), as in, I literally just pulled from the repo like 5 minutes ago, after reportedly the problem had been fixed in the latest code. Except not.


*What other browser extensions are installed?*  
  n/a

*Did you read the known issues and search /r/RESissues?*  
  I am aware the wiki said this was fixed in the latest code.



- Night mode: false
- RES Version: 4.7.0
- Browser: Chrome
- Browser Version: 49
- Cookies Enabled: true
- Platform: Windows

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> PSA: DMs, do not be afraid to bend the rules for the sake of cool </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-17 17:36:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Looking for a Youtube alternative with swipe-seek </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-10-15 20:23:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The situation out there is horrifying!

Doesn't have to be playstore-available. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [Online][3.5/3.P][GMT+1] High-fantasy small-party game </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-10-01 23:53:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What can I say... I am looking simply for a good, heroic game with a **small, tight-knit party of mature folk**(no more than 4 players)!

It seems all of roll20 just creams itself over kindergarten-style campaigns with 6-10 players. It's unmanageable for 99% of DMs there.

I'd prefer the main system to be 3.5, but I don't have a problem with liberally borrowing ideas from PF. I am decently experienced in the former and somewhat in the latter. I'd also like a game where I'd have freedom to experiment.
***
Groups and DMs who do not know what "The Stormwind Fallacy" is need not respond to this thread. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> How fast does venom act? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-09-27 21:55:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I know there are different types of venom, which probably also means the condition progressed differently, so then the question might become - How fast do venoms of different types act? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [WP] Jules and Vincent go in to collect Marcellus' suitcase, but there's a twist - Brett is now one of Michael Westen's clients. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-08-17 18:57:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> For reference:  
1. Jules and Vincent are from the movie *Pulp Fiction*.  
2. Michael Westen is the lead character in the TV series *Burn Notice*. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Recommend a DM Software </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-08-17 02:46:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I have arrived at the point where pen and paper(or even its digital equivalents - a *really* good editor and .txt files) are simply inadequate to properly prepare my campaign.

Therefore I am looking alternatives that will help me organize the massive amounts of interconnected information into an easy to use and navigate database.

I am aware of DMGenie and RealmWorks - one is discontinued, the other is way to expensive for me.

The current working candidates are Trello and Twine.

Features I want ideally:  
Ability to link to files(or attach)  
Graphs  
Auto-complete(and auto-link)  
Being able to attach metadata - like tags, categories, etc.  

**Basically... I want an IDE for D D.**  

Any suggestions will have to be system-agnostic or 3.5e/PF compatible. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Medieval shipbuilding times </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-08-08 19:43:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So I've been doing some research today on medieval maritime vessels for a game system I'm designing.

The thing is - there is not a lot of information on what goes into building those. That I've been able to find anyway(maybe my google-fu just isn't strong enough).  
The manpower and the time and resources that such vessels require.

I'm not looking for extensive data(though that would be cool), just a good sample for all the sizes and types - from generic boats and small vessels like a keelboat or a caravel to galleys, to the large medieval galleons and the largest wooden enlightenment-era ships.

So if anyone here is an expert, or has some good resources to offer on the subject, please share. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [Online][3.5e][GMT, Not Wed/Fri] LF high-fantasy/high-power </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-30 06:06:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Mainly I'd like to try a certain wacky character concept.

It's kind of finicky rules-wise though, so I'd need freedom with the resources I can pull from, including being *(mildly)* homebrew-friendly.  
But it's a martial character without 3.0 shenanigans, so casters still one-up me.
***
As for me, I'm experienced and patient. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The difference between min-maxing and optimizing </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-19 02:18:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yes, I know in a sense it's arguing semantics, but hear me out.  
(Naturally this is most relevant for 3.5 due to the amount of material, but isn't exclusive to it.)
***
I actually believe that there *is* a difference.  
We all know the negative connotations of min-maxing and we've all been warned by a myriad DMs against it.  
Optimizing is kind of the "politically correct" term many people use.

And I do like to optimize. Like a lot... but I don't actually consider myself a min-maxer.

The way I see it, min-maxing is favoring mechanical performance to the exclusion of **everything** else.  
While optimizing means picking an idea and making it work as best as possible within the confines of the system.

I'll take all the flaws and templates and what-have-you I can get away with, use every book, magazine and resource ever published, but I have no problem foregoing "established" tricks to make a character thematically consistent or subvert the expected trope.  
I'll pick an idea(maybe it will be a song, a video I saw, something I read in a book) and try to recreate some cool piece of character design or role, and then I try to optimize the hell out of it.

***

So what do you guys think?  
Is there a difference?  
What kind of player are you(I don't judge, I can max it with the best of them)?  
Do you consider min-maxing and/or optimizing bad?  
Have you had books thrown at you? How did your DM handle power-level disparities?  
Have some of the players you've played with lived up to the min-maxing, murder-hoboing stereotype, and how did the group deal with them? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [Online][3.5e][GMT] Looking for gestalt </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-06 05:56:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Always wanted to play one of those campaigns, but no DM seems to be willing to tackle that task.

It's like they're all scared shitless of this variant. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Reddit, what is your internet persona? And how is it different from your real-life demeanour? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-24 19:45:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> GTA5 should get its own flair </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-07 17:28:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> ...just so we filter out posts about it.

I'm tired, *exhausted* of seeing that thing every second post.  
For the sake of mine and no doubt many other's sanity, please make this happen. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Exponentiation approaching multiplication? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-05 03:22:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> **Just noticed that for x=1.00...00abc, the more zeroes you have, the more *x^y* approaches *(x-1)y+1*.  
Why is that?**

Semi-interesting backstory:
I was designing the mechanic behind a game-mod I'm doing and needed to make something happen 4 times faster in certain cases. Meaning I had to expo my multiplier to the 4th power. Only my multiplier was rather small to begin with. And then I noticed this peculiarity in my maths - it was like raising to the x power multiplied only the fraction by x. Then I tried different numbers and discovered it wasn't a fluke either.

Now I'm both puzzled and curious. But my math isn't that strong so I wouldn't even know where to begin. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Looking for a small, free, portable cue splitter? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-11 06:40:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Does such a beast exists somewhere on the internets?  
I need to split a couple of cue/flac files and I cannot for the life of me locate a fast, non-malware looking way to do it.
P.S. Here's the type of awesome software I'm looking for:
http://www.sector-seven.net/software/flicflac

Small, free, no install, does one job perfectly. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> How do I markup? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-11-20 03:18:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Why in poo-perfect hell does this work?

asdf^(word word) [asdf\^(word word)]

And this doesnt:

asdf^(2^(asdf 2)) [asdf\^(2\^(asdf 2))]

And how do I make it work? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> If you could delete /b/, would you? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-11-07 11:51:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Quite simply, if you had the power to remove /b/ from existence, would you make use of that power and *why*?

For those that do not know: /b/ is a subsection of the site 4chan and is commonly quoted as the shithole of the internet. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The reviews for the 980 are in and Anandtech is pulling out all the stops </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-09-19 07:13:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Silly markup implementation </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-09-03 00:08:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Reddit's markup is not properly implemented.

Just try an put a named link in superscript. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> A short PC master race survey </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-07-31 17:57:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm conducting a study on video gaming and have made a short [SURVEY](https://www.surveymonkey.com/s/VJ8ZTWP).
I've looked many previous ones, but none were inclusive enough to provide a decent snapshot of our glorious community(which is specifically what I'm interested in).

I would very much appreciate if you take a minute of your time to fill it out.

Once we collect a decent amount of data(say 200 responses) I'll sift through it and include it back in this post in an easy to digest format.^(that was a problem with a lot of the other surveys - never posting a meaningful result)

Edit:
Well... I guess the site refuses to give you results past 100 responses on the free plan, which is just as well because we've plateaued anyway. Here's a running commentary:

The majority of visitors are young individuals, with the age group of 15-23 making up 75% of all replies, with NA residents being 2/3rds, Europeans 1/3rd and minor contributions from other continents.
Perhaps unsurprisingly then, the most popular genre is Shooters.

What I did find surprising is that MOBAs are actually lower than RTS - and even simulators in ranking.

A lot of you(a third) also spend a full day gaming each week. That's an entire saturday, midnight to midnight spent in front of a screen of some kind.
Being the PCMR, all of you seem to spend that time on your PCs more than anywhere else, with 2/3rds gaming almost exclusively on their glorious rig. The rest is actually spent more on mobile devices - smartphones mostly, but even tablet gaming alone is outpacing the consoles here.

58 of 83 were on Intel CPUs(there were only 2 i3s), on AMD phenoms are still quite popular; 52 out of 85 are on nvidia with the 770 the most popular card, followed closely by 780/660. There was one Titan Black in there. Most of you are still on Win7, but Win8 is hot on it's heels(47/34). There were a few on linux and a few dual-booters(the most verbose people). The one person on Mac put a frowney face at the end.

Here are the charts:
https://imgur.com/r2Ro6AJ

It's been rather educational for me. :) Thanks to everybody who participated. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Reddit Comment Navigator userscript </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-07-25 03:29:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Time to go full on meta!

So, in a bid to make my life on reddit easier to I wrote a little script that allows you to navigate reddit using the keyboard. You can find it here:

https://openuserjs.org/scripts/subject8211/Reddit_Comment_Navigator

The only issue is - I'm using this [this](https://github.com/jeresig/jquery.hotkeys) jQuery plugin currently residing on my machine and I'm open to suggestions on replacing that link with something that will be up 24/7.

Feel free to use it as you please and report any bugs. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> How massive does a black hole need to be to be dangerous? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-07-21 04:46:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Yakety meets GTA4. Chaos ensues. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-12-12 07:09:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
