<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject7374</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-17 10:43:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That look...THAT look. I feel sorry for the giver AND the receiver. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-14 05:35:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Then there's Trottimus, taken from the hobo named Trott Imus, the little-known, middle-aged, illegitimate son of Don Imus. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-12 07:19:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Ross Hornby, ladies and gentlemen. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-10 02:30:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> KAYTON B9UT could actually be KAYTON GROUP. This fits as Kayton Group is a banking group and is in the list of "WATCH THEIR BANKS..." with their offices located in Little Seoul, corner of Vespucci and Ginger. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-09 01:01:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> 9:56 What a great cam switch. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-08 01:46:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Stunt Lads: Snow Crew </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-07 04:26:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Implying Donald Trump isn't a dick or a joke </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-07 00:54:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm with Smith on this one. The new Ghostbusters movie didn't need to be made. I feel sorry for future generations who will use that movie as their introduction to the Ghostbusters franchise. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-29 11:49:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Anyone? No? Fine.

Nice TRON: Legacy shirt, Bruce. Hopefully TRON: Ascension lives too. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-29 00:18:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That music when Sjin shows off the toilet car and subsequent vehicles...I'm getting a serious 'Birdland' (Weather Report, 1977) vibe there. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-26 12:29:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Holy shit snacks! Is that Tim Matheson? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-25 02:10:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> ...but a birch ain't one. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-25 00:54:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> For those wondering what song Trott is trumpeting at the start of 'Ballz to the Wallz', it's 'Sir Duke' by Stevie Wonder. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-22 13:18:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I should have clarified that I meant the entire episode was quieter than previous installments. I had to have my television twice as loud as normal to get the same volume. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-22 11:27:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> In the wake of Poseidon, GET SOME CONSISTENT VOLUME!!! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-22 09:43:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> For a moment, I thought you meant that custom sonic screwdriver maker on YouTube.

Still, quality content either way. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-21 00:00:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I could watch Smith being Smith for days and not get bored. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-12 23:45:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> DREAMS REALLY DO COME TRUE! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-10 22:22:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Maybe, but more than likely not; the whole "crazy pills" thing originated from the first Zoolander film. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-08 04:58:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Gluttony kek

(Read a book, people.) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-08 04:56:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Now we just have to wait for people to photoshop this into sad and horrifying modern and historical pictures. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-06 23:53:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'd love to hear the instrumental of this. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-05 10:48:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That sounds like a dick-rippingly good idea. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-03 07:06:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> *A wild Ross appeared!* </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-01 12:39:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I wonder if Vikkstar123 watches these.



(HELMET BOY ORIGINS!) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-26 13:01:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Far less than the Hat Films boys deserve. Far, far less... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-23 06:04:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I saw "Shatfilms" and thought it was the Hat Films logo with inverted colours, so the Hat was white and the splatter was black, but then the splatter was coloured brown. And underneath that would be "S.H.A.T Films" with the letters of "S.H.A.T" coloured pink, blue, green and red, respectively.

That's what I expected, but instead I got jiggling poo. Some would argue that's pretty much the same. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> This pleases me (Ross appreciation) </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-21 09:17:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Personally, I think Ross has excellent taste is music. Take his love of Arthur Brown, for example; how many times has he tweeted about Arthur Brown (and more specifically the iconic song "Fire")?

It's great that even the young ones (I know he's not really 'young', per se) keep on respecting the classics of yesteryear. But here's my opinion; the work of Arthur Brown feels a lot like the work of Hat Films.

Example: [THIS](http://www.soundstation.dk/images/products/large/33/135133-b.jpg) is the album cover for "Galactic Zoo Dossier" by Arthur Brown's Kingdom Come from 1970. Read closely; doesn't it seem like one of the kinds of covers that the boys would put out? Also, [THIS] (https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=8o6hQKsX7R4) is the song "Gypsy Escape" from the album and (to me) sounds like the crazy, erratic stuff that we love hearing from the Sirs; imagine if you will, Smith doing the guitar/s, Trott on the keyboard and Ross on the drums (but done on a keyboard, too).

Seriously though, Ross: good taste in music you've got. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-18 06:30:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Imagine the following:

Chris "I'm still on the ramp!" Trott of Hat Films doing a collaboration with Ryan "I'm still in the air!" Haywood of Achievement Hunter. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-17 12:43:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I think the Yogscast and the Ultimate Sidemen should collaborate on something. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-09 09:59:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> How about Smith in his Chun-Li outfit? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-07 01:55:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So, Smith; when can we expect the next episode of GymnastiCars? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-29 10:54:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Holy Jesusfuck... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-19 11:12:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> No! No! That's not true! That's impossible! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-12 04:31:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Trott, please forgive us. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Idea for a short video </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-08 11:00:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I love the outrageous accents the Sirs come out with and the talk about accents and language in the latest Trials (inb4 I LIKE TRIALS) gave me a good idea.

Imagine, if you will, the Sirs compiling a list of phrases of their own choosing in different languages, then proceeding to say those phrases in accents that sound wrong for the language.

Example: Smith saying "Guten Morgan meine Freunde" (German: Good morning, my friends.) in an over-the-top Australian accent. The mental image of that gets me chucking every time.

What foreign phrases in which accents would you like to hear them say? Post them below! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-06 01:48:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I LIKE TRIALS! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-11-30 13:00:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Plausible, but the evidence says otherwise. The Fallout Wiki states that development began after the release of Fallout 3 in 2009, but it was minor compared to Skyrim because they were being developed at the same time. Fallout 4's development kicked into maximum after the release of Skyrim. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Got a mystery for y'all... </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-11-30 10:50:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [Take a look at this.](http://imgur.com/JR6JBO4)

I can't remember where I found it, but look at the "score". Can anyone here figure out the significance of the date shown?

And for those who can't load the image, it's a pinball machine where the score says "2011.09.24" which is the date "September 24th, 2011".

Like the rebuilding of the wasteland, this one's up to you guys! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-11-29 10:24:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I know there's some bastard talk in the GTA:V Liberated! video but I don't know how far in it is. (inb4 that's what she said) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-11-22 00:58:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Called it.

https://m.reddit.com/r/Yogscast/comments/3tbgns/yogskim_vlog_special_new_minecraft_series_reveal/cx54yh9 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-11-21 00:53:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Huh, I didn't know one-seventh of the Ultimate Sidemen sponsored this. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-11-19 01:19:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Nice Milo Kerrigan impression, guys. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-11-19 01:03:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Planet Miranda, huh?

*'Firefly' theme plays in distance* </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-11-18 21:50:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> There's Rebecca (how can anyone forget Rebecca?), Smith's costumed persona in the Witcher 3 Vlog and Foxxy the Wolf from the Filfy Animals "Valentine's Special".

EDIT

The whole Chun Li thing. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-11-16 01:20:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> There's a delightful "Weird Science" vibe going on here. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-11-07 01:09:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Anyone else think he should utilise the massive hole under the ground for something? I was kind of hoping he'd just have a massive garden on the ground above and build the castle hanging upside-down in the hole beneath them under a layer or two of obsidian for protection from confused invaders. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-11-04 11:30:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Nah, the age says 20 years old. My guess? He got thrown in jail after a few officers made one too many TA jokes. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-11-02 00:22:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You'll have to be a little patient; I'm new to game-making (I'm using RPG Maker MV) and I'm currently making a short interactive interpretation of Eliot's "The Hollow Men". It's a challenge, but one I go into smiling. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-11-01 04:01:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Now, there's a thought; a Christmas murder mystery where you have to figure out which of the 9 reindeer killed Santa. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-10-31 10:35:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I watch Hat Films and make games based on famous short poems, but never at the same time. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-10-31 10:33:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> ...if he had that voice at 5 years old, sure. XD </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-10-28 12:01:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The official Stunt Lads episodes, the wonderfully made Fanimations and Ross' grotesque birthday Kinder slab.

I mean, these are the videos I'd show them if I HAD friends. All I've got are you twats and pricks who already know and love them. :P </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-10-20 23:07:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> *starts humming Around The World by Daft Punk* </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-10-20 23:07:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That's the bus stop in the middle of Cattley Street in Burnie, so that's the North West. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-10-07 12:08:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You have got to be the most active and dedicated Hatter to the cause.

May the Hand bless you and your work. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Stunt Lads Logo </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-10-05 10:26:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-09-25 04:54:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'd say it's the gritted teeth insult that reminds you of him. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-09-22 12:03:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> All I'm saying is that the whole "incestuous backwards state" thing is getting old. We're not Texas. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-09-22 09:37:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That's an outdated and frankly insulting reference. We can make the same claim about the ACT, but we don't because we're nice like that. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-09-21 12:27:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> JizzForChris?

Could be used for Sips or Trott. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-09-19 08:16:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Damn. You and I are at opposite ends of the state. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-09-19 08:10:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> North or South? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-09-19 04:09:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Same here. Burnie located? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-09-19 01:46:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Closest major city. I'm in Howth, about a 10-15 minute drive east out of Burnie. It sucks; there's nothing here and, without me, the average age of the people around here would be about 60 years old. Hat Films provide a much-needed comedy outlet around here. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-09-19 01:34:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm guessing you're more South, towards Hobart area, yeah? That where everyone is and everything seems to happen. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-09-19 00:29:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hat Films take on Australia? Mate, you're gonna have yourselves a Golden Gaytime down here.

Just one question; everyone seems to forget about Tasmania (those darn Mainlanders :P ), so would a visit to the Island State be feasible? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-09-19 00:26:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> WOO! North-West Tasmanian here. That makes...three Hatters I am aware of in Tasmania. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Australian Fanbase </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-09-18 07:48:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hey, are there any Australian Hatters like myself bouncing around this sub-reddit?

If so, leave a comment about how surprised (or disappointed) you are with the overseas fanbase of Hat Films.

If you want to say where in Australia you're from, who knows? You might find that your next door neighbour or the guy behind the counter on the corner shop or that one bus driver you really don't like is actually a Hatter! Anything is possible!

- subject7374 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-09-18 05:03:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You're doing God's work, Sir/Madam/Other.

Here's my two cents; Crazy Pills! They're a consumable item that induce a sort of berserk state at the cost of other faculties, like a temporary Attack boost for a certain number of turns but enemy attacks do more damage for the same time. One possible description of them could be "A bottle of banana-shaped pills. May cause more harm than good."

Don't know if that'd be possible, though. I'm unfamiliar with the restrictions of the program you're using. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Found Asian Xephos in GTA:V (Single Player) </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-08-02 07:58:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-29 13:25:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I can...almost see it. The eyes throw the whole thing off, though. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [OPINION] I've figured it out </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-29 13:21:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Guys and girls, I think I've finally figured out just what Alsmiffy's Minecraft avatar is.

Now, stay with me as this might not be the conclusion you're expecting, but I think it's...

...A HUMANOID CLUMP OF SENTIENT SEAWEED.

Weird, eh? But it fits, I assure you. Let's look at the facts:

Smith is salty. I mean REALLY salty; if you combined all of the salt in all the salt mines of Russia, you'd maybe have an arm of Smith.

Now, the avatar of Alsmiffy is green; it's not all the same shade, however, as you can see there a few different shades of green used as a gradient.

Thirdly, the avatar has no discernible mouth, meaning that it can't speak or feed itself with the standard food you and I eat.

Let's look at the similarities here:

1. Have you ever tasted seaweed? Depending on the variety and application, it can have a lot of different flavours. But if you were to take it straight from the ocean and tasted it (you weirdo), it would be incredibly salty as you just picked it out of the saltwater ocean.

2. Like the flavour, the colour of seaweed can come in different varieties: for the purpose of this, I'm focusing on mainly the green-coloured variations of seaweed, within which are several shades of green not dissimilar from the greens on the avatar.

3. Seaweed can't speak. No duh, right? But what about food? That's simple: seaweed is a plant and derives its food and energy from the sun via photosynthesis and plants don't need a mouth for that.

Still with me?

"But what about his eyes?", you may ask, to which I'd respond "You have me over a barrel there." But I ask you "What evidence is there that the eyes are functional?" I mean, for all we know, those are just a couple of squid eyes picked up from a dead specimen on a beach somewhere and shoved into what constitutes the head to give the appearance of a normal-ish humanoid being.

"And the suit? Why the suit?" Well, that's easy. A big clump of tendrils is just a clump unless molded into a semi-permanent shape and THAT'S why the suit: to give the clump the shape we know and fear.

"And the predilection with fire as shown in many a well-drawn fan art?" ...that's just Smith in general. If you want to go ahead and imagine the personality of Smith resides in the seaweed, go ahead: I, for one, can't comment on what ANY plant is thinking, so the interpretation is up to you.

"And just how did the seaweed become sentient in the first place?" HOW SHOULD I KNOW? It's fantasy, people: make something up!

"And the backstory of how it-" Enough, all right? If you like my theory, make up your own freaking story.

So, let's recap: salty, green and doesn't eat with a mouth (and MAYBE doesn't know what it's doing half the time...maybe MOST of the time, but that's Smith for you). There aren't many things that have those same key points and seaweed is at the top of my list (above the super-strain of watermelon watered with saline solution).

What do you think? Like the title says, this is purely an opinion: whether you agree or disagree is none of my business. I just want to get this out of my head because I forgot it.


From the middle of nowhere in the arse end of the world, I'm subject7374. Good day. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
