<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject966</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-20 19:47:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What a pissing contest.... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-19 19:18:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If it was clear and wasn't hazy, I used to be able to see Fuji-san from the flight deck of the ship I was on in Japan. It's such a majestic figure to have looking over you in the distance... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> South Park has gotta be approaching Patch Adams on the all-time list of touchy conclusions tackled with humor by now. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-19 08:47:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Best possible accountant slogan: I put your money where my math is. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-19 08:32:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-19 08:26:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I really want to have sex with a president. That's why I'm really hoping a woman gets elected. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Dad Joke: What did the horse get on his oral exam? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-16 23:42:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> A-neigh </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> My monkey's dad in Vietnam (1969) </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-14 06:59:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> My monkey's dad in Vietnam </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-14 06:46:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> An appeal to moderators of this sub... </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-13 07:20:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I love Bernie deeply, just as many of you. We fought with him, we worked with him, we became better people because of his resolve.
Because of these facts, we all feel a certain level of defeat because of today's 
My last post was deleted because apparently the campaigning for other candidates isn't allowed, but now, I ask the moderators to allow it. 
Bernie doesn't intend to keep running, or atleast I presume that after his announcement today. I also feel, since almost ALL of the followers of this sub endorsed Bernie, not because of his party affiliations, but because of his values and his stances. 
I feel as though the best use of this subreddit, for as long as it exists, is to segway Bern's belief structure behind another candidate.
Regardless of his political endorsement, his supporters deserve the right to be informed and educate themselves based on what they know ans then ultimately choose a candidate that doesn't necessarily include the bipartisan candidates....

Don't play the same game that the media plays, Reddit. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> A positive prospective after today. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-13 06:14:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-12 08:41:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So, you forgot to put brickdust at the bottom of your recycle bins outside the house you built on an old Indian burial ground... could'a happened to any one of us... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-11 17:29:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Icee </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> If I use my selfie stick in the shower, I can probably take selfies with water Pokmon without fucking up my phone. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-10 21:54:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> When you want to be honest but don't want to research your competitors... </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-07 22:10:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Home improvement or home invasion?! </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-04 04:09:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> These player's cards have been showing up in my Yahoo Fantasy Sports app. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-04 00:45:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Home improvement of home invasion? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-04 00:37:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-01 03:16:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Martin Luther Kingfisher Jr. had a bream..... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> For the past week or so, these player cards have been showing up in Yahoo's Fantasy Sports searches (Screenshot is for the sake of proof) </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-21 03:30:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The best possible accountant slogan: I put my money where my math is. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-18 05:37:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-06 06:41:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Obligatory Bob Ross cloud in the foreground... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Above the Arkansas River in Eastern Arkansas (4160x2340) </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-06 04:32:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Over the Arkansas River in Eastern Arkansas </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-06 04:21:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> I made a bad goat pun...Hall and Goates was not pleased </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-01 22:46:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-28 00:33:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Their taps had Property of the USA stickers on them when the Russians found them haha </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> When you wanna be the princess of relaxation AND all Sayans... </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-27 15:26:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Why do Donald Trump's hands seem to act erratically and sometimes seem to stop where they are at the worst times? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-05 03:04:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> He suffers from low-handwidth... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Why do Donald Trump's hands seem to lag behind his statements and are sometimes erratic? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-05 02:50:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> He has low-handwidth </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> This depiction of my family crest has a lion taking a selfie </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-04 22:25:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-03 22:55:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Am I the first one to utter the name "Nicolas Clayge?!" </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Ron White Turns Into Ron Red </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-03 21:12:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-29 03:51:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> C'mon! This deserves gold...I saw a guy on r/CatsStandingUp get gold the other day for typing "Cat." Albeit, their name WAS Fat_Dennings </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-25 06:16:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> And his sidekick, BRRRRRRRR </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-25 05:06:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Your Dad looks like he's posing for the happiest and most inappropriately-angled yearbook photo ever... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-24 07:02:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If I can attempt to add to this already stellar response, I learned from a highly-decorated Vietnam vet that success comes more expeditiously to those who foster "ownership" in WHATEVER you do. If you acknowledge ownership of something, you unconsciously put your seal of approval on it because it's a direct reflection of your own efforts. Own your your profession or find one you don't mind owning...and stop listening to society and how it defines success.

We live in a Capitalist society where your class status is defined by how much capital you have. That's why our society perverts what "success" is. Stop listening to society and the media. It's all driven by Capitalist motives.

Be true to yourself; own what you decide to be and turn off the mainstream propaganda. 

Good luck, buddy. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-22 06:10:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The Doom "port" is 666 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-19 20:43:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Straight outta Paradise City </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> This must have been what Ace of Base was talking about... </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-24 23:03:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-19 00:15:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Pecker. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-18 22:47:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Shift+F3. This toggles the case of all the selected text (CTRL+A selects all, btw) from standard to all uppercase in Word. 

Also, I feel like ALT+TAB isn't utilized by as many people as I think it should. It's an excellent way to toggle windows and back out of full-screen applications, such as games. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-15 00:25:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> To be fair, the US was definitely bombed and invaded. Hawaii was a US territory and we lost thousands there due to the bombing of Pearl Harbor, as well as having the Philippines, another US territory, which sustained some of the heaviest causality numbers of the war. In fact, there was even a successful Japanese bombing in Oregon that killed six people in 1945. 

While both PI and Hawaii were both American territories as a result of colonial expansion, they were still homes to American citizens, therefore, must be included. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-07 03:27:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Anything that North Korea fires at any other country will get blown out of the sky. They are testing something that will never reach its intended target. If anyone doubts that, go back to footage of Desert Storm when Iraq was shooting at our forces in Kuwait...our Patriot Missiles took their SCUDs out, and that was 30 years ago. Nice try, Ken, but no cigar.... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-03 20:17:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Fucking. Marathons. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-26 00:01:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I Saw The Devil. Korean. Action endurance trial....incredible movie. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-25 20:35:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I think this is the perfect time to remind people that sea otters have been known to fuck a baby seal to death...and then continue to fuck it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-07 20:09:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Racism is more about fear than it is about hatred. Its the fear of the disruption to the established hierarchy of ethnic, racial, and cultural pecking order structure. We are almost all racist, or at least raised to be, and very few people manage to overcome its sway... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> If Rick Sanchez is wrong and there is a God, Heaven would have a fuck-ton of Meeseeks </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-11 06:14:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-10-20 23:44:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This is about as smart as having Jesus take the wheel... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-10-12 02:47:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> There sure seem to be a lot of "Hope Solos" in the NBA...just ask Soccer.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-09-03 23:51:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I guess he heard winter was coming....damnit Jon Snow </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The fine folks at the NYPD gave me two parking tickets in the last week. Neither officer knew the correct abbreviation for Arkansas, because that's where my car is registered. Not too sure if these should be paid.... </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-09-03 21:48:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Evening Hymns - Dead Deer [indie] (2011) </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-08-22 08:14:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Dead Deer by Evening Hymns - the most beautiful music video ever in my opinion. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-08-22 08:02:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-08-22 07:59:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Dead Dear by Evening Hymns

http://youtu.be/B5NOg6n_ruQ This video is a must watch </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-08-19 20:53:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm shocked, after seeing the horseshoe, that there isn't a rabbit's foot and a few lucky charms from the Austin Powers assasins bracelet... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-08-04 18:57:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Purrfect </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-08-04 03:08:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Coming from a guy that probably got stuck in a lot of playground equipment in his day... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Ferris, the optimistic amputee </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-08-02 17:11:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-08-01 00:26:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thanks. I needed that laugh after reading about the NYPD hate crime. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> If taken literally, "Jesus, Take the Wheel" by Carrie Underwood could kill more Christians than the Romans. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-31 17:42:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Too soon? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-31 17:08:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I bet this dog can count to potato. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> ELI5: Why have there not been any lawsuits against Fox News for libel and slander...or for the fact that they have the word "news" in their title without any intention to live up to that moniker </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-25 17:39:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-24 23:41:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I don't know if ketchup is a smoothie but I know this cat's sup is smooth. http://imgur.com/KjPseBS </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-24 23:38:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I don't know if ketchup is a smoothie but I know this cat's sup is smooth. http://imgur.com/KjPseBS </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-24 16:09:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Tomatoes are a fruit. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The phrase "Needless to say" should be accepted as a complete sentence...the reason for which, should be....apparent. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-24 16:03:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-14 22:21:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The title sounds like how Ron Swanson starts explaining most life lessons... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-12 19:20:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Another trend we can thank the Japanese for. They put their dogs in strollers so they can take them onto trains. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> TIFU by getting a cheap scooter ride to the airport in Thailand (WARNING: Unabridged but worth it)... </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-20 17:29:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I have spent the past few days in Thailand while in a "treat-myself" vacation from my day gig in Japan where I'm stationed. On my first day out here in Phuket, I decided to go down to a few of the "classier establishments"(if you don't quite understand why I'm using a ridiculous amount of quotations, just Google Paying Beach, probably NSFW btw) After a lengthy perusement of the "local talent" and a thourough sampling of booze, a whiskey-fueled trip back to my hotel room to "freshen up" seemed llike the right call. I made it about half way to my hotel before I made a pit stop at a street-side bar to talk to a girl in a red dress. We hit it off pretty well. So well in fact, that I didn't immediately notice the not-so-convincing transvestite with "her" posse of compatriots that were immediately behind us that had them began to exchange loud, masculine Thai-speak with my ladyfriend. For the sake of not having any pictures, imagine a mid-90s version of Artie Lange in a tube top who just got a regrettable chin job done.  Despite this being a descent into what I can only imagine what resembles a LITERAL manifestation of the cusps of Paul Reuben's unconscious wantings, I weathered the barrage of advances from the hoard of "ladies" that were now swooping in with the persistence of gadflies.  Relatively unscathed, I made it through the night only mildly violated and asked my lady friend to accompany me to my room. 

I am terrible with names but the girl's name was Nancy and YES! every other question I asked her was to inquire of her natural gender, which was female. 

Because yesterday was my last day in Thailand, and I had a 6AM flight about a 45 minute drive away, I decided to reserve a driver and go back to the bar and find Nancy in hopes of just repeating the events of my first night. I returned to find Nancy and a depleted yet still formidable version of the tranny gang, spearheaded by Mr. Lange himself. After continued advances by the diversity squad, me and Nancy slipped away from the group after another heated exchange of their native tongue. At about 1AM, after telling her about my car service plans, she asked me the price of the trip. After divulging that it was 1000 baht and her getting WAY TOO UPSET over the equivalent of 30 USD, she insisted she would give me a ride on her scooter for half price but that she would have to drop her roommate off at their place first. Knowing I only had a backpack to carry and the whole thing would be a pretty good story to tell, I accepted. 
She left and then returned with her roommate, none other than Ms. Artie Lange AKA Mimi. Using my backpack as an eexcuse and with Nancy driving, decided it would be best to sit as far back on the helmet rack as possible, attempting to keep my uglies from bumping into Miss Lange's VIP entrance. One overlooked aspect of the ordeal on my part was the complete lack of sobriety on the part of the driver. We made it about a kilometer before she made her first death-defying maneuver around a chicken truck. Though she defied deaths clutches on that go-around, it became apparent that I had to chose between expiration or holding onto something "sturdier" than the helmet rack. At the sight of us rapidly approaching an even more suspect chicken truck, I instinctively latched onto Mimi's "hate handles," burying the side of my face into his/her back and hoping for the best. Mimi's response to my sudden epiphany of attraction during the 20 minute drive once we arrived at their place was to ask me to come upstairs for "one drink." After emphatically declining, I eventually arrived at the airport, safe and sound. I then felt compelled to do several "manly things" in rapid procession. I made out with Nancy, slapped her on the ads as she speed off and went into the airport and chugged a beer. No ragrets, folks!
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> A nice couple was sitting on the porch of their vacation home on a river in Canada... </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-07 17:11:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> A nice couple was sitting on the porch of their vacation home on a river in Canada. The woman raises her gaze from the book she was reading and stated to her partner, "Did you hear that a family of beavers moved into a nice place just up stream." The man looks up from the publication he was reading, smirks and stares disillusioned into the distance and said, "Well I'll be damned." </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Im starting to question the authenticity of Mongolian barbecue in all aspects from it's portion size to it's ingredient variety to it's selection of sauces. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-15 16:10:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> It's not so lonely at the top after all... </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-11-04 11:41:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Taking the "pun" out of bird watching </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-08-17 23:34:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
