<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject1935</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-31 14:11:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> SAG is one of the most powerful unions in the U.S.. Trying to copy Crispin Glover's face in BttF 2 was enough to get them to take action. They aren't going to let contracts like this happen. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-31 14:08:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Those are fictional characters and are copyrighted. You can't copyright history the same way. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-31 13:54:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm sure when they started getting rid of the tenements, would lads were complaining 'it didn't feel like Dublin at all'. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-30 17:14:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Got that same feeling in Frank. Is it really Fassbander or just a guy in a mask? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-30 17:13:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [That movie is kinda of a twofer. When the guy is dead and you can see the body is clearly not of Keither, I just figured only his voice would be in the movie. Then real life Keither appears. On a side note isn't weird that he looks so like his dad but both of them were cast in A Time to Kill and the characters weren't related or anything?](\spoiler) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-30 17:10:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I read about it and accidentally spoiled it on a friend who was going to see it. Luckily they corrected me and said he was going to be in the sequel so the movie was spoiled after all. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-30 17:08:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> They should have credited Jesse Plemons and then have Matt Damon show up. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-30 17:07:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hey Geoff, what are you doing here today? 

Oh nothing. Just came in to talk to a guy about a thing. 

Why are you all dressed up like a pirate Geoff. 

Nah, these are my street clothes. This look is big in Paris.

Why is there a makeup call for you and a chair with your name on it, Geoff. 

It must be for Jeffery Rush. I'm Geoffrey Rush. Big difference.

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-30 17:03:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Also Scream 2 did the same with Jada Plinkett Smith. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-30 17:02:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Psycho does it too. It made a big deal about Janet Leigh being the star and set the whole film up as a thriller, only to kill her halfway through and switch to a more horror like story. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-30 16:15:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm not saying he was. I'm just commenting on Cuba's history with regards to LGB rights. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-30 16:11:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> They are grand. If you play the main series, there is something new to learn if you care about the modern story. They are good laptop games to play with something on in the background. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-30 16:08:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I really wish they trimmed down a lot of the game and rebrand Mass Effect as Epic Speech Simulator. Just have Shepard giving speeches before going into battle. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-30 15:31:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I think Arkham Asylym got back tracking pretty spot on. The game was almost like a 3D Metroid game. Getting new gadgets unlocked new areas and when walking old places there were new things to see.

Unfortunately this tight and fun gameplay was ruined when the second game went open world. It's still a good game but the progression was less fulfilling.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-30 15:08:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  It is a law because the government doesn't want the homeless camping in parks and squares.

That's what they say but lets be honest, it is because they don't want homeless full stop. Same reason why they outlaw panhandling. So the police can stop and move the homeless along,

Other examples are mandatory sentences applying to drugs like crack, but not the more rich people friendly cocaine. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-30 14:56:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I love that movie and I think she is great in it. Her character is speaking her second language, it's not suprising that she would talk the way she did.

Also people are watching Pacific Rim for robots fighting dinosaurs. No one cares if the actress can't speak English like a native. Also she is probably the only Japanese actress with enough recognition to an US or international audience. The only other option would be Chiaki Kuriyama from Kill Bill and I'm pretty sure she can't speak any English. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-30 14:42:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Places outlaw sleeping on the street. That is a quick one. They outlaw homelessness but don't pass laws to keep rents/property prices spiraling or provide shelter.

In SF they have to bus people in to work the service industry because cashiers, baristas and bus drivers can't afford to live in the city. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-30 14:38:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Lets be honest. Most times when people spend 14 hours in the office, they spend about half of each hour goofing or just working really slowly. If you work full throttle for your first six hours, you are working at about 20% for the rest of the day. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-30 14:35:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I think how the justice system works will look like a joke. the current system does not try to find the truth of an incident. Rather it is a competition for each side. This goes for criminal cases and civil matters like divorce and it leads to innocent people taking plea bargains and is horribly biased towards the affluent. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-30 14:28:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Her English isn't great but she is a great actress. She has played mute characters in to English films and even got an Oscar nom as a mute. That's something. Getting nominated for an Oscar without even talking. Take that Leo. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-30 14:24:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> No sheep though. Disappointing. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-30 14:24:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What to do another one?

What do you think?

Falling slowly?

I'll do Falling Slowly, yeah.

https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=ymm0IGMaSYE) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-30 13:40:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The US is a weird edge case. You don't see any other first world country idolize its founders as the US does. So many debates bring up what the Founding Founders would have imagined. 

I hear what you are saying but I think we should consider the opinions of an upper class slave owner from 200 years ago before we continue this debate.

I think most people respect the people who put their nation into motion but are also smart enough to know their opinions were of their time. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-30 12:41:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Going around with your yellow regs and NHS, thinking they are better than us. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-30 12:34:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It is if you are the US. Unless that dictator suddenly turns on the US. Like Pinochet. Or Saddam. Or the others. Man the CIA are really shit and protecting US interests abroad. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-30 11:54:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That is a reason to dislike him.

Cuba has an interesting history with LGBT rights and we can only speculate how Che would have felt, but Castro would have had similar views as Che at the time, but sometime in the 80's he (or the general Cuban administration) seemed to do a 180 and Cuban government attitudes towards gay people in Cuban media changed drastically.

Just look at this [video from the Reagan press secretary](https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=yAzDn7tE1lU) that basically treated concern for gay people dying from AIDS as a joke. In 1981 the Cuban government was releasing publications that homosexuality was another facet of human love. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-30 11:52:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> At least Dre somewhat admits he has done awful things. Sean Connery has no shame in his women beating views. Dre raps about what a shithead he is in Guilty Conscience with Eminem. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-30 11:49:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Herge (creator and writer of Tintin) was a big racist too. But when he actually started researching the nations Tintin would visit and talking to natives (admittedly far too late into Tintin's success) he had a change of heart. He even went as far as to redraw panels in his older comics to remove content he thought was offensive with his new outlook. If I recall correctly he (and his estate) pledged never to print Tintin in Tibet in China because hina would have him change the title.

I'm pretty sure Seuss had a similar revelation and was not happy about his war era deceptions.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-30 11:37:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> He wrote a book for women about how it is their own fault if they don't have a boyfriend for having standards. They made a movie about it. It was an interesting but shit watch. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-30 11:34:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I love the irony of how Reagan gutted trade unions in the US despite being the head of a trade union. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-30 11:29:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You could say that about Washington and Mandela. He was a revolutionary and he was fighting in a war. I mean he is a controversial figure, but he was basically a war vet so saying he killed people isn't really a reason to discredit him, without discrediting pretty much every revolution with the exception of Gandhi (also a controversial figure, but almost definitely never killed anyone). </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-30 11:22:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What gets me is his writing. It is obvious that when you see a Woody Allen movie, that the main character is some sort of extension or persona of himself. It doesn't matter if he plays the character or Owen Wilson. And in pretty much every incarnation there is a male lead who isn't good looking or charming but somehow gets attractive women who are significantly younger than him. Alvy Singer in Annie Hall starts dating a sixteen year old. If Alvy is the same age as Woody he is late thirties or early forties. That's just rotten. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-30 11:11:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  To be fair, his dickishness probably contributed to the success of Apple.

It also probably contributed to the fall of Apple when they needed to be bailed out by Microsoft. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-30 11:10:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Wasn't even that great of a business man. He did get fired from Apple. For every great concept he had, he stole five others and stole or came up with another four or five bad ideas.

I honestly think that Apple's success was Apple going through a Golden Age. Apple was already considered a high end brand for creative type people. They innovated with a combination of fashion with tech that was just about to break anyway. Blackberry needed to break out of the stagnated business market, MP3s needed a way to go main stream. iTunes and iPhone made Apple a market player again and the iStore and iTunes meant they would never go poor again (the same way Steam means Valve don't need to make video games, despite being a video game company).

Apple hit these emerging markets and became early market leaders. This may or may not have been because of Jobs, but they were already trending off as the alternative cool brand and I think they just had their second lightning in a bottle moment. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-30 10:55:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Two of the biggest game franchises are CoD and Assassin's Creed. Both games are usually rated M. If anything the west considers games to be associated with male teenagers and arrested development men in their thirties. Only your parents look at games and think 10 year olds. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-30 07:36:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Literally, Abe's fame was more from being wrongly attributed as dead than his acting work. I can arely remember him in Godfather but I have a more vivid memory of 'Vigoda died, oh wait no he didn't'. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-30 07:29:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I get what you are saying but the people who work for Microsoft or Sony or even Nintendo don't live in Trump's America. They see their market is 25 - 35 sub/urban American's who see a high speed Internet connection is more important than a cable connection. And in the next decade this demographic will only grow. Just look at /r/cordcutters . Physical data will be the fax machine of the 2020's. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-30 07:14:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  Are we allowed to say that I don't think this trailer is good?

Of course. You are allowed to have an opinion. The whole premise of the movie is that it is The Expendables in the Batman world, so if you can't get behind that you were probably never going to like it. 

To me, this trailer looked like it a fast paced action movie with fun characters, that for the most part wouldn't take itself to seriously (Joker being the exception). In the end we got a movie that had the same deadpan stick in its ass that Man Of Steal and Batman Vs Superman had and while I can't really fault the casting or performances, there was just nothing there.

If WB can get their finger out of their ass and actually make one DCU film that is worth watching I would love to see a Will Smith Deadshot movie or a Robbie Quinn movie. I would love for Leto to have an actual chance to play Joker, rather than cameo.
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-29 21:55:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Well if it was anything like my school experience, PE is pretty much catered around the 5 members of the class who were really into one sport and were good at it.

If other courses were thought similarly it would be like if one student (or three) were really good at Yeats so instead of doing various poets and drama and stories, the teacher spent most of the time just teaching Yeats to cater to those students.

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-29 15:35:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You can't fault the [Suicide Squad trailer.](https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=CmRih_VtVAs) It makes the movie look cool, exciting and fun. Unfortunately the movie itself was balls, but we will always have that time between trailer and release. We were younger then, more naive. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-29 14:30:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> People still complain about uPlay which just keeps getting better and better.

Steam's UI is still looking old and dated. Core updates seem to push to Big Screen instead of the desktop experience.

But Steam is not a monopoly and people need to stop saying it is. They have the largest market share and probably the largest library, but that doesn't make them a monopoly. Coke isn't a monopoly because it sells more than Pepsi. We don't describe WalMart or Amazon as Monopolies. Just because you go to Steam first before checking Origin, uPlay, GOG or the Humble store doesn't make them a Monopoly. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-29 14:24:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The original proposals for XBox One will be the standard, if not in the next generation of consoles, the one after that. Physical media is on the way out. Even GameStop can see that, which is why they are focusing on selling merch now over games. Anyone insisting on boxed games are in for a culture shock in the next decade. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-29 14:13:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Logging in with a MS account is so much handier. I had family members forget logins. In 7 you can work around this, but since 8 I don't know of a way to reset a password. With a MS account they can reset their password anywhere, from any machine. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-29 14:06:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Microsoft now has a thing called Azure AD. When you start up a new install it will ask you is it a work machine or a home machine. If it is a work machine you can log into the corporate domain with Azure AD and your corporate login, which will also act as your Office 365 login. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-29 13:56:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's Little Sister. It's about a nun and her brother who was disfigured by an IED. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-29 13:54:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Considering how Gremlins 2 went batshit insane, 3 will probably be some trippy experimental film. With Gremlins. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-29 13:52:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The bandits had guns. One Samurai raids their camp and steals some of them but dies in the process. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-29 13:45:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  Why does nobody ever seem to finish their meals, they just get up and leave after a few bites

In Grease they order these two gorgeous looking hamburgers and then just leave without even looking at them. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-29 13:44:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> In MCU, science is essentially magic and then magic is something else. I wouldn't be surprised if in that world those things made sense. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-29 13:42:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I think that's a BS excuse. I know nothing about doctoring but when I watch a scene in House M.D. I feel like the diagnostic scenes make sense and not just shouting medical words. Anyone who has ever used a computer will know why two people using a keyboard doesn't make sense.

You can lie a little, like DNA results coming back instantly and computers zooming on photos (although that is cliche at this point) but if you do something ridiculous in a procedural it is painfully obvious. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-29 13:38:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The Social Network 'hacking scene' seemed pretty accurate. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-29 13:36:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Nocturnal Animals was great but I love how Amy Adams had her day makeup and then switches to her ready for bed make up. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-29 13:34:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You can't just lead a comment like that without a link. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-29 13:34:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Anything featuring lawyers do this to. One lawyer explains a basic legal concept (like discovery) to a room full of lawyers and then they just continue talking. No one stops to say 'We all passed the bar here, why are you telling us this?' </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-29 13:09:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hey, technically that's not illegal. Adverse possession is a thing in Ireland.

I think a bigger problem is that there are people who are sleeping out on the streets when there are hundreds of vacant houses and hotels around the country. Families without homes and homes without families. That's sickening.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-29 12:55:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> balance a check book

While we are at it, lets teach them how to send a fax and work a VCR. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-29 12:53:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Really should be thought in more of a social civics class. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-29 12:52:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  Ireland's history and culture is tied to Catholicism

A lot of our classic poetry and literature is made by people bemoaning the Catholic status. Joyyce wasn't a fan of the church and neither was Sean O Casey. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-29 12:49:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> PE needs to be more engaging. Pretty much every week we just played soccer. Then the odd week we would play rugby or gaelic. 

Why is it always competitive sports? If you are not fit, getting picked last or whatever doesn't engage you and PE can become a weekly humiliation. It should focus on healthy lifestyle and not just ranking how good people are at running or football. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-29 11:18:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Adobe became a market leader through piracy. How's the next gen of graphic designers suppose to learn now. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-29 11:12:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I think the issue was when they decided to stop charging people for news when they put it online. That was a huge mistake and such a shot in the foot. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-28 17:18:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I would argue that Jasmin would look strange in Beauty and the Beast. None of the characters in Hercules would fit nicely in any other movie. Timon and Pumbaa would stick out against the animals of Princess and the Frog. It is a new thing. It's animation, it should push imagination, not colouring between the lines. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-28 17:05:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Problem is, it is spreading. This model is from [The Little Prince](http://www.aceshowbiz.com/images/still/the-little-prince04.jpg). Not a Disney movie but if this girl showed up in Arondale it wouldn't look weird. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-28 17:03:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> But it is the same thing. Content advisory warnings. It's just a different thing that has been around forever. People are now pretending it is something new for millennials who can't handle reality. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-28 17:01:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Which is ironic because Toy Story is all about playing with mismatched toys. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-28 17:01:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Things don't look good for Frozone. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-28 16:19:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Grown up movie starts:

Up. Obvious.

Wall E. They tell an apocalyptic tale about the Earth being destroyed by wreckless endangerment of the environment.

Finding Nemo. A domestic scene, hit by tragedy when a husband loses his wife and his kid gets hurt.

Inside Out. They do a quick story about losing your innocence and childhood wonder. It could be argued that this goes through the whole movie but it is all really set up in the first act and most of the rest of the movie is stagnated in that moment while Joy has her adventure.

It's actually written down somewhere. I mentioned it to a animator friend and he confirmed that there is an actual formula and he confirmed that the first minutes are for the parents and have themes that the kids might not notice. This was a while ago and we were drinking so I wasn't taking notes. Sorry. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-28 16:12:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I loved Pixar movies. But now that I've seen 'behind the curtain' and have noticed that they have a formula, I didn't enjoy Inside Out. People raved about it but I saw Bing Bong's sacrifice and the core memories being shared with Sadness a mile off. Ruined the film really. Even if I could shut it off, Pixar movies just stick to stridently to the formula. It's okay to have a formula and it worked for years but now I thin k they need to be more malleable with it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-28 16:08:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That's not an excuse. Even if you are writing to a formula (and not just a three act structure, redemption cycle, etc.) you should hide it. It shouldn't be immediately obvious to an audience. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-28 16:04:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm a huge animation fan. I love Disney and Pixar but it's when Laika have an upcoming release I get excited. Even if a Laika movie has a weaker story, the movies are always visually interesting. Disney movies (and other studios) are beginning to look very samey. You could take a model from one movie and insert it into another and it would fit. You could put the Rapunzil model or the Elsa model in most Disney films and it will suit. Throwing a boxtroll into Kubo and it will stick out. Paranormal would look weird hanging out with Coraline. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-28 15:59:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah. So in UP! there is the obvious start about his wife dying and not being able to have kids. Then the middle emotional part when Russel mentions his father. New outlook is when Carl joins Russel to get his merit badges and isn't such a grumpy bastard anymore.

Inside Out has the death of Bing Bong as its big emotional part. Joy learning she needs sadness too. Toy Story 2 has Jessie's song for its midpoint feels. Monsters Inc. has Boo getting upset when Sully is teaching others how to scare, then Mike rebuilding Boo's door. Toy Story 3 has the incinerator and then then Andy passing the toys on. That's just going from memory. I know people loved Inside Out, but anticipating the formula I couldn't enjoy it and I really don't get excited for Pixar movies anymore. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-28 15:33:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The Lovely Bones how?

There are almost no movies that show that part of America, unless it is a horror movie, where city people are being hunted by yokels or about a high school football team.

EDIT: Realize I was thinking about Winter's Bone. Leaving the comment here to remind me of my stupidity.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-28 15:31:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Sad thing is, these are the movies that usually end up with Best Picture too. The only two movies that didn't follow this in recent years was Birdman and Midnight Cowboy.

In WWII movies about the war were pretty baity and post war it was all about big Musicals. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-28 15:30:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> He wants an Oscar and he says he is pretty much owed one. I thought he was going to retire Stark but those pay checks are just to lucrative and every Marvel movie with Stark in it breaks records. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-28 15:29:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Sully is a weird movie because they had to invent villains. Everyone thought what happened was heroic and brilliant and Sully got a lot of praise. But that's not a movie. everyone just congratulating a guy for doing his job extremely well. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-28 15:27:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  Also they just feel the need to constantly hammer on the fact that "racism is bad"

If you watch it again, it doesn't even do this. All it is really saying is 'Everyone is a bit racist, what can you do about it? \_()_/' </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-28 15:02:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You can do it well or you can just pile on the emotion in the most cloying, saccharine way. The scene in Crash actually made me laugh because it was trying so hard to be emotional. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-28 15:00:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Crash was so by the numbers. Also it is kinda hard to see what the movie was trying to say. the moral seems to be that everyone is a bit racist, so just ignore it and it will probably work itself out.

I mean that is a great solution for a white middle class person, but probably not people who are affected by racism. Maybe that's why it won? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-28 14:56:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I can't believe Redmayne didn't get a nom for Jupiter Rising. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-28 14:55:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> According to Tarantino you need to see AH on the big screen. He saw it on a TV first and didn't get it. Then he saw it on a big screen and loved it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-28 14:53:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> People take the Raspberry's too seriously. I think people don't realize that for the longest time they were held in a guys living room, turning up means you win. If no one wants to turn up, then the winner is by vote and the vote is by anyone who has the twenty odd dollars to join. Also past winners include The Shinning. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-28 14:51:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Crash. And worst of all it worked. I blame Brendan Frasier who you forgot was even in that movie. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-28 14:50:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> With Cars, Brave and The Good Dinosaur, Pixar is just not the stamp of quality it used to be. Even its hit movies seem very formulaic after a while. There is the first 15 minutes for the grown ups, there is the overly emotional tragedy about 3/4 ways through to make you cry in front of your SO/kids, and then the new outlook on life ending. To be fair, that ending applies to a lot, but Pixar have it in every movie. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-28 14:46:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Rabbit revolution. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-28 14:36:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Every year people complain about actors who were overlooked or not included. It is going to be a banner year for those complainers. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-28 14:34:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Dude, you should try letterboxd.com for tracking what you watched. It will even give you a statistical breakdown of the movies you watched over the year, including movies by country, genre, year etc. watches vs rewatches, most watched actors, etc., tec. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-28 14:22:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> For Fury Road, Miller wrote loads of back stories for characters. Thing is, he didn't bother filming them. I think the only character that really needed backstory in SS was Harley so they could show her relationship with Joker (Joker, a character who always works better with no origin story). </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-28 11:11:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You posted an image with text on it.That isn't a news source. I bet if you read into this, you would find that the actual scenario is completely different to the one playing in your head. This is how fake news spreads. You have put your faith in an image macro. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-28 11:10:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  I can't make any sort of joke without having to wonder who will take it up the wrong way.

Bernard Manning use to say the same thing about jokes about the Irish. What sort of jokes are you making?  

If you want to see people being easily offended, use the term British Isles on any other sub and wait for it to be posted here. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-28 11:07:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  The whole safe space cultural seems to be an American thing and even at that

It's actually nothing new. The terminology is new, but they have existed for years, yes even in Ireland. People complain that life doesn't have trigger warnings and it doesn't. But you know what reddit has? NSFW/NSFL tags. You know what that is, it's a trigger warning. Telling people that 'Hey maybe you have a sensitive disposition or maybe you had a friend die in a car crash recently so you probably don't want to watch the movie crash right now' is just politeness, not PC gone mad. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-28 11:04:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> With the young Muslims, I suggested that mocking the prophet Muhammad was no reason for the atrocities which happened at the Charlie Hebdo office.

No matter what you think of Hedbo, pretty much no one is trying to pretend that murder is okay.

In fact, this whole article is wank. Lets not pretend this person has anything new to say. She is getting offended by people getting offended. She is just a different type of snowflake. And she is not saying anything of value. In fact he is showing his own thin-skinnedness. 

If you are going to talk on topics that are controversial, and people question you or challenge you on it, don't call those people 'Generation Snowflake'. Be prepared to defend your opinions and not write off people as playing victims for the mere thought of saying something you disagree with. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-27 18:40:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Mutants will always be a metaphor for some under privileged or oppressed class. But if you really think about it, actual people would probably be more sympathetic to people born with as mutants (an accident, something they couldn't prevent) over the guy who was fucking around with gamma rays and now destroys city blocks when he gets angry or the Fantastic Four who pushed the limits of science and used themselves as canaries in their experiments. 

Also I'm not up to date with the comic lore, but how does the average Joe see someone like Cyclops and think he is a mutant and then see Spiderman and think he is not. Spidey's identity is secret, so even if he is open about how he got his powers, wouldn't people just presume he was lying and was actually born a mutant, and therefore face the same prejudices as the Xmen? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-26 17:56:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> He didn't rebrand, just got clean. He is still the same ole RDJ. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-26 17:56:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Katy Perry went from Chrsitian Singer to pop singer. Taylor went from country to pop. Gaga went from lounge to pop to lounge again.
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-26 17:02:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Look, if you like the film that's fine, but it is not Thus Spoke Zarathustra. It's not even I 3 Huckabees. It's a superhero film and the philosophy you talk about is no more than Neckbeard vs Jaden Smith.

Also, not a plot hole, just not Oz not being very smart. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-26 16:35:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  No rational person

People think Sandy Hook never happened or was staged. People think 9/11 was an inside job. What planet have you been on where a bunch of nations will just believe stuff because the government says so. The world is the closest it has ever been to doomsday because people see Dr Manhattan as a US super weapon. That US super weapon ends up killing millions of people. That is people's worst fears come to life. That is 12 o clock on the meter. America saying 'it wasn't me' isn't going to solve that.

A live body and a dead body contain the same number of particles. Structurally, theres no discernible difference. Life and death are unquantifiable abstracts. Why should I be concerned?

That's Jaden Smith, /r/im14andthisisdeep talking. Of course there is a difference between 130 pounds of meat or plastic and a living sentient being. Even a nihilist would admit that.

Also the 'smartest person in the world' isn't going around telling people he is the smartest person in the world every five minutes. And his password isn't practically written beside his computer. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-26 16:25:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I don't mind so much, except who really doesn't know Batman or Superman or Spiderman's story at this stage. I always think Arkham Asylum did Batman well. We are just popped right into the story, Batman is taking Joker into Arkham and he meets Commissioner Gordon. No explanation on how these people know each other because we are expected to have rudimentary knowledge of the characters. Imagine if every Sherlock Holmes movie started with the day he got addicted to coke and became a detective. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-26 16:18:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Is there any proof to artificial scarcity, or did they just underestimate demand. In the eighties, it was a bit more sensical, but all these games are readily available and easy to torrent. I don't think they gain anything by shorting demand. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-26 16:04:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  can find a lot more to enjoy in the rival philosophies made manifest by our "heroes."

The rival philosophies are shallow and the ending doesn't make narrative sense. If people were afraid Dr. Manhattan was an American super weapon, pinning the blame of the deaths of a million people is going to make people trust the US less, not more. The domestic attacks will be written off as a false flag attack. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-26 16:00:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I don't think Xmen fits with other Marvel movie properties. In the comics the distinction between a mutant and an other superpowered being is flimsy at best. I think it would just shake up the narrative the wrong way in MCU. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Fifa: the video game that changed football </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-21 13:42:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
