<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject6703</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-07 05:52:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> okay </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-06 21:08:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That's not really trivia so much as an anecdote about something tangentially related. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-06 07:47:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Oh gross 0/10 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-06 07:41:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It is taking all of my willpower not to downvote you for that opinion. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-06 07:39:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Also Transformers had probably the worst line of dialogue I've ever heard.

"Where's your warrant?"

"**My face is my warrant**." </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-06 07:32:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> DELETE THIS COMMENT NOW, LEST YOUR COMMENT KARMA BE STRICKEN

Just kidding, but seriously. You seem like a reasonable person so that probably doesn't matter to you. A while ago I made the mistake of saying Fury Road was cool but not some revolutionary movie like this sub makes it out to be, and for three fucking days I had people telling me I'm retarded and illiterate in film. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-06 07:29:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Literally every time I come here.

I feel like most comments are either extremely pretentious and douchey or have the credibility of saying "I think Transformers 4 is objectively the best movie ever created". Yeah, a lot of you guys have really great and insightful things to add, but that seems like the minority. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-04 21:08:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I've been watching it lately and everyone can suck it, it's fucking good. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-04 21:02:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The part with just Cap, Iron Man, and Bucky? I did like that part, but I think that was mostly static shots, right? Pretty hard to screw that up. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-04 07:16:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yes! Every time someone asks me why I didn't like CW all that much I point to the action sequences looking terrible, and they don't understand why that would be a big deal.

I mean there were other flaws in the movie, but that one bugged me the most. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-04 05:22:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> https://youtu.be/PaWXgCsrS4Y?t=59s </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-03 08:57:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm a horror fan as well as a western fan. We have a ton of great and original western movies, even in the past few years, long after westerns have seemed to fall out of favor.

However, we don't get a lot of good horror movies, let alone original ones. This movie, though, other than being great, was so...unexpected? I really did not see the movie going the way it did. They way the action just started so abruptly, and then just got so insane so quickly, felt perfect for the movie. Not a lot of movies do it that way. Also, the characters who survived weren't the ones I expected to, and really just the way everything ended up didn't seem contrived at all.

So personally, I'm glad we had a great horror movie, rather than a great western, because great horror movies are more rare, especially nowadays. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-03 08:44:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This is the most oddly and satisfyingly positive and understanding comment thread I've seen in a while. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-03 08:34:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I thought Live Die Repeat was just the tagline? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-03 08:16:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Wait, how do they know the walkie-talkies are stolen? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-02 23:24:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> lol </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-01 08:19:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [INVESTIGATE 3/11](https://youtu.be/SVhme1eb8SI?t=1m43s) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-01 08:13:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> And? It's still ironic that you chose "God's work" to give props to a post criticizing religion. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-01 08:10:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I thought Shaak-Ti died in Ep. 3? I know that one deleted scene isn't canon but isn't it heavily implied that Anakin kills her right before all the younglings? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-01 08:06:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Have you heard the good news of the de-specialized editions? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-30 19:47:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> And? At least they kind of fit together. Fury Road changed Max's age, his kid, had no mention of his wife, and had all those mutants and stuff, whereas the only thing really similar in the other movies was Master Blaster, and even that's a stretch. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-30 19:45:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The Lion King is one of my favorite movies, but it was never *that* sad to me, I don't know why. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-30 19:39:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  criticizes the prevalence of religion

 God's work

lol </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-30 19:24:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I frequent both /r/music and /r/books. /r/music is definitely just a bunch of elitists who hate pop music unless it came out 25 years ago, jerking each other off about musical tastes. /r/books is actually really weird because it's probably the only subreddit I go to often where the users aren't constantly shitting on each other's likes and dislikes. I think its because a smaller crowd of people like reading books than watching movies and listening to music, so there's already some kind of elitism inherent in being there. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-30 09:09:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Nice try boy, but you can still fuck off. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-30 09:08:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> lol </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-30 08:18:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> No question, just wanted to say I love the Fix and please keep it up. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-30 08:14:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah, I disagree. What was so revolutionary about the movie? Special effects, emphasis on action, minimal plot, strong female characters, saying "fuck the timeline/canon/almost everything the other movies established"?

Because I've seen those in plenty of other movies. Except maybe that last one. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-30 08:10:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I didn't mind any of this...until the prequel trilogy.

Please seek help. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-30 08:00:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Fox and the Hound.

Has to be one of the saddest movies I've ever seen.

Runner up, the Iron Giant. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-30 08:00:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> People always disagree when I say that movie isn't a total comedy but that is one of my favorite dramatic scenes in film. It's so relatable, well acted, and unexpected. Damn it now I need to go watch it on youtube. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-30 07:53:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> On my list of best movies of 2015, it ranks only behind Band of Robbers, TFA, The Revenant, and It Follows.

Still think this movie is way overrated. Guys, it's good, great even, but chill out, it wasn't this revolutionary movie like you're all making it out to be. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-30 07:46:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I've never heard of that last one, but if its one of those shitty parodies that people are saying it is, it seems a little late. The last Taken movie came out early last year, I think. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-30 07:44:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Oh God I think it has to be a tie between the new Daniel Wan movie (surprise it's another Daniel Wan movie about a fucking haunting who could have guessed it, also he stole that opening "scare" from a short film) and Absolutely Fabulous: the Movie (Jesus Christ). I saw the trailer for that today and I've never said this about anything else, but I think that trailer gave me cancer.

Holy fuck, that was worse than the trailer for Hologram for the King. I almost walked out of Neon Demon because I couldn't stand that trailer anymore. No, I'm changing my answer to just that one. The James Wan one still looks terrible, but at least it just made me dislike him even more. But Absolutely Fabulous: The Trailer just made me hate some people I've never even heard of, and I don't know who to aim these emotions at because I don't know who deserves it and I am sure as hell not going to look it up.

Shit now I'm upset just thinking about it.

Edit: Okay I guess neither of these movies are really in production but they're not out yet so I'm leaving this comment here. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-29 00:29:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm going to watch the movie tomorrow. Should I watch this before or after the movie? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-28 05:31:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Bruce Campbell

Maika Monroe

Hannibal Burress

Sam Rockwell </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-28 05:19:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I read the reason this movie scored so low was because it was too highbrow to appeal to "idiots and kids", but too lowbrow to appeal to "mature audiences". </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-28 05:16:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That movie has probably the most accurate depiction of "the future" of any movie I've ever seen, barring Terminator 2. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-28 05:09:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The speech from Heat. It's in almost every heist movie post-Heat. I don't know how many actual bank robbers use those lines, but it's not even close to the relative amount used in movies. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-27 17:28:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Great movie, or greatest movie? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-26 20:22:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I liked it, but I haven't seen it in years. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-26 05:06:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Except he only kills one dude and that's by accident. The rest of the fighting is him in defense mode. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-26 03:58:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Have you seen First Blood? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-26 03:56:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's fine if you like to hate Marvel movies, no one is going to judge you for it, stop trying to discredit the franchise because its not high art. These movies are made to make billions of dollars and sell lots of toys and merchandise to children. I hardly think these movies can't be anything more than that, though. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-26 03:52:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This title. It hurts me. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-26 03:48:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This is crazy to me. I thought I was getting Army of Two: The Movie, but it was mostly some potheads who do stupid stuff for pretty stupid reasons. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-26 03:46:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Vantage Point is perfect for this. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-25 20:18:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Life Pro Tip: Try to let air flow in and out of your lungs regularly so you don't fucking die. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-20 09:19:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm legitimately surprised this is my first time seeing Nate here. I love this stuff. The Learning About Dogs and Bad Boy Teenager Club videos are my favorites. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-20 05:21:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I have no idea how people do that. Like how do they even know where/when the last one happened? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-20 04:03:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What kind of sick bastard hangs a bird? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-20 03:55:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> TIL I've committed a ton of felonies against my friends. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-20 03:50:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That movie has so many stupid cameos. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-20 03:45:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Can confirm, momentum is very useful. I do stupid voices and accents a lot, and sometimes I'll lose one for a while (if not permanently) if I don't keep it going continuously. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-20 02:59:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Shit dude I'm 18 and most of my friends are trying to see it opening weekend. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-20 01:43:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I really hope this guy keeps this up, I'm loving these videos. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-20 01:29:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This is pretty much the first Inhumans story I've kept up with, and I love it. Reader is one of my new favorites, I think. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-20 01:14:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Why did you do this to me </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-18 06:01:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> In the comic that you buy to support the writer and artists. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-18 04:30:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That's what I thought. I've been saying that a lot but no one usually agrees with me, so this makes me happy. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-18 03:49:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I know this is a joke, but Marvel just got Ewing to give every book a direction and define exactly what the effects of the incursions were, they'd be golden. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-18 03:46:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  Stop liking what I don't like

Would you prefer Marvel not have any diversity and only sell X-Men, Avengers, and Spider-Man?

That's fucking stupid. The more books coming out, the more choice we have as to what we read. Uncanny Inhumans is great, and this is coming from someone who doesn't read Inhumans. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-18 03:43:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What do you mean generic house art? I've never heard that before. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-18 03:34:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Holy fuck how have I never noticed that A Bug's Life is Seven Samurai. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-18 03:28:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That first one pisses me off so much. I know it's not a movie but I really liked the Baird/Sam relationship in Gears of War 3.

They start out insulting each other and its kind of vague whether they actually hate each other or if its just friendly insults but it seems more like the former. Then the bridge explodes and she catches his arm and saves him from falling to his death.

"I suppose you want me to say I've always loved you. But I don't. I really, **really** don't."

By the end of the game they're a little friendlier, but there's no indication of romance and they still insult each other. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-18 03:20:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Actually I think a real love triangle like you explain here would be a lot more interesting. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-18 02:32:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You're right, my bad. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-16 00:45:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Holy shit this is awesome. Especially now that BB doesn't really have to deal with the rest of the Inhumans. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-15 06:08:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The theme is by far my favorite part about this movie. I don't think I can say that for any other movie. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-15 05:44:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Can you imagine if 5-10 minutes into Homecoming, Peter gets killed, and then we're introduced to Miles as the hero of the movie?

No one would see it coming. It would be one of the most surprising movie plot twists ever. I would shit myself. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-14 22:33:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> THEY'RE TAUNTING US THEY KNOW WE WANTED HIM TO BE SPIDER-MAN </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-13 21:54:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If its any consolation, you're still better looking than me. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-13 21:51:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I (probably) don't know your husband so I can't speak for him personally, but I don't think most guys are going to be upset if you're masturbating in front of them. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-13 21:39:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  social anarchism

 literal communist

Pick one. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-13 09:11:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I doubt they would have such a new character get her own movie. Most people outside of comic fans wouldn't know who she is at all, and her being a Muslim wouldn't sell very well in the US right now probably. Not saying that's right, I'm just being realistic. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-13 09:04:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Is that second image CGI? Her face looks fake. I haven't seen BvS yet, so I might be missing something. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-13 07:12:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Well this isn't funny at all. I am just sad. Why have you done this to me. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-13 07:00:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That's what I was hoping, thanks! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-13 06:06:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> *solidarity* </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-13 05:50:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> No, [Banjo Gyro](https://www.reddit.com/r/DeepIntoYouTube/comments/1ie593/banjo_gyro_honestly_the_deepest_ive_ever_been_so/). </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-13 05:49:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I didn't see this reply for some reason so I spent like four hours looking for it the other night, to no avail. Thank you so much. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-13 05:46:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Does this really matter though? If you really care about the news, you're probably not relying on facebook to get it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Can someone give me a recommended reading order for the whole Mutants vs Inhumans thing that was (maybe still is) going on for a while? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-08 02:55:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I stopped reading anything current quite a while ago but now I'm back on board. I read two recent-ish issues, Civil War II #1 and Uncanny X-Men #1. Civil War says something about the mutants and inhumans having a beef (though maybe this is a longstanding thing, I've never been too into either), and in the X-Men issue, they talk about the terrigen mists killing most of the mutants?

Is there a series that follows/explains the beginning of this? I'm kind of lost and it seems really interesting. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Anyone have any ideas for a argumentative thesis, based on at least a couple books? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-16 02:48:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> How much harder would it be do do a "pacifist" run on survival mode? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-15 03:39:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I've been considering this for a few days, and I really want to try it. I think I'd mostly do Sneak and Charisma, and probably join the the railroad (I'll let my companions do all the necessary killing). Impossible? Or just really, really hard? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What should my group do after prom? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-06 02:07:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> My prom is downtown on Saturday, and ends around 11. Right now, my group is thinking about going to see a movie afterwards, but that's not a very memorable after-prom activity. We like adventurous stuff but most stuff will be closed. Also, there's no good parties, so that's out.

Any ideas? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [Video] My friends and I made a Macbeth "movie" for an AP English project. It's pretty terrible, you should watch it. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-05 03:24:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Best place to buy a suit/tux around Salem </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-30 01:18:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> My prom is next week and I totally spaced on renting a tux. At this point, due to the rush fees I would have to pay to rent a tux, it won't be much more to just buy one. Anyone know where the best place to do this is? I'm looking for something relatively inexpensive but not shoddy.

And can anyone recommend a tailor? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Headphones won't fit in the jack (already tried digging it out, not working). Any ideas? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-18 07:01:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's an iPod touch 3(I think). Headphones fit about halfway into the jack, and won't find all the way in. I've tried pushing really hard, and I've tried digging out lint with a safety pin. I've gotten tiny bits of fuzz out but nothing substantial. I can't see what's inside at all. I'm going to try compressed air tomorrow but I doubt that will work. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [TOMT] [Movie] Late 80s/early 90s movie set in a poor LA neighborhood (I think). sort of like Friday, Do the Right Thing, and Boys in the Hood. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-12 06:35:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> For the life of me, all I can remember is the setting, but I know it's a movie I really liked when I saw it years ago. I think it might have been set over the course of one day but I might be mixing it up with Friday or DtRT. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [Discussion] Some issues aren't showing up on Midtown Comics and TFAW, anyone know why? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-01 04:51:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm trying to buy some comics on line for the first time (kind of) and I'm having difficulties. Some just won't show up. For example, I'm trying to get Paper Girls #4 and 5. However, when I search "paper girls" on TFAW, the only results are the TPB, #3, #5, and #6. If the other are just out of stock, I feel like it would say so.


Same goes for Midtown. TP, and 1,2,3, and 6. I know Midtown does still show out of stock issues, so I don't know why some aren't popping up at all.


Anyone know what this is? I guess I could be doing something wrong but I don't know what that could be. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> How much do you spend on comics a month? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-16 03:18:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm setting up a pull list for the first time (normally I just go in and grab my books) and I'm looking at several new series. I did the math and holy shit, it's a lot more than I'm used to. So, what do you spend on average per month? Mostly I mean on your pull list but back stock and trades I guess, too.

Edit: Welp, I guess I'm not in too bad a shape after all. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Is there a good explanation of Secret Wars for someone kind of new to Marvel? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-11 06:53:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I want to get into a few current Marvel series but I feel like I should know what happened with Secret Wars. Most of the stuff I've googled is either from before the event, during the event, or afterwards but with very little useful information. My current understanding is for some reason all of the universes got together and fought or something, and now they're all jumbled but it's also kinda like the New 52 reboot or something, but apparently that's incorrect.

I'm looking for a summary, the big changes, and the meta stuff like how it's going to affect my reading (if at all). Anyone know somewhere I can find all this stuff? Or, would anyone be kind enough to explain it here? Sorry, I know this must seem really lazy but I'm struggling a bit.

Edit: By extension, if there are any really good arcs I should read, I could use some pointers. I don't have a ton of excess cash right now so I can't read a lot, but I could probably get one or two series if they're necessary. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Anyone know of any current "one story per issue" kind of series? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-04 06:29:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Like Warren Ellis' Fell or silver/golden age comics (that I've read, this might not be the case I guess), where there is maybe an overlying storyline but each individual issue is usually a one shot sorta deal. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Do you think teachers ever masturbate to the thought of students? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-02 04:27:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I don't know I just thought about this today. Opinions? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> How do you shop for back issues? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-28 09:48:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I love browsing through comic shops, but I've never really got the concept of getting the old back issues. Like what are the odds of finding something from a series you're collecting? Or is it not about that? I don't know, it just seems like the chances of finding something relevant to you is pretty low. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Is there a reason I get put on bad teams, or is it just bad luck? (Not a rant I promise) </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-25 07:27:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I've been playing for a couple of days now, and I'm *okay*. So I'm not greatest or anything, but I'm not the worst, either. However, the last probably 15 or so matches (more before that, but those weren't such huge streaks) I've played, my team got steamrolled. I'm not entirely devoid of blame because I'm not amazing at the game, but most of the time it's because either my teammates are incompetent to say the least, or the other team is Sofia Vergara-level stacked against us.

These aren't just regular losses, either. These are games where we might go the entire round without being able to leave the base. Even if it was just me being terrible, it wouldn't make sense that the entire fate of the game should rest on my skill. That might be cause for loss in a close game, but these aren't close games.

I'm not complaining right now, I'm just trying to show that I've thought this out and I'm not a whiny little turd. Is there some system I don't know about that puts players together of similar skill levels? It's not even ranked play. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> How important do you think an author's "voice" is? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-16 05:47:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I've been writing a lot lately (mostly just as a hobby, I'm not planning on trying to publish anything) and it's got me thinking about the voices of different authors. It seems that most popular authors develop way of writing and stick to it. James Joyce used super complex language that makes it really difficult to read, whereas Hunter S. Thompson wrote news in a really personal way. Both of those contributed hugely to their voices.

So, as the title asks, how important is the author's voice? If it's nothing particularly interesting, how does that affect your enjoyment of the book? And how much would it affect your opinion of, let's say, your favorite author, if they changed their voice drastically from book to book (assuming it would stay at a consistent level of quality)? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Are amazon reviews to be trusted? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-03 20:17:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> In regards to speakers, turntables, etc. Is the average person knowledgeable enough to buy something or will I need to check reviews elsewhere? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [Need recommendations] What are some good, recently started series for me to get into? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-11-30 01:29:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I want to start reading current series but I'm not big on DC or Marvel, or really anything with a large shared universe. I started Papergirls recently, but that's about it.

Preferably nothing more than 2 or 3 months old because I hate buying multiple books of the same title at once. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [Question] There is an "Absolute" edition of Preacher coming out next year. Is that going to contain all of Preacher? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-11-29 09:28:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [The book in question.](http://www.amazon.com/Absolute-Preacher-Vol-Garth-Ennis/dp/1401264417/ref=sr_1_3?s=books ie=UTF8 qid=1448785117 sr=1-3 keywords=preacher+omnibus)

I thought Absolute editions was like DC's hardcover version of trades, but this thing is 736 pages long. I don't know if that would encompass the whole thing, because Preacher seems longer than that. Also, it says volume 1 but I'm holding out hope that it is the whole thing and even as I type this I realize I think I already know the answer Goddamn it.

I'm going to post this anyway and hope someone gives me an answer I like.

Sorry if this is obvious but I can't find much info on this online as it comes out in 8 months.

But, if it is the whole series, holy shit I'm excited. I've been holding off on buying my own copies (I loved the series when I borrowed it from a friend) because I figured they would re-release the trades for the show, but if I can buy the whole thing together, that's even better. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [TOMT][song] Nathaniel Rateliff and the Night Sweats' S.O.B. sounds a lot like an old song I know. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-11-18 06:32:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This song reminds me of an old rock and roll or country song (can't remember exactly) that (I'm totally guessing here) probably came out in the 40s or 50s.

https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=1iAYhQsQhSY

The background singers and parts of the guitar riff are making me think of the song and this is driving me crazy holy shit. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Any fun things for teenagers to do in the larger Salem area? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-09-09 04:44:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Lately I've had the hankering to do stuff. Normally when I'm with friends we just browse through record shops or go to Get Air or something. But I'm only going to be a kid for a little while longer (I'm 18 and just started my senior year) and I want some cool stories to tell when I'm older.

I remember there being a creepy old abandoned asylum or factory or something that my sister used to talk about sneaking into, but I don't remember what it was. That's the kind of stuff I'm looking for. Something maybe a little bit adventurous, or even slightly dangerous. The kind of things most adults don't do. Or maybe even something like really cheap concerts like those couple dollar admission house shows like I used to see in Portland. Something unique, I guess.

If it matters, we're not really into drugs. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Did anyone recognize the car Dre drives at the beginning of Straight Outta Compton? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-08-25 23:17:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Sorry if this isn't the place for this question, but I didn't find a more relevant subreddit and I couldn't find the answer elsewhere.

At the beginning of SOC, Dre drives a car for one or two scenes. Not the Ferrari later on. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Just watched the Horde, what the fuck was with the end? [spoilers] </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-08-25 08:33:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Okay, so up until the end, I was really liking the movie, mostly. I really didn't like Bola and Aurore, but I figured they would die pretty quickly so I wouldn't have to tolerate them too long. Then she pulled the gun on the one guy and killed him for defending himself(?). Then later on she says something rude about the main guy (sorry, the names are hard to remember), and the "antagonist" is like he just saved us, be grateful. She replies "I don't care." What the fuck? Why? It doesn't make any sense! He insulted her, what, once? And to top it off, she fucking executes the last guy because he did something bad BEFORE THE FUCKING APOCALYPSE. I'm all for revenge but he helped her multiple times, and he probably wasn't even the one who killed the guy anyway. Why! Why is she the lone survivor? She wasn't even a main character until the last half hour, and she didn't really do anything that would put her in the spotlight other than be a woman. Oh, sorry, I forgot, if there's one woman, she has to survive no matter how shitty of a character she is.

This leads to my bigger gripe which is horror movies being predictable, especially with who lives and dies (either pretty much no one in ghost movies or everyone except the innocent one in slasher movies), which effectively kills the scariness. It's not scary if you know what's going to happen, is it? Anyway, that's another post for another day. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
