<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject6512</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-29 00:21:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> My advice:

- Free Reddit ads through /r/subredditads
- crossposting to other subs with [x-post /r/europes] in the title. This makes others aware this subreddit exists.
- You, a mod, or anyone who cares about this sub: Commit yourself to submitting something every day or every few days. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-28 17:23:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> #Submission statement

I value privacy. Pseudonymity and anonymity are a valuable tool to protect your privacy. Privacy is about incremental choices, choosing what to reveal, and whom you reveal it to.  
Anonymity often gets a bad rap online. This research shows, or may indicate, that it's not all bad. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-27 16:18:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Downright terrifying. A direct threat to personal freedom. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-25 17:02:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This is a repost

Apologies. Reddit did not give its usual warning that the URL had already been submitted to this sub. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-24 16:54:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  The more peaceful the world becomes, the more we will notice violent events.

This goes alongside the changes to our news cycle. In the (distant) past, we wouldn't have learned about attacks in real time. Or only in a short update on the hour. Usually it was the morning after, when the morning paper hit your doorstep. By that time, most of your questions would have been answered, and the event would be presented with a context.  
  
Now, we hear about events instantly. No answers, no context, just questions and uncertainty. For hours. During those hours we are left to imagine the most horrible things. People fill the void with their imagination, or the imagination of others. Or rumor and opinions of people trying to use the uncertainty to their benefit.  
  
By the time vital facts roll in, you're already shocked and saturated. And because the facts and context aren't presented at the moment you learn of an attack, you are less likely to spend time consuming the facts. Especially because the next Sensational Event pops up into your news and social feeds.

Or at least, that's the rough theory knocking about in my head. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-24 16:40:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If you think that's what all of us are like, you don't know us very well.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-24 00:03:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What you're witnessing here is the result of Stockholm Syndrome. After the fact justification for sitting through all seasons. It started out interesting, but it kinda got out of control. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-23 16:43:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I would like to see this integrated into a face mask. That way you can block ads and block real life tracking through surveillance (and facial recognition). </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-23 14:55:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The one thing he's almost completely lost due to his fame, and can't buy with the fortune that came along with it, is privacy. I'm pleasantly surprised that he's connecting this common celebrity problem to the general loss of privacy everyone is starting to experience. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-23 03:25:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Then there's the scenario of Russia v Europe spiraling further out of control, bringer the nuclear threat from superpowers back to the foreground. I fear that a Cuban missile crisis-like scenario with Trump at the helm would not end well for humanity. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-22 16:21:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This American Life's latest episode has a segment on LL Bean's return policy:
http://www.thisamericanlife.org/radio-archives/episode/591/get-your-moneys-worth?act=2#play </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-22 04:33:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I like how request_bot lists itself as an active moderator. For all we know, *all* of these mods are bots. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-21 03:39:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  A business running Windows 10 can set up their own security policies though, right? The data collection is most likely going to be an issue for your everyday consumer, not a business.

Exactly, so the users with the least power are getting screwed the most.

If you are choosing to give away your data, you are choosing to give up your rights, just like if I allow the police into my house without a warrant.

No, I don't. Businesses are subject to data protection laws. Any identifiable data they collect - and almost any data is (re)identifiable, they are obligated to protect.

 good luck relying on the government to efficiently protect you

It's not my only strategy, but it is one of them. I do what I can to protect myself, while helping the government to better protect us.   Through successful lobbying and campaigning we've managed to get a pretty decent [General Data Protection Regulation](https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/General_Data_Protection_Regulation) in the EU, which goes into effect next year. Similar regulations in different sectors have lead to similar laws in other countries. I'm confident it will impact U.S. regulations in a positive manner in the decade to come. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-21 03:01:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> There are a lot of problems with that belief, some of which I'll address.

1) Humans have the Human Right to Privacy. No EULA can take that away from them.  
2) Different countries, different cultures, different laws. What may be seen as acceptable in the U.S., where anti-government sentiments are more common than in France, may not be viewed the same in countries such as France.  
3) Microsoft's primary customers for Windows - the ones who are actually paying for this - are businesses. They buy the operating system in bulk, slap it on their corporate devices, and their staff uses it. Individual, private persons are almost inconsequential to Microsoft, and they won't notice you not giving them your business. This is also why several opt-outs are only available for the more expensive, business versions of the OS.  
4) Individuals don't have the power to protect their human and constitutional rights from multinationals. Especially in societies that are less litigational than the U.S.. And especially for users who don't live in the same country as the HQ of the multinational.  
5) The majority of the users don't understand or aren't aware of any privacy infringements, let alone how they work and why it is a threat to their privacy. They just see "free upgrade", or they buy a laptop that looks nice or is cheapest. We've given the power to our governments to sometimes protect those who can't protect themselves. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-21 02:14:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Just for fun: 

Look at the comments on the [/r/Windows10 thread](https://www.reddit.com/r/Windows10/comments/4tt2lc/french_dpa_to_microsoft_on_windows_10_in_formal/) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-21 02:12:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> They've also hidden the opt-outs that do exist in their 'Express install'. They're only available in the Advanced installation menu.
It's all designed to screw those who don't know enough or aren't smart enough to protect themselves.

Really glad the EU and its member states are taking privacy more seriously than the U.S. government does. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-21 00:22:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thanks for that, but the original post is in /r/europrivacy :) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-19 12:34:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> https://imgur.com/A7cfSbL </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-19 11:46:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Page 1: https://archive.is/9fXRw

Page 2: https://archive.is/15OAi </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-19 11:31:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [Direct link to the transparency report, broken down by country.](https://www.google.com/transparencyreport/userdatarequests/countries/) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-19 11:26:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That explains the downvotes; If it's not on the front page, it's not reality, right? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-19 01:00:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The difference between this and bias, is that these are facts. Indisputable facts, which HuffPo backs up by linking the claims to the evidence backing it up.  
  
And as with everything, there is a history that lead to that Editor's Note. In reverse chronological order: 
  
- [HuffPost to publish anti-Trump kicker with all Trump coverage](http://www.politico.com/blogs/on-media/2016/01/huffpost-to-publish-anti-trump-kicker-with-all-trump-coverage-218345)
- [A Note on Trump: We Are No Longer Entertained](http://www.huffingtonpost.com/arianna-huffington/a-note-on-trump_b_8744476.html) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-18 23:19:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I really like Firefox, but it practically breaks down if I have more than 15 or 20 tabs open. It needs far more system resources than Chrome to perform the same tasks.  
  
I should clarify: I'm talking about the desktop client. The mobile client does well even with _hundreds_ of tabs. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-18 21:41:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> How are they acquiring this browsing data? Is it one of the following?

- People who sign into Chrome
- People who use opt-out services, like:
 - "Use a web service to help resolve navigation errors"
 - "Use a prediction service to help complete searches and URLs typed into the address bar or the app launcher search box"
 - "Use a prediction service to load pages more quickly"
 - "Automatically report details of possible security incidents to Google"
 - "Protect you and your device from dangerous sites"
 - "Automatically send usage statistics and crash reports to Google"

Or are they collecting this data from _everyone_ who uses Chrome, even those who take care to opt out of the above-listed services? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-18 18:21:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [Repost ;)](https://www.reddit.com/r/europrivacy/comments/4stdhr/britain_has_a_new_snooperinchief/)
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-17 22:37:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Contact your local (city) government. They will be able to tell you. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-16 17:34:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  like this man?

Nobody said they couldn't be. I was referring to the 'man' in /u/temporarilyyours their reply, and they were referring to the man who owns the house in the picture. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-16 17:16:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Assume his identity and kill him. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-16 14:22:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Couldn't agree more! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-16 00:46:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You would probably be better off using a search engine to find information in your native language, as it's not an easy subject.  
  
This information is in English, but it might help you to understand what net neutrality is and why it matters:

- https://www.savetheinternet.eu/en/faq/#what-is-net-neutrality
- https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=p90McT24Z6w
- http://www.dummies.com/how-to/content/understanding-net-neutrality.html </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-16 00:31:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Could you be more specific? Do you want to know what net neutrality is?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-16 00:13:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> http://arstechnica.com/tech-policy/2016/01/dutch-government-encryption-good-backdoors-bad/ </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-16 00:06:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> English-language article: http://www.theverge.com/2016/7/15/12197152/net-neutrality-europe-tim-berners-lee-letter

Sir Berners-Lee's letter:
http://webfoundation.org/2016/07/four-days-to-save-the-open-internet-in-europe-an-open-letter/ </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-14 01:48:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Off with your head! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-14 01:20:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> He was singing, not whistling. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-13 19:52:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If the network is watching this subreddit, reporting which number your hoodie has will tie your Reddit username to your postal address and (possibly) your real name. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-13 16:28:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> And if a nation state is in your threat model, you may want to start buying your hardware in person instead of having it shipped: http://www.forbes.com/sites/erikkain/2013/12/29/report-nsa-intercepting-laptops-ordered-online-installing-spyware/#3a97259354ae

Alternative URL because Forbes sucks: https://archive.is/9eAUk </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-13 03:46:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Agreed. Major improvements in the last ten to fifteen years. Much higher quality, and architects are no longer ashamed to look at the past and use that which has stood the test of time. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-12 23:43:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> There are 360-degree photos available as well: http://www.funda.nl/koop/zaandam/huis-49810871-czaar-peterstraat-79/#360-foto-foto1 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-12 17:58:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That doesn't necessarily disprove that migrants aren't responsible for more crime. It could mean that they are disproportionately targeted by police, for example.

Just look at the U.S. and the disproportionate incarceration of young black men. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-12 15:48:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Related:

- [Privacy Shield: The new EU rules on transatlantic data sharing will not protect you | by Jan Albrecht   Max Schrems](https://www.reddit.com/r/europrivacy/comments/4sgqsk/privacy_shield_the_new_eu_rules_on_transatlantic/)
- [EU-US Privacy Shield now officially adopted but criticisms linger](https://techcrunch.com/2016/07/12/eu-us-privacy-shield-now-officially-adopted-but-criticisms-linger/) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-12 14:45:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Same story on TorrentFreak:  
https://torrentfreak.com/vpn-provider-pia-exits-russia-server-seizures-160712/ </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-12 04:27:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I kinda do, although the feeling is more related to its limited size than the population density. I've hiked for days without seeing much sign of civilization in the UK. Here you find (perfectly designed, well-kept, and clean) bike paths, roads, villages, etc. within a few hours walk in any direction.  
  
And that's also what has spoiled me: The design and level of quality of public infrastructure is generally high. Going to almost any other country means settling for less. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-12 04:00:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  (eg, All Lives Matter)

There was a good ELI5 regarding ALM versus BLM a while back:
https://www.reddit.com/r/explainlikeimfive/comments/3du1qm/eli5_why_is_it_so_controversial_when_someone_says/ </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-12 01:17:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Talked to some of the mods of /r/journalism. They seem to welcome and even prefer submissions like these on that sub. You may get more responses there, as that sub has more than 1 subscriber ;) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-11 23:55:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> EU price check, please.  
  
Brand: Olivetti  
Model: KBD 2811  
Layout: ANSI  
FCC ID: GDD5YOG81-300  
Key caps: Dyesub, black legends, Cherry MX compatible   
Switches : Vintage Cherry MY Blacks, with black stem  
Condition: Mint or near mint.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-11 22:14:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Relevant reading:  
  
- https://decorrespondent.nl/4401/Time-for-the-facts-What-do-we-know-about-Cologne-four-months-later-/1073698080444-e20ada1b
- https://decorrespondent.nl/4406/Minute-by-minute-This-is-what-happened-in-Cologne-on-New-Years-Eve/1078757391184-66dd7a56 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-11 22:09:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Not to mention that they're creating one of the largest databases of location data ever.

Sure, there's Ingress, but this collection is (becoming) much larger.

- https://www.buzzfeed.com/josephbernstein/heres-all-the-data-pokemon-go-is-collecting-from-your-phone
- http://blackbag.gawker.com/pokemon-go-is-a-government-surveillance-psyop-conspirac-1783461240
- https://www.theguardian.com/technology/2016/jul/10/pokemon-go-armed-robbers-dead-body

^edit: ^removed ^a ^redundant ^word </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-11 19:31:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Resubmitted because the actual title assumes that 'renditioning' can be 'rightful'. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-11 19:26:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Good point. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-11 18:22:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I've had it happen once or twice, but usually there is some kind of redirect set up. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-09 21:16:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If we can't convince those who do care about privacy and/or security to use Signal because they keep using Telegram, despite it being insecure, we won't convince anyone. User base needs to start somewhere. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-09 02:57:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Signal yes, Facebook's Messenger no. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-09 02:53:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Keep in mind that it is *not* E2E-encrypted by default, either on Messenger or Allo. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-09 02:52:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> http://gizmodo.com/why-you-should-stop-using-telegram-right-now-1782557415 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-09 02:48:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Read this: http://gizmodo.com/why-you-should-stop-using-telegram-right-now-1782557415 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-09 02:48:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> http://gizmodo.com/why-you-should-stop-using-telegram-right-now-1782557415 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-09 02:47:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You would notice this in Signal, as the fingerprints would change, and the app would let you know this change occurred. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-09 02:45:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> http://gizmodo.com/why-you-should-stop-using-telegram-right-now-1782557415 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-08 20:26:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> They don't have to change completely. They can use several messenger apps concurrently. One for you (Signal) and one for others. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-08 18:42:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You are ignoring that I've refuted your claim.  
  
They are not discarded as you claimed, they are kept for 100 days.  
  
If you are active within those 100 days, it moves forward. IP addresses of active users are always known and kept. It's not like Reddit doesn't use logs IP logs.    
  
Go troll someone else. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-08 17:56:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> demonstrated a clear effort to use canaries, so we know what their position with leo is

One canary. We only know that something is happening which we don't know anything about. Warrant canaries only cover National Security Letters. We don't know anything about all other avenues. Now that the canary is dead, we won't know about any future NSLs either.
  
 I seem to distinctly remember them verifying these were discarded  
  
Not immediately:  
  
 One notable change is that we are increasing the number of days we store IP addresses from 90 to 100 [(source)](https://www.reddit.com/r/announcements/comments/3tlcil/we_are_updating_our_privacy_policy_effective_jan/)  
  
If you're not going to bother to back up your claims in the vain hope that I will rely on your memory, or bother to read the links I provide, I see no point in continuing this discussion. Have a nice day. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-08 17:21:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  they

Who?

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-08 17:15:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [This is what I could find](http://www.euractiv.com/section/digital/news/privacy-shield-agreement-signed-off-despite-vote-abstentions/):  
  
The Commission has vowed to review the new deal once every year.

One diplomat said the countries that abstained from the vote would be extremely vigilant during the review.

This is not just going to be a box-ticking exercise, this is going to be a very detailed and in-depth review. Only adjustments from the review can save this from the ECJ, the diplomat said.

It appears they're very skeptical of the new agreement. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-08 17:11:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  if this username is never connected to your personal identity  
  
That is a very big if. It already is tied to identity through users' IP addressess, e-mail addresses, etc. Not everyone uses disposable e-mails, pseudonyms, VPNs or Tor. And people may use the same username across a variety of sites and services.  
  
We know that Reddit collects this information. What we don't know is how they will use this information in the future. Will they auction it off when they go bankrupt? Will they sell it to companies that combine data sets to (re)identify and profile people for targeting in marketing campaigns? Will they give access to law enforcement? Will Reddit be compromised and the be data copied? These are just a few examples.

- http://www.nytimes.com/2015/06/29/technology/when-a-company-goes-up-for-sale-in-many-cases-so-does-your-personal-data.html?_r=0
- http://www.theatlantic.com/technology/archive/2016/06/your-data-is-forever/485219/
- https://motherboard.vice.com/read/the-data-hoarders
- http://arstechnica.com/tech-policy/2009/09/your-secrets-live-online-in-databases-of-ruin/

If anyone doesn't understand the problems with this, it's you. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-08 17:00:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You are already sharing your data with a U.S. corporation right now: Reddit, Inc. Have you watched a YouTube video or used Google search lately? Bingo. Do you have a Facebook account? Do you use LinkedIn, Snapchat, WhatsApp, Android, any Apple device?  
  
Before the Privacy* Shield there was the Safe Harbour agreement.  The principles of this agreement were designed to prevent private organizations within the European Union or United States which store customer data from accidentally disclosing or losing personal information.  
  
The agreement was struck down by the European Court of Justice, because: "legislation permitting the public authorities to have access on a generalised basis to the content of electronic communications must be regarded as compromising the essence of the fundamental right to respect for private life"  
  
Suddenly, there was no legal way for U.S. companies to collect, transmit, or use data from people within the EU. Which is why negotiations started to create the Privacy Shield.  
  
The Privacy Shield is flawed, so it probably won't live long:  
  
Conclusions. Given the flawed premises  trying to fix data protection deficit in the U.S. by means of the Obama Administrations assurances as opposed to meaningful legislative reform  it is not surprising that the new Privacy Shield remains full of holes and offers limited protections.  
  
The coming days will likely see the adoption of this flawed text by the EU, but it is unlikely to be the final chapter of the EU-US data transfer saga. Because it fails to address the concerns expressed by the Court of Justice of the EU in the Schrems case last year, the new Privacy Shield is likely to be challenged in courts.  
  
Source: https://privacyinternational.org/node/889 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-08 13:58:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I don't know the greater why, and I hope someone will take the time to explain it. What I do know is that this agreement only needs the go-ahead from the EU member states. Any resolution by the European Parliament would be non-binding.  
  
And they have done just that. You can find the resolution [here](http://www.europarl.europa.eu/sides/getDoc.do?type=MOTION reference=P8-RC-2016-0623 language=EN) and the press release [here](http://www.europarl.europa.eu/news/en/news-room/20160524IPR28820/EU-US-%E2%80%9CPrivacy-Shield%E2%80%9D-for-data-transfers-further-improvements-needed-MEPs-say).

This offers some explanation, but it doesn't answer your question: https://www.euractiv.com/section/digital/news/meps-battle-to-get-their-vote-on-privacy-shield/ </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-08 13:11:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yes, some of us. Not all of us. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-08 13:09:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Your front page is sorted by an algorithm which decides which topics rise to the front page, how long they stay there, etc. If they better know your preferences, they will adjust this sorting to better suit your interests. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-08 13:08:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Your reading habit and interests is personal information. Just like our upvotes, it can be used to determine your political interests, among other things.  
The click-tracking is for *personalization*, which means that they register what we click down to the user level.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-08 13:06:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If you had bothered to read the post on /r/changelog, you would have seen the name of the opt-out checkbox: "allow reddit to log my outbound clicks for **personalization**"  
  
Also, they explain it here:  
https://np.reddit.com/r/changelog/comments/4rl5to/outbound_clicks_rollout_complete/d52s3mu </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-08 03:57:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You are right that it is a wrong analogy, but my goal was not to make a correct analogy. Or any analogy.  
  
 it's either 'be raped' or 'not be raped' (by opting out).

I'll bite. The correct way to look at it would be: Either everyone gets raped, or the precious few who know about the opt-out don't get raped, but everyone else will still get raped. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-08 03:56:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You are right that it is a wrong analogy, but my goal was not to make a correct analogy. Or any analogy. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-08 03:48:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> **How to opt out:**  

- Go to your [account preferences](https://www.reddit.com/prefs/)  
- Scroll down to "privacy options"  
- Uncheck the box that says: "allow reddit to log my outbound clicks for personalization"  
  
Related discussions on other subreddits: 
 
- [Thread on /r/Technology](https://www.reddit.com/r/technology/comments/4rpkt8/reddit_now_tracks_all_outbound_link_clicks_by/)  
- [Thread on /r/privacy](https://www.reddit.com/r/privacy/comments/4rm8ik/reddit_tracking_outbound_links_has_been_deployed/)   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-08 03:41:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  Be glad  
  
No. I could maybe get myself to be a little less angry and disappointed, though.  
  
I confirmed that it does not work as expected. I know I disabled tracking yesterday at work, and now clicked an article and found it used out.reddit.com tracking. Yet the other options I changed were retained. It's broken either by design or incompetence, so fuck 'em.  
  
Instead of lowering it, I'm going to go ahead and up my level anger. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-08 03:38:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> There actually is something to gain. I oppose this course of action, but they track your clicks to sort the content to suit your tastes. They want to create a happy little filter bubble for you.  
We've learned from Google and Facebook that users generally enjoy personalized environments.  
  
I wouldn't opt-in to that, because I'm very privacy-conscious. This also makes me highly aware of how many people are not, and how they prefer ease of use over pretty much anything. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-08 03:31:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Will you notify each user directly of this new infringement of* their privacy? Most users will never notice this update, or the threads linking here from other subs. How will they know they have the choice to opt out?  
  
If you fail to notify each user individually, your opt-out is meaningless. The opt-out only serves to defuse opposition to this change. It's privacy theatre. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-08 03:23:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> There's a [pretty active debate about this change](https://www.reddit.com/r/technology/comments/4rpkt8/reddit_now_tracks_all_outbound_link_clicks_by/) over on /r/Technology.  
  
[My humble contribution.](https://www.reddit.com/r/technology/comments/4rpkt8/reddit_now_tracks_all_outbound_link_clicks_by/d53mw0d?context=3) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-08 03:14:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yes, which was the point. I made it absurd, to make clear what you were saying. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-08 03:12:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> No. We already had more privacy. Thanks to this move we have less of it on Reddit. The opt-out is a pacifier. It serves only to give you the illusion of choice. Most users will never be aware of this change, or that the opt-out exists.  
Reddit used to not only value, but actively advertise their commitment to user privacy and transparency. Not anymore. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-08 03:09:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> snip here once stood an exaggeration that was mistaken for an analogy /snip
  
Few users will ever be aware of that opt-out, while Reddit chips away at their privacy. The opt-out is a pacifier, to elicit the exact reluctant acceptance you show. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-08 03:03:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Reddit, Inc. used to care about things like transparency and user privacy. You are looking at it from the outside, with a perspective influenced by how fucked up everyone else is.  
We are looking at it from a different perspective. We are worried about Reddit betraying values that brought and kept us here. *Two* of them, the transparency and user privacy I mentioned, are being violated by this action.  
Of all Reddit users, few will know /r/changelog exists. Some will see this post or similar ones on other subreddits. The majority of users won't know that Reddit has slid yet another few feet down the slippery slope of /r/privacy infringement.  
Those of us who do know can inform others, we can protest these actions, and we can prepare ourselves to try to stop Reddit from slipping further.  
We've got to take a /r/Stand some time and somewhere; It might as well be* now, and it might as well be Reddit. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-08 02:51:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> And all characters need to be the letter G. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-08 00:57:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Related thread in /r/technology: https://www.reddit.com/r/technology/comments/4rnxya/eu_telecoms_industry_well_update_our_networks_to/ </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-07 23:56:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm disappointed this has gathered so few votes in /r/europe. Thankfully /r/Technology picked up the slack. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-07 19:29:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The actual piece you were trying to submit is welcome on /r/europrivacy. Please submit it again with a direct link - no LinkedIn short url - and as a link post, not a text post. Thank you. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-07 19:00:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Don't the people from Mars still outnumber those from Venus on Reddit? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-07 17:13:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> to produce encryption keys **to decrypt all data on the Internet**.

I needed a good laugh. Thanks! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-07 16:04:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That's a matter of copyright, I believe, and not of privacy. But I'll add a disclaimer with that or similar text. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-07 15:37:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I haven't yet implemented flair, but you can add something like [Peer Review] or [Feedback Wanted] in the title, if you want :)  
  
Privacy protection for sources used in the submitted works, or the privacy of the submitter themselves?  
  
Content protection as in: "be aware that you could be ripped off / please don't rip people off"? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-07 15:35:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Mother Jones' Shane Bauer went undercover as a security guard in a private prison in the U.S.:

[My Four Months as a Private Prison Guard](http://www.motherjones.com/politics/2016/06/cca-executive-summary).

It's 35,000 words in total. Don't despair, there's a summary of his key findings: [Inside Shane Bauer's Gripping Look at the Workings of a Private Prison](http://www.motherjones.com/politics/2016/06/cca-executive-summary)

Margaret Sullivan, former public editor of The New York Times and now media columnist for WaPo, dedicated a column to the ethical problems that come with going undercover: [How Mother Jones went undercover to reveal ugly truths about for-profit prisons](https://www.washingtonpost.com/lifestyle/style/how-mother-jones-went-undercover-to-reveal-ugly-truths-about-for-profit-prisons/2016/07/03/014cafb2-3e0c-11e6-80bc-d06711fd2125_story.html?postshare=3091467585119747 tid=ss_tw)

This reminded me of a not so recent piece by MoJo: [I Was a Warehouse Wage Slave: My brief, backbreaking, rage-inducing, low-paying, dildo-packing time inside the online-shipping machine.](http://www.motherjones.com/politics/2012/02/mac-mcclelland-free-online-shipping-warehouses-labor) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-07 14:46:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Well, /r/JournalismSchool/ is now open for business :)  
  
Feel free to submit your work for review. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-07 13:18:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I didn't know this sub allowed gore. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-07 13:11:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Technically it's all information, there's just not a lot of useful information. 

I would argue that knowing that the minister responsible for data protection, who is expected to have access to all relevant and current information on the subject, can't say for certain which set of rules my business has to follow in less than a year is valuable information. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-07 05:02:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Have you found better alternative subs? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-07 01:38:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> encourage journalists to use those personal data access laws in the same way they would use Freedom of Information laws. 

That's a good idea.

Bits of Freedom built a tool called 'Privacy Inzage Machine' or [PIM](https://pim.bof.nl/) years ago, which helps people exercise that right in The Netherlands. It's lead to a few stories in the press over the years.

Rejo Zenger exercised the same right many times and wrote [several accounts](https://rejo.zenger.nl/tag/inzageverzoek/) based on the information he received. He later joined Bits of Freedom.  
  
[Dimitri Tokmetzis](https://twitter.com/tokmetzis) is another journalist that comes to mind who might be receptive of your efforts. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-06 23:52:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It reads like an interesting game of chess. Please keep us posted!  
  
Have any media contacted you about this chain of events? Have you sent out a press release?

I'm sure sites like http://arstechnica.co.uk and http://politico.eu would be interested working on this story, even if there might not be enough to publish yet. Maybe contact [Glyn Moody](https://twitter.com/) or [Chris Spillane](https://twitter.com/ChrisSpillane) or someone you're else you're comfortable with? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-06 23:33:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Check out /r/privacytoolsIO and their site https://privacytools.io </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-06 23:25:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Reminds me of this thread:  
https://www.reddit.com/r/privacy/comments/4q4nhk/fake_fingerprints_chinese_student_develops_rubber/ </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-06 23:23:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Or [LOVEINT](https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/LOVEINT) at the NSA:

http://arstechnica.com/tech-policy/2015/02/no-one-knows-what-happened-to-nsa-staffers-who-snooped-on-their-lovers/ </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-06 21:42:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> They're adding networked features because they can, or because the marketing department tells them to add them, while not realizing that you're also introducing an attack surface the size of the entire internet-connected world, along with many software vulnerabilities.  
  
It's just one of the many examples of the stupidity that is the [Internet of ~~Things~~ Shit](https://reddit.com/r/theinternetofshit) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-06 18:35:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thank you for letting us know :) Consider adding some links to back up your story? I saw you(?) provide a link in [a tweet](https://twitter.com/podehaye/status/750615731516112896), for example. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-06 01:57:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'll let you know when I have the basic things in order. I'm hoping I can get it done tomorrow :) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-05 23:38:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This story just got worse and worse as I kept reading. Messing around with the canary, then dodging questions about new app permissions? At the very least sloppy PR, but it looks like something worse. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-05 22:39:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> A takedown by one publication of another publication's shitty security/privacy guide. They were responding to this: https://www.theguardian.com/technology/2016/jul/03/online-security-measures-digital-privacy-guide </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-05 22:36:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I share your optimism that they will provide a greater physical safety. However, I don't believe society has put enough thought in what the transition from a human-driven car to a self-driving, always connected, always 'aware' car will do to our privacy.
~~3 or more~~ [four locations combined with when you are there](http://www.nature.com/articles/srep01376) is enough to fairly accurately identify an individual. If/when these cars phone home your trips to the psychiatrist, sex club, cancer ward, or fast food restaurants, that data would be *very* valuable. And it would make you vulnerable in other ways than you are now to the dangers of driving. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-05 20:43:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If someone could x-post this to /r/unitedkingdom, that would be awesome :) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-05 19:38:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I tried to start one here on Reddit. It didn't exactly take off straight away. If there are people here who'd like to try again, I'm willing to help.

Currently, I have the following subs registered:

- /r/JournalismReview (that's the one I tried to get off the ground)
- /r/JournalismSchool
- /r/SchoolOfJournalism

For some reason I have it in my head that a Reddit School of Journalism would be a fun community to have, especially as so many of the popular subs revolve around news. Media literacy is something many Redditors could use some help with...

TL;DR Sorry, I don't know any, but we can start one! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-05 19:08:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>   You must trust that the other party has enabled encryption on their device.

This is wrong. You cannot turn it on or off as a user, it's always on. The problem is that WhatsApp can switch E2E out for non-E2E, to help law enforcement for example, without you knowing it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-05 18:44:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Try Firefox for Android or iOS. It supports plug-ins like uBlock Origin and HTTPS Everywhere. Safer browsing with fewer annoyances :) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-05 18:02:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> There's a fourth downside to Whatsapp: You won't be able to see if/when they switch off e2e encryption on their side. You're essentially trusting them on their word that your conversations are encrypted.

Keeping that in mind, they do encrypt by default with a vetted protocol. For that reason, I would recommend it over Telegram for casual users.

Also, there's no reason why your audience can't install both WhatsApp and Signal, and just use what they can with whom they can. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-05 17:31:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Niks is onvermijdelijk.

Het zou inderdaad fijn zijn als jongeren weer meer gaan stemmen, maar omdat zij zich niet naar de stembus kunnen bewegen hoeven we toch niet het stemproces, en daarmee onze parlementaire democratie, op het spel te zetten?  

Digitaal stemmen tellen - offline - is al problematisch vergeleken met het proces wat we nu hebben. Niemand kan van buiten zien of de software in de telmachine betrouwbaar is. Om het te checken, moet je alsnog alles met de hand tellen.

Zodra we ons stemproces aan het internet hangen, vergroten we het aanvalsoppervlak tot het absolute; wil je het stemproces beinvloeden, dan hoef je als China, Rusland, of private partij niet meer een leger mannetjes en busjes op pad te sturen met nagemaakte stembiljetten. Je hoeft enkel een legertje hackers in te schakelen, die je al in dienst hebt, of kunt huren.
 Die hackers kunnen dan vanuit hun luie stoel, van over de hele wereld, het online stemsysteem benaderen.

Dan is er nog de insider threat. Iemand die bij de fabrikant werkt, binnenglipt, of daar de systemen weet te hacken, en zo hun invloed weten uit te oefenen.

Vrijwel iedereen kan met het blote oog controleren of de zaken gaan zoals ze moeten gaan in het stemlokaal. Er is zeer specialistische kennis en bijzondere toegang nodig om hetzelfde niveau van controle en transparantie te krijgen bij online stemmen.

En dit is nog maar een fractie van de problemen met online stemmen. Om een idee te krijgen van de vooralsnog onopgeloste problemen die er bestaan, raad ik je aan deze videos te bekijken:

- [Internet Voting? Really? | Andrew Appel | TEDxPrincetonU](https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=abQCqIbBBeM)
- [Barbara Simons: I can bank online, why can't I vote online?](https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=Wv3VuGZzdK8)
- [Security Analysis of Estonia's Internet Voting System [31c3] by J. Alex Halderman](https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=JY_pHvhE4os)

Het is wel mogelijk om iets anders te doen met internet om jongeren naar de stembus te krijgen. En manier voor de burger om zich meer betrokken te voelen de politiek is lid te worden van een partij. Politieke partijen en (toekomstige) leden moeten elkaar online gaan vinden.  Klinkt ouderwets, partijlidmaatschap, maar *daarmee* kun je invloed uitoefenen. *Daarmee* heb je de kans dat jouw standpunt daadwerkelijk in het partijprogramma terecht komt. En dan wordt de drempel om te gaan stemmen vanzelf lager, en de democratie juist robuuster. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-05 16:59:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Ik neem aan dat hij bedoelt dat er binnen de groep tot-levenslang-veroordeelden ook weer een verdeling valt te maken van kwaad to erger. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-05 15:47:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You shouldn't use, let alone recommend, Telegram. Even if it has certain features Signal doesn't.  
  
Some required reading:  
  
- http://gizmodo.com/why-you-should-stop-using-telegram-right-now-1782557415  
- http://mediashift.org/2016/06/why-telegrams-security-flaws-may-put-irans-journalists-at-risk/  
- https://motherboard.vice.com/read/encryption-app-telegram-probably-isnt-as-secure-for-terrorists-as-isis-thinks  
- http://www.theregister.co.uk/2015/11/23/homebrew_crypto_in_telegram_app/   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-05 15:05:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> With a name like that, this is totally gonna take off. /s

'most well designed'? Who sez? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-05 13:15:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Doctorow offers some additional comments on this column here: https://boingboing.net/2016/07/03/peak-indifference-privacy-as.html </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-05 03:11:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> 17 users and it was still going (annoyingly) strong. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-05 03:01:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  Telegram

Just FYI: http://gizmodo.com/why-you-should-stop-using-telegram-right-now-1782557415 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-05 03:00:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> A long time ago, in the old privacy   settings dashboard, I switched everything off. In this new overview, it shows nothing: https://i.imgur.com/Fb7tsBJ.png

I guess they're not officially tracking me in the five areas they mention. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-04 22:40:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I don't believe he has a clear political agenda. He is one reporter, covering one beat, and yes, he's being kind of one-sided, which is something that can happen when you specialize in covering a subject.

There should be a balance in the reporting on Al Jazeera, by having him *or other* reporters covering other aspects of the same beat.

I don't see a clear political agenda, and I don't see a clear political purpose. He's reporting on the experiences of migrants and refugees, which is generally under-reported, where the problems stemming from migration are generally over-reported.

Bias, sure, I could give you that one. And if he's the only one reporting on this subject, then AJ has a problem with one-sided coverage. Still, I don't see activism. These are not opinion pieces, he's not covering the migrants as great heroes while vilifying all who stand in their way. He's pretty even-handed within the narrow focus. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-04 22:03:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You're welcome :) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-04 22:00:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> He does tend to pick subjects that are looking at issues from the migrant's point of view. He's selective, which invites bias because it's generally one-sided coverage, but I don't see any basis for your claim that he's an activist. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-04 17:39:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Where do you get the idea that he's a "pro-migrant activist"?

His byline on Al Jazeera reads:

 reports on international affairs in Europe and the Levant, focusing mostly on migration issues.

And his byline on Twitter reads:  
  
Reporter, covering migration-integration issues in Europe.

Migration is his beat as a reporter. Unless you can provide hard proof that he is *also* a "pro-migrant activist", you're engaging in slander. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-04 04:28:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It should be added that you can also contact the site owners to request deletion of your data.

If you live in Europe, you can do two more things:
- Request a copy of all data they have on you. Even non-EU companies are required to apply if they allow European users.
- You can try to have Google hide specific results that come up when someone Googles your real name. To learn the details, search for "the right to be forgotton". </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-04 03:52:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That's the best reply in this thread so far, imho. Thank you! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-04 03:49:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Who is the wrong question. Or at least, I don't know whom it might be, now, or in the future.  
  
What I am trying to prevent is me using the same camera over the course of years, sharing different kinds of photos through different kinds of identities, and then having these separate identities linked together through those photos by [unknown party]. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-03 23:20:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> No. Flickr is/was a place for professional and ambitious amateurs to share their work. 500px has become a serious competitor, as well as Instagram.

https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Flickr </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-03 21:45:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That's the most creative answer so far! ;) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-03 21:01:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You can start by reading my other comment on this post:  
  
https://www.reddit.com/r/PoliticalDiscussion/comments/4qxh5b/ive_seen_mentioned_many_times_that_the_obama/d4wtpmy </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-03 20:58:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thanks!

 what would tie the images together and to a single identity would be in the content

Only if I would share the same or similar content across different identities. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-03 20:29:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  there is no way anyone could find such a fingerprint useful.  
  
I believe this shows a lack of imagination on your part. Sharing photographs by the same camera across different identities allows for the possibility of tying them together.  
  
We know there are businesses dedicated to re-identification of anonymized or incomplete data sets. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-03 19:42:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I assure you that I have not and will not engage in illegal activity. I'm just a citizen who cares about their privacy. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-03 19:21:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You don't have to take my word for it.
  
Like actual fingerprints, the digital "noise" in original images is stochastic in nature  that is, it contains random variables  which are inevitably created during the manufacturing process of the camera and its sensors. This virtually ensures that the noise imposed on the digital images from any particular camera will be consistent from one image to the next, even while it is distinctly different.

Source: https://www.schneier.com/blog/archives/2006/04/digital_cameras.html </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-03 19:10:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I understand, but I am going to be sharing photos and am willing to spend some time minimizing the possibility of (re-)identification. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-03 17:19:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> ###Submission Statement  
  
Every day I encounter people on Reddit and other platforms that still believe refugees are primarily to blame for the events on New Years Eve in Cologne, Germany. They use this account to justify their hostile stance against refugees. 
  
De Correspondent, a Dutch journalism startup, set upon a months-long investigation to separate fact from fiction.  
The result is the story I've submitted, [and this minute-by-minute timeline.](https://decorrespondent.nl/4406/Minute-by-minute-This-is-what-happened-in-Cologne-on-New-Years-Eve/1078757391184-66dd7a56)  
  
Unfounded statements made by police in the days after became headlines, while the truth has taken months to surface, only to be ignored.  
I hope the actual account of what happened that night will spread far and wide. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-03 16:50:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You seem to be limiting your view to Reddit, and limiting the scope to your view of whistleblowers. The 'War on Whistleblowers' by the Obama administration is well-known outside of Reddit, and a topic actively covered by national security journalists. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-03 03:18:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Worth reading, as these explain some of the differences, but keep in mind that they are all dated.
  
- http://www.nytimes.com/2015/10/07/technology/european-union-us-data-collection.html?_r=0
- http://www.nbcnews.com/id/15221111/ns/technology_and_science-privacy_lost/t/la-difference-stark-eu-us-privacy-laws/
- http://www.cato.org/pubs/wtpapers/991201paper.html
  
My opinion:  
  
Yes, generally speaking. It differs a little from country to country, but personal privacy is definitely better protected in most compared to the U.S.  
  
Companies are a lot more restricted in what they can collect and do with the data they collect. The government tends to collect as much or more, as most European countries tend to have something of a welfare state.  
And of course we suffer from the same terrorism scare, so more and more systems and laws are being implemented to surveil us. 
  
A lot will improve as of 25 May, 2018 when the [General Data Protection Regulation](https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/General_Data_Protection_Regulation) will go into force. It's a much-needed update for the information age, giving people who reside in the EU a say in who collects their information, for what purpose, etc. And they can request a copy of whatever data any company holds on them. This, for example, is a right that does not exist in the U.S.  
  
No country is perfect, but Germany is a good bet if you value privacy. They have a constitutional court that keeps both German lawmakers and European lawmakers in check.  
Belgium has increasingly become better at it; They even have a State Secretary of Privacy! The Netherlands is alright on paper, less so in practice, but civil society (privacy activists) are organized and working on keeping the government honest.  
  
I'm not sure about the Nordics, but I know Sweden, for example, publishes everyone's tax records. Your neighbors could check how much you make, etc.  
I would stay away from France, as they've gone all-in on anti-terrorism for obvious reasons. The declared a state of emergency after the last attacks in Paris and have extended it until after the European Football Championship ends, which they are hosting right now.  
  
If you could tell us which specific country or countries you have in mind, it would be easier to give you more specific advice. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-03 02:10:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The why? To keep private what you want to keep private. If you're a doctor, a patient, a lawyer, a client, a journalist, a source, etc. you may need to keep your movements untracked some of the time. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-03 02:06:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Nothing of that is part of my claims. He is a legitimate whistleblower, that is all I proved.

As for the proper channels claim you make, you should read this:

- [Exclusive: Snowden Tried to Tell NSA About Surveillance Concerns, Documents Reveal](https://news.vice.com/article/edward-snowden-leaks-tried-to-tell-nsa-about-surveillance-concerns-exclusive)
- [Vindication for Edward Snowden From a New Player in NSA Whistleblowing Saga](https://theintercept.com/2016/05/23/vindication-for-edward-snowden-from-a-new-player-in-nsa-whistleblowing-saga/)
- [How the Pentagon punished NSA whistleblowers](https://www.theguardian.com/us-news/2016/may/22/how-pentagon-punished-nsa-whistleblowers)

As you can read, his predecessors tried, and failed. Snowden knew this. And recently the NSA released e-mails backing up Snowden's claims of raising concerns internally. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-02 20:50:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> To use Snowden as an example, courts have found government abuse based on the evidence he provided.

A federal appeals court has ruled that one of the NSA programs he exposed was illegal.

Source: http://www.theatlantic.com/politics/archive/2015/05/the-vindication-of-edward-snowden/392741/

This makes him a whistleblower. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-02 20:38:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yes, it does make a difference, because my phone is not my car. Right now, I can leave my phone at home or remove the battery when I go for a drive. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-02 20:34:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> 'Obama' is shorthand for his administration. He doesn't set the agenda alone, but he does bear the ultimate responsibility for it. I don't believe there is much hard evidence out there of Obama deliberately instructing people to directly target individual leakers/whistleblowers. It is clear that his administration is behaving extraordinary compared to all its predecessors in how it deals with leakers/whistleblowers.

The 'War on Whistleblowers' exists, but it is part of a larger agenda, that includes a war on *unauthorized* leaks to the press, and an attack on source protection by journalists.

[This chart by ProPublica](https://www.propublica.org/special/sealing-loose-lips-charting-obamas-crackdown-on-national-security-leaks) which ends at the conviction of Bradley/Chelsea Manning, shows how leak prosecutions under the Espionage Act have picked up steam under Obama. 

The lede of this Guardian piece, detailing a double standard in dealing with leakers/whistleblowers, may make the distinction between President Obama and his administration more clear (emphasis mine):

Since Barack Obama entered the White House in 2009, *his government* has waged a war against whistleblowers and official leakers. *On his watch*, there have been eight prosecutions under the 1917 Espionage Act  more than double those under all previous presidents combined.

Source: https://www.theguardian.com/us-news/2015/mar/16/whistleblowers-double-standard-obama-david-petraeus-chelsea-manning

During Obama's re-election campaign in 2012, he/his campaign boasted about prosecuting "twice as many cases under the Espionage Act as all other administrations combined".

Source: https://www.theguardian.com/commentisfree/2012/sep/05/obama-campaign-brags-about-whistleblower-persecutions

A very different message from his 2008 campaign:

Protect Whistleblowers: Often the best source of information about waste, fraud, and abuse in government is an existing government employee committed to public integrity and willing to speak out. Such acts of courage and patriotism, which can sometimes save lives and often save taxpayer dollars, should be encouraged rather than stifled as they have been during the Bush administration. We need to empower federal employees as watchdogs of wrongdoing and partners in performance. Barack Obama will strengthen whistleblower laws to protect federal workers who expose waste, fraud, and abuse of authority in government. Obama will ensure that federal agencies expedite the process for reviewing whistleblower claims and whistleblowers have full access to courts and due process.

Source: http://obama.3cdn.net/0080cc578614b42284_2a0mvyxpz.pdf

Some further reading:

- [Obama Has Rarely Or Never Praised Whistleblowers](http://www.huffingtonpost.com/2013/05/18/obama-whistleblowers_n_3294417.html)
- ["Long before Edward Snowden went public, John Crane was a top Pentagon official fighting to protect NSA whistleblowers. Instead their lives were ruined  and so was his"](https://www.theguardian.com/us-news/2016/may/22/how-pentagon-punished-nsa-whistleblowers)

President Obama is cracking down on leakers. Both Edward Snowden and Bradley Manning face prosecution under the Espionage Act, while a New York Times reporter was ordered to reveal his sources or risk jail time. Is Washington turning its back on freedom of the press?

Source: http://www.spiegel.de/international/world/obama-wages-war-on-whistleblowers-and-journalists-a-912852.html

There are two 2015 documentaries:

- **War On Whistleblowers** [You can watch it for free on YouTube.](https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=OWBQGVc2kq8)
- [**Silenced: The War on Whistleblowers**](http://silencedfilm.com/), which is available on Netflix in some countries.

To understand the bigger picture, [you should research the legal battle of journalist James Risen.](http://www.nytimes.com/2015/01/13/us/times-reporter-james-risen-will-not-be-called-to-testify-in-leak-case-lawyers-say.html) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-02 16:28:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> With the way things are going, self-driving cars will be the norm, and they are already a privacy nightmare with all the tracking they have to do to function. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-02 16:27:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [Sousveillance](https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Sousveillance). </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-02 15:48:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> And thank you for taking on the advice. Good luck! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-02 02:50:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I have the opposite problem. I care about my privacy and want to have the choice to pay anonymously (with cash). Unfortunately, many businesses here are 'plastic only'. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-02 00:37:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If you're asking, you can find that information here:

- https://epic.org/privacy/nsl/
- https://www.eff.org/issues/national-security-letters
- https://www.aclu.org/national-security-letters </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-01 23:28:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Why do people insist on saying this when they are presented with proof? Sure, we may have suspected this, but actually having proof and learning the details is entirely different, and - to use your wording - **new**. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-01 21:39:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Currently, you depend on:

- ajax.googleapis.com
- fonts.googleapis.com
- fonts.gstatic.com  
  
 and you load your app buttons from:


- linkmaker.itunes.apple.com
- play.google.com.

I would suggest hosting all that yourself.

And this is just your website. I don't know what your apps are doing. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-01 18:24:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Why not link to the source of the scoop?

https://theintercept.com/2016/06/30/secret-rules-make-it-pretty-easy-for-the-fbi-to-spy-on-journalists/ </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-01 05:58:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Direct link to article (paywall):
http://www.wsj.com/articles/u-k-s-eu-exit-poses-data-protection-dilemma-1467280852 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-01 05:53:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  "I am taking something but not telling you what and giving you this for it". And I'm thinking we might need a new term other than 'capitalism' for that kind of commerce.

Good point. And they take it even if you don't want what they give you in return. (Many in this sub try to have a Google-free experience, but blocking them breaks many sites. Plus they own parts of the core infrastructure of the net.)

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-01 04:29:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thank you, and you're welcome! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-01 03:44:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Apathy and laziness aren't enough to explain it. Using that as an explanation doesn't really invite us to look into actual or other causes.

The benefits of surveillance capitalism are clear to even the simplest of people, while the dangers are* not. Humans are great with immediate feedback and gratification, and terrible with delayed feedback and gratification. Even more so if the negative effects of their behavior affects others, and not them.

And even that explanation is too limited, so I'll keep looking for others and better ones. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-01 03:00:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You're welcome! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-01 00:27:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Related reading (and a must-read imo):

[The Secrets of Surveillance Capitalism - Shoshana Zuboff](http://www.faz.net/aktuell/feuilleton/debatten/the-digital-debate/shoshana-zuboff-secrets-of-surveillance-capitalism-14103616.html)

and

[Big Other: Surveillance Capitalism and the Prospects of an Information Civilization - 
Shoshana Zuboff ](http://papers.ssrn.com/sol3/papers.cfm?abstract_id=2594754) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-30 23:38:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Great! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-30 22:58:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> No worries, thank you for actually reading it! :D </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-30 22:57:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  playing with #Brexit

\ leaves the EU  
\ still surveils you through TEMPORA

GCHQ is watching EU #justBREXITthings

 And, any thoughts of having /r/EuroPrivacy subscribers voting on the finalists? We'd be fine w/ a cross-link for that, if you go there.

Good idea! Would make a good PR stunt :) I'll let you know if/when we do this.

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-30 21:06:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This is a talk given by Maciej Cegowski on June 26, 2016, at a panel on the Moral Economy of Tech at the SASE conference in Berkeley.

Related reading (and a must-read imo):

[The Secrets of Surveillance Capitalism - Shoshana Zuboff](http://www.faz.net/aktuell/feuilleton/debatten/the-digital-debate/shoshana-zuboff-secrets-of-surveillance-capitalism-14103616.html)

and

[Big Other: Surveillance Capitalism and the Prospects of an Information Civilization - 
Shoshana Zuboff ](http://papers.ssrn.com/sol3/papers.cfm?abstract_id=2594754) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-30 20:45:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thank you! That's very kind :) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-30 20:44:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thank you so much for the encouragement and compliments. Keep up the good work on /r/privacy, love your sub :) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-30 17:00:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Great comment. You will probably enjoy reading this:

http://idlewords.com/talks/sase_panel.htm

I hope you'll consider hanging out in /r/europrivacy :) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-29 22:44:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Who is the action figure? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-29 19:04:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> There are cheaper options if you're open to DIY-ing or using something that's ugly but functional.

Some links to get you started:

- [A standing desk for $22](http://iamnotaprogrammer.com/Ikea-Standing-desk-for-22-dollars.html)
- [Make Yourself a Standing Desk This Weekend](http://lifehacker.com/5929765/make-yourself-a-standing-desk-this-weekend)
- [Standing Desks: The Definitive Guide to Standing at Work](http://www.simplifiedbuilding.com/blog/standing-desks/)
- [Get Up, Stand Up: 10 Do-It-Yourself Standing Desks](http://www.brit.co/standing-desks/) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-29 18:47:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If someone could cross-post this to /r/unitedkingdom with [x-post /r/europrivacy] in the title, that would be great. Thank you :) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-29 00:14:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Aye, ANSI layout. Thinking of selling it as well. GLWS! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-28 23:19:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> EU-NL or worldwide price check for:

- Kinesis Advantage Contoured UK
- Model#: KB500USB-BLK-UK
- Condition: Good as new
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-28 23:05:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Are the Olivetti caps double shots or dyed? I'm asking because I already have one, but it has dyed caps. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-28 21:35:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Usually biometrics are used as part of a two-factor authentication. You can choose out of three different things for the two factors: Something you have, something you know, and something you are.

In this case, your dick is something you are, which you should always combine with one of the other two, like something you know, like a password. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-27 19:14:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Take it slow, learn the maps, and make note of your routes, your teammates routes. It will give you insight into the enemy routes once the teams are reversed. Moving slowly and anticipating where the enemy comes from will make you live longer and kill more.  
  
Read a few guides on steam, watch a few tips   tricks videos on YouTube and you'll start performing better.  
  
You don't need to spend all your supply points. The lighter you are, the faster you are. If you have a decent objective score and a bad kdr, you're doing fine; Objectives are the most important thing in the game, kdr means little, except that dying less means you can cap and defend more objectives.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-24 01:47:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> In addition to the other suggestions, you can just wipe your cookies. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-22 02:02:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> *everyone who can afford it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-22 02:01:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Just make sure you die before you need to have those loans repaid. The robot will clean you up. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-22 01:18:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This paragraph is particularly interesting. Emphasis is mine.

In its law enforcement guide, Yahoo says it is not able to search for or produce deleted emails. But, lawyers of Knaggs claim that Yahoo did just that, and handed over 6 months worth of erased communications, leading them to say something might be afoot: at minimum, that Yahoo has not been forthcoming with how the emails were obtained, **or that perhapsspeculativelythey came from an NSA surveillance program**. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-19 20:49:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Changing how you spend your money is something small that you can do incrementally, which can and does have an impact. Especially if you get others to follow suit.

Examples: Don't buy a car, or buy one that is either an EV or very fuel efficient. Don't eat meat, or eat less (much) less of it. Etc.

DISCLAIMER: I'm not telling you or anyone reading this how to live or that if you do own a gas guzzler or eat half a cow for breakfast that you are somehow an awful person; I'm just giving examples of life choices than can have an impact on the environment. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-18 05:39:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Happy birthday, GLWS! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-15 00:54:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thanks to you I won't be able to sleep tonight... O.O </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-15 00:52:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> One of them will hold the camera and narrates. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-15 00:49:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> emigrate </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-15 00:49:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> emigrate </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-15 00:48:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The privacy-loving crowd here would burn the place down. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-14 22:08:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Clueless? I think she's being very deliberate. Never waste a good crisis to push for more surveillance powers, and to quell the post-Snowden emergence of anti-surveillance sentiments in Silicon Valley. SV is very susceptible to pro-LGBTQ rhetoric, and may throw encryption under the bus because of it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-13 20:38:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> There was a man in Amsterdam who slept in a different hotel every night for a year. He paid for this himself at first, but as the ball got rolling, his presence became a valuable way to get good PR - journalists covered his experiences and he kept a blog - so they either comped the room, upgraded his room, or allowed him a taste of the extras.
It probably cost him somewhere between 2000 and 4000 a month just for the rooms, depending on the season.

If you want to figure out if you can pull off living in just one hotel, contact the hotels in the city you're looking at, at the locations you're looking at, and ask them the rates for long-term stay, including internet access (which isn't usually free or unlimited). 
Then figure out how much it would cost you to eat out 3 times a day. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-13 20:28:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> There are apartment buildings adjacent to hotels that give access to the hotel's services, including the ones you've mentioned. Unfortunately, those apartments go for tens of millions of dollars/euros, and the service comes at a high price as well. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-13 18:09:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> We've been on top of this story in /r/europrivacy for a while :) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-12 19:19:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Little Brother by Cory Doctorow. I read it right after RPO and the first third of the book felt very similar. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-12 18:34:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The thing with security and privacy is that you don't get to decide whether you're special or not. Others don't judge you by your standards.
You, your knowledge, your access, or your social or professional contacts may make you a person of interest to someone. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-12 18:32:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That entirely depends on the country/jurisdiction you're in. Several countries have something called a 'decryption order', compelling you to disclose your password or key. If you decline, you get jail time.  
  
They can't force you in the same way they can forcefully take biometric information from you, but they can try to force you by pressuring you. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-11 17:36:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You're sort of explaining why having a proper social security system reduces incentives for crime. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-11 16:21:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> They banned production of that kind of porn on their soil. They are still allowed to watch it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-09 17:22:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This list may help you find who you're looking for:  
http://smartprivacy.tumblr.com/therapists

This is a listing for tech, digital, and Internet-savvy therapists. All of the mental health professionals listed below identify as tech-savvy and tech-affirming. They also have agreed to abide by the Code of Ethics of their respective discipline.

The list is limited to the United States and Japan. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-09 03:50:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah, that's why there are so many bad reviews. The marketing of it isn't in line with the content. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-09 02:58:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's not about organized crime. It's about this one guy, his goal, and the challenges he faces while trying to achieve that goal. It's really not a mob movie. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-08 23:45:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Very good. Don't expect an action movie, view it as a character study. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-08 21:48:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah, I pretty much followed the same path. These are a great help:

/r/linux4noobs  
/r/linuxquestions  
/r/linux 
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-08 20:18:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Another post on today's front page ties in neatly with this thread/sub:

https://www.reddit.com/r/videos/comments/4n4j4r/guy_shows_how_to_repair_apple_systems_for_free/ </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-08 19:03:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Interesting! Thank you. I'm having trouble finding English-language stories about it. 

I did find https://www.buepf.ch/ and https://stopbuepf.ch/  
  
If any of your countrymen read this, they can find more information there :) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-07 00:31:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's a North American thing ;) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-06 21:06:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> EU pricecheck for:

- Name: Olivetti KBD 2811 
- Condition: Mint
- Layout: ANSI
- Switches: black?

There's one  on eBay right now, current bid is $220 US with three days to go:
http://www.ebay.com/itm/Olivetti-KBD-2811-Vintage-Keyboard-Clicky-MINT-West-Germany-GDD5Y0G81-3000-/262474353090?hash=item3d1cb0c9c2:g:JtYAAOSwqBJXWe47 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
