<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject8860</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-14 21:57:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> after the third hour at my computer i started to lose my mind.
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-14 21:56:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Also never writing one of these again. This took me three hours. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-14 21:55:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> literally never posted a decklist onreddit before, how do i format?
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Grixis tezz top8 at face to face toronto </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-14 19:04:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> decklist ( completly misbuilt due to card availibility)
4 ancient tomb
4 polluted delta 
2 flooded strand 
2 volcanic island
2 underground sea
2 island 
1 swamp
3 wasteland
1 urborg, tomb of yawgmoth
1 inventors fair
1 darkslick shores
1 academy ruins
4 mox diamond 
2 dimir signet
4 tezzeret, agent of bolas
3 dack fayden
3 daretti, genius iconiclast
4 baleful strix
3 thopter foundry
3 sword of the meek
2 toxic deluge
1 ensaring bridge
1 phyrexian revoker
4 chalice of the void
1 sudden shock !
1 transmute artifact

sideboard 
4 force of will 
2 gloom
2 blood moon
1 tormods crypt
1 wurmcoil engine
1 padeem, consul of innovation
1 necromancy
1 dread of night
1 cursed totem
1 ghirapur aether grid


woke up on sunday, wanted to play anything but d t, only had grixis tezz as an alternative.

leave at 9:50 to arrive for a 12:00 event. easy game right?

10:00 - go to pay for lemonade at shoppers, cashier #1 has line 8 deep, cashier#2 is in the back doing something for the 1 customer in front of me for 8 minutes. he comes back and the other line has served three people, i walk out to see my bus drive away. Hmm. 

11:30 - Miss my stop. This ones on me.HMM.

11:42 - arrive.

eta: 1 hour 20 minutes at the outside. real time: 1 hour 52 min. HMM HMM . eta needs revision. tournament starts at 12:30 instead of 12:00 cause a judge had to be shipped in.
(cue mental image of judge arriving via battletech-style dropship)

39 oldwalkers, none of this gatewatch bullcrap 6 rds top 8 (lllemonadeeee)

don't have real notes, writing from memory, already wrecked from lack of food. LEMONAD-

round  1  STORM - ANT -Togores list - player experience level : competent beginner, Storm on play.

my opponent fetches for sea and plays ponder, i waste his sea, he fetches island and plays top. i cast chalice on 1 and my opponent passes. i play sword of the meek, my opponent tops on his end step. then he goes so deep into the tank i think hes gonna drown.

stage 1 of top thinking: cool, maybe he overthinks it.
stage 2 of top thinking: cmon man we got two more games to play!

at this point i have no idea what hes on. hes played misty, misty as fetches, usea island as land, top ponder as spells. first i thought it was bug delver, otherwise he would've got island, right? nope. top. shardless dosen't play top so i put him on- get this - bug standstill.
then he tanked for over five minutes. 

stage three of top thinking: wow okay no ones this bad at resolving top, somethings up. Hes trying to figure out if he can kill me. NO ONE takes this long. 

stage four: i begin piecing together what his hand is based on what i have in play, what he does, and what his presideboard configuration must be. Turns out I'm only off by two cards.

stage five, acceptance: he stops thinking, untaps and draws, plays out LED, petal,petal. volc
and passes the turn. i proceed to dack his petal and transmute for lil rex revoker on LED.
He mini combos, but then dosent have the red mana to PIF due to the lock on LED. He dies just after that, tezz ult then 5/5 put it away.

I'm just glad i had plays during my opponents top activation.

game 2 opponent kills me through chalice. at this point i start to wonder if my opponent isnt playing 4 dark ritual or something. ability to play around chalice is disturbing...

game 3 the game progresses to the point where i have double chalice on one. my opponent has echoing truth, I have force of will, tezz puts it away with 5/5 chalices.

2-1 games 1-0 matches. cool goblin piker bro.

round 2: eldrazi stompy- player experience level: competent beginner, i'm on play.

game 1 : I play land go.  he goes mana source into mimic, i waste him. he attacks plays mana source into mimic and i waste him again. he plays mana source attack pass, i play mox diamond pitch tomb fetch land and deluge x-1, and he blanks on mana for way too long.

game 2: he surgicals all my fetchlands, needles naming wasteland, then i set up bridge and proceed to assemble thopter sword at my leisure. I really hope hes not still kicking himself.

4-1 games  2-0 matches. elvish ranger. sweet!

Round three:  Infect - player experience level: seasoned vet, hes playing first.

he starts pendelhaven into hierach, i play waste and pass, he plays inkmoth nexus and passes back. i think a moment, go to waste his nexus, he activates and uses vines. hmm.
i play waste and waste nexus on his upkeep. it works, he plays foothills. Then this beating occurs:  "play ancient tomb, chalice 1?" float blue, brainstorm, daze chalice, fetch. untap, land pass. "play land chalice 1?" spell pierce your chalice. Well crap then, pass turn. untap, brainstorm blighted agent. okay still got outs. untap, "play strix?" force of will . okay, "bridge"?  "cards in hand?" Uh oh. "One." untap draw land, attack with agent,  invigorate
into berserk. :0 

game 2 waste a wasteland on irrelavent dual, lose to inkmoth.

" There is no game you deserve to win, but plenty you deserve to lose."

4-3 in games , 2-1 in matches  Dreg reaver! take me back to the forest! DRINK MOAR LEMO

round 4 Bant with tamyo field researcher - player experince level: sesoned vet.

honestly i dont remember much of this match except that my opponent had to remind me on two seperate occasions that I actually won game one, including after game 2 when i went to pick up the match slip and sign my loss in. " We still have another game." "Wait what? "     
talked about how much i like tamyo in bant, probably better than jace in that list given that the deck wants to beat down anyways, and the meta just having more creatures in it. 
Bonus corner case: interacts with top for the purposes of counterbalance!

edit: SmellyTofu reminds me that I made the misplay of taking batterskull with dack, not realizing that it did not take control of the germ. I had not cast dack before that day, and not stolen equipment before that play. I'm told
i was salty. If someone could tell me what else happened in that match, i would very much like to know. i still don't know how i won game one.   

5 - 5 in games, 2 -2 in matches  jedit ojannen. Hmm.

round 5: D T Player experience level: On the low side, reletive to d ts necessary skill level.
he takes the play :

"Plains vial go". this could be really good or really bad depending what his two drop is. i make chalice 1 off mox diamond island, he plays mystic getting batterskull, i play tomb into
tezz - 1 turns chalice into 5/5 and attack, he vials mom, untaps plays land and passes.
i attack with tezz token and he blocks with mystic. uh oh. i play a strix, minus tezz for a 5/5
then the following turn plus that one and play another. hes seen enough.

game 2 this game went long, but i locked him with ghirapur aether grid, then toxic deluge,

thopter foundry grid, then thopter sword for a turn prior to revoker on it, he got a jitte then i had dack for vial, daretti your other vial then Gloom for the concession.

Gloom is as targeted as hate gets man. Gloom dont play.

7-5 in games 3-2 in matches. I'm No longer vanilla - now I'm COMMANDER GREVEN IL VEC

oww my spine fix it with more lemonade-

round 6 mono red aggro-comb - its burn. just burn. - player experience level : i have to assume it was his first time playing legacy, i know there was a very new burn player in the room. 
 
brutal honesty here, i deserved to lose this match. the matchup is terrible but more than that, I gave him every oppurtunity to kill me in game three. As in, i knew full well what the correct line was  3-4 turns in a row( make 6 thopters, gain 4 life ) and decided not to take it
in favor of doing something cool that i hadn't done that day yet on all those turns. I would have even lost had my opponent prioritized his targets better or drawn better.

   
4-2 in matches , 9-6 in games. there are no 9/6 creatures in magic. which means...

I'M A REAL BOY!!!

I sit down to play a fun game against one of the local miracles players( Yes I'm the nutjob who enjoys playing against miracles. Sue me.) when i hear my name for top 8.
" I what!? How the heck did that happen, and who's responsible for it!? Me? No, see i distinctly remember this game in round 6..." 


semifinals match : Wilkin Chau on... hoo boy. 

So Wilkin is a well known deadguy ale player. Iv'e seen him play other decks, but  not to good finishes. In fact, I've never seen him pilot a non deadguy deck to a successful finish in an event longer than 4 rounds. I'm not saying it hasn't happened, I'm saying when i sat down across from him with him being the number one seed in a six round event, i struggled to come up with ways that he was not on deadguy.

wilkin plays first, top8 play draw rule.

game one: wilkin mulls to 5. "Go." "uh youre on the play wilkin." "I know. Go." "I'm confused, did you chose to draw?" "No I'm on the play and i'm passing the turn."

Oh. Ohhh. Now i understand.

wilkin cast no spells that game, and conceded when he would have had to discard for hand size.

game 2: i board both glooms, aether grid, dread of night, padeem and wormcoil engine.

he goes turn 2 chandra, turn 3 koth, turn 4 three for one fiery confluence.

"I've been got." Me, 2016. I had gloom and deluge sitting in my hand.

fixed my sideboard, on to the clincher.

game three: he plays no less than ten different cards that i did not see in game 2(or 1 obviously) and i lose to fiery confluence on my everything.

9-8 in games 4/3 in matches. I AM THE EATER OF DAYSSSSSSS

all in all i had fun, could have done better in games with better play, but the guys i lost to got me pretty freaking good. really glad i didn't play d t today. daretti was one of the best cards in the deck. not much miracles in the room which is sad because i think i'm favored and i love playing against it anyways.

PRRROPPS-
-The Gentleman of the Green for lending me an ensaring bridge. You know who you are. 

-The special guest judge for having split second and awesome

-the guys at F2F for putting up with my bullcrap

SLLLOOOPPS
- the cashier for taking way too long. I could have not gotten lemonade, but then the way the day goes i don't get to eat or drink till 6:00 maybe, and i certainly play worse and am less sociable.

- the spectator who said "I think you missed your trigger " when i did nothing of the sort. I get it, call the judge, even if like in this case you just finished your judge call 15 seconds ago(no hyperbole) and you just want to get your burn game over with so you can get your food from across the street.

     

             




            
       



     </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-13 15:30:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah thanks this was really helpful. Its the time investment and not the money that matters .What would you play over the missing two cards? 
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-13 15:19:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> might help in future if you tell me what was too much. 

edit ; btw i always enjoy getting reamed by those guys. if i got reamed by those guys more often, id get reamed less often by other guys who use those... decks.

(am i doing the funny better?) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-13 15:17:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> oops whoa was that insulting? sorry i'm more abrasive typing than speaking in general. sorry if i offended.

looking back at what i typed it looks a little over the top maybe? hard to know where the line is without crossing it a couple of times and hoping you guys forgive me after. not going to edit, leaving it there so i can reference example number one.  hope mods don't delete its important.
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-13 14:55:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> okay but now that i'm in this situation, today, what do you think i should do.

i do feel confident in d t, but the primary goal here isn't to win, its to enjoy playing magic. i play reasonably well with the deck, and i like it, i'm just really not feeling it right now.

i'm just thinking of how bad this is gonna be: me, to round three opponent while on tilt cause of loss;
"yeah i should have just played my shitty tezz deck." opponent " ur what? lool! keep tilting scrub."

      </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> don't wanna play d t today </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-13 13:48:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> i have d t built and i dont wanna play it in my monthly today.

i also have grixis tezz, with only one bridge and one transmute artifact.

I'd really rather not play d t, as while i believe i am a competent pilot, i feel ATM that my enjoyment of playing that deck is too tied up with how often i win with it. 

so do i play optimal d t and hate it, unfinished grixis tezz and win like no games, or just not play. 

i want to at least feel like there's some chance of winning my games when i sit down.

playing at face to face today, gonna get reamed by rich mattuzio, lam "always has the force" phan,   or aaron "top 8 Again??" kasprzak. 

also see the resurgence of deadguy ale, too moch pox, too much eldrazi, and then all the miracles players are also grixis players, you can only bring one deck, and they usually all bring the same one. 

always 2 ur
always 1 mud
always 2 cloudpost

usually 30 + person event, but team unified modern elsewhere. ?????? 


edit: playing tezz, would rather run crap and have fun than run the nut and present as a douche.

tounament report later cause there just isn't enough on this thing! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-04 15:44:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> modern is faster than legacy. starting games at twenty life helps a lot. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-04 15:27:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Please tell me how you did this? I'm trying to do the same in west toronto. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-04 14:51:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I want to point out BR reaninmator and manaless dredge both won large legacy tournaments (10+ rounds) recently, and that burn is 15th on mtg top8 for most successful decks. 

also, check out ari laxs video series on belcher. winning way too much with that thing online.

I think turbo depths did somthing huge lately too? 

D   T is obv the best of these. 

burn only costs so much cause of goblin guide, and you can build it
less controlling with no fetches and flame rift in the searing blaze slot.

I've been supporting my legacy addiction with limited twice a week + $125 a month on singles actually. only that much cause i'm trying to build dredge and grixis tezzerator at the same time.

    </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-04 01:16:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> i would argue that burn could be built to crush that meta fairly easily, with the caveat that miracles is miracles and would take some extra work to break even on.

also, miracles is a pain in the arse to play if you are tired or over long tournaments, especially among new arrivals to the deck. not neccesesarily because you make mistakes per se, but remembering what U/x fetch you have on top for predict is harder when you're in round 3 game 2 and you came here after work or got up super early for this thing or whatever.

death and taxes is a good beginners deck only if you watch an obscene amount of footage and take notes on your opponents opening 4 turns. otherwise, get ready to get ranched for a while as you figure out how to predict your opponents development so you can sequence your lock pieces to stop it. 

Less white weenie, more monowhite control.  Thalia/Waste is my Counter/Top! (hyperbole)  
  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-03 20:03:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah thats right. Burn makes top 16 here. Oh yeah. Deal with it. 

/salty about non legacy players not thinking burn is a real deck. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-03 18:27:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> cardhoarder has decent legacy players playing decks they have no experience with badly now. Thats fun.

the best of them is couch chris anderson (chran's) corner. where he shows someone how its done in the (insert deck here) house.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-03 18:15:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> revoker and port against miracles, wasteland and combat creatures against delver. active jitte is a lock piece.

crusader over big thalia is probably a mistake depending on your meta, eldrazi is extremely difficult to beat without that card, now the deck is durduling with recruiter and prelate. 

understand that with the new options, your cmc is higher and now you are worse against non-blue, which matters depending on the meta you are expecting to face.  remember that there are no sacred cows, if you get wrecked by miracles and delver, play more disruptive creatures. if jund and eldrazi dump in your cereal, 
play more flyers, thalias and lieges in your 75. sometimes mangara is too slow. sometimes theres so much 
eldrazi, 4th mom makes no sense. 

Sometimes you get a meta where no one respects wasteland and you get to play 4 arbiter 4 ghost quarter 4 path. -1 stoneforge. 

Prison is a form of control. Bring the right answers to your opponents threats. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-02 17:29:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Of course there are people in my own city. My problem is there are no locations to play.

Major metropolitan city. no stores in the western half of it.

pet peeve: when my mid- length post asks 5+ questions and a generic throwaway answer is given that clears up none of them. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-02 17:23:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> because the legacy players in my city, while plentiful, are not so committed to the format that hosting it in the stores is a thing that will work. i also kind of wanted to set something up in an underserviced part of the city, 
 
namely the entire western half of it.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> how do i set up local weekly legacy in my area </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-02 16:47:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Heyo reddit! I want to run a local legacy thing on a weekly basis. i live in a major metropolitan city, but the western half of that city dosent have any stores, nevermind legacy. the other places that have weeklys are at the far east end  or the center north. i'm far west. 

the problem is I've never really done this before and legacy players are harder to herd than a bunch of cats.

questions:

1: where do i do this? i have seating and tables for 8 people comfortably at my apartment, but it's my apartment so...  alternatively is the local mall, but im pretty sure its not open late enough. Help?

2: prize support is the easiest part,  ironically.  %100 into prize pool, done and done.
totally willing to eat a loss here in order to provide like coffee or snacks to the players or whatever.

3: lending decks and cards. Im close to finishing my second legacy deck and am a bunch of recently spiked modern cards away from two more. totally willing to lend shit, but dont know the etiquite for that. help?

4: rules enforcement: it may be a very slight exaggeration to say there are as many judges as  non- judge legacy players locally, but only a very slight exaggeration. the problems come with stuff like:
 4a: can i play the event and run the event?
 4b: can a judge play the event and judge the event if its non-sanctioned like this? 
 4c: local players wont play in this unless there is prize support. this makes the previous
 two  things maybe a little more dicey than they might be otherwise.
 
5: how do i advertise this? facebook didnt work so hot last time i sorta tried this, but obviously ill try again. what other avenues should i explore?

edit: should i just give the city to stop people assuming i live in a small town despite saying major metropolitan area? how about biggest city in the province?     </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-26 15:56:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> ug enchantress is much closer to unplayable since the land drop rule change gimped words of wind. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-24 00:14:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> the problem is more that chalice is pretty disruptive to the base plan against eldrazi. if they chalice, elephant grass isn't an option. youv'e just got moat/sphere/quick confinement lock,all of which now have to happen with no guile to search nor accelerants for mana advantage. sanctum is much worse now too.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-23 08:22:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Theres basically Two directions you can go in.

the first is with the rest in peace helm win condition. these decks tend to be stronger against discard and stoneblade strategies, as well as control strategies that utilize the graveyard.
decay is a boning, and somtimes BGx also has golgari charm. 

the second is with replenish as a focal point. these decks have more resillience to countermagic and decay in exchange for having a more awkward win condition.

no enchantress list can reliably beat any form of combo deck without introducing large
amounts of dissynergy. TES, ANT, sneak show, painter stone, omni-tell, elves, belcher,
oops all spells, reanimator of the UB or BR variety.

all of these decks either go under you, interact with your first hate card then kill you,
or sidestep your hate/locks almost entirely in the case of elves. you have no turn 0 or 1 interaction.

i haven't played this vs eldrazi yet, but i cant imagine chalice plus clock is good news either.

lastly, the reason the lists are varied is because a lot of normally sacred cows get slaughtered depending on what you are expecting to see, and then certain card choices - most of them actually - inform others in the deck. for example, miracles can't function properly with suppression field in play. combined with choke, this is close to a hard lock, and pretty easy to set up with replenish, but all of this is a total nonbo with rip-helm...

if you do decide to consider playing this thing, know that miracles is by far your best matchup. their cards do not line up well at all against yours.

know also that a splash of some sort will always be more beneficial than straight GW. red offers words of war and blood moon as well as sick seal of fire tech against delver in replenish
strategies. blue gives you energy field in rest in peace builds. in the eye of chaos is pretty hit 
or miss nowadays though, but it was a house against dig through time. black offers doomwake giant in replenish builds(dont laugh) and discard out of the board. 

good luck! don't emrakul annihilate anyone i wouldn't!
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-31 01:34:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Okay but if a cellphone is the only photo taking implement i have, how the hell am i supposed to provide that? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-31 01:24:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> so 1190 anyways. thanks for the help!  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-31 01:00:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> 100% of the canadian price or the amerecan price? should i expect 120 percent of the american price? 110%? The Canadian dollar is garbage and this answer is vague to someone who really dosent know what they're doing.

market is american market.
  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-31 00:46:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> youre getting so many prices cause your shipping country is america. i just realized mine wasn't. It was canada. 

I gave cell pics. Thats all i have.
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-31 00:42:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> oops sorry now i see it layout is different. under market price right? also canada dollars suck
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-31 00:40:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> i dont see a price there cause they are all sold out.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> tabernacle of pendrell vale </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-31 00:28:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> SCD: Circle of protection: Red </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-24 17:02:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Why isnt this card played more? it seems like it is very hard to lose the red aggro mirror with this card in play, or even in general against red aggro decks. does burn just not make up enough of the meta? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-14 08:22:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If you want one spell in the yard yeah. If you're actually going to need all four, gifts is what you want.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-14 08:18:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Would you run daze or discard? If discard, is just baleful strix enough to consider cabal therapy? If daze, what other countermagic should i consider? Whats the best control shell for this abomination? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-14 08:13:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm pretty sure this takes half as many slots. you then fill the rest with way more disruption than doomsday has. Also, doomsday makes you lose half your life and is way more all in. You
dont have the option to bolt your opponent out or something if you screw up. 12 Slots.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-14 08:08:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I have read the card intuition. It does not get four spells. This is very important. Three copies of the same spell is not important. The first, when conditions are met, wins the game. The second still does, but the conditions are more resource intensive, either in deckbuilding or in gameplay or both.    </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-14 05:39:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> intuition does not do what this card does in specifically this instance. if the plan was at any point to gifts for value, yes, intuition would be the card i want. but the fact that gifts gets four cards is important here, because you actually do need them all in your hand or graveyard. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-14 04:54:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> d rit  - cabal rit -pif - d rit - cabal rit - seething song hold priority increasing vengence the song - ( 4 black 15 red in pool)- manamorphose red to blue, recast gifts, get past in flames 
tendrils, two extras, recast PIF and tendrils ftw. There's some variation, rarely you need a little more, sometimes you need a little less, but the absolute most you will ever need assuming no opposition  is  6 IMS and two of the six key bits. i think there are 15 different combinations of these, and i think only 5 of those need 6 IMS. I'm not 100% sure,
uncharted waters here!        </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-14 03:17:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> i figured the reason to play this over storm is that you then have 12 slots on the combo instead of 38 or whatever ANT has. consider a disruption suite of : counter top, force of will, thoughtseize with strix and bolt to buy time and brainstorm to tie it together.  the closest comparison would be sneak and show or other "slow combo" and i could be mistaken, but i think this takes up less slots than all of those. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-14 02:48:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> the cards devoted to the combo are
* 2 pif
* 2 dark ritual
* 2 cabal ritual
*1 increasing vengence
*1 seething song
*1 manamophphose
*1 tendrils
with the rest just being a grixis control list probably. The pile is hold any two of
*PIF
*Increasing vengence
*dark ritual
*cabal ritual
*seething song
*manamorphose
and cast gifts then untap and win.  Important to note that with certain initial resources, having 2 of these may not be strictly necessary.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-14 02:00:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  Why does the answer depend on the pile? I want to know because it may be better to just fork over a list. Assume that 3 cards are mostly dead outside the combo, and further assume the deck can combo without casting gifts if nesccesary.

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> on gifts ungiven </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-14 01:31:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> How viable is the line " gifts on endstep, untap, win the game" in legacy? The only other discussions about it that i was able to find seemed to hinge on the fact that there was no pile
that would win, and i found one. So i want to know how viable "resolve 4 mana instant on opponent's end step" is as a tier 2 strategy, realistically.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Need help with d t sideboard </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-07 14:16:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> going to a legacy monthly 1k today, and need some advice putting together a death and taxes sideboard. my meta has a higher than usual concentration of  Lands and pox, and most of the miracles players also own grixis delver so they can go either way. the sideboard looks like this right now:

2 cataclysym
1 councils judgement
1 disenchant
2 ethersworn cannonist
1 pithing needle
2 gideon, ally of zendikar
3 rest in peace
1 grafdiggers cage 
1 containment preist
1 COP: red

help soon thx!

edit ps:
 if someone could tell me how to make a list not look like cat barf... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-20 06:14:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> the tendrils in main is bad because   
A: you have no way to really find it and   
B: The tendrils plan is plan D anyways.  
You're really supposed to only use it to make a grislebrand hit immediately lethal, in the case that you weren't able to find and reanimate sufficient redundant fat. It's a corner case that comes up often enough to be worth a slot in the sideboard.  
Yeah, Lowry's list needed some tuning. I also got the impression from the article he didn't want to screw around with it too much, or at least that he didn't feel comfortable doing so. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-20 06:02:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [sure](http://deckstats.net/deck-8622526-e22b497f4a8d1ea2da34247cf527aa58.html) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-20 05:37:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm not so sure a deck with this much redundancy has as much inherent consistency problems as a typical non-blue combo deck.
However, I also believe that this is less consistent than your typical
reanimator shell. I consider this to be the TES to Reanimators ANT-
not the optimal choice all the time, but a solid option if you want to
reanimate but there are too many deathrites in the room.

force is beat by protection hands and this deck, like storm, has mana such that daze can be played around sometimes. this said,
you're correct in that sometimes you just have to go for it and lose
to force. Its not like we're the only combo deck that's like that either.

lastly, you wouldn't believe the number of terrible or outdated list's of this I've seen. I'm not saying mine is perfect(there are some slightly budget manabase options, for instance) but having the right distribution is key for this list. Maybe we can compare lists.    </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-20 05:11:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I play a lot of competitive legacy and a little bit of modern I'm pretty new to 
cockatrice, but I played a bunch of MWS back when that was a thing. Also,
I can be your vintage specialist if necessary? Gotta cover all the eternal formats,
amirite?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-20 03:49:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> more goldfish results, I mean anecdotal but c'mon, why is no one playing this? 

game 11 turn 1 without protection, mull 6  
game 12 turn 1 without protection, gas for turn 2   
OR turn 2 with protection  
game 13 turn 1 without protection  
game 14 turn 2 with protection mull 6  
game 14 turn 1 with protection  
game 15 turn 2 with protection  
game 16 turn 1 with protection  
game 17 fizzle  
game 18 turn 2 without protection  
game 19 turn 2 without protection  
game 20 turn 4 without protection mull 4 (not finding lands did it here)  
 
Wheels fell of at the end a liitle. more coming. I'll stop when people tell me they 
don't care. 

edit: last goldfish block!

 game 21 turn 1 with protection  
game 22 turn 2 without protection mull 5  
game 23 turn 4 without protection mull 4  
game 24 fizzle  
game 25 turn 2 with protection  
game 26 turn 1 without protection  
game 27 no protection,  attempt on turn 2,3 and 4    
game 28 turn 3 without protection mull 5  
game 29 turn 2 without protection.   
hand plays around deathrite  
game 30 disruption on turn 1 and 2, attempt on turn 3 and 4   

Conclusion is that this deck is better than people give it credit for. At the very least
it's more explosive than regular reanimator and at least has the ability to go under the hate that is giving that deck fits right now.
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Goldfishing burning reanimator </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-20 02:54:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This deck seems really good. Everything about consistency that people seem   to say about it just looks not to be the case. Ten games:  
game 1 turn 1 with protection  
game 2 turn 1 without protection, mull 5  
game 3 turn 1 with protection  
game 4 fizzle  
game 5 turn 1 without protection,  
gas for turn 2  
game 6 turn 1 without protection,  
gas for turn 2  
game 7 turn 1 with protection on the   
draw, risky if they counter ritual,  
mull 5  
game 8 turn 2 without protection  
game 9 turn 1 without protection mull 5  
game 10 turn 1 without protection, gas for turn 2  

um, that's a pretty good track record if you ask me. I'll post more but, jeez.

List if you ask. 
 
edit:why does this look like a wall of text now?
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-10-30 18:16:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> the trick is to overload on things they absolutely can't let resolve. short list:

Confinement(with two enchantresses)
helm obv(in concert with R.I.P.)
choke
city of solitude
sigil of the empty throne
These are just the things that don't tend to blank their deck. humility, grass and sphere
rek offense. then
blue splash: in the eye of chaos, energy field
black splash: doomwake giant(yes seriously)
non rest in peace: replenish 
So yeah, GW stax really. jam lock pieces and bombs until they die.        


 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-10-30 17:59:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Actually, if constucted correctly gw can seriously give bgx strategys serious fits. If you want to beat those decks leyline of sanctity in the board as a three of,  humility, and the sterling
groves and mirri's guiles you should already be playing are just a kick in the nuts.

ugin still kills you though. Race it I guess ? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-09-25 21:16:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah my combo matchup is garbage, but I'm thinking of bringing it cause of the high volume
of more fair stuff. does this sound acceptable?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-09-25 20:26:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thanks this is exactly the sort of of thing i was looking for. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-09-25 20:06:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Sure, I'll just put 100$ a month into volcs. Just have to quit playing magic for a year.
Seriously, I think its more realistic to trade/sell the things I have for the things I need.
Question is, what do I ditch? Most of this stuff is format staples.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-09-25 19:55:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> looks interesting, is the deck playable without show and tell in the board?   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-09-25 19:29:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> what would you suggest I get rid of for the volcanic islands? is there a remotely reasonable
interim manabase i could use?(not talking steam vents, more about some number of usea,
one volc, fetches, ????, profit) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-09-25 19:20:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I kind of regret mentioning the budget angle honestly. I only mentioned it to explain that costs are higher here. Another way to think of this is given what I have, what are my best "paths into legacy"?    I'm a little scared because I mostly built storm then people packed
stuff to hate omni out of the meta and I was stuck holding a pile of hot garbage. I don't
want that to happen again so I want something more universally playable.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-09-25 19:09:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> the cheap half ie not chain lightning,eidolon,or goblin guide </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-09-25 18:47:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Should I buy in to fetches at this point or has the ship sailed?
I want to get in and flip them in a few months, but I don't know 
how much more they'll go up.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Have a bunch of bad legacy decks, don't know what to do </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-09-25 18:24:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> My legacy collection is moderate but missing extremely key things so i don't know what deck to build next. I want something competitive in my meta. my meta is:
lots of grixis,
lots of miracles,
some stoneblade,
the guy who top 8 jersey with landstill (still playing it,still kicking ass),
a couple omnishow players,
a smattering of other things

I have:
enchantress(fun, but I want to start winning matches eventually)
tes(minus volcanic islands,bad in meta I'm told)
ant(minus same, bad in meta I'm told)
grixis delver(minus same)
junk rhino nic fit(minus top)
food chain  (bad in meta)
wrong half of a burn deck

high end stuff:
set of forces,2 seas ,trop, taiga, scrubland,savannah, bayou,2 wastes,2 ven cliques,

key things I'm missing: UG , UR and BR fetchlands

What the heck do i do with this? Help!   Keep in mind i live in canada and our dollar is 70% of american,
so most budget options aren't actually budget anymore. For example Flip Jace is $65 ($65!) here 
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
