<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject2045</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-11-13 13:28:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This has been done. Found some party invitations to friends, pictures, etc.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-11-12 20:34:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thanks for the great, detailed response.

I lived there for the entire time - 1 year, roughly.

One important detail - we broke our 3 year mortgage and paid a hefty penalty.




 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-11-12 18:03:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Haha I admit nothing!! But seriously. I was living at a friends house temporarily as my parents moved (without me, waa!). A friend and I really didn't want to rent and bought a place instead.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-11-12 16:35:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Criminal charges are not in question. It's simply a monetary. I owe 'X' in taxes. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-11-12 16:10:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You and your friend made a business deal (split everything).
Reply: So purchasing a home with someone because we couldn't do so separately means this is a business purchase? 

Invested (bought a house and did reno's).
Reply: Many people do this for both business and non-business.

Sold the investment for a profit ("we made a little money").
Reply: Many people sell their homes and make a profit on them, so that point doesn't hold much weight.

I'm not really seeing your points here. You're just assuming. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The CRA is claiming I didn't live in my home and used it for business purposes. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-11-12 15:04:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> A friend and I purchased a house a few years back with plans only to live and slowly renovate. Everything was split down the middle and we renovated the entire basement in the first year. 

Shortly after, I decided I'd like to sell the house and move closer to work as my commute was taking a toll. Sale completes, we make a little money and we move on. I rent for 3 years and then decide to buy again. 

Now the CRA is claiming we worked together in a business manner and should have taxed our earnings as such.

In their initial investigation I worked with and provided them with various information...really just asking if this was my intent and if I lived there for the duration. We also submitted a letter from our cable provider stating we received service for that time. 

Shortly after I receive a notice claiming I am guilty of negligent tax submission and have to pay a large sum. 

I lived in this house for the entire time as my primary address. Of course people buy houses, renovate and expect a return at some point, but in this case it was a faster than expected turn around. 

Has anyone ran into this issue and have any advice to share? Seems like I'm guilty before proven innocent here... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-11-10 23:28:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The WHOLE song!!?!?!  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> How 30 year old men waste bathroom time at work on Snapchat. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-11-10 18:20:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-11-07 22:35:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> She can get it. Still.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-10-31 05:55:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Native advertising
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> I never draw it doodle but I found a great app! SketchBook! - Sick Pig </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-08-13 04:18:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-08-08 21:19:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This is a horse shit PR stunt in effort to keep her relevant.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Hotel shower thought: why do hotels provide copious amounts of soaps and lotions but no tooth paste? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-08-03 17:47:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
