<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject8335</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-09-23 18:03:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I think I meant black.  I was referring to the racial classification, not the colour  -_-  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-09-23 04:46:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Well, at least they are diverse shades of black. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-09-23 03:04:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It sounds like you have chronic fatigue syndrome.  It's an awful thing, but also one with a lot of ways you can get treatment.  There's a world of things to live for.  You can feel better, if you just get some help. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-09-23 02:57:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I would always, always recommend against playing games (which is inevitably what happens when you try to find ways to get someone to pursue you, or try to seem/be unavailable).  I'd say be open and honest with her, without being needy/pushy.  Be thoughtful and romantic w/o being clingy, and if she's right for things will progress organically and honestly, and after a little while have the relationship talk. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Retiring boss gives staff $1000 for each year of work </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-09-17 14:59:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-09-16 23:09:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I hate that too.  Also, when you drive up to a drive-thru window and they stare blankly at you, waiting for you to just give them money.  Use your words, damnit! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Teacher in Edmonton, Alberta fired for giving 0s for unsubmitted assignments </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-09-15 02:23:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-09-15 01:50:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I don't even know what Romney said, but I can guarantee: yes. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-09-15 01:43:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> DUDE.  That is sick.  I feel for you but srsly, take a second to wipe the blood off your face  -_- </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Seagull takes camera from tourist, shoots video! </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-09-13 18:54:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-09-08 17:16:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I would try not to let this bother me.  You've made a huge self-improvement physically and you happen to have some "scars" to show how far you've come!  Nothing to be ashamed of there.  If some people see your scars when you're on the beach/wherever and finds them unattractive... well, who cares?  That's on them. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-09-07 03:51:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Holy shit Dan.  First, you nominate Ian: OK.  THEN Ian is HANDED a competition to win (a puzzle?  OBVS a runaway win for Ian).  THEN Danielle?  
But truly, I will miss Frank.  I know most of y'all aren't fans, but I love that man.
Great episode so far. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-09-07 02:47:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I bought a vegan wrap (tofu and veggies) at a supposedly ultra-fresh/healthy restaurant in NYC last month.  The name escapes me.. Fresh Something-or-other.  Anyway, I ate almost half of it before I realised that most of the tofu was actually still wrapped in paper.  I`m not sure if paper is vegan, but I was unimpressed.

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-09-02 00:28:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> 1 - ultimately it depends on who the WINNER is.  There's only one first prize, and having 1 of your 3 players win is better than having 3 in the top 7. 

2 - Dan.  After all, he's the only one still coaching, no?  Plus, Boogie and Janelle couldn't even maintain their players' trust and loyalty. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-08-31 17:20:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Personally, I would probably classify as a hindu, but like many religious people, I believe that logic is not a sufficient method to discover the most fundamental truths of human existence; that ultimate reality is fundamentally immaterial and therefore predominantly outside the scope of science.  God/religious truth cannot be found in a closed system, like a tunnel of logic.  Rather, God/truth is revealed to one through spiritual practise, which involves an open mind, an open spirit, and at least a little bit of faith.  

You say you are a scientist, and an atheist, and are looking to understand faith.  Here you automatically have a problem.  Faith involves belief in that which cannot be "proven", but "science" generally disallows belief in that which cannot be proven.  In this search of yours, the first thing you have to be prepared to do is accept that 
a) "science" may not be the best path to lead you to religious truth and 
b) God may plausibly exist, and be knowable to us. 
Only if/when you get to a point where you can accept those 2 things will you be ready to truly begin your search. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-08-31 02:42:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Mad Men.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-08-31 02:41:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Good old fashioned introversion.  You, me, and about 25% of the rest of the general population have the same thing going on. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-08-31 02:38:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If you hate your major, unless you have a career lined up completely unrelated to what you're doing/studying, it'd be insane NOT to switch.  Life is short, and college (if you're in the states, which I assume you are) is expensive.  2 years isn't much in the grand scheme of things.  Study something you don't hate.  Ideally, something you love. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-08-31 02:28:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> *ma'am... and I actually have other things that need doing... enjoy! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-08-31 02:25:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I bet you could do 24,000 comments yourself at this rate, oracle...  Good luck! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-08-31 02:22:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> isuncjdhfjhjk 828 hhJJloveFhz nn%%46gg </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Teenage pot smoking tied to loss of IQ </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-08-27 23:58:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-08-26 15:35:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I love the mild irony here!  Poor sap comes to r/grammar to ask a basic grammatical question. Top comment is a suggestion to prioritise by making his titles more specific; top commenter has left no grammatical guidance.  Lolz! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-08-26 15:30:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> "the" is probably what you want, though "a" would work if you're having a more casual conversation about having bought **a** book.  Suppose you saw Leonardo DiCaprio at the bakery.  If the focus was on the fact that you saw any old actor you may say, "I saw an actor yesterday, Leonardo DiCaprio." If your emphasis was that you saw him SPECIFICALLY, you'd say "the." Depends on the context. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-08-25 04:56:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I find ALL interesting people are geeks in at least one domain (usuallly a few!).. and most Buddhists I've met TEND to be interesting people.  I'd draw a Venn diagram here if I could, but I can't. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-08-25 04:18:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What is the meaning of life? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-08-24 04:31:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> No.  But then, I'm not in the USA. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-08-24 02:27:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm definitely not a proponent of bowing down to injustice, incompetence, or disrespect.   What I was saying is that the worth you extract from teaching is largely irrespective of these things.  Absolutely, fight against the bullshit--I do that constantly, as do many good teachers--but someone who is meant to teach doesn't leave because the system is the system. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-08-24 01:17:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I believe I will be happier for having quit teaching. I will make more money. I will have more time. I will no longer sacrifice myself for the sake of others' children. I would like to go back someday when the system finally figures out how lucky it is that people are so dedicated to teaching.

This is a great quote exemplifying why this woman should have left teaching.  By contrast, what schools need most are those who are not looking for great money, and are willing to make sacrifices, sometimes significant ones, for the sake of the children they teach.  Nor should we wait for the system, usually one bureaucratic and corporate-minded in nature, to recognise our worth.  You may not be "recognised" by the administration, the policy makers, or parents, but what matters is the kids in front of you, and being the best teacher you can for each of them, never giving into cynicism or jadedness.  That's where your true worth as a teacher comes from, and its rewards are beyond measure. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-08-23 04:48:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It depends on your qualifications.  If your French is AMAZING, or if it's your first language, you can often walk right into a job.  But if your French is simply passable, or if you're just *basically* bilingual, you'll probably have to rough it for a year or two at least. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-08-22 17:30:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hey. I'm a teacher in a place in Canada that (like mannnny places) is continually cutting back on funding and teachers, everywhere.  One thing I always recommend to people just finishing their degree is to go around to different schools and actually MEET principals in person.  For an administrator, talking to a genuine, enthusiastic person for 5 minutes leaves much more of an impression than a verbal correspondence (like e-mails or letters).  

Here, you HAVE to supply teach, usually for a couple of years, before you can land something more permanent, but supplying at different schools is a great way for administration to get a feel for what kind of teacher you are.  If you're good, and/or have potential, that should be recognised.  And things come up mid-year consistently.  People have babies, get sick, move, and quit, allll the time.  You just finished your masters degree?  WAAAAY too early to throw in the towel.  Make contacts, stay optimistic, and good luck :) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-08-21 21:55:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> $100,000. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-08-21 21:55:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It does seem kinda weak compared to the other "big" reality shows in the states.  The 1st (english) Big Brother in Canada is casting right now, and the prize will be a paltry $100,000... almost not even worth it! (...almost) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-08-20 14:53:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> On TV, was Skyler censored in the IFT episode?  I was watching on the internet at that time. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-08-20 14:51:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Not on AMC.  Two letters were blurred out. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-08-18 19:27:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> K, stupid question: what's non-vegan about most wine?  Something to do with insects getting in the wine? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-08-16 17:57:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Small city in New Brunswick, Canada.  My fan, and if the windows are open, the distant sound of highway traffic (huzzzzzzzzzz).  Occasionally, the thumps of my elephant-footed neighbour upstairs. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Reddit, what is something you routinely lie about? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-08-14 18:14:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Perhaps as a leftover from being a semi-pathological liar as a child, I will almost always lie about basic details of my life when I first meet people: my age, my job, my relationship status, where I've lived, occasionally my name...  Granted, never in times when it socially "counts", but almost always when I meet people I know I'll never have a working/social relationship with.  What about you, reddit?  Are you a liar??? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-08-14 18:02:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It sounds like social anxiety disorder.  To reiterate e36: you should really really try cognitive behavioural therapy.  Good luck. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-07-08 14:42:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> When around her and a small group of people, if you're close to her, you could say, "Do you smell BO?" kind of innocuously, as if it may be someone else.  She might get the hint. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-04-20 18:41:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> When I was 5, my friend's father, Bill,* began driving us to and from kindergarten.  At least once a week he would drink coffee in the car, which TERRIFIED me as, you know, "drinking and driving" was a surefire way to die immediately.  I tried to convince my friend that she had to make her father stop driving when he drank, but she didn't understand how dangerous he was being.  After a few weeks of this, I told my mother that I didn't want to drive with Bill anymore as sometimes he was "drinking and driving" first thing in the morning.  Hilarity ensued.

*name has been changed to protect the guilty </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-04-20 16:35:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What... a... trans... forma...tion! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-04-06 17:02:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I neither agree nor disagree with the trainers' decision, but I look at it like this: their response to your wish to miss part of your training may be strict, but it is what it is, and you did make a commitment that you should honour.  From a more cosmic perspective: you will have an opportunity to learn from this Kathryn Budig (or whoever else can best help you with that part of your practise) when the time is right.  

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-03-30 00:07:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I always know how to spell this word.  My username may or may not prove this. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-03-20 23:33:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm sorry that you're struggling so much with this.  That you recognise your ambivalence--and the "poisoning" that is or may be occurring--is in itself very important.  Can a buddhist, or anyone abiding by the principle of *ahimsa*, be employed by a military organisation?  The US military is--and sorry if this is unwanted conjecture--much more served toward imperialism than, say, peace-keeping.  In general it is more violent and destructive than peaceful and constructive (globally/politically).  Ideologically the US military in general is in opposition to *ahimsa*, and while not directly physically harming anyone or thing as a reservist, you are still employed by this institution, and are part of something ultimately quite destructive and harmful to much of the world.  What you may be called on to do in the future may further distress you, and negatively affect your karma.  (If you're interested, there's a short but interesting wiki article on ahimsa, as well as some discussion of Buddhism and the military, historically and ideologically).

You say that you "need" the army to pay for your education and life.  Isn't it truer to say that it is more convenient for you to use the army to pay for these things?  Are there not, in fact, other alternatives that, though perhaps less convenient, would ease your ambivalence, and leave you happier, and freer? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-03-19 23:57:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> about 2/3 of the way through the hatha yoga pradipika I realised that I (as a female, that is) really was probably never the intended audience.. it kind of messed with my head.  Then I started questioning the entire asana canon--what about the fact that men and women are simply BUILT differently?  What if what stimulates pranic flow / heightens prana sakti / etc in a man doesn't actually do the same thing in a female body?  What if I should actually have a different practise?   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-03-19 22:57:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> A true writer can write well about nearly anything.  And those hypothetical English professors have probably read a few things he should: Orwell.  de Montaigne.  Woolf.  Pick up a copy of Harpers, or the New Yorker.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-03-19 22:42:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Don't toy with us, Aaron Paul!!!  Our expectations were already enormously high!!!   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-03-17 22:53:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I teach grade 9 English, and usually pay more heed to medians than averages.  If the median is 60-70%, I feel like that's probably appropriate.  Anything below 60 has to be re-evaluated, either because the test was too difficult, or the kids just didn't. get. it.  A median approaching the 80% mark is usually an indication that the kids have mastered the material, or the test was too easy. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-03-17 22:03:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> back and forth...forever.  irrelevant, but still awesome :) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-03-16 02:21:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I've met approximately 0 available straight men like the yogis described here.  But... nice to know they exist :) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-03-15 01:57:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So sad.  What about a type of intervention where you get everyone who loves/cares about her together to try to... get her back?   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-03-14 22:12:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Just tried to submit this, but apparently you did.  This album is BLOWING MY MIND :D </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-03-13 22:36:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> A lot of great points in this thread!  Another perspective is that instead of viewing something as "self-confidence" (which is obviously SELF-centred) you could see it as LACK of insecurity, or the ABSENCE of fear, or anxiety.  It's not a feeling of assurance of the 'ego', but the absence of negative and useless insecurities and attachments. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-03-12 23:40:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This is an outline of [Sivananda Yoga style of meditation](http://www.sivananda.org/teachings/fivepoints.html#meditation) .  Also some interesting insights into positive thinking. Whatever path you choose, enjoy :D </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-03-11 15:16:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> ~~possible spoiler alert~~ **absolute definite total spoiler alert** </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-03-11 04:11:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> BAHAHAHA!!!!  You are leagues below all the thresholds here.  I like you :D </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-03-11 03:32:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> YES.  That movie is such a beautiful mindfuck... gahhh </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-03-10 05:09:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> "I know you are, but what am I?"  Sometime circa 1990.  Not an original, obviously, but still... felt good. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-03-09 15:09:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> * how out of control my monkey mind was and 
* that first time I realised my mind had actually quieted
* time is an illusion (yes OP!)
* the perceiver and the perceived are one. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-03-09 04:03:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> lolllllllllllll!!!!  just stumbled upon this via "random"..... this is an amazing subreddit.  Thanks whynotbeetc. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-03-08 01:16:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Now, now.  The real (or "literary") Khal Drogo was a sensitive and even sometimes-gentle lover :D </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-03-07 00:56:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Um, kinda weird.. I don't scream when reliving/thinking of an embarrassing situation, but I always verbalise SOMETHING random.  Usually it's just a word, or a short sentence to distract myself, but I have to SAY something.  Kinda neurotic, right?   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-03-07 00:46:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> All of my experiences with lucid dreams are, sadly, actually semi-lucid dreams just like the one you described.  I just.. can't make them true lucid!  :( </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-03-06 22:43:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> buyers beware!!!!  men who promise not to sell a girl to the russian mafia always, always do. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Django Django - Default [art rock].  This is delightful/infectious. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-03-06 15:54:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-03-06 02:52:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The tanning salon "base tan" that a lot of people insist they need before a mid-winter sunvacation really only provides an SPF of about 4, while exposing you to insane uvradiation.. Pretty useless.  Wear a high spf suncreen as per your plan, and what the folks below said. :)
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Over Confident Ginger </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-03-06 02:33:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-03-05 16:27:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> My meditation practise is probably more yogic/hindu than "buddhist", but I try to use mala beads a couple of times a week at least, which I got at a localish general-spiritual-materials store.   My mantra is "OM."  A mantra can be very effective as it gives you something positive to focus on.  It may also be helpful to have a specific space in your house/apartment set aside for meditation, as a) you will naturally slip into "meditation" mode easier and b) after a period of time, it will become infused with a positive energy.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-03-04 19:49:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This sounds like one part friendzoning, three parts mind-fucking.  walk quickly to the nearest exit.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-02-25 19:26:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> As some have implied, as interesting/dramatic an experience as this may be, this Vegan Week may end up looking like a slow-mo car crash.  Your body and mind have become used to a very specific kind of diet and lifestyle, and "going vegan" for a week will probably result in you fantasising about/craving steak and omelettes.  A gradual change in your diet leading up to a Vegan Week in, say, 2 months time, would be a far more beneficial experience, and healthier for your mind and body--and WAYYYY more likely to stick (if sticking's something you'd be into).  I went from being an omnivore to a lacto-veg in about 6 weeks, and if you can commit 2 months to a more organic experiment, that's what I'd recommend. Far easier and more seamless than a cold turkey temporary moratorium on meat, cheese, eggs, fish, and any of the other animal-based shiz you've been eating on what I assume is a near-daily basis for the past X decades.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-02-18 03:36:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I've been wanting to read 'In Search of Lost Time' for ages, but feel immediately turned off by any translations titled 'Remembrances of Things Past.' I know many translators have had their reasons for such a translation, but I just...can't...accept it. I judge the entire translation on the liberties taken with the re-titling. Unreasonable? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-02-14 03:02:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm reading 1q84 by Murakami right now.  It comprises exactly half of all Japanese novels I've ever read, but it is beautiful and strange and has infiltrated my consciousness in ways usually only brilliant writing can. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-02-14 00:40:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This may contradict or repeat several other comments, but these are my rec's:
*eat either a snack or a small meal 2-3 hours before practicing.  a lot of asanas involve so much abdominal movement you don't want to be either digesting or completely starving (not to mention not having enough energy)
*have an empty bladder and don't drink water DURING yoga unless you really have to 
*listen to your body.  if doing a posture makes you nauseated/dizzy/experience pain/etc, STOP.  go at your own pace.
*focus on your breath as much as possible.  if, like you mention below, you're "panting" then you're pushing yourself WAY too hard.  Not sure what class you're in, but 1.5 hours is a bit long for a beginner..ideally there would be specific beginner's classes you could take that may be exactly what you need. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-01-09 17:26:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> "Excape." 
"Girls" for females of all ages.  
"Cunt", ever.  
"Oh-em-gee." 
And, most egregiously, "seen" when it should be "saw."  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
