<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject6580</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-15 00:22:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Every third post I make here.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-15 00:15:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm from Chicago Heights and can pick up on a Blues Brothers reference from a mile away - I didn't. :( </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> When someone asks me a serious question, my brain immediately searches for a relevant late-80s action movie quote. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-15 00:11:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-15 00:09:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Either Bruce or Julian.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-15 00:08:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> While you're sitting at your computer on a Friday evening, I'm knee-deep in pseudo-roast beef and Arby's special red ranch sauce. Endgame. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-15 00:07:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Interdimensional reptoids. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-15 00:06:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Why would a giant octopus win in a fight with Godzilla? Not "would" but "why." </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-15 00:04:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I was just joking, dude. The modern tractor enables hundreds of millions to eat regularly.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-15 00:01:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Letting Alan Rickman drop prematurely at the end of Die Hard. His face and body movement was perfect.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-15 00:00:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hold on, I'm trying to think of a dick joke.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-14 23:59:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Meth addict.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-14 23:59:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Jesus Murphy! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-14 23:45:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Sir, please. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-14 23:40:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Apple Cinnamon vs Honey Nut.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-14 23:12:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I don't know what I'd do without my tractor. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-14 23:08:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Like the other dude said: Old Navy items may last six weeks or six years. You might just be stuck with them for awhile, bro.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-14 23:06:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Coincidentally, he did save me money. Maybe all those bar tabs I picked up throughout the years even out with the shoe purchase. ;) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> I've reached that sliver of years in my thirties where I dress like the middle-managment type that I am and play music from the '90s with the windows down hoping that someone, anyone goes "That was an amazing song." </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-14 21:42:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-14 21:31:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Oh, Docs, how I miss thee.


I purchased three pairs of 1460s (which were then made in England) in my late teens and early twenties, all of which I beat the hell out of. One pair lasted me two years as a laborer for a plumbing outfit I... labored for. Not bad considering they aren't a true work boot. One pair lasted me five, FIVE, years in the food service industry. That's five years of walking miles and miles a day for fifty to sixty hours a week. Astonishing. The last pair, which were my casual go-to in the beginning of their life, finally gave up the ghost two years back after long ago being relegated to the miscellaneous handy man/painting/I-don't-care-what-happens-to-these spot. They were at least eight years old. Wow.

After Dr. Martens ceased large scale production in England, I have purchased three pairs. The first pair took almost a month to break in, but once they were, they were really comfortable. Until the sole split down the middle after only having them for four months. Hmmm... Well, I chalked it up to a fluke, and order another pair shortly thereafter. This pair was sub-Walmart GARBAGE. The "leather" started cracking after five or six weeks of wear, and...whatever, they were trash. The third pair were plastic-looking leather, and, just... I can't even talk about it. It was the nail in the coffin. I'm done with a company which I once loved; a company that used to make a quality product. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-14 19:56:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Whenever a candidate for office calls for "bringing back manufacturing," you must realize that those days are gone for good.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-14 18:46:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Number 36 is killing it.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What percentage of posters on here actually know what the hell they're talking about? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-14 18:31:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-14 18:27:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> William Jefferson Clinton is on the *board*. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-14 18:26:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> George C. Scott being hit in the crotch with a football.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-14 18:26:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Stunning. Where was this taken?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-14 18:00:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> An oldie, but an okay-eee. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-14 17:43:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hi-top leather sneakers with Velcro straps. Just, uuugggghhhhhh.... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-14 17:42:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Looking at this and then looking around my office makes me hurt inside. Looks like I'll be going for a hike this weekend! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-14 16:51:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> My grandfather, who was in the Marines in WWII, once told me that the scar on his stomach came from a crazy, bayonet-wielding Japanese soldier. Turns out he had his appendix out. He also told me he was being transported on the *Silver Sides* (which was an actual US submarine in the war) and couldn't handle it, so he "stormed" up to the captain and demanded to be let off, to which the captain replied, "Sure, Tom." 

The man could bullshit.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-14 16:37:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> A pair of Old Navy canvas sneakers. 

A friend brought them for me seven years ago as a wedding gift (*super* cheap dude, but he's a good guy) because we went "tropical beach" for our honeymoon, and I've beat on them every summer since. They've outlasted two pairs of Sperry's. They couldn't have been more than twenty bucks, but it appears they're indestructible.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-14 16:31:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm envious of those who will eventually explore such a place first-hand.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-14 15:42:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The tweed suit and beard *does* lend a bit of credibility.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Wearing a new shirt to work pretty much guarantees that I'll spill coffee on it. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-14 15:32:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-14 15:14:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> O, empty coffee cup, where hath your delicious beverage gone?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-14 04:09:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Uhhh, that's a negative.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-14 04:01:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> When I ask my wife if we can have a three-way with her sister.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-14 03:59:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Everyone on *this* team gets a trophy, bud.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-14 03:58:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The Abrahamic God would be backed further into the corner. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-14 03:56:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That every single black guy I delivered to bellowed "WHO IS IT?!" after I knocked on the door, and most were super polite after they saw it was the delivery guy.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-14 03:52:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> There was absolutely no grab-ass or tomfoolery when that dude was around.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-14 03:51:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> In this day and age, *every* actoree is a winner. Every. Single. Actoree. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-14 02:19:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Puma Whirlwind Classic, bro.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-14 02:19:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Once I hit thirty, I had to put my last pair to rest; it just seemed like their time in my life was over. And it should've happened sooner, as they're murder on my feet. But, yeah, Chucks are pretty gender neutral.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-14 02:16:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That's in really good condition. Nice find!  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-14 01:55:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Playing bass for The Who must've been amazing.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-14 01:54:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Be cool, trust the universe, and don't worry about what you can't control.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-14 01:52:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> All the girls who couldn't understand why the movie Titanic didn't have a happy ending.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-14 01:50:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> People don't find too many duffel bags full of heads here. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-14 01:06:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> No Breaker Morant reference? You make me SICK.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-14 01:05:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Blow me.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-14 01:04:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I will never forget you, Cumbomb. Oh, hey, I can just type "Cumbomb." </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-14 01:02:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Unity. And government subsidised pastry.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-14 00:20:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> An extreme close up of a vagina. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-13 19:57:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Michigan's huge, bro.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-13 19:54:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm hoping to be reincarnated a few hundred times in order to see a full-on galaxy rise.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-13 19:48:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Had their staff given me a definitive "no" right off the bat, the whole process wouldn't have left such a bad taste in my mouth.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-13 19:36:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> She borrowed a pen from me at work one day. After talking a few times over the course of some weeks, we went on a "date." Ended up getting hammered and she let me put my mouth on her vagina. After that, we were golden. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-13 19:25:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I had a pair of ASOS brogues (don't remember the model name) and they came looking quite nice and they were reasonably comfortable from the get-go. After a few weeks, they started creasing horribly, getting loose grain all over and about four months in some of the stitching started to fray, and another month later it failed. I contacted customer service and was put on an endless loop of transfers, carbon copies, and "Uhhhhh..."s. I would not buy from them again.

Shirts would be another story, but this is my experience with the company.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-13 19:07:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> For what it's worth, the MaxWear sole on the Thorogood will most likely last longer and they'll be much more comfortable right out of the box. 

I've had a pair of 877s (I can't imagine too many differences with the 875) and Thorogoods Mocs, and if I were to buy again I'd think I'd go with the Thorogood.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-13 18:52:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Of course he does.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-13 17:48:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Try to change the printer settings by pressing random buttons and, eventually, by *mashing* them.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-13 17:45:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> How to convince people that I'm an expert in a certain area with Wikipedia open on another tab.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-13 17:14:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> App-ordered and drone-delivered. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-13 16:59:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm not a big steak guy; I get a craving maybe two or three times per year. But, this looks *good*.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-13 16:43:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> "You better hurry up, I'm in dutch with the wife!" </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
