<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject9366</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-29 06:16:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> At work, I hardly use my MacBook Pro directly. I connect it with a huge monitor, a keyboard and a mouse, because it's more comfortable that way.
What if phones, or especially tablets, some day become as powerful as to replace my laptop, with supporting OS and everything of course. I might as well get rid of my laptop then. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-29 06:09:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What about something similar to what they showed in Minority Report? A phone projects a 3D hologram of a keyboard on a table and you type directly on it.
That would require lot of computing power that OP is talking about. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Tutorial suggestions for learning Lightroom? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-29 05:45:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hi,
Apologies, if this question has already been asked before.

Can you suggest 1-2 good tutorials to learn Lightroom? I had bought [Adobe Lightroom Crash Course: Start Photo Editing Today!](https://www.udemy.com/adobe-lightroom-5/learn/v4/overview) on Udemy- anyone tried that before?

Thanks. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-29 05:38:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Just beginning to realize that folks go to such lengths for music. And here I am, all happy from the ordinary sound oozing out from a bluetooth speaker!

Thanks for the subreddit- will check that out. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-29 05:32:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I like photography- used to take decent pictures using my DSLR. But then I realized that photo-editing is as important, otherwise my photos will always miss that oomphh factor. Now, there is this learning curve that I need to cross before I make more progress. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-29 05:19:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What happens if you threw Marilyn Monroe to the wolves, while she was wearing high heels? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-29 05:17:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Throw me to the wolves and I'll return leading the pack *or never return at all*. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-29 05:13:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Where did you write this post from?! Not from the apartment, I hope. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-29 05:10:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'd like to learn photography editing, using Lightroom or Photoshop. But aargghh, never started any serious work on it! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-29 05:03:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hmmm, makes sense. I never liked the idea of *owning* things that I could avoid, but I guess that is important to some folks.

On the other hand, "it's not just 1s and 0s being played back"- *that* is just in your head! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-29 04:54:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I didn't know vinyl has superior sound quality. Gotta check that out sometime.

By the way, will vinyl also beat music playing on Bose speakers? :-P </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-29 04:49:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yes, the uncertainty factor is always there. Still, I think I can take my chances.

I guess the side effect of pay increase, both in current company and in future as you mentioned, is going to be significant. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Depth vs Breadth of experience. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-28 21:36:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I am a Software Developer at a big MNC. I have two options in near future:

* Stick with my current team, where I have a decent chance of getting a promotion by next October. Pros: Bigger paycheck after promotion. Cons: I have (sort of) learnt almost everything that is there to be offered. So, won't improve much on technical front.
* Screw the promotion and move to some other team, and learn more about a new and (possibly) interesting technical and business domain.

Thoughts? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-28 20:41:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> i don't get it. what's the motivation behind owning vinyl records?

i too am a big fan of Pink Floyd. but i might as well listen to them on Spotify. why the need to *own* the records, that too vinyl? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-26 18:28:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Interesting! Do you blog or tweet often, where I can learn more about your experiences? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-25 05:14:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Please add me! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
