<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject2963</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-10 20:12:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> They are just fuck buddies. If I were to show any emotion toward them they would probably end it with me. Since they just want to be fuck buddies too. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-10 20:11:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The ones I have came with my computer. Windows Media Player and one called Movies   TV. I will check out MPC-HC. I was thinking up downloading that over VLC but the reddit thread I made on it had more people saying VLC was better. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-10 20:08:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I actually have to go through all the videos and rename some of them that were doubles but haven't had the time. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-10 20:06:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I masturbate to it whenever my fuck buddies are busy. I upload the videos to streaming/torrent sites once in a while. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-10 20:02:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I only use it as default because it supports a wide range of video types. Naughty America's videos from 2010-2012 are in the f4v format and I was too lazy to convert them to mp4 or a format that could be used in other media players. I do have other ones. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> I purchased a Brazzers subscription for 9.95 and downloaded 2.24 TB of their videos AMA. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-10 19:56:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> They aren't the only company I have videos from my total collection is at 80 TB now. AMA

Here is proof.
[the size of the folder](http://i.imgur.com/DeNWrTp.png) [Screen shot of one folder](http://i.imgur.com/xh0tycE.png) [Screenshot of another folder](http://i.imgur.com/YgzDdVI.png) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-10 06:56:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Minnesota just lost so unfortunately the darkest timeline is still possible. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> If Knicks beat Sixers what is the worse thing that can happen in terms of draft position? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-10 02:38:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I am hoping they lose but the Sixers have a worse record than Knicks so it is possible the Knicks win. What would be the difference in draft position in who the knicks might be able to pick if they don't move up in lottery after a win. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-08 17:55:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Reddit has always been like that. With the upvote system it makes the site favor lurking than creating content and discussions. Since if you create a thread that disagrees with the majority or share a minority view you could lose a lot of Karma. I learned that the hard way when I  was happy the Knicks won a game. Apparently a lot of the people on that sub are rooting for the knicks to lose all their games. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-07 05:58:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> ok </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-07 05:58:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I am aware of that. I felt I need to add some info. I am the one who says we should use protection. It is often turned on me and they say I must have something since I want to wear a condom. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-07 05:36:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I should mention that I am a male the people I bang are women and trans women. With trans women this baby thing isn't something I have to worry about.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Is it ever a good idea to go through with an encounter with someone who says wearing a [condom is a deal breaker]? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-07 04:28:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I have had several encounters who said that. They either wanted to fuck bare or give head to me without condom. I say I would prefer to wear a condom and am often rejected if I don't go along with unprotected sex. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What is the most unprofessional thing a doctor has said to you during a visit? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-06 03:57:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> So, the top post on reddit is making fun of this sub. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-04 06:49:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Why is that allowed? I have never seen any other sub get made fun of and make it to the #1 post on this site. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-03 08:00:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> She is a G/G (lesbian) performer. The joke is that she is doing a scene with a man. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-03 07:25:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I think people would be more likely to post things that go against the majority. If you say something in a popular sub that goes against their views that could be an instant 40 downvotes.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> If Derrick Rose were to retire following this season would he be a Hall Of Famer? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-03 05:32:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-03 00:08:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Done </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-02 23:19:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> No. He worded what I was asking right. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-02 22:30:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> They are neither. I wanted to post examples but didn't want to offend anyone with nudity. They are cisgender men looking for men. Here is an example

https://newyork.craigslist.org/brx/cas/6070473175.html </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> On craigslist why are there gay men who post in the t4m (transgender for men) section? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-02 21:48:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I am lurking that section and there are ad created by gay cisgender men. They aren't trans and don't even crossdress. That post in the transgender for male section. Why don't they post in the men for men section since that is what they are looking for and it correctly represents them.

Bonus and possibly related question. Why do gay men respond to men who create women for men personals. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Abbott   Costello - Two Tens For A Five </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-02 19:10:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Abbott   Costello - Loan Me 50 cents </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-02 08:00:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-02 07:24:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Just comment and i will upvote you. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> I need some comment karma so I can make a thread on r/videos I will return the favor. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-02 07:24:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-02 07:19:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> hey </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-02 07:11:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> upvote done </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-02 07:10:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I upvoted both of you. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-02 07:10:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> done </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-02 07:09:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That is one explanation for why he always wore turtlenecks. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Rich kid beats gang-rape case because he didnt enjoy it </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-31 09:02:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> After threat of boycott, deal brings U.S. women back for hockey world championships in Plymouth </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-31 06:56:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Are you a slow walker or a fast walker? Why? Why not? How do you feel about someone who is the opposite? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-30 06:00:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-30 05:53:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I know you mean federally but it is legal in my state. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Sex offender wrongly banned from Internet, court rules </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-30 05:44:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Racehorse called 'President Trump' castrated and renamed Fake News </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-29 21:01:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Dave Chapelle's comeback accused of transphobia, homophobia </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-28 21:13:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Woman uses Tinder profile to scam gullible men out of money </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-28 05:18:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Transgender girl says she is rejected by straight guys for having male parts. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-27 21:07:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-27 19:56:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It wasn't a stunt. Someone said the cops were coming and he jumped across roofs to try to get away. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Memorial grows for teen killed jumping building to building in Bushwick </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-27 19:38:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Viewers miss game winning Carolina-Kentucky shot as game is interrupted for a weather report. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-27 05:04:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-27 00:26:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yanks have one injury right now. Didi Gregorius is hurt. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-25 22:45:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I think even if the Yankees go 162-0 the tabloids would try to create a negative article just for views. It is what they do. As someone who follows the knicks it happens way more often with them. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-24 03:38:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Skyla Novea </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-24 03:16:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Tina Kay </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
