<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject6782</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-05-24 07:57:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> How did you manage to get an exemption to drive it? Or haven't you yet?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-05-24 03:56:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> But you bought the car? You don't have the car currently? Oh how convienient. Good luck driving it on your Ps anyway.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-05-24 03:51:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Clearly for you, yes. I don't know why you'd lie about it. The only reason I'm doing this is because I wouldn't want someone else using a picture of my car as their own.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-05-24 03:47:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> No, how about a picture of proof with the said car and a piece of paper with your username and date on it?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-05-24 03:13:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> 3.0 came with Brembos standard in NZ? Didn't know this. I'm guessing only with some 3.0R spec.Bs and not the normal 3.0R?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-05-23 18:36:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It was owned by someone on a Subaru Club I am part of, picture was taken in 2007. I also may or may not know who OP is. If you don't believe me, ask OP for a picture of proof.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-05-23 18:05:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The face-lifted model, spec.B in AUS comes with Bilstein suspension, can come with 6 spd STI manual (normal GT only in Auto), different front fascia and different rims. I think some other small things as well but I can't really remember too well, someone might want to add in.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> I DON'T CARE WHO YOU ARE </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-05-23 17:17:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> NO MORE TEARS TO CRY </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-05-23 17:16:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> NO WAY </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-05-23 16:54:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-05-23 16:53:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This isn't your car. 

EDIT: Found proof.

http://forum.liberty.asn.au/viewtopic.php?f=11 t=1070 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-05-20 10:14:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Nice Lib, saw these pics on club.lib too!  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-05-17 03:59:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Also doesn't help when it rattles and echoes loudly in a drivethrough, along with my squeaky DMF.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-04-03 05:16:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Ride, mostly for their album, Nowhere.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-04-03 03:40:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I love that colour on the Libs, it looks really nice and it's quite rare too. If you haven't found club Lib already, here's a link: http://forum.liberty.asn.au/index.php  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-03-16 01:29:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> McDonalds and Subway are very close by.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-03-13 14:39:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Don't think it's that old... but it was reasonably popular.

[The Burger King Song] (http://www.youtube.com/watch?v=92utho4PjH0) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-03-10 06:36:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hi from Club Lib... lol, Turbo Lag here.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-03-07 05:47:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Nice, I also got a(nother) Liberty recently as my first car (I'm also on red Ps). Everything you'll need to find is here... http://forum.liberty.asn.au/index.php </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-01-26 05:09:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I drove this route some time ago, and it was great fun. I still haven't found anything that can top the driving here, but the scenery really isn't anything great, plus there were some unsealed sections. Most of the roads in the surrounding areas are also great. http://goo.gl/maps/AU4Js </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-01-11 01:55:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I honestly don't think you can properly 'learn to drive' with just 50 hours (as you say). However, you probably can pass a test with a lot less since it's way too easy, and if you're doing it in an auto, and can't pass, then of course, I don't think you deserve a licence at all. If you just want a licence, I'm sure you can get away with 50, but I really wouldn't advise this at all. I had to do my 120 hours, but I ended up completing them in just over a month and must've clocked up around 1000 at least before I sat my test. I still learn things on the road every time I drive on my Ps, so just doing 50 hours is definitely not the end of learning. 

Maybe what you should do is, simply learn to pass your test (which is easy), then get your Ps, and *then* learn to drive on your own. 

$40 an hour certainly doesn't sound too bad, an instructor I used charged $60 an hour and this seems to be the standard rate in my area for all instructors. 

Surely there are a few deserted or mostly unused back streets in your area? How about an unused carpark? I don't think you necessarily need a paddock or a field. Do you need a fully licensed driver if you're in a completely deserted carpark in the middle of nowhere? 

I find it extremely unfortunate that for those of you that actually follow the rules (such as OP) and want to learn to actually drive struggle to find someone to take them driving. A lot of people I know just faked their hours and are now driving on the roads, which *sucks*.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-01-07 07:59:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Plenty more photos...

http://imgur.com/a/UFZr9 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-01-02 12:13:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Oh wow I'm not the only one.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-12-28 01:41:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I also buy most of my PC parts and other stuff from the Malvern branch. I've had a router die on me after a few months, and they still replaced it. They didn't bother testing it either. I've also returned a gaming headset which broke after about a month, which they also took back and gave me full cash back. Sometimes it's a little hard to understand what the employees there say but hey, it's *cheap.*  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-12-25 01:11:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The Liberty is the AUDM name for the Legacy. Obviously, all Liberties are RHD and have a few small changes for the AUDM.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-12-17 03:47:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Fast vibration or rattle would make sense. It's very difficult to hear it while driving however, and only makes this sound loudly enough to hear when you rev it freely. Mine too happens around ~4k to idle.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-12-17 03:42:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I've actually taken a video like this already but the noise doesn't really change if the hood is up or closed. I suppose the heat shield would explain this but doesn't for when the clutch is dropped hard.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-12-17 03:39:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Someone on a Subaru forum thinks it could be the heat shield would explain the noise while just revving it, but there's also a very loud screech/grinding noise (my dad heard it while driving the other Lib with the windows all up) when I launch hard in first (which can kind of be felt through the clutch pedal), especially on a hill where you need to up the revs for a quick start. The clutch feels fine but there's a squeak too at low speed, and I'm assuming it's on it's original clutch, so it's safe to assume it still has the dual-mass setup. Mechanic took it for a drive and said he'd never heard this noise before from any car too. Could it be related?
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> My 04' Liberty 2.5i has a bad noise when the revs drop... help?  </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-12-16 11:24:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> http://www.youtube.com/watch?v=pY_LQVhTDmk

My newly purchased 2.5i Liberty (EJ253 SOHC) manual is making a kind of grinding/rattling sound. I compared it to my other car (an 08' 2.5i) and it simply doesn't have a sound like this. It happens mostly when the revs drop hard, coming from the engine bay. You can slightly hear it in the video but it's a little louder in reality since my phone's mic isn't that good. I launched at the lights reasonably hard yesterday and the noise was quite loud too. Any ideas?
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-12-14 13:00:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Nice, is it an auto or manual?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-11-28 00:19:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You can't get more power from it (that's very noticeable anyway) unless you go with forced induction, where supercharging is somewhat getting popular over here in Aus. It's a fairly long process and costs a lot. You'd be better off selling and getting a car that's already turbocharged from the factory.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-11-19 15:46:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm assuming you're also from Aus since you want a Liberty. I don't know if you're on your Ps or whatever, but remember that you can't get a turbo'd Suby at all if you are (unless you're from SA or something).  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-11-19 15:39:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I have a Liberty 2.5i 08' 4EAT (Yeah the auto sucks) as my first proper car. As much as I initially regret not purchasing a 6 cyl model, the 2.5 is plentiful for a new driver. Sometimes you just need to rev it a little harder to get it going but it's also kind of fun doing that too. The only main let down is the 4EAT which absolutely sucks in normal auto, so I only ever drive in sequential (what's worse is that I have a manual licence).

Just get an N/A Subaru, there's really nothing wrong with the power/torque for a new driver. I imagined the car to be underpowered but it's certainly got enough to have some fun with. Plus, it's the handling of the Lib that impresses me, just stay away from the autos unless they have some sort of manual shiftability.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> It has once been attempted </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-11-15 15:53:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> oh god why

http://i.imgur.com/u8t2x.jpg </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-11-15 15:43:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yep me too.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-11-13 01:46:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Guvera is also a 'free' source of music however, instead of paying, you watch ads etc. https://www.guvera.com/ </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-11-02 09:17:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I don't personally remodel vehicles, sorry if I was unclear. I simply edit the physics and sometimes models/textures, sounds etc until I'm happy with the cars. Most road cars (other than the Supra) have terrible physics, so I usually tinker with them. I've sent you a PM with some links.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-11-02 09:03:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I've found that most rF mods are terrible physics-wise (at least from my perspective). If you want good physics without a hassle, I wouldn't recommend rF as you're going to have to try a lot of mods until you find something you like. There's only a few mods I personally drive without editing myself, being WSC70, HistorX, DRM and FIA GT3 2010. 

However, rF is a fantastic base game to mod with, and it's really a sandbox once you know what you're doing. I usually just use other people's converted models (mostly road cars) and re-do the physics myself to my own liking until I make something I enjoy. Rinse, and repeat.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-10-16 11:25:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Suby Club or the WRX Club are sure to have something.. 

http://www.subyclub.com/index.php/index
http://www.wrx.com.au/forum/ </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-09-30 15:35:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> * Neutral Milk Hotel - In The Aeroplane Over The Sea
* Jimmy Eat World - Futures
* Weezer - Weezer (The Blue Album)
* Ride - Nowhere
* My Bloody Valentine - Loveless </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-08-31 09:56:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Seriously you don't need to be studying all the time if you go to the school. The people who get in are still completely normal human beings, lol. Some will study, some simply won't. Don't think of it as some sort of competition, only the entrance exam is.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-08-31 09:48:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I was in an ALP type thing too but only for maths (the school only had that). If you got in (or anyone else for that matter), you'll probably be just fine with the rest of the group who also enter Mac Rob. I would say to just do it, it'll provide you with a lot of different experiences and you don't need to lose contact with your old friends. It might help if you have starting ground in the form of other friends entering from your school too however, if not, it may seem a little daunting at first. Within the first week, you'll be completely fine.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-08-31 09:29:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I wanted to go instantly from my place. I left with no regrets as I didn't fit in at my old school even though it was a decent place. If you are seriously contemplating staying, accept the Mac Rob offer, then negotiate with your current school that you will stay with benefits. The school will not want to lose you as you will push their results up. I'm fairly sure you can decline the Mac Rob offer quite easily as there are people waiting to get in. Did you get in to a Yr. 10 or 11 entry or into Yr. 9? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-08-31 09:26:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I don't think Balwyn would be considered far at all, I know some people who used to come to mine all the way from Sunbury each day.. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-08-31 09:06:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I go to MHS, basically the equivalent boys school, I certainly don't regret going to it, and it was a fairly large change from a decent Catholic school. You won't regret it as long as you expect what's to come. Just a word of warning, the people there are usually a completely different demographic to what you may find in a more.. 'ordinary' school. 

Quick edit, fire me a PM if you want more details or whatever.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-07-14 03:55:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Two Headed Boy Part-2. Easily.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-05-01 16:43:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It wasn't Tangcla who owned it, it was "Arith" who sold and parted the car out. Tangcla however did have a silver pre-facelift which is also sold too now.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
