<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject5188</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-11-08 23:08:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> When that photo appeared I literally threw my hands into the air and silently (I was playing the episode at 3 in the morning) screamed a triumphant "YES" that denoted victory. This game man. It does this to me.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-11-08 23:05:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Meh. It's still the best, most meaningful game I've ever played. Scratch that: it's still the best, most meaningful story I've ever experienced. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-11-08 23:02:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Because it's still Max. Autopilot Max still thinks and feels and walks and talks like our Max. She is our Max. Autopilot Max has no idea that she isn't the "real Max". It's probably really weird for Chloe, but at the end of the day she has to realize that she's still with the same Max, still kicking. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-11-08 22:59:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I wonder if we will ever see them again on the screen. I know that I'll still see them again in my dreams. This story is a part of me now. I don't think it's leaving anytime soon.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-11-08 22:56:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I refuse to choose the Sacrifice Chloe option. I couldn't do it. I saw a little bit of the bathroom scene in a tribute video, and I had to look away. I only heard the gunshot, and I was in tears. I would completely break if I went through with that ending. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-11-08 22:52:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I think that when Max and Chloe leave Arcadia Bay at the end, they'll reinvent themselves and try to do some real good in the world. I can see Max pursuing her passion in photography but also getting involved in groups to help people with depression and the like. Chloe seems to me like she'd be helping people in rehab or people with PTSD, as well as continuing her studies.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-11-08 22:43:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Sure, it's just a game, but like you said the emotions are very real. If it makes an impact on you, it's real.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-11-08 22:30:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I think it's a bit like the ending to The Last of Us (although you don't make a choice in that game). I think you're supposed to assume that you're choosing between two extremes. The person you care about most dies, or literally everyone else is doomed. That makes the action you take that much more powerful. So if you choose to sacrifice the town, that's saying that Chloe means more to you than the whole world. I think that might be the way this was intended to be looked at as a moral conundrum, but it's very open to interpretation so *whatevs!* </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [EP5 SPOILERS] A few things I just need to let out...(rant-ish) </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-11-08 22:19:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I played Episode 5 last night, and I've been dealing with the everything that comes with that since then. I don't claim that this post is incredibly original, in fact it's probably old news, but I just needed to compile my thoughts somewhere. This rant began as a comment I was leaving somewhere, but I ended up going a little off topic and decided I should post this by itself. Background: I chose to Sacrifice Arcadia Bay. 

**Wall of text imminent**

Chloe wouldn't leave me, so I sure as hell wouldn't leave her. Around Episode 3 Chloe makes it very clear that Max is the most important thing her world. I fell in love with the character around the same time. I realized that I (well, Max. Not me. Kinda me.) was all she had, and that she was all I cared about. When Episode 3 ended I realized that I had to save and protect Chloe no matter what (and she shows in Episode 4 at Frank's RV that she's willing to do the same for Max), and that's been my only goal since then. All the way through Episode 5 I had to fight to save Chloe. In Jefferson's car, when The Sense of Me was playing, and sitting in the Two Whales I was repeating over and over in my mind *"I can save her"* and *"I will save her"*. When I finally found her, saved her from Jefferson, I told myself that I wouldn't let her be taken away again. The nightmare sequence, particularly when Chloe gets it on with literally everyone else and you have to watch, was torture for me. But I had to push through for Chloe. And I did. Then we came to the final choice. Lose the most important person in the world to you, or let countless innocent people die? Was letting Chloe die in the bathroom really what had to be done to stop the storm? More importantly, would that be worth it? Wouldn't that mean that everything I had done that week (or in real time, this year) was for nothing? Chloe would die alone, bitter, and scared. No one would know what had happened in that imaginary week. Just Max. Just me. It's not just that I can't let her die; I can't let her suffer. Chloe deserves better. She deserves to see her best friend (or perhaps soulmate) again and finally be happy. I've seen some people saying that it's the same as the choice to euthanize Chloe in Episode 4. It's not the same as when she asks you to end her life then. There she gets to pass in the dream. Her final moments are some of the happiest of her life. She gets to spend her last day with her best friend, her angel. She dies with a smile on her face. Wherever the hell(a) she goes after she passes, she won't forget Max. But rewinding to the bathroom? Letting her get shot and killed, bleeding out alone on the cold bathroom floor? Hating everyone and everything, probably thinking of the three greatest loves of her life abandoning her as she slips away? *What kind of world does this?* *Who does this?* How could you expect me/Max to leave my/her best friend to die like *that*? And then live with it? Alone? If you let Arcadia Bay get destroyed, Max and Chloe will still be there for each other. They'll still always have each others back. The death that may have been inadvertently caused by them is a tough pill to swallow, but as long and they have each other they'll be able to make it. They make each other stronger. They complete each other. But if you let Chloe die? Max has to carry all of that weight on her own shoulders. She'll be suffering for every second of the rest of her life. She has to live knowing that she let the person who she loved most, and who loved her more than anything, die in the most awful way imaginable. Max is strong, but do you have any idea how much that would fuck you up? I don't know if I'd be able to recover from a wound like that, let alone bear it. I could *never* let my best friend die. I would do literally anything to save my best friend, whether we're talking about Chloe Price or my best friend in "real" life. I can't *let* them die. If my best friend were to die, I'd want to be able to rewind and save them more than anything. Whether it brings a colossal tornado down upon my city or not, I would do it. That's how much love is worth. It gives you the strength to weather the storm. We may have doomed thousands, but as long as we still have each other we can endure. At the end of the day, that's all you need. It's all you can ask for. A dancing partner. Someone who moves with you, someone who's with you every step of the way, someone who's as committed to you as you are to them. Arcadia Bay may be gone, but Chloe and Max aren't. They're stronger, better people as a result of what they've experienced. Together they can take on the world. If you choose to sacrifice the town, Max and Chloe get the chance to leave together *and to be happy*. The scars might not ever heal, but together they can find something to cover them up with. 

**tl;dr** I have no idea to sum up my thoughts concisely. My mind is a whirlwind and I've broken into tears many times today under the slightest touch. Thank you for reading if you did. Maybe you old geezers can give me ideas how to cope, or at least let me know what your thoughts are? Or, you know, tell me how crazy I am :P </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-11-08 22:08:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That looks beautiful. I don't know if I'd be able to buy one, but it is certainly hella cool. Chloe'll always be with you then I guess? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-11-08 21:14:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm going to be around this sub until the end of time, so hopefully we will meet in the comments section again. :) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-11-08 20:41:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I love Dontnod and want to support them, especially after hearing about what happened with Episode 5 and their budget. They've earned my trust, so I figure I might as well see what this Vampyr shit is all about! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-11-08 20:36:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hella glad to have been along for the ride with you and everyone else! It's been a true honor, and a great time. Together we can rebuild Arcadia Bay. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-11-08 20:31:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thanks for the memories Dontnod AND thanks to everyone who came along for the ride here. It's been incredible.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-11-08 20:23:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I like that Chloe and Max's relationship never felt like "this is our *gay* couple". It never felt like Dontnod was making an explicit statement or challenge. I've said it before (to calm shippers), and I feel like it perfeclty defines the relationship between Max and Chloe: *love is love.* These two people love each other, so who gives a fuck if they're gay or straight, lovers or best friends? It's a truly beautiful and, as you said, organic relationship. 

***Max and Chloe FOREVAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAA*** </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-11-08 20:17:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> How did I experience this scene? I didn't. I don't think I ever will. I can't bring myself to choose that ending, or even watch it on Youtube. Not just because I can't let Chloe die, but because Max will have to live with the memories of the past week alone. That is torture.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-11-08 20:15:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hearing that gunshot made me shatter like a glass butterfly. The tribute video I saw used Spanish Sahara, which I had never heard before. It's become my "goodbye" song for Life is Strange. I might still have Chloe, but Life is Strange is over now. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-11-08 20:07:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> But we also haven't been trying to save Chloe over and over for nothing.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-11-08 20:05:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I like both endings. I do however agree that the Sacrifice Arcadia Bay ending felt really short. I believe it had something to do with budget limitations, which really sucks. I would've liked if it was longer, or at least if they ended it with one last dialogue tree.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-11-08 19:47:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I don't think it makes you a shitty person. To be quite honest with you, I feel like Max and Chloe are worth more to me than most of the people I know irl too. Maybe it's because they're are always there for me, or because I honestly feel like I know them better than most of my friends, or because I've gone to such lengths to make things better for them. Max and Chloe have had a greater impact on me than most of the people around me. I don't think there's any shame in admitting that. 

That said I would be willing to sacrifice virtually anything for the people close to me, even though I don't feel as connected to most of them as I do to Max and Chloe.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-11-08 19:37:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hey, you replied! That means you could answer my question. Sorry I'm late to the party, I didn't want to be either. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-11-08 19:36:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This was a phenomenal finale episode. It was very different to the first four episodes of Life is Strange (less color, less quirkiness), but I think it's great in its own right. 

I haven't seen anyone really talking about it (yet; I still have a bunch of posts to go through from the last two weeks), but the scene when you travel through Warren's photo to save Chloe was the most emotional scene for me in the entire game. I told Chloe everything about William and AU-Chloe; when I told her about how she was paralyzed and asked me to euthanize her, I broke. That was the hardest cry I had out of the whole game. It was bad enough having to do it in Episode 4, but having to tell it to Chloe was something else entirely. Kudos to Hannah and Ashly for their ***incredible*** performances that brought that scene to life.

I also gotta admit, when the "previously on Life is Strange" segment began at the very start of the episode I got really choked up. Having a look back at the journey for one last time was really special. The beginning of the end. 

I chose to sacrifice the town so that Chloe could live. I fought the whole time to be with Chloe; I wasn't going to let her go, not for anything. I'm a little sad that I didn't get my Pricefield kiss, but Michel explained it quite well. I like my ending. I haven't watched the "Sacrifice Chloe" ending, and I don't think I will. I could never bring myself to choose that path, and I know that it'll break me if I see it. I saw a tribute that began to play out what happens in the bathroom, and I had to look away. I heard the gunshot though, and I couldn't take it. I could never make that choice. 

It's been a great year in Arcadia Bay with Max and Chloe, and with all of you. I can't thank Dontnod or you guys enough for making this one of the most special experiences of my life. And always remember...


***KICK THE TABLE!***


   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-11-08 18:56:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Blackwell Ninjas. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-11-08 18:54:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This is the cutest thing I've seen all day, the day after I played Polarized. The feels, the feels! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-11-08 18:39:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I don't know what it is. Maybe it's because I just played Episode 5 and it's been the only thing on my mind all day. Maybe it's because I was just listening to Spanish Sahara. Maybe it's because I haven't actually called him in forever. But I read your reply and couldn't keep myself from crying. I guess Dontnod broke me. 

I think I'll take your advice and call him today. Thanks op :)  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-11-08 15:44:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I have many people in my life who I'd do that for. It's selfish, I know. But selfishness isn't the same thing as evil. I'd trade dozens for my good friends or my parents or my older brother. I need these people. And what kind of friend/son/brother would I be if I let them die?

I've thought about these kind of things before, and I came to the conclusion that you and the people closest to you always have to come first. I honestly don't believe it's possible to help others without helping yourself.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-11-08 15:41:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Oh man, it would be incredible to see this put into motion. I know it's been two weeks since you posted this, so have you made any progress or anything? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-11-08 15:40:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I started to tear up a tiny bit reading this. Thank you for making this.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-11-08 15:35:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Which ones? If you're referring to characters, know that they begin as archetypes and evolve into real people over the course of the five episodes. If you're talking about the beat for beat plot revolving around Jefferson and a missing girl, know that most of that is just surface level; the real story is about characters, relationships, the town, and who you are/Max is as a person. Even the final choice is more about Max as a person and her relationship with Chloe than it is about some storm. 

(Reading over this, I don't mean to be coming across as dickish. Sorry if that's how it sounds.) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-11-08 15:31:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> My major takeaway from Life is Strange never was the plot. The storm, Jefferson, Rachel Amber, Kate, that's never what the story was about for me. It was always about Max and Chloe, and the relationship they shared. And in that respect Dontnod delivered. They went above and beyond what I feel we expected from them. I won't remember Life is Strange for the Everyday Heroes contest, or the red binders, or the storm. I'll remember it for getting to wake up in Chloe's room in Episode 3, or getting to watch Blade Runner with my best friend in Episode 4. That's what the journey was for me. It was never about anything or anyone else but Max and Chloe for me. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-11-08 15:28:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I loved the ending actually. I didn't get to play the game for a while, so I saw a few people saying things like that the ending sucked. I didn't believe them anyways. The ending I picked (option B) was the ending I wanted since Episode 3 anyways. Chloe comes first. When the option came up, I didn't hesitate. I would've liked to have on more dialogue tree though... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-11-08 15:25:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Go cuddle with your own Arcadia Bae.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-11-08 15:24:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I had a friend like Chloe once. Don't get me wrong, I have some great friends now, but none of them were like him. We still talk (I moved away, far away), but it's weird not being able to see him. If I could just hang out with him again for a week, or a day, or a minute, I'd give virtually anything for that.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-11-08 15:20:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> AAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAA </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-11-08 15:17:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The last time I experienced a depression like this was back in the 1930s! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-11-08 15:16:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I intend to do the exact same thing. I didn't savor my time with the first two episodes. I didn't realize that there was an end to this story and that it was imminent. I want to take a week and play one episode a night, taking my time, enjoying the company of Chloe, taking in the atmosphere and the scenery, and remembering better times. And then I'll approach the finale with complete conviction. Maybe I'll do a few things differently, I don't know. But I'm still in this for Chloe. That's the number one priority.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-11-08 15:12:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I remember rewinding over and over trying to find the right option to pick. Warn David? Nooope. Grab gun? Nawww. 

Kick table? Why not! 

*"YES SIR!"*

*bang*

Oh.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-11-08 15:02:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I don't know about pain or sadness...just nostalgia, fondness. Like Chloe told us (and broke my heart into millions of tiny pieces in the process), what happened was real and will always be with us. No matter what happens, no matter what ending you chose, no matter where *you* go next, those memories are real. Treasure them. And keep a spare barrel for your tears.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-11-08 14:58:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Emptiness seems to have been the defining feeling around here the last three weeks...I sacrificed the Bay and I also feel similarly empty. Not because I allowed hundreds, maybe thousands (I don't know the population of Arcadia Bay, sorry), of innocent people to die. I feel empty because its over. I'm never going to get to pick up the controller and explore Arcadia Bay again like I've got to these past months. Arcadia Bay, and more importantly Arcadia Bae, now only exist in our dreams. That's kind of bittersweet.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-11-08 14:49:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I have a best friend, but I haven't seen him in person in 5 years (coincidence?). I got in contact with him a little bit before I found LiS (...) which is awesome, so we still talk pretty much every day. It's just weird not being able to see him. 5 years, and separated by the Atlantic Ocean. First chance I get, I'm heading home to see him; I can't just assume that he'll always be there, as sad a thought as that is.

I think that's why I connected with Max and Chloe like I did.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-11-08 14:46:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Maybe a few years down the road. :) I'm trying to look up. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-11-08 14:44:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's so weird, right? I just finished the story, and it's a strange feeling knowing that there aren't any more episodes of LiS to look forward to. I expected the ending (I sacrificed the Bay to be clear) to turn me into a sobbing emotional wreck going into the episode. I expected to be in tears knowing that Life is Strange, something that's been a huge part of my life since spring, was over. But I wasn't. I was just...empty, like you said. I was choked up, but emptiness is what I felt more than anything. I think Geek Remix said it best in her video on the ending where she said that, although it's a great and well written ending, it's not a very fulfilling one.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-11-08 14:38:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I finished Life is Strange last night, and I've been struggling to put into words (or even coherent thoughts) what I'm feeling and why I love this game so much. I think you're hitting the nail on the head when you talk about how when they were happy, you were happy, and when they were hurt, you were hurt. I've never EVER before experienced a story that was as involving as Life is Strange and allowed me to really become the protagonists like Life is Strange did. There's no doubt that this is a hallmark moment for gaming and, more important to me, a significant life experience. Life is Strange reached through to me, and it changed me.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-11-08 14:31:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That's incredible. Bravo sir, bravo. "*Eat shit and die.*" </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-11-08 14:27:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hear hear.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-11-08 14:23:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Regardless of which ending you chose, Max and Chloe will most definitely live on forever. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-11-08 12:55:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I looked at this a different way. The final choice is Chloe or Everyone in Arcadia Bay. You could say that maybe Joyce and David and plenty of people survived, but I don't think that's the point. Choosing to sacrifice Arcadia Bay is saying that Chloe is worth more to you than countless lives of others. It's a bit like the ending of The Last of Us, which I won't spoil here. In Max's mind there's complete certainty that saving Chloe equals the deaths of the entire population of Arcadia Bay, and that sacrificing her 100% stops the storm and saves everyone from everything that happened that week. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-11-08 12:50:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'll have you know I considered showing him no affection. Warren's great and all, but I was worried he might get touchy feely. Later I realized that would've been a complete dick move, and that I was an idiot to think that. Warren's a great guy, he's always had Max's back. He deserves a hug. But not a kiss. Chloe's the only girl for me. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-11-08 12:44:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The Max/Kate hug was perfect. I didn't expect to tear up at that( I didn't when Kate was on the roof), but I did. It was a beautiful moment. Not every emotional scene has to be sad.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-11-08 12:42:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> When Chloe tells Max that, no matter what happens to her, she'll always be with her, I died. I couldn't take it. I also couldn't let that happen. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-11-08 12:37:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I don't think any of us can thank Dontnod enough. I can't put into words what this game has made me feel, or how grateful I am to Dontnod. Thanks just doesn't quite cover it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-11-08 12:31:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  She won't rewind the decision you make at the ending, she (AKA you, the player) has learned to accept her decisions. That might be the first real choice Max has done in her life.

I played the episode last night, and that was something that confused me. I was wondering why you didn't have the ability to rewind and see the other outcome (not that I had any doubt as to which choice I was going to make). You just made it make sense to me. Thank you. (I feel dumb now too :P) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-11-08 12:28:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I was moved by that scene, not because I've always been sympathetic for Nathan, but because of the way he died. He just wanted to be like Jefferson, and then Jefferson killed him. Damn. It happening off screen is way more powerful in my opinion.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> GOG Show Episodes 1-100: Favorite episodes? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-11-06 14:16:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Now that the Gameovergreggy Show has passed 100 episodes, I was thinking back on what the best episodes of the show are. I thought it'd be cool to see what all the other best friends' favorites are. 

Here's my personal top ten, in no particular order:

-Episode 7: Birth of the Shadowboxer (OMG! We all almost died!)

-Episode 28: Aisha Tyler

-Episode 56: Dave Fennoy 

-Episode 92: (Nearly) Everyone at Kinda Funny Is Dead

-Episode 83: Stripper and Gay Marriage

-Episode 38: Bad Dates, Good Meats, and Dead Bodies

-Episode 100: Alex Aziz

-Episode 23: Alexis Cozombolidis 

-Episode 12: Brian Altano  

-Episode 30: Girlfriend Porn, World Cup, and a Mystery Box

(Shoutout to Episodes 97 through 100, I feel like they've been on a roll lately.) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-11-06 14:00:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I can't even imagine how they would implement this. That's a level of realism way beyond what Factions is.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-11-06 13:56:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Rockhold, Cerrone, McGregor, Joanna Champion </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-11-05 11:55:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Even in the post apocalypse people will be expressing themselves through their clothes. Especially considering The Last of Us takes place 20 years after the fall. Most people have probably become accustomed to it. The customization items probably wouldn't be vibrant, colorful, and brand new stylish clothing, but that doesn't mean they couldn't have a robust set of options.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-11-03 22:56:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> To be fair, The Walking Dead Season 1 had a little bit of exploration (nothing compared to the Blackwell campus or Price Household though). But afterwards, when Telltale began juggling a (baker's!) dozen games at once, they scaled back pretty much everything. The art style got much prettier, but in terms of actual playable content we  got a lot less out of our TT games. They even made the episodes shorter! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-11-03 22:53:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's a lot more light hearted. The characters are very well written, well acted, and well rounded. They're very likeable and you *will* grow attached to them. I personally felt the lack of urgency (in comparison to Telltale's other, ultra serious titles) made them feel more like real and relatable people, kind of similarly to LiS in a way; you get to connect with the characters under more positive circumstances. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-11-03 22:49:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  Pretty much anything by Telltale is almost identical mechanically.

Not really. Sure, there's dialogue trees and point and click interactivity, but LiS has deeper mechanics than Telltale's games. For starters there's a lot more exploration in LiS; TT games are generally more confined, a little more limited. But the big difference mechanically is rewinding. Rewinding is a HUGE part of LiS's gameplay (and narrative). It's the core of the whole game (both in terms of gameplay and narrative (ludo-narrative resonance, yay!)) I think that LiS has more engaging gameplay as a result (that bit's my opinion, but there's no denying that rewinding adds a whole new layer to the gameplay).  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-11-03 21:55:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I wish I had something funny to say, but this is just one of those genuinely fucked up and traumatizing stories. I got the jitters just reading it.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-11-03 20:14:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Chloe, you used to be a straight A student!

...is it about that Rachel girl you've been hanging out with? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-11-03 20:10:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> A hell of a lot of the combat encounters. Particularly the ones at Tommy's Dam and in the Ranch House. That Ranch House fight was so forced. The sniper shootout in the suburbs, while I wouldn't want it removed, would have probably benefited from being made more low key. 

The bit in the mine with David, where you have to fight off a million infected and a bloater, was also completely ridiculous. I loved the bit when you get separated from him and have to get past the clickers though.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-11-03 19:57:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm giving Holly the benefit of the doubt, purely because of the drama around Ronda right now. It might seem dumb of me, but with the whole Travis Browne thing and and the Mama Rousey thing, I think Ronda might not be coming into this fight in the best state of mind. 

Also it'll be interesting to see how Ronda's standup holds up against Holly's, provided Holly can keep it on the feet for more than 16 seconds.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-11-03 19:48:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> To be honest with you, a 6/10 or 7/10 is a pretty respectable score. I don't mind seeing a reviewer give LiS that score; not only is it justifiable, but he or she is entitled to his/her opinion. What I do mind is when the review is absolute nonsense ("utter tripe" as a friend of mine would say). The IGN reviews of Life is Strange are pretty awful. I don't hate Mitch Dyer (IGN) because he doesn't like the same game I do; his reviews of the episodes are just complete nonsense. His Episode 4 review literally criticizes the game *for the reviewer being dumb* (literally, go read the bit on the evidence puzzle). The same goes for other outlets. Polygon has generally been a site that I take issue with, because I feel that a lot of their reviews are written purely to stir controversy; most of the controversial reviews of theirs that I've read present opinions with poor justification, which leads me to think that they were written for clicks. 

tl;dr Everyone's entitled to their own opinion, and I respect that. I just feel that the quality of journalism/criticism that we see a lot in the games media (and movie) industry is pretty poor. Big sites like IGN, Polygon, etc seem like they are merely pushing clicks (and pushing sales when it comes to huge releases). 

(P.S. Thank you for having the guts to say that LiS doesn't have the best plot in this sub. The world is amazing, the characters are phenomenal, but the moment to moment *plot* is actually nothing special. That doesn't necessarily make the overall narrative worse; The Last of Us has a great story as well, but it has very little to do with the actual plot as much as it does the world and the characters.) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-11-02 23:39:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I couldn't help but think about the public's reception of cocky Conor McGregor listening to this.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-11-01 22:03:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's entirely subjective. /u/Pegalicious99 finds them hot.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-11-01 20:17:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Aw man, you missed out! It's a blast to play as well! I'd loan you my PS4 if I could, but that's just ridiculous.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-11-01 20:14:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That's awesome. This is one of my favorite scenes from the whole game. They're so adorable! Proportions are off, but don't worry about it too much. Focus on capturing the mood and essence of the scene. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-11-01 20:13:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Three weeks later and it'll be a different kind of fallout.... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-11-01 20:12:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Wait the week. I'm in the exact same situation. It won't be fun to go through the lovely experience that is Episode 5 and THEN engage in the even more fun time that is studying. Take the tests, then play the episode. You won't have anything to worry about afterwards, so you can spend as long as you want crying and cursing Dontnod while also being very grateful towards them. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-11-01 20:06:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Probably worth mentioning that, even though they're both southpaws, their stances aren't the same. In this gif anyways, Kenny's stance is a lot less wide than Conor's.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-11-01 20:03:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The thing about objectivity, especially in regards to art, is that it doesn't exist. Everything is subjective. That's why abstract art is a thing.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-11-01 20:01:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Definitely. Life is Strange was actually the catalyst for me no longer relying on traditional games media and journalism. I realized that I shouldn't be letting critics and the media be dictating what I play and what my views are. Life is Strange has been the most incredible and meaningful experience I've ever had in fiction, and otherwise to be honest, so IGN or Gamespot or Polygon saying that the game is mediocre has absolutely no impact on it's actual value.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-11-01 19:58:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's another game where the characters really are real people, even though they begin as relatively cliche personas.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-11-01 19:57:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> 100 %, yeah. 

"6/10 IGN, can't fucking read, not enough water" </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-11-01 16:39:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I've got a slightly different take on this. LiS seems to be something along the lines of a cult hit; it's got an incredibly loyal fanbase that believes it's one of the greatest games ever made, but it got pretty lukewarm reception from critics. Something that we can *all* agree on though is that Life is Strange is super weird. Some people are completely turned off by the weirdness (particularly in the dialogue) and some of us adore it. The only other game I know that matches this description is **Deadly Premonition**. That game was too weird for me, but who knows, you might like it. 

Then of course I've got a more normal answer. **The Last of Us** is a great game that revolves around the strong relationship between its two protagonists, Joel and Ellie. Joel and Ellie are right up there with Max and Chloe as one of the best video game duos ever. 

EDIT: For clarification, I don't give a flying fuck about critical reception. I was just drawing a parallel between LiS and Deadly Premonition.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-11-01 12:45:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Furious Master Lee Bates.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [SPOILERS] Good or Bad vibes? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-11-01 01:20:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I was curious about the kind of vibes we all got from this game. It's a dark and violent story about the end of our days, but there's a lot of hope and light (*"look for the light"*) in it as well. For every death, tragedy, and brutal murder, there's a heartfelt conversation with Ellie or a beautiful vista to look out at. As opposed to something like The Road, Children of Men, or The Walking Dead, there's a lot of life and vibrance to The Last of Us. I personally found there to be more and greater uplifting moments than brutally tragic ones, but I'm also batshit crazy. 

So I was honestly wondering, was your takeaway of the game more positive or negative? Did it leave you fulfilled or depressed? Spoiler tagged so that we can discuss particular examples and moments.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Not going to play Ep5 for a while, figure I should put this out there while you're all here: </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-10-19 22:39:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [FANART] Cartoony Max Caulfield </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-10-09 00:45:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> I'd like your advice on this... </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-10-05 23:08:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I've found myself in a bit of a conundrum involving the release of Episode 5 and another important event on my calendar.

Okay, so we all know that Episode 5: Polarized will roll out on October 20th worldwide. There's a really cool counter in the subreddit banner with awesome art reminding us of how close the release day is. We're all super excited for the 20th in one way or another. On the day and the following days we're all going to be here in /r/lifeisstrange crying together or jumping-for-joy together, depending on how evil those Dontnod fellows are. 

But I've got a bit of a dilemma. I can't wait for Episode 5. I really want to jump on it ASAP, and then get involved with the community and be on the ground floor when we're all coming together and reacting to the finale. *But*, about two weeks after Episode 5 releases (towards the end of the first week of November) I've got a rather important, let's say, event coming up. It's the kind of thing that will need to have my full attention, my complete focus. And I know that, no matter what happens in Episode 5, I'm not going to be able to think about anything BUT Life is Strange for a long while afterwards; I won't be able to keep my eye on the ball and give this other thing my undivided attention. 

So my dilemma (sorry for the semi-long-windedness and weirdness) is whether or not I should put off playing Episode 5 *for more than two weeks*, *giving up getting to experience the conclusion to this life-changing story (to me, personally) with everyone else here in the LiS community*, in favor of having a clearer mind and therefore better performance in this other important thing. First World Problems, I know, but this is actually something that really matters to me. This is a decision that ultimately I will have to make myself, but I wanted to just hear some advice from you guys and gals, if you have any, on what *you* think I should do. Or rather if you were in my position, "What would you do now?" 

Even if this proves fruitless (which I'm sure won't happen, I have a lot of faith in this sub), typing this out is helping me process this whole situation. Clock's ticking. Thank you for reading this far down.

EDIT: I wasn't very clear about this, but time is not the issue. The issue is that the finale is going to completely fuck with my head and occupy every nook and cranny of my cranium at a time when I need to have a clear head.    </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Bored in class, doodled Max! </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-09-21 18:27:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> If WB Montreal makes a sequel to Arkham Origins, should Kevin Conroy play the role of Batman? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-08-25 00:20:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I was thinking about this the other day and wanted to hear some of you guys' opinions. Kevin Conroy most likely wasn't in Arkham Origins because he was already working on Arkham Knight (let that slip), so Roger Craig Smith got the role of Batman. General consensus seems to be that RCS did an excellent job as the Dark Knight. Should he continue to play Batman in WB Montreal's games, or would it be best if Conroy took over?

Personally I think Roger Craig Smith should play Batman in any further installments. Kevin Conroy is my Batman, but I feel that he shouldn't feature in any further Arkham titles (at least not as Batman). I'm not too sure why I feel this way, but I do.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Why do you think the Tac Shotgun is overpowered? (serious) </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-08-19 13:31:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Venture into this sub and you'll hear a lot about how OP the Tactical Shotgun is. I never understood where this claim came from. I've used the Tac Shotgun myself, not my weapon of choice, but I thought it was fine. Played against plenty of Tac Shotguns, never really angered or bothered me. So many people think the gun is OP. How and why? Seriously, this post isn't meant to defy you guys, I just want someone to *explain how and why the Tac Shotgun is OP.* It has never made sense to me. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [EP4 SPOILERS] Something bugging me about Warren's big moment... </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-08-15 01:56:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If you didn't hold him back against Nathan, Warren's knuckles should be broken. When you look at the way he repeatedly punches Nathan with his bare fist, there's no way he wouldn't have broken them. Punching someone in the face won't just damage them, it'll damage your hand. Fun fact, gloves weren't introduced in Boxing to protect your face; they were introduced to prevent hand and knuckle injuries. 

I know this is completely insignificant and totally nitpicky, but it has been bugging me recently (provided the amount of times I've watched that scene over and over). Thought I'd throw it out there. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Would anyone else want some kind of Collector's Edition of the game? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-08-08 01:16:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> When Episode 5 is out and Max and Chloe's story is all said and done I'd really like some kind of Collector's Edition, or just a physical copy, of the game. It's been one hell of a journey, and I want a hard copy of the game to keep for the future and to remember the game by. (And in case PSN implodes.)(And because of Collector's Edition *swag*.) What about you guys? Anyone else want this too? 

Also, what kind of other stuff would you like to see in a hypothetical Collector's Edition? I think a poster or two, a statuette, a cool box, and maybe some polaroids from the game would be cool. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Got this awesome gift for my birthday </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-08-06 19:49:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [EP4 SPOILERS] If you blamed you-know-who in Episode 2... </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-08-02 01:34:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I know most of us didn't, but what happens with Jefferson in Episode 4 is you blamed him at the end of Episode 2? If memory serves me right, he gets temporarily suspended and gets removed from the Everyday Heroes contest. So, does he not show up to give the award to Victoria? Does he even show up to the Vortex Club party?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [EP4 SPOILERS] About that ending... </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-31 13:18:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I thought this episode was phenomenal all the way through. I freaking loved it. But then there's that ending. The ending was hella fucked up and creepy, and Jefferson FUCKING KILLED CHLOE, but didn't we kinda see that all coming? Since Episode 1 a lot of us have been convinced that Jefferson was the evil binder-man, and before this episode a lot of us were saying that it would probably end with Max getting drugged and taken to the Dark Room. And yeah it was crazy when they FUCKING KILLED CHLOE, but it also felt to me like a fake out after the whole alt universe Chloe thing. I didn't believe for a second that Chloe was gone for good. 

I guess what I'm trying to say is that I didn't feel the same emotional punch in face with the ending of this episode that I did in the last episode. Especially since the ending of Ep4 was out of our control; the ending of Ep3 was actually a direct result of something we did. But it seems like I might be alone on this (?). 

P.S. Did anyone else think the episode was going to end with Nathan shooting up the Vortex Club party? It made sense in my head, considering the subject matter this game has dealt with already. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> How long is Episode 4? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-29 23:13:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm waiting for the episode to download (a few hours left, curse you, slow internet!), and I'm losing daylight. How much time will I need to set aside to play this episode? I want to play through it in one sitting, but I have to be up early tomorrow and can't stay up all night. 

(I usually like explore areas fully and attempt to find as much extra stuffs as I can, but I don't usually find everything/get every photo.)  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Has LiS changed your life? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-25 00:58:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> We see a lot of posts about how Life Is Strange has affected people in huge ways (sometimes saving lives), and I wanted to see if and how the game has affected the rest of us. (I honestly can't say the game has had a significant impact on my character, but I have formed a routine of listening to the game's soundtrack in the morning when I wake up and at night before I hit the sack. And saying hella a lot.)

Sound off below, and remember: no emoji. 

EDIT/UPDATE: I didn't expect this many comments. Wow. I want to reply to every one of them, but I'm a little too dumb to come up with anything to say. This community rocks.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [SPOILERS] Is it just me, or was that a bit anticlimactic? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-05 19:11:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Specifically what I am referring to is the conclusion to Jason/Arkham Knight's story. He just drops the whole "I hate Batman" thing and literally gets up and leaves. Then he turns up for the finale in one shot, and you don't see anything else of him. He doesn't even get a single line of dialogue there! They don't explain what's going on, why Jason is suddenly back on Batman's side, and what happens to him following the capture of Scarecrow. There is no closure to his story. 

(I haven't yet achieved the final ending, so if his story is given a proper conclusion following this please let me know and excuse my ignorance) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> I just want to say... </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-06-07 20:18:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This sub is exactly what I hoped it would be. Found it yesterday after completing Episode 3. Tons of goofy shit mixed with a myriad of insightful shit. I guess Chloe and Max are even more relatable than I already thought they were. This game is so fucking good. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> How many pull ups (max) can you do? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-26 23:49:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I can bang out 17, and I'm only improving from here. A year ago I could barely do eight, and a year before that I could only do two or three.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Chrysanthemums </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-23 15:38:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Team Balancing Issues (PS3) </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-14 01:31:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I know this gets addressed a lot, and I also know that this is very likely to get downvoted t'fuck, but there are some serious balancing issues in matchmaking. I'm a PS3 player. Tonight, after a few good games, I was literally put on a team of level 0-5s against teams where everyone was level 200 or above. This happened more than once. I know the Dogs read this sub, which is why I have decided to shout this from the mountain top. My night culminated in the most epic of rage quits. Help me ND, you're my only hope. (No, seriously) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Let's talk play styles... </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-09 17:22:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What is your play style like? Are you a Lone Wolf, or a Team Player? Do you patiently flank, or do you charge in guns blazing? Do you need a certain gun/set of perks, or can you make do with anything? And most importantly, are you an asshole who doesn't revive teammates two feet away from you? What's your game plan? 

I see a lot of posts about certain guns, maps, perks, etc, and it usually devolves into a divide between people based on individual play styles, so I was curious to hear specifically how you guys play.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [Arkham Knight: My Theory](/spoiler) </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-12-29 01:17:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This is my theory as to who the Arkham Knight is. Arkham City spoilers within. 

The guys at Rocksteady have said again and again that the Arkham Knight is an original character; I believe them 100%. My theory begins with the death of the Joker at the end of Arkham City. There is (obviously) some speculation that the Joker is actually alive and that he's going to come back in Arkham Knight, but that's not true. In the Arkhamverse, Joker is dead. The clever kids at Rocksteady know that it would be cheap and stupid to bring him back having previously killed him off in such dramatic fashion. But with him being the main antagonist in both Arkham Asylum and Arkham City, Rocksteady can't leave him out entirely. We already know Harley Quinn has a presence in the game, but I don't think that'll be it for Mista J's legacy. 

In the Harley Quinn's Revenge DLC for Arkham City, there were several signs and posters for Cadmus Labs throughout the Steel Mill. Cadmus Labs has a history in DC comics lore for creating all kinds of wacky science projects and most notably created a clone of Superman, Superboy. This led to many fans speculating that Cadmus would create a clone of the Joker for Arkham 3, effectively reincarnating the Joker. Once again, that's not going to happen. Not only would this feel cheap (Sefton Hill is a smart guy), but it also wouldn't have much impact as it wouldn't actually be the real Joker; the clone wouldn't have his brain. Yet Cadmus Labs still plays into my theory.

The most notorious Easter Egg from Arkham City is Harley's pregnancy test. This (accompanied by her chilling voice over from the credits) suggested that the sequel to Arkham City would involve Harley and the Joker's child taking revenge on Batman (or at least it'd involve the damn kid, I don't know). This seemed solid. For a few months everyone believed it. Then Harley Quinn's Revenge turned this plot around completely. In the Steel Mill there was a stack of pregnancy tests, all negative, next to Scarface painted like the Joker in a crib. This completely debunked the Harley/Joker kid theory that we had all gotten behind. But something that you may have overlooked is the number of negative pregnancy tests. Obviously it was a lot, as to clearly and openly say to you "NOPE", but there's more to it than that. You can deduce by the sheer number of pregnancy tests that Harley took that she was desperately hoping for Joker's child; she had everything hinged on that hope, and it drove her further into insanity. Point is, she really wanted that kid. 

It may seem like I've been ranting for a while, but here's where this theory begins to take form. Cadmus Labs will not clone the Joker, and Harley is not going to give birth to Joker Jr. What I believe is going to happen is somewhere in between. Cadmus Labs will, using Joker's DNA, create the 'son' of the Joker in a laboratory. It's possible that Harley will somehow get them to do this. His aging will be accelerated, and he will be made into the perfect physical specimen, a living weapon. But with the Joker having been his 'father', he'll have reason to hate Batman and seek vengeance (or at least Cadmus could program it into him). Cadmus, with their virtually limitless resources, will be where he got his private army from. This 'son' of the Joker is the Arkham Knight. 

A slightly more offhand part to this theory is that the Arkham Knight was made from DNA from both Joker and Batman. This would explain his resemblance to the Dark Knight in costume.

The Arkham Knight will be the ultimate anti-Batman. His 'parent' was 'killed' by Batman, and his life goal is to get vengeance on Joker's killer. He is not the Knight of Gotham, but the Knight of Arkham. What I'm getting at here is similar to the story of Batman's rogue Prometheus. In both appearance and MO he will be the antithesis of Batman. Batman works alone, Arkham Knight has an army. Batman doesn't kill, Arkham Knight does. So on and so forth. 

In short, the Arkham Knight will be the Joker's 'son', created by Cadmus Labs as the ultimate killer and physical specimen, and dedicated to the destruction of the Dark Knight. 

That's my theory. Maybe you've heard it before, maybe not, but I felt like pitching in. And I am pretty confident in this theory. Thank you for taking the time to read this, and please let me know what you think about this theory. Thank you. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The Flamethrower Quartet </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-10-29 16:02:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I just played a match against a team of medics with flamethrowers. Everyone seemed to have reviver 3 and they all had the flamethrower. Needless to say, we got boned. They seemed unstoppable. Was wondering if anyone else has tried this, or has any tactics to use against it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What mask/hat do you wear? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-10-19 13:05:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I've been wearing the Dia de los Muertos mask ever since I got it. Before that I only wore the bandana, because I thought it seemed the most fitting. In the way of hats, I've been rolling with the Jeep Cap since the start, but I recently switched over to the Aussie Cattleman.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [SPOILERS] Most Underrated TWD Episodes? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-08-03 22:41:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The Walking Dead (the TV series) has had its ups and downs, but what do you guys think are some of the most underrated episodes of the series?
For me it's definitely "Claimed" (S4E11), purely because of the scenes with Rick in the house. That is some of the most tense and nerve wracking shit I've ever seen.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> You can't deny the view (artwork) </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-07-29 11:59:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
