<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject9073</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-11-05 00:33:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [**Punisher: War Zone**](http://www.rottentomatoes.com/m/punisher_war_zone/) - 27% - w/ Ray Stevenson. Ridiculous and over the top, but by far the best Punisher movie.

[**Weird Science**](http://www.rottentomatoes.com/m/1023316-weird_science/) - 56% - One of my favorite comedies of all time.

[**Detroit Rock City**](http://www.rottentomatoes.com/m/detroit_rock_city/) - 47% - Much more than a "Kiss" film... This is a truly funny movie. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-11-05 00:30:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Pootie Tang is great. Not good, but great. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-11-04 19:14:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> VERSUS

Best Japanese Zombie Movie period. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-11-04 06:35:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Schindler's Fist </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-11-04 06:34:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Diarrhea Anne Frank </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> SHIT MY CHRISTIAN FAMILY SAYS ON FACEBOOK:

Nothing more precious than Bibles stories and pillow talk with-- wait what now? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-10-21 13:46:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-10-13 18:45:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Virginity Taken-- YES / NO </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Reddit What are your Best/Worst FOUND MONEY STORIES? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-10-04 02:22:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I have never found more than $20 at one time... But it happened twice under drastically different circumstances:

Back in the day when I was always **poor**, I had to make an emergency drive from Miami to Orlando and I had to get there fast. I had already gotten onto a Toll Road when I realized I hadn't scraped enough change together to pay all the tolls. As I went through one of the stops, the driver in front of me dropped a dollar bill and drove away. I assumed it was a single. I pulled forward and realized that it was a crisp $20 bill-- and it was about to blow out of my reach. Just then, I spotted neighboring toll collector leave his booth to also try and chase down the money. I quickly opened the door and snatched it up. He shouted "I saw it first" but it was too late. I was gone. Not only did that pay the tolls, but it got me some gas and food.

Nowadays I make decent living... About 4 months ago I found a $20 bill somebody had accidentally left at the ATM (*automated bank teller machine -- for everybody's benefit*). It was around midnight. I didn't see it in the dispenser until I was already waiting for my requested cash to be dispensed, so I took it, walked right outside the vestibule and handed it to a homeless couple. They looked hungry and I didn't need the extra cash. Even if they just bought meth, it felt good to give it away.

I'M SURE SOMEBODY ON REDDIT CAN BEAT BOTH OF THESE STORIES! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-10-04 01:02:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> DO NO HARM </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-10-02 19:52:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Anybody notice the author's name is Felch? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-10-01 04:48:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I don't have to compromise on anything.

I do whatever the fuck I want, whenever the fuck I want to do it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-09-29 04:43:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That's not true!

Or maybe it is. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-09-29 04:41:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> actual laugh out loud </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> In honor of the STEPHEN HAWKING MISQUOTE...  What is your favorite quote that you made up right now? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-09-29 04:39:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> "If I could punch one person in the face for all of America, it would without a doubt be Kim Kardashian." -- President Barack Obama </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-09-29 04:14:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I love the term "shoehorned" and I'm glad to see it used so well. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-09-27 16:59:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Couldn't agree more. This movie was really fucking cool.

I'm a lifelong fan of action films, and there was a lot about this movie that impressed me. K'Urban is the shit as always.

I'm really hoping it does well in the UK and overseas in general. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-09-27 08:52:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> America is not in denial, my friend.

Just think of it like this... With so many fat people watching television, why are there so few fat people represented ON television. The answer is-- even the obese are more interested in observing attractive people than they are in watching other fat people.

That same attitude permeates all aspects of life.  No matter how many of us there are (*and I'm including myself because I'm fat*), the ideal human form will never be an obese one.

I will admit, it is amusing to see how making fun of racial stereotypes or sexual preference is now very much taboo, but it is still completely acceptable to make fun of the overweight.

I'd say, get used to it or lose weight. The whole world isn't much different with regard to the way the obese are treated.

***OH YEAH*** and I think that 90% statistic is a little off. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> "God is good" -- WTF ?? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-09-27 04:14:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-09-27 00:45:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [Strokin](http://www.youtube.com/watch?v=P7gMkiOPSeA) by **Clarence Carter** </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-09-21 22:26:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> **Blue Eyes Crying in the Rain** by Willie Nelson

(*written by Fred Rose and originally performed by Roy Acuff-- but made famous by Nelson on his album* Red Headed Stranger)

This was historically the song that my Father always insisted should be played at his funeral. And we did. He died when I was 18.

It's a simple, little ditty about a man who left his love and will always remember her 'blue eys crying in the rain' and someday they will meet again, etc.

But to me, this is just a sweet song about the inevitability of loss and the possibility of reunion. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-09-21 22:14:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I definitly believed for my entire pre-school year that L-M-N-O-P was one word-- Elemenopee-- whenever I sang the Alphabet.

In my defense, I was only 4. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-09-21 05:47:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> But it's so dumb. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Am I the only one who LAUGHS HYSTERICALLY every time I see this part of LORD OF THE RINGS ?? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-09-20 06:47:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-09-14 16:56:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Just clarifying here... Your name is *Norrbotten*? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-09-14 16:49:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> A couple of years after my father died (I was 18 years old when he passed) my Mother comes out into the living room with a video cassette and asks me if I want to watch the memorial service. She had a tear in her eye, so I agreed.

She pops the tape in and it starts to play... On the TV is my Mom... Taking off her clothes... And initiating dirty porno sex with my Dad (when he was still alive--of course).

Apparently they had been making sex tapes for years and she mixed one in with the funeral tape by mistake. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Wrong Decision Fidel Urbina </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-09-10 03:01:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-09-09 16:44:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> **DIE HARD**

**WEIRD SCIENCE**

**PREDATOR** </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-09-09 16:32:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> YES!!! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-09-09 10:59:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> this shit made me laugh so goddamn hard </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Cut her some slack... She's from Florida </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-09-09 07:00:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Every goddamned time I post a funny picture on Reddit... </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-09-09 05:59:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> How I feel about my life today-- </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-09-09 04:19:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What I typically think of whenever somebody tells me about their "bad temper"-- </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-09-09 04:08:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-09-05 17:11:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The Middle Class. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-09-01 01:06:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Read on several social media websites that people actually believe the AURORA COLORADO MOVIE THEATER SHOOTING was orchestrated by the Obama administration in order to justify suspending elections and taking firearms away from American citizens in the wake of the UN Gun Ban Treaty.

DUMB. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-08-31 20:56:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> **DIE HULK**

New York Scientist Doctor Bruce Banner has just arrived in Los Angeles to spend the holiday with his wife Holly. Unfortunately, it's not going to be a Merry Christmas. A group of Eurotrash terrorists led by the sinister Hans Gruber takes Holly and her coworkers hostage inside a skyscraper.
They've made him angry And now theyre not going to like him.

**TAGLINE:** Ho Ho HoIm the fucking Hulk

**NEW ENDING:** Bruce banner Hulks out, rips the building off of its foundations and kills everybody, including his wife. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-08-31 20:37:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> They exist!

At least... they do at the Wendy's in Empire Center, Burbank, cA. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-08-30 23:07:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Dar Robinson is also one of the greatest Stuntmen of all time. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> One of the greatest inventions since the creation of tomato KETCHUP... </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-08-30 23:06:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> TIL that the highest stunt fall in motion picture history was in a film that you've never heard of. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-08-30 05:00:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-08-30 02:25:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> No offense, but at this stage of the game this is essentially a non-issue.

HERE IS HOW TO SOLVE THIS PROBLEM IN ONE SWIFT STEP:

You or somebody older and bigger than the 15 year old shit just needs to grab him by the fucking shoulders and shake the shit out of him while putting the fear of Jesus H God into his little 15 year old brain. Let him know that if he wants to act like a pervert, he just scored his ONE FREEBIE. If you guys ever catch him again, he will be reported to the authorities, and if he fucks with your Sister again, he goes to the Emergency Room and walks with a severe limp the rest of his life.

SIMPLE!

FYI... A 15 year old acting horny and irresposnible with a camera is NOT UNUSUAL. But you still have an obligation to protect your Sister. So fuck him. Don't ruin his life, but don't let him mess with your Sister or any other girls. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-08-29 08:38:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I think that's her Stom-Back </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-08-24 23:09:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I was thinking along these same line.

And the Americans would also be "digging in and praying" during a cold Russian Winter if they tried the old Brun and Retreat.

I think the Russians would have been a very formitable opponent... Especially after the U.S. had just finished the European campaign. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-08-24 23:06:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The American Propaganda machine was pretty effective during WWII. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-08-23 23:19:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I play Classic MS.PAC MAN a lot, but rather than go for the highest possible score (which has been done), I enable 2x Speed via the Dip Switches and try to finish each maze in the fastest possible time Which means avoiding eating ghosts because that slows you down.

Eating fruit, however, does not slow you down, so the ideal score after completing the first level is 2600. 2400 base points and 100 points each for the fruit.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-08-23 10:19:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I know. I was trying to fuck with it.

Damn. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> TIL... The JESUS page on Wikipedia is locked for EDITING. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-08-23 08:06:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-08-23 07:34:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If you have any documentation on this, please share it. (--not sarcasm) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-08-23 07:28:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Interesting points and counterpoints.

How much do you think America troop morale would have been effected by the decision to attack Moscow?

They were technically a member of the Allied Powers after Operation Barbarossa, correct?

How would the increase/decrease in morale effect their performance, taking **mattbryce2000's** 2nd and 3rd points into account? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-08-23 06:34:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> **DVincee** has the best advice by far.

I was YOU, **xStimorolx**, at a point not very long ago, and I have been able to almost completely overhaul my life by taking BABY STEPS.

When I wanted to change the way I was eating, I started by eliminating all deep-fired carbs. That was it. Then I replaced diet soda with water. And just like **DVincee** said, a third step happened so naturally that it started a trend, and I now eat much healthier.

When I wanted to keep a cleaner household, I started by doing ONE THING... Running the vacuum cleaner once every 2 weekends. Of all the household chores, vacuuming is my favorite so I focused on that, which led to me vacuuming once a week, which inspired me to keep shit off the floor, which inspired me to keep other surfaces free of clutter, which eventually led to me ACTUALLY DUSTING. Holy shit.

Do not overwhelm yourself. Pinpoint something super easy and make that your first wee, little, baby step. You might have to get 3 or 4 steps in before it becomes automatic, but it WILL BECOME AUTOMATIC.

And then you win! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-08-23 06:00:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Gladiator is an American science fiction novel first published in 1930 about Hugo Danner, a boy born with the strength of an ant and the leaping ability of the grasshopper (the same metaphors which were used to originally describe Superman's powers).
He posses superhuman strength, speed, and bulletproof skin.
The novel is widely assumed to have been an inspiration for Superman though no confirmation exists that Superman creators Jerry Siegel and Joe Shuster were influenced by it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> TIL... The idea for SUPERMAN was most likely lifted from this novel. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-08-23 05:56:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-08-22 00:33:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So nice to hear a dentist say these thing.

I am not really a sweet tooth person... I always prefer salty/fatty snacks to sweet.

And I have always wondered about things like PH balance being a better indicator for how often one should brush... One rule for everybody never seems to work. So to hear you say 2 or 3 days provided brushing is done properly makes total sense.

I just keep thinking about proto-humans and primates. They had/have no modern oral hygine, and yet they didn't/don't have an epidemic of dental issues... Of course... They didn't consume any refined sugar. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-08-21 23:24:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Never beg. But always be willing to pay. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-08-21 23:24:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yes... And I have never been a drinker of bottled water. Always tap. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-08-21 23:23:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> More semen is in order. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-08-21 23:21:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's so contrary to the way we've been brought up (*i.e. go to the dentist every 6 months*) but I actually believe this.

I also think that over-brushing and self-whitening cannot be good for enamel.

It makes me sound crazy, but I won't go to a doctor uinless I'm really sick either... In my opinion, you can walk into a Doctor's office healthy and walk out sick. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Dentists of Reddit 
I don't take exceptional care of my teeth and I never have... Why have I never had a cavity? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-08-21 22:54:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I am a 35 year old man and I have never had a cavity. I've never even experienced a toothache. I brush my teeth 2-3 times a week and I never floss. I also routinely bite my nails and chew ice (which I have done since I was a kid).

How 'normal' is this? Why am I so lucky??


I have a few theories:

**A. Good genetics**-- The problem with that idea is that nobody else in my family has good teeth. My paretns and Grandparents all had cavities in their early to mid-twenties, and they all had much better oral hygine discipline than I do.

**B. I drank a shit load of milk gorwing up**-- But I don't really belive that the calciuim from milk would make my teeth that much stronger.

**C. I have my own set of dental picks**-- And I've had them for years... So I have never allowed tarter or plaque to build up oon my teeth.

**D. I have gaps between my teeth**-- I have always had small spaces between most of my teeth, so there isn't a lot of room for tarter build up. Also, I have no wisdom teeth, so they never pushed my teeth closer together becuase they never came in.

**EDIT:** I have also only been to see a dentist 3 times in my life... Twice when I was in middle school and 1 time 6 months ago.  I only went because I have great Dental benefits and I never use them, so somebody suggested I get a cleaning. It was at that visit that they conformed I have no wosdom teeth and they were shocked at how good my teeth looked when I told them I hadn't seen a dentist in over 20 years. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-08-21 22:42:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I have slept in my tidey whities only my whole life. I never understood pajamas and why people wore them.

The same thing with slippers... It never occured to me (until I grew up) that pajamas are worn to keep sheets clean and slippers are supposed to keep your feet clean.

To me... Pajamas and Slippers were things that made your body and feet warm. And I never wanted to be warm. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-08-21 22:36:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I used to take the rings you peel off from gallons of milk and toss them behind our family fridge.

One year during Spring cleaning my Mom found them all and freaked out.

The best part was... After she threw them away, I pulled them out of the garbage and kept them until Christmas and stuffed them inside her stocking. Brilliant. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-08-21 22:33:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I never shit less than twice a day.

I thought this was completely normal until I had a girlfriend who explained that she and th members of her family were typically shit only  3-4 times a week. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-08-21 22:26:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Every night I do this. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-08-21 22:20:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> booger blaster </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> TIL.... Women in China have begun wearing nylon masks to the beach to block UV rays from their faces. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-08-21 20:16:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-08-21 07:06:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Awesome question!  Here are some of my favorites in no particular order:

[**The Mighty Quinn** - Manfred Mann](http://www.youtube.com/watch?v=K13hH0pJx5s)

[**Renegades of Funk** - Rage Against the Machine](http://www.youtube.com/watch?v=9z4NKVHX8yI)

[**Hazy Shade of Winter** - The Bangles](http://www.youtube.com/watch?v=NFRx4PkXeVM)

[**Mad World** - Gary Jules](http://www.youtube.com/watch?v=4N3N1MlvVc4)

[**I Hate You** - Slayer](http://www.youtube.com/watch?v=TAXzGkzj5E8)

[**Kickstart My Heart** - Between the Buried and Me](http://www.youtube.com/watch?v=iEXYSxT4phw)

[**Dear Prudence** - Siouxsie And The Banshees](http://www.youtube.com/watch?v=3ww-pKVClzU)

[**Higher Ground** - The Red Hot Chili Peppers](http://www.youtube.com/watch?v=7gs2o5T7oN8)

[**Smokin in the Boys Room** - Mtley Cre](http://www.youtube.com/watch?v=PYhGi65Lijg)

[**China Girl** - David Bowie](http://www.youtube.com/watch?v=BzcCVGiP-OE) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-08-21 06:38:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I challenge anyone to not feel happy when this shit plays--

[FUN by Confunkshun](http://www.youtube.com/watch?v=8ecacoC_YlE) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-08-21 03:51:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You seem like you might be more interested in a forum to express your reasons for disagreeing that 2001 is a great film-- as the majority of people seem to enjoy it. And I can appreciate that. There is nothing worse than not liking a movie that everyone else seems to love. I have the same issue currently with The Dark Knight Rises.

If you're really interested in learning about why 2001 is so well respected, it is a topic that has been discussed to death for almost 50 years-- [CHECK THIS SHIT OUT](http://www.google.com/#hl=en sugexp=les%3Beqrwrth gs_nf=1 qe=MjAwMSBhIHNwYWNlIG9keXNzZXkgYQ qesig=yaTowSjmS72N1Tca1dmj5w pkc=AFgZ2tnnZehHNM5HOKo8_q_idKcSqrQhFnTWGi9UpAviuE1_vXUEpfxRXo1mqo_SzeDiKTpg-hWiZnkbzHJFouK9KBfDE91P8w cp=22 gs_id=11 xhr=t q=2001+a+space+odyssey+analysis pf=p safe=off sclient=psy-ab oq=2001+a+space+odyssey+a gs_l= pbx=1 bav=on.2,or.r_gc.r_pw.r_cp.r_qf. fp=b07c58d71b392d97 biw=1284 bih=897)

The fact is, there a few films in history that have been studied and analyzed as much as 2001... So if you really think you're missing something, there are a ton of resources available. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-08-21 01:51:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> HONORABLE MENTION: Peter Berg.

Hancock and Battleship were awful. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-08-21 01:51:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Is it really that crazy? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> 5 DIRECTORS I WOULD RATHER SEE JUMP OFF A BRIDGE THAN TONY SCOTT </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-08-20 11:37:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> I don't believe in Ghosts, but I think I might have seen one... HAS ANYBODY ELSE WHO IS A SKEPTIC EVER SEEN A GHOST?? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-08-20 09:53:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> There was a theater we used to go to back in high school-- a 10 screen multiplex--and the rumor was that a man had died in Auditorium # 10 and it was haunted. I have never really believed in ghosts--at least not like in the stories or movies--so I never really paid much attention.

FF several years and I find myself working at this place, and of course the rumors still persist. Not only is auditorium # 10 haunted, but many of the employees had strange stories to tell.  I just couldn't give a shit. One night we were closing the place down. We had already walked from theater to theater to make sure there were no people hiding and everybody else had left for the night.

I was threading the projectors for the next day and I came to projector #10. As I was threading, I glanced over to the booth porthole down into auditorium #10 and I saw a gentleman stand up from his seat and walk out of the theater!! I freaked the fuck out, grabbed a pipe and ran downstairs. There was nobody there!

We have sensors on all of the doors and windows, none of them were opened during that time. I checked. So if somebody was really in there, they spent the night and hid themselves from the multiple motion sensors we had in every auditorium.

I think the most likely explanation is that I was tired and my mind was playing tricks on me... But it was interesting that it happened while I was near #10.

Despite this, I still do not believe in spirits and ghosts.

Has this ever happened to any other skeptics? Did it change how you feel about ghosts?? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-08-20 09:35:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> FOREIGN FILMS 

I prefer to watch any "action" oriented movies with an English audio dub rather than watching with subtitles. This drive many of my cinema-nerd friends up the fucking wall.

The best example is CROUCHING TIGER HIDDEN DRAGON. They talk a lot during the fight scenes, and it sucks having to look away from what is happening to read words at the bottom of the screen. Plus the dub on Crouching Tiger is really good--that helps. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-08-20 05:38:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I used to work a 7pm to 5am shift. During these hours the overnight cleaning staff cleaned the bathrooms. Every now and again I would need to go to the bathroom and they would have it "sectioned-off" so we couldn't use it while they were cleaning.

This one particular night I had some "issues" with my butt and I was taking frequent, URGENT shits. The third time I felt a rumble in my guts I wobbled down the hall to the Men's room and found it "**CLOSED FOR CLEANING**". This typically meant that I would have to either wait or try to go to a different floor. The problem was, our access cards only really worked on our floor (although it was possible to sneak around if you had time), and I didn't think I could hold out for the cleaning people to finish.

At this time, the third shift was exclusively male-- there were no females at all. So I hatched a genius plan... I DECIDED TO TAKE A SHIT IN THE WOMEN'S ROOM.

Aside from the rotten twat stink (*which is apparently permanently burned into the walls in all Ladies restrooms*), it was just like a Men's Room without Urinals. So I got comfy in the handicapped stall and unloaded.

At the peak of my shit, the door swings open and two girls I know from the second shift walk in. Apparently they were working late as a favor for somebody. They used the bathroom and then started talking to each other. OH MY GOD they talked forEVER! At a certain point, they realized there was a third person in the bathroom with them. I WAS TRAPPED! They started whispering to each other and left. I wiped my ass and snuck back to my office.

The next day there was a big inner-office memo posted about NOT using the wrong bathrooms. And they had figured out it was me but were to embarrassed to say anything. It took me a while to get over that one. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-08-20 05:18:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Back when we were just wee teenagers, a buddy and I were driving back to his place on a Saturday afternoon and a couple of Bro-Dudes cut us off. We shouted something clever (*like "fuck you!"*), swerved in front of them and tried to race away, but they sped up and followed us all the way back to my buddy's house.

We jumped out of the car. I ran inside and grabbed his Dad's unloaded .357 revolver and ran back out just as the Bro-Dudes arrived. They jumped out of their sports car and started shouting at my buddy (*and these guys were freaking huge*) so I popped out and pointed the gun at them and told them to get the fuck away. They were like "*Yo! Chill out*" and "*Calm down*" etc.

A moment later they apologized and asked us if we smoked weed. We did. So they rolled a joint and we smoked it with them.

We learned that they were just basically twenty-something versions of us (they had grown up in the area and gone to the same schools we had, etc). They ended up being really cool guys.

Right before we parted company, the driver Bro-Dude waved me over to his car and said he wanted to show me something-- and he pulled a **9MM** out from under his driver's seat. He said "The only difference between mine and yours is that mine is loaded. You should never point a gun at anybody unless you're ready for a gunfight".

I've never pointed a gun at anybody else in my whole life and I probably never will. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-08-20 04:46:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Every time I'm reminded of this... I actually want to insert more misspelled words just to upset those people. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-08-19 23:30:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [This is how I feel when I lose my Roomba](http://imgur.com/a/J3FaK#jUzlU) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-08-19 23:00:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> No... Bill Parker is my reddit pseudonym.

I stole it from a line in Raising Arizona. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-08-19 20:29:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> DIE SATISFIED </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-08-19 18:52:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> When I was a kid, there was another boy in the neighborhood who was always bragging about how much money his parents had and about all the cool stuff they owned. We'll call him BILLY. Needless to say, we stopped playing with Billy because of said douchery.

But our neighborhood was basically one big circle so we were always riding our bikes passed their house. When we would NOT say hello to him, his parents would say things very loudly (obviously so we could hear) like "It's okay, Billy, they're just jealous." We were not jealous.

But they basically became militant about the fact that none of the kids in the neighborhood liked their son. His mom would even spray us with their water hose if we used the sidewalk in front of their house.

Please note: We never picked on Billy because he was bigger than all of us (even though he was the same age). We just stopped asking him to play with us.

Anyway... FF several months... We were playing in the street NEAR their house (not in front, but near). Billy came out and told us to leave. Their were a bunch of us so I told him to fuck off. He went inside and got his mom. She came out and told us to leave, and we all told her to fuck off too. So she ordered Billy to "get over there" and make us leave.

He marched right towards me-- and I'm not sure what his plan was or what he was expecting, but he was almost 6 inches taller than me and looked pretty menacing-- AND he was talking shit the whole way about beating the crap about me.
As soon as he got within arms reach of me I just beat the fucking shit out him-- and it only took about 8-10 seconds. He was on the concrete screaming and his Mom ran over and shoulder-rammed me onto the ground, then stood over me and screamed at me for beating Billy up.

I was so shocked I couldn't even tell her it was all her fault.

Some parents are just fucking weird. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-08-19 18:24:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Fuck both of these losers.

When is the last time either of them made a watchable film??

They both suck. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> I just deleted a nasty remark I made here on reddit before I fully understood how the karma system works.

WHAT ROOKIE MISTAKES HAVE YOU MADE ON REDDIT?? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-08-18 02:49:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I was a little hit high and it was late, and I was in a sub-reddit about gay/lesbian tax reform in germany, and I made a tastless joke-- something to the effect of: "Too bad they started both world wars and killed all those jews because nobody care about their progressive social reform". It was a touch below the belt. Perhaps I shouldn't have said it, but I did. Needless to say this was not a popular comment. But I owned it.

FF a couple weeks... I realize people are still downvoting my comment. So I deleted it. I'm not really ashamed of what I said... I tacked on an edit that said--"Just Kidding". I typically get one or two points per dumb remark/story, but this one got me a whopping -29 points! Yikes. The funny thing is, I have no problem with Germans. It just seemed more funny when I typed it than it did the next day.

The point is... It was an insensitive joke and it cost me some karma (both here on reddit and probably a little bit in real life). Lesson learned.

What dumb things have you done on reddit that you lived to talk about? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-08-17 22:41:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I needed somebody to follow me to the mechanic shop. My car was riding dirty and I was worried it might break down on the way.

As I was taking a right onto the freeway, my buddy didn't stop so he could stay right behind me and he got pulled over by a Highway Patrolman. He got a $175 ticket.

I payed for half. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> SCUMBAG CHUCK NORRIS </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-08-17 09:20:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-08-17 01:44:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> No offense... These are not that good. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-08-17 01:30:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This is a horrible thing to have happened.

But I am of the opinion that **concerneddad1965** has done all he can do at this point... Now he is now on the recieving and of ridicuolous accusations from his wife, his kid is not being helped and the Dog is still in danger of abuse.

Call me crazy, but at this point, I think the authorities need to be involved. Clearly, keeping things quiet to preserve the kid's dignity has back-fired. The authorities need to be called in and official records need to begin.

If left untreated, this teenager could very well progress down this sick pathway and end up being a problem for society and not just this family. Knowing what he knows, **concerneddad1965** might be obligated to report his son to the police and force him to get help.

The Wife needs to be overruled, the kid needs therapy and the dogs needs protection... Unfortunatly, the only person who can really ensure all of these things happen is **concerneddad1965** </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-08-16 19:50:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I used to manage a movie theater and at least once a week somebody would ask (regarding popcorn or soda) --

"Do you have anything smaller than a Large?"

Yeah, you fuckin moron. Regular and Medium. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-08-16 19:45:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> "Jesus Christ died for my sins." </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Who The Fuck is Robert Picardo? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-08-12 09:00:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-08-10 23:49:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> **STORY 1:** I was walking through the SEARS in North Hollywood, CA and I was strolling down the bathroom/plumbing supply isle looking for a gasket for my toilet. I wasn't watching where I was going and I slammed (pretty hard) into a pleasent looking old man. It was Ernest Borgnine. I recognized him , and he saw that I knew who he was and smiled. I was kind of high at the time, and all I managed to say was "AIRWOLF!" Without missing a beat, he said "Yup". We shook hands and I walked away.

**STORY 2:** I used to work at the Blockbuster Video in North Hollywood, and one day, a shorter black guy wearing a colorful outfit walked in and started asking about Brigitte Nielson movies. I was the go to trivia guy at my store, so I started walking him around and pulling the Brigitte Nielson movies of the shelf and he was holding onto all of them. I said "You must really like Brigitte Nielson " and he responded (in a VERY familiar voice) "Do I like Brigitte Nielson ?" while pulling his shades down. I turned around and realized it was FLAVA FLAV. Apparently he had just wrapped The Surreal Life on VH1 where he and Brigitte had hooked up. He rented RED SONJA, ROCKY 4, COBRA and BEVERLY HILLS COP 3.

**STORY 3:** I was driving down Overland Ave. in Culver City, CA and a dumb ass driver flew accross 3 lanes of traffic to get into the left-hand turn lane and almost t-boned my car. Instead I just got side-swiped. I jumped out of my car screaming "What the fuck??" when I got a good look at the other driver. She was really pretty. When we exchanged information and went about business. Later I realized that she was AnnaLynne McCord from the new 90210 tv show. After I notified my insurance comapny that evening, I got a nasty phone call from her bitch sister (from a private number) who threatens me by saying they were going to file a lawsuit against me-- even thhough she admitted being at fault. So I posted all of her personal info in Facebook. Then I sold the story to TMZ. Later, her insurance company cut me a check for $1200... Turns out the damage she did was only superficial and could be wiped off with a rag.

**STORY 4:** I got on-stage at a GEORGE CLINTON concert in Miami Florida. He apparently liked me so much that he gave me his wedding veil (he was weraing a wedding dress) and invited me backstage to hang out in the green room. After the show I enjoyed the unique privilage of watching George Clinton smoke crack cocaine in front of me. I also scored some free sandwiches. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> When will the Conspiracy Theorists learn that their so-called inside information is just as unrealiable as information from the Government and Mass Media? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-08-09 23:21:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Is it just me or have the Conspiracy Theorists gotten kind of lazy?

I keep seeing all of these posts on Reddit and Facebook where people act like they have the inside scoop on some covert information that theyre going to blow the lid off of, and they ultimately are just posting a link to Wikipedia or an Alex Jones video. BORING! The worst part is they are so quick to believe the dumbest shit.

When will these people learn that Conspiracy Theory information is  unrealiable as information from the Government and Mass Media? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-08-09 22:50:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> HOW TO VIDEO: The proper way to racially segregate a public school district. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-08-09 16:00:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm a competitive eater.

I've always secretly hoped to eat a rapist in order to save a young woman's honor. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-08-09 02:44:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> "What keeps me up is my personal life choices.. "

Jesus... I would quadruple UpVote this comment if I could. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-08-09 02:13:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I say shit like that to people every day, and I have a stright look on my face when I say it-- but I'm always joking.

Are you sure he wasn't joking? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-08-09 00:38:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Whenever I eat a bowl of CHILI I have to serve it over FRITOS with Cheese and onions!!! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-08-08 00:34:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I had a very large homeless man tell me that he needed moeny for Ballet Lessons. He got some cash. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-08-07 23:27:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I woke up in the First Class cabin of an airplane headed for San Antonio.

I was a Freshman in college in Miami, FL. It was last Friday before Spring Break and I was supposed to catch a flight out of Miami International at 6am on Saturday morning.  Around 10pm I was packing when my buddies came to my room and told me we were going drinking.

We started pounding pitchers of beer around 11pm and kept drinking until 2 when the bars closed. We then proceeded to an after hours spot and drank hard liquor for the next couple of hours. Around 4:30am I realized my ride to the airport was leaving our campus at 5-- so we haul ass back to the dorm. Enroute, I vomitted all over myself and the inside of my buddy's vintage Duster.

He helps me inside, helps me change clothes and then loads me into my buddy's rental car. On the way to the airport I barfed in the rental car (but not on myself). My buddy was pissed, so he loaded me onto the bus from the rental car place to the terminal and that's the last hing I remember.

I don't remember getting to the airport, going through security or boarding my plane. I woke up 20 minutes before landing in San Antonio and I was sitting with a row to myself in the First Class cabin. As I opened my eyes I fumbled for an air-sick bag and completely filled it with blown chunks. Before I could even fold up the bag a stewdardess approached with a pitcher of water and traded me for the vomit bag. I asked her what I was doing in first class and she told me I had gotten on a flight that was an hour earlier than my scheduled flight and they bumped me to first class. I didn't even get to enjoy it because I was passed-the-fuck-out.

The worst part was, I got to San Antonio an hour early and had to sit in the airport for an hour waiting for my parents and I was still wasted. When they walked up and found me half-concious, I tried telling them I had the flu, but my dad took one look at me, laughed and said "You're hungover". Then they made me walk around the fucking Alamo all day. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-08-07 01:06:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Nobody cares what it's really called, you Canadian freak. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The Top 5 Guys KRISTEN STEWART Should Have Cheated With Instead of Rupert Sanders </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-08-05 04:30:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-07-23 09:26:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The worst part is... He was re-shooting the end of the film so that the Great White Shark explodes after being impaled by the boat. (--Not a joke) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> TIL... MICHAEL CAINE could not attend the Academy Awards to collect his Best Supporting Actor Oscar for Hannah and Her Sisters because of his shooting commitments on JAWS 4:THE REVENGE. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-07-23 08:48:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Law Enforcement, Military and Counter-Terrorist experts PLEASE ADVISE  Should America create something similar to "STOP, DROP and ROLL" in the event of a mass shooting? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-07-21 05:24:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> We need a better way to respond to mass shooters. Hitting the deck and hoping to not get shot is a poor option.

Before we were taught the simple practice of Stop, Drop and Roll... More people suffered severe burns and death from fire. Stop, Drop and Roll works.

When an anthill is attacked by an invader, the ants swarm en masse and engulf the offender. Could people do something similar to a gunman?

Once a shooting begins, there will never be time for the potential victims (who are also likely to be strangers) to coordinate an offensive. But if we had an AUTOMATIC REFLEXIVE ACTION drilled into us, could we respond without thinking and achieve a more positive outcome?? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
