<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject4909</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-26 06:13:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> @dolphinesque: I agree sooo much!!! Thank You </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-26 06:10:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hey I did go to my interviews; I am glad that I did. I agree small steps. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> 24 1/2 Years Old Female: No job living with parents in squatters' condition   depressed VENT. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-25 13:45:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> TITLE: 24 1/2 Years Old Female: No job living with parents in squatters' condition   depressed VENT. I don't know why I am up this late and I am ashamed to be posting this (and probably will regret this later) but I got to get a few things off my chest. THIS IS HELLA LONG BUT I APPRECIATE ANYONE WHO CAN READ   LEND A PAIR OF EYES/HEARTS. JUST NEED TO VENT. As the title suggests I am 24 1/2 Years Old Female: No job living with parents in squatters' condition   depressed.
By squatters' conditions I mean: Living in a house that had two fires almost 10 years ago/on-going construction. Living without heat, running/drinking water, shower/tub, toilet, stove/gas. Aka can't shower, cook, or shit properly. Living in a living room/sleeping on couches with my parents. This is where we eat, sleep, "lounge"
How I got here/Where I was: Almost a year ago. Got laid off unexpectedly. I was very unprofessional at this job and surprised I didn't get fired (due to depression). Weird but kinda saw this as a blessing in disguise. Mom got fired (again) from part-time job, lost apartment we all had to move back to the house. Mom previously left Dad after first fire. My mom has lost hope. Dad living paycheck to paycheck, constantly working. For months before internship, half-assingly looked for apartments, sublets, full-times jobs, but never really followed through because of depression, fear, and anxiety. Have savings but don't want to touch in case of emergencies. I am very disciplined when it comes to money. I save constantly and can pay for food/phone bill. Fear of being broke; also makes me afraid to spend money. Been battling diagnosed depression for 5+ years. I had a counselor for 2 1/2 years and she told me she things I have major depression.
Where I am/Present day: Let go from internship recently after a long bout of unemployment due to small non-profit budget reasons. Got let go in early August. Mom has part-time job. Before then used to help out/give her $$$ Dad has full-time job. Again half-assingly looking for apartments, sublets, and jobs. Actually have 2 job interviews today but I am not sure I am going (fear, developing slight Agoraphobia). Not sure if I want a job now. Managed to save money from internship (already on top of savings from last job). I can live off these savings for a couple of months. Family is divided. Father stubborn and overworked. Mother hopeless and slightly irresponsible. Etc. Constant fights. Feel alone, that no one has my back, that I can't trust anyone. Resentment, betrayal, anger, sadness/mixed feelings, towards parents/family. My parents has let me down so much. Don't have confidence in myself/ going out on my own because I don't have anyone to truly fall back on if I fail. 1st world poor.
Now that I got the backstory out the way it's time for feelings. This past couple of months have been the worst of my life. I have never felt soo lost and soo weak ever. On days that I didn't have my internship I used be afraid to leave my house. I only survived at my internship because my fear of being completely broke outweighs my fear of being outside. Towards the end of my internship it has gotten way worst (my developing Agoraphobia). I say developing because I can physically go outside it's just that I need to mentally distract myself (playing games on phone, listening to music, reading). I even experienced silent freakouts at my internship. The house has made me a bit crazy. Thoughts racing, constant stomachaches when I think about my "reality"; feeling unhinged/unsafe. The only way I can relax myself is Netflix. I have developed escapist tendencies   I don't think I can face reality head on.
LOGIC/HEAD IS TELLING ME Get a full time job Save some more. Get the fuck out. Don't want to enable my mental illnesses.
HEART/BODY IS TELLING ME: Slow down, take it easy, take care of your mental health FIRST. Be creative, use this free time to write and figure out life/career. Need emotional support. Fear I am heading towards a breakdown
I feel I always have to choose between them. To be honest I am leaning more towards my heart. I am not sure if it's my fear/mental issues talking or if it's actually what I want to do. The only real reason I am leaning towards my heart is, I never actually truly followed my heart. I always did what was expected of me, always was responsible, mature, put together. And for 5 years onward my programming/facade is breaking down. I always did my school work, hardly ever socialized, never got in trouble, always obeyed my parents. I was always smart with money, controlled, and careful. Got to college and all that I was, was questioned. I realized at 18 I was never actually truly happy. I did things because I thought that is what I should be doing than what I want to be doing. Negative thinking, social media, social community isolation (went away for college).
Before I close this novel of a post; I just want to let you know that I am NOT/NEVER WAS SUICIDAL. I also don't think I am completely hopeless. I know I am smart   responsible I just need help/time/emotional support and to not be soo hard on myself. Even so, I don't believe it (I know this is statement contradictory   weird). I struggling with knowing   believing. I know things/have insight, but I can't put them into believing/action.
Anyway vent over (I got much more to say but this is HELLA long). </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> 24 1/2 Years Old Female: No job living with parents in squatters' condition   depressed VENT. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-08-25 12:25:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> TITLE: 24 1/2 Years Old Female: No job living with parents in squatters' condition   depressed VENT.
I don't know why I am up this late and I am ashamed to be posting this (and probably will regret this later) but I got to get a few things off my chest. THIS IS HELLA LONG BUT I APPRECIATE ANYONE WHO CAN READ   LEND A PAIR OF EYES/HEARTS. JUST NEED TO VENT.
As the title suggests I am 24 1/2 Years Old Female: No job living with parents in squatters' condition   depressed.

By squatters' conditions I mean:
Living in a house that had two fires almost 10 years ago/on-going construction.
Living without heat, running/drinking water, shower/tub, toilet, stove/gas. Aka can't shower, cook, or shit properly. 
Living in a living room/sleeping on couches with my parents. This is where we eat, sleep, "lounge"

How I got here/Where I was: Almost a year ago.
Got laid off unexpectedly. I was very unprofessional at this job and surprised I didn't get fired (due to depression). Weird but kinda saw this as a blessing in disguise.
Mom got fired (again) from part-time job, lost apartment we all had to move back to the house. Mom previously left Dad after first fire. My mom has lost hope.
Dad living paycheck to paycheck, constantly working.
For months before internship, half-assingly looked for apartments, sublets, full-times jobs, but never really followed through because of depression, fear, and anxiety.
Have savings but don't want to touch in case of emergencies.
I am very disciplined when it comes to money. I save constantly and can pay for food/phone bill.
Fear of being broke; also makes me afraid to spend money.
Been battling diagnosed depression for 5+ years. I had a counselor for 2 1/2 years and she told me she things I have major depression.

Where I am/Present day:
Let go from internship recently after a long bout of unemployment due to small non-profit budget reasons. Got let go in early August.
Mom has part-time job. Before then used to help out/give her $$$
Dad has full-time job.
Again half-assingly looking for apartments, sublets, and jobs.  Actually have 2 job interviews today but I am not sure I am going (fear, developing slight Agoraphobia). Not sure if I want a job now.
Managed to save money from internship (already on top of savings from last job). I can live off these savings for a couple of months.
Family is divided. Father stubborn and overworked. Mother hopeless and slightly irresponsible. Etc. Constant fights. 
Feel alone, that no one has my back, that I can't trust anyone.
Resentment, betrayal, anger, sadness/mixed feelings, towards parents/family. My parents has let me down so much.
Don't have confidence in myself/ going out on my own because I don't have anyone to truly fall back on if I fail. 1st world poor.

Now that I got the backstory out the way it's time for feelings.
This past couple of months have been the worst of my life. I have never felt soo lost and soo weak ever. On days that I didn't have my internship I used be afraid to leave my house. I only survived at my internship because my fear of being completely broke outweighs my fear of being outside. Towards the end of my internship it has gotten way worst (my developing Agoraphobia). I say developing because I can physically go outside it's just that I need to mentally distract myself (playing games on phone, listening to music, reading). I even experienced silent freakouts at my internship. The house has made me a bit crazy. Thoughts racing, constant stomachaches when I think about my "reality"; feeling unhinged/unsafe. The only way I can relax myself is Netflix. I have developed escapist tendencies   I don't think I can face reality head on. 

LOGIC/HEAD IS TELLING ME
Get a full time job
Save some more.
Get the fuck out.
Don't want to enable my mental illnesses.

HEART/BODY IS TELLING ME:
Slow down, take it easy, take care of your mental health FIRST.
Be creative, use this free time to write and figure out life/career.
Need emotional support.
Fear I am heading towards a breakdown

I feel I always have to choose between them. To be honest I am leaning more towards my heart. I am not sure if it's my fear/mental issues talking or if it's actually what I want to do. The only real reason I am leaning towards my heart is, I never actually truly followed my heart. I always did what was expected of me, always was responsible, mature, put together. And for 5 years onward my programming/facade is breaking down. I always did my school work, hardly ever socialized, never got in trouble, always obeyed my parents. I was always smart with money, controlled, and careful. Got to college and all that I was, was questioned. I realized at 18 I was never actually truly happy. I did things because I thought that is what I should be doing than what I want to be doing. Negative thinking, social media, social community isolation (went away for college).

Before I close this novel of a post; I just want to let you know that I am NOT/NEVER WAS SUICIDAL. I also don't think I am completely hopeless. I know I am smart   responsible I just need help/time/emotional support and to not be soo hard on myself. Even so, I don't believe it (I know this is statement contradictory   weird). I struggling with knowing   believing. I know things/have insight, but I can't put them into believing/action.

Anyway vent over (I got much more to say but this is HELLA long). </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
