<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject6412</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> How I feel whenever I stop drinking and am still awake when the hangover kicks in... </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-01-17 09:51:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> TIL Billy Crystal is a dick. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-01-11 23:06:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-12-19 23:52:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> A few years ago, I was trying to get a job as a writer on a major Hollywood film.  My agent at the time wasn't so hot, so I got drunk one New Year's Eve (also happens to be my birthday) and decided to berate the producer (I had gotten his personal cell number) right there at the shitty, sorta-collegetown bar I was at with my friends... while I didn't get the job necessarily, a few months later I was given a copy of the script asking for my input and to punch up some of the dialogue (which I was paid for)... apparently the producer in question found me "funny and ballsy."  The kicker?  I don't remember AT ALL what we talked about.  I was told by a friend later at one point I was just shouting expletives.

...anywho, WHO-RAY BEER! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-12-09 10:48:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Get high and watch Your Highness. I promise, for 90 minutes, your beautiful smile will never leave your face... and, in the end, is that not what every comedy wishes to achieve? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-11-23 06:29:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Don't like it, move on. Simple as that. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-11-23 06:27:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I fucking love Baseketball! Wildly underrated. It's a shame Matt and Trey seem to disown it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-11-01 09:18:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> somebody is trying way too hard to troll... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Including a working light for the "face" and roller blades to create that floaty effect, I felt my buddy's costume deserved some love... </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-11-01 07:39:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-10-03 20:32:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Ravenous!  Such a wonderful, underrated dark comedy </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The many reasons I am currently nailing a tape-covered, filth-encrusted, two dollar Wal-Mart flip-flop to my bedroom wall. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-05-30 02:37:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Last Tuesday morning I received a phone call from my brother.  I let it ring.  Then I got another.  And another.  Finally I answered.  My father, who lived in Melbourne, Florida, was just rushed to the hospital and thrown into the ICU.  I work in a restaurant (although, as you can see, I pretend to be a writer as well).  Tuesday, for me, is my Monday, in that I have off Sunday and Monday and work Tues., Wed., Thurs., Fri. and Saturday.  I called out.  And, as I was about to find out in the coming twelve hours, I was not going to be back to work for at least a week.

Thursday morning my brother and I woke up very early to fly down to Florida (we live in PA).  At the Philly airport, waiting for the first of four flights altogether (two there, two back), my faux-army camouflage painted flip-flop decided to come apart.  I had purchased them maybe three months prior for $2.50 at Wal-Mart.  I immediately knew that the flops un-doing would be my own as well.  Between the initial two flights, they came apart at least a dozen more times, always at the worst moment.  One hour delay on the first flight, and they come undone.  Two hour lay-over in Charlotte, and they come undone.  Finally get on the plane in Charlotte, and an older woman passes out from the extreme heat, forcing us to un-board and wait an additional hour for a new plane to arrive.  They come undone.  Twice.

When we touch down in the tiny Melbourne airport, I immediately know that there is no denying the inevitable.  My aunts face says it all.  

They come undone.  

My father, always a heavy drinker, was dying.  His liver had pretty much called it quits and, as we watched and waited, I saw the man who showed me Jaws for the first time at the wee age of 5. The man who gave me my first type writer. The man who took me to countless Phllies games. The man who rented my brother and I Robocop 2 and The Toxic Avenger without bothering to read the rating.  The man who bought us an N64 just because, as a huge Bond fan, he wanted Goldeneye.  The frustrated man who threw the same controller to the ground because, as he claimed, the Japs had something against lefties.  The drunken man who would go on tirades about O.J. Simpson and the inevitable draft that was coming.  That same drunken man hours later, falling asleep on the same goddamn chair he fell asleep on every single night, a half-drunk glass of wine usually by his side.

The man who comforted me when my agent dumped me right before signing a potential deal with Marvel two summers ago.  Crushing my dream of working for a company I have admired since he bought me that first X-Men Vs. Fantastic Four comic at the boardwalk all those years ago.  Crushing my dream of getting out of the fucking restaurant business forever.  As youll come to learn, theyre all assholes, he said, sort of laughing.  All of em.

The man who, just a few months ago, right after moving to Florida, sent me his half-finished notebook in the mail.  The thing was old and filled with scribbled anecdotes, some profound, some confusing and some a touch angry.  But despite any of that, its what is written upon that very last page he left that will forever remind me of him:

Grammo: This book has brought me great luck - Same to you! - Now finish the rest of it! - Dad

The man that I called dad was dying.

As we head for the ICU wing, they come undone for what I have decided is the last time.  I pick up the single fuck-flop and carry it with me, wandering around the sterile environment with a slight limp, but not caring at all.  The sight of my father lying in a practically comatose state, fetal position is enough to make you forget about every undone flip-flop on the planet, let alone the filthy, mud-covered one I was currently clutching in my right paw.

My brother and I stayed in Melbourne the rest of the night, all day Friday and, finally, left Saturday morning.  By this point, I had finally taken a roll of industrial medical tape to the bastard flops, wrangling them together into a grotesque mess of dirt, dead grass and debilitating odor.  But at that point, the damage had been done.

My dad was dying, and now it was just a matter of waiting.

Yesterday I received that call.  And now, Im writing this just an hour after taking down the cardboard storyboard that was hanging above my laptop.  In actuality, a beaten up Dawn of the Dead poster I flipped over to use as a giant note pad, outlining the sequel to a script Im pretty sure only five people on this planet have read.  In its place, the flip-flop, now nailed upon the wooden frame of the wall, a ghastly reminder of the worst weekend of my life.  

A reminder that no matter how bad things might seem, they could always be worse.

A few hours ago I tried to go to work but, seeing as I hadnt called to say I was home, they didnt bother putting me on the floorplan.  When I returned home, my roommate, a South American native by the name of Dave had poured three shots of Johnny Walker Blue.  One shot for me, one shot for you, one shot for your dad.  Spic tradition, he continues, is that when youre ready to let go, you pour the third shot upon the ground.  We cheersed to Rocky Paschall before throwing back our own.  And now, just three hours later, my fathers glass sits next to me.  And as I type these last few ramblings, I know I am about to go outside, into the storm currently nailing Philadelphia and pour my dads shot of 200-dollar-a-bottle whiskey upon the grass.

With love to Al Paschall.

-Graham Paschall, May 2012 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
