<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject3471</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> When They Come For Me, They Will Find Me </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-07 00:29:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Theyre in the house.

Two of them, at least, and probably more. Im sorry that this will be typed so fast, I have to get everything out as quickly as I can.

My husband was out when someone knocked on the door after 10:00 p.m. I knew something was wrong, so I backed out of the living room. I took Chloe (six-year-old daughter) with me very quietly. 

When the living room window shattered, I grabbed her and ran up the stairs. Were hiding under my bed. 

I left my phone on the kitchen counter. No time to grab it.
 
I was able to grab the laptop off the bed, but have no messenger program and no time to download one. I need to type up what is happening in case we disappear.

I have a very bad feeling about what these people want. I wont send an email because those can be deleted. Im going to send this to the biggest message board I can find; theres no way to call for help, but Ill be damned if I go away and no one knows why. At least Ill have that.
 
Madison (16-year-old daughter) was in her room when this happened. I have not heard a sound from there. I have my arm wrapped around Chloes head to keep her quiet. Call me a bad mom if you will, I wont have her dying because her cries were too loud. I told her to bite down on my arm if she feels she cant hold it in. 

This bedroom is on the second floor. Only one inside staircase. No roof under the window, just a straight sixteen-foot plummet. This is bad.

Shit shit shit

Keep it together, Lacy. Okay, half of the reason Im writing this is to stay sane, Im trembling in the dark and squeezed under my bed. Chloe is shaking to the point of nearly convulsing. 

I hear voices downstairs. Angry talking. I do not recognize them. They are mens voices.


No


A gunshot.  A loud one. Cooper (eight-year-old son) was in his bedroom. I did not have a chance to get to him before I ran upstairs. 

No, I chose not to. Its true. And if I die tonight Ill burn in hell. 

Now theyre shouting. 

Come on OUT, Lacy. We know youre up there.

An angry voice. 

And I realize that being under the bed is the FIRST place theyll look. Of course it is. The bed and the closet. The most obvious places.

When they come for me, they will find me.
 
I have to plan. God help me. What do I do? 

I have to get out of this hiding place. I have to get out of this house. I have to move now, before they come up here and its far too late. 

Think.

Were losing PATIENCE. Angier still.

Lacy, stop writing. Stop yourself and get out from under this bed. Move NOW.


Oh no.


Terrified screaming. Its Coopers voice. They have him.
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> When They Come For Me, They Will Find Me </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-06 19:45:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
