<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject2082</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-16 22:03:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>   That's how they can get the third party support they're lacking.

Third party games don't seem to be a big priority for Nintendo. It's baffling, but since the Gamecube, they seem not to care about third parties. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-16 21:50:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  It seems to me like they thought they would the first ones into an otherwise empty market, and that didn't happen.

Yes, I've said the same thing in the past.

When they've had a chance to reevaluate their position, they'll probably give some ground on this one, particularly as more and more headsets show up running OVR. It will give them a much needed PR win, and bring their storefront a crapload of new customers.

Maybe. It depends how successful their current strategy will be. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-16 20:34:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That's possibly what will happen, but they might be able to secure their platform since they have a hardware dongle (the rift). </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-16 17:01:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Oblivion gates had a similar aesthetic. They were very annoying. Draug tombs are repetitive but much better. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-16 16:54:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  PoE 

Pillars of Eternity made me doubt the quality of their writers. I found the story extremely boring. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-16 16:51:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>   The only reason to do what they are doing is to try and lock people into their hardware platform

I agree. They're playing the long term game. They prefer not to get money from Vive owners to ensure that their platform becomes the dominant one.

Catch is, there's no way to enforce this indefinitely on an open platform like PC, and you usually need a pretty sizeable headstart on the competition to make it work. This would have been a really good plan if the vive hadn't come out of freakin nowhere two months before pre-orders went live.

I mostly agree. But if Oculus keeps buying all the good games and Valve doesn't do anything in response, then buyers will notice that the Rift offers a superior experience. This will be an expensive strategy in the long term and I don't know if they can keep this up indefinitely. Eventually, they won't just be competing against the Vive but against an army of Chinese clones. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-16 15:03:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If anything, new process nodes are going to be coming slower and slower. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-16 15:01:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I understand, but if Vive owners can use their storefront, then the exclusives aren't really exclusive anymore. Sony wouldn't want Xbox One owners to buy uncharted through the PSN store on Xbox. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-16 05:55:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Having exclusives makes their platform more attractive. If all the good games are exclusive to Oculus, it will take wind out of the Vive's sails. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-16 05:49:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yes, I think so. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-15 22:49:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> We'll see how much time they spend on optimization. But supporting two platforms is not impossible. Many developers are already dealing with the PS4 + XboxOne. The PC has an almost infinite number of different configurations, so it's a very different problem. Plus, PC drivers are high level (as of now). </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-15 22:47:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I know. I didn't say that it was perfect. Don't you think that a 30% margin of error is pretty good? Read up https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/FLOPS and processor design. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-15 20:55:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Okay, but 6Teraflops is a pretty useful metric. It gives us a rough idea of the performance we can expect. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-15 20:54:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Read this: http://www.eurogamer.net/articles/digitalfoundry-2016-xbox-one-project-scorpio-spec-analysis

According to Eurogamer, it's not Polaris but Vega (hence the 2017 date). </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-15 20:52:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  The question that remains however is what developers would develop for the Scorpio if it's install base were small

Developers won't even be allowed to make exclusive for the Scorpio. It's not a new generation, but an upgraded Xbox One. 

Standard Xbox One games will just run at a better resolution on the Scorpio. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-15 20:49:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This is why they're not calling the Scorpio Next Gen. It's a higher spec Xbox. It runs the same games, but at 4k resolution. Devs are not allowed to develop Scorpio exclusives.

This means that supporting Scorpio will, hopefully, be very easy. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-15 20:43:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> 30% is a huge number, so results shouldn't favor Nvidia so heavily if Tflops were a good indicator at all

It not how big it is, it's how you use it. AMD cards tend to have better compute capabilities, but games are not always optimized to take advantage of them. Things are different in a console. 

It's a bit like with the PS3. Not everyone could use the Cell processor efficiently. Many developers let the SPUs go to waste. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-15 20:40:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The FuryX is probably starved for memory bandwidth. 

I'm assuming that Microsoft has designed its new console properly. I can't tell you if they'll deliver what they've promised, but it looks possible. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-15 20:13:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  But buying out games that were already in development or close to completion like what they did with Giant Cop is just objectively anti-consumer. 

The real reason is that they'll never make money by just being a hardware manufacturer. They need to create a locked-down ecosystem, like Apple or Sony. That's obviously not in the best interest of customers who want an open platform. 

But they don't want to see customers buying a game through Steam and giving a 30% cut to Valve while they struggle to make 5% on hardware. Oculus is not a viable investment as a pure hardware manufacturer. Better leave that low-margin business to Asian manufacturers who are close to the production. (TVs and computer monitors are all manufactured by Asian companies)

I'm just trying to be informative. Not defending Facebook but explaining why they might be making those decisions with the Oculus Rift. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-15 16:40:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Consoles are always better at using the hardware. The PS4 and Xbox One use a weak laptop CPU. It's clocked at 1.6Ghz (PS4) and 1.75Ghz (Xbox One), which is in the PS4's case about half of what a normal i5 cpu is clocked at.

The PS4 GPU is equivalent to the now completely obsolete Radeon HD 7850. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-15 16:37:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  I can't imagine how they're gonna get 4k when there are still popular console games running at 720p

They designed their console to do exactly that: run games in 4k. That's why they have a 6Teraflop GPU. If they didn't mess up, it should be possible. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-15 16:36:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> They said that games would have the same framerate. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-15 16:34:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This interview seems more reliable than a quick statement made in a video. Statement: "a true 4k gaming machine, giving you a native 4k framebuffer so you can see games in all their beauty, or if developers want to use these 6 Teraflops in other ways they're free to do that."

He might have just been referring to the fact that developers could choose to upscale from, say 1440p and then use the extra power in other ways, like extra effects or whatever. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-15 16:14:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So, what IPs do they own?

- Quake
- Wolfenstein

They've also published some obscure stuff, like this: https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Zero_Critical </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-15 15:48:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I wonder if this has anything to do with VR. Kinect takes extra CPU power and that just wouldn't work with VR at the same time. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-15 06:34:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It makes sense for a developer to choose one framerate for both consoles, since a lot systems could be tied to it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> SimCity 2013's creative director explains what went right and what went wrong </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-09 19:18:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Hong Kong NEON, Sharon Blance, Photography, 2016 </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-09 15:58:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> KSP lead dev Resigns </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-06 17:42:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Retro '80s Rhythm Game Neon Drive Hits Greenlight </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-06 15:32:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Kerbal Space Program Lead Dev Quits </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-06 04:59:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> McDonalds ex-CEO: $15/hr minimum wage will unleash the robot rebellion </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-25 19:59:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> McDonalds ex-CEO: $15/hr minimum wage will unleash the robot rebellion </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-05-25 19:37:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Intel announces move away from PCs </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-20 02:38:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> After 15 years of disappointment, can Final Fantasy be great again? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-14 18:03:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Preview of Planet Coaster: RCT successor </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-22 18:02:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Trading in new ipad air 2 for ipad pro? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-03-22 16:02:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hi,

I just bought a new ipad air 2 128 GB, used mostly for office work, web and TV series.

Would it be worth returning it and then waiting to get the new 10in iPad pro? I don't do color sensitive work or movie editing. The pencil could be useful for signing documents, instead of those cheaper pencils I use. Keyboard is interesting but a bit pricey (but worth it?).

What do you think? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> StarCraft: Building A Brilliant Brood War Bot </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-01 06:55:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Dolphin Emulator - Wii USB support </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-26 17:01:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Dolphin Emulator : November Progress Report </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-12-01 15:21:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Is Star Citizen Going to Crash and Burn? - Big Star Citizen Controversy erupted a few days ago </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-10-03 23:33:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Gaming computers offer huge, untapped energy savings potential </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-08-31 19:11:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Gaming computers offer huge, untapped energy savings potential </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-08-31 18:58:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Trine 3 is short because the devs ran out of money </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-08-22 14:33:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The best PC games that you should play right now (Eurogamer) </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-20 06:18:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [Review] My observations after 24 hours </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-22 21:16:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I like the game. I got it yesterday and then played until 4 in the morning.

What I liked less:

- Repetitive buildings
- no autosave: My computer crashed after maybe 2 hours and I lost everything.
- Wrong difficulty curve: 

The game was actually a bit challenging at first. I kept running out of money in the early stages because I built up too fast. When you run out of money you can't build anything, and at first you can't even take a loan so you're pretty much doomed. Also, you can't take multiple small loans like in CiM2.

But once I got past a certain point, I had almost too much money and 5 star properties everywhere. I do have experience with SC4, but I found it a bit too easy to build a successful city. This is was really my first city if you don't count me restarting a few times at the beginning.

- The wrong things are failing in my city. What I mean is that my biggest problems are things that shouldn't be big problems in real life (hearses).

For example, one of my biggest problems is that hearses are not reaching their "customers". I do have more than enough crematoriums and graveyards.. It's probably because of the huge traffic jams. 

However, workers seem to be able to go to work, or at least my businesses aren't being abandoned. In real life, even though traffic might be bad, hearses can still move around the city. But you might expect workers to look for jobs closer to their homes and so for inaccessible businesses to shut down. SC4 simulated this much better, especially with the NAM addon.

Another problem is fire trucks. My buildings burn down even with good coverage, probably because the fire trucks are stuck in traffic. They really should have a way to get to fires quickly.

Keeping crime under control seems a bit too easy. I just have a few police stations and that's it. Maybe that's because the developers are Finnish, but it would be fun to have a "high-crime" scenario or have crime as a difficulty setting. Also, maybe other stuff like jails and helicopters could be added. Same thing for healthcare.

Something seems a bit weird about the way that workers get to work. I don't see businesses being abandoned because workers can't reach them. And I don't seem to see a realistic number of parked cars on the street near businesses. I need to investigate this, but I feel like workers don't really commute. Also, there doesn't seem to be rush hours or anything like that. So, the result is that traffic seems to have a bigger effect on hearses, garbage trucks and fire trucks than on businesses and workers, which is the opposite of what I would expect.

Too many garbage trucks. I have an army of garbage trucks in my city and they seem to generate a much too high proportion of traffic.

- Unique buildings are not very good. They're kind of bland. Their effect is not clear. They don't cost that much. They don't really seem to employ people, even the big commercial ones. THey don't have the little stats that gave a little bit of personality to the SC4 unique buildings. The aquarium, for example, is boring. I can't see whales, sharks or dolphins. It just looks like a generic modern building and doesn't seem to really draw in visitors or anything.

Pollution seems very easy to contain. My industrial sector barely sends any smoke into the air. It seems to stay concentrated within a very tight radius.

High tech industrial buildings don't look high tech enough... SC4 had better building design overall.

The school system is simple. There are no private schools, small high schools, college, huge universities, branch and city libraries, city museums. It's much simpler than SC4 and probably why it's so easy.

Road maintenance doesn't seem to be as important. I haven't really checked this out, but it seems possible to just leave it at 100% even when building a ton of roads.

Buggy traffic. It's been reported here. The traffic algorithms used in Skylines and CIM2 are far from perfect. Cars seem to rarely used all of the available lanes efficiently.

Low density is not really low density: Houses don't have a large yard and house more than one household. It would be interesting to truly replicate urban sprawl.

High density is not really high density: High rises have, what, 20 households living in them? Not really realistic.

Public transportation not as good as in CiM2: I don't expect CO to pack Cities in Motion inside of CSKY, but it would be great to have a few more options. I'd like to pack my longer routes with more buses. I'd like to have trams. I'd like to have different vehicles.

Also, I'd like to have more than one underground level and to be able to see inside my metro stations like in CIM2.

No control over zone size: When I make a zone along a long road, I don't see a way of making it a certain size.

Airports: Seems to be only a single size of airport.

Chirps are annoying: Any way of making the bird fly away? It keeps repeating the same stupid things and is useless most of the time.

Disasters: No disasters?

Regions: No regions I guess.

These are my thoughts about the game so far. I've had a lot of fun, but I expect that I'll probably get bored fairly quickly. Seems to have less depth than SC4. Top-tier buildings are easy to get and don't seem to require as much effort to get. I do really like the tools for building highways. 
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> VICE esports documentary </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-19 01:30:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> 300 hp car can't go up hill </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-07 19:29:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Has anyone noticed that if you crash in the uphill portion of the matterhorn (night race), that your car can be unable to go up the hill. I have a modified Lancia Delta with 300hp, yet it can't get up the hill, even starting from the top portion of the hill if it starts from a complete stop (like after a crash). The car will actually roll backwards as it's unable to counteract the insane gravitational forces of GT Earth. In reality, a 100hp engine should easily be able to push a 1300kg car up a hill. And the car does have 300 ft-pound of torque, which would put it in the same class as some fairly powerful cars: http://www.autosnout.com/Car-Torque-List.php. This shows how bad the physics engine is. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Simcity dev adds more comment: Simcity was developed by a small team, like Skylines </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-07 16:03:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Does resolution really matter?  Eurogamer.net </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-02 05:39:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Less than 48 hours left and mini-campaign funded! </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-16 04:46:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> On Kickstarter, everyone is Peter Molyneux </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-14 20:37:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Has Oculus Finally Conquered the Virtual-Reality Vomit Problem? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-12-05 02:53:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Camera during dialogues, bug or feature? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-11-23 15:56:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> On PC, when I start a conversation, not a cutscene, the camera just freezes in whatever position I was when I initiated the conversation. This means that I can spend an entire conversation looking at a door and having sound only coming in from the left speaker (if the characters are on my left). Is this a PC bug or is it the same across all platforms? In past games, you used to have a zoomed up view of characters' faces during conversations and I think that was rather better. But I'm still not sure if it's a bug or if it's intended to be that way.

Also, I often hear other characters talking during conversations or other sounds. It seems like they don't mute background noise enough. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Oculus Rift users to see Moon live through robot </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-10-24 04:20:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> RoomAlive: Microsoft Research team shows gaming future </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-10-07 01:08:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Half Life 2: Lost Coast is worth 40$??? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-09-25 04:59:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> http://store.steampowered.com/sub/29197/

To artificially inflate the discount given during this promotion, HL2:LC is given a non-discount price of 40$ and a discounted price of 10$. Lost Coast is a small tech demo that was given for free to all HL2 owners back in 2005. In no conceivable way can it be worth 40$ today. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> More Expensive Games means less Games and Less Studios </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-07-19 16:59:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> DragonFall 6$ on the Humble Store </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-07-16 02:38:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Why arguing against women appearing in games to preserve historical accuracy is silly </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-07-06 08:49:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Can joy be more 'adult' than violence? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-07-05 00:35:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> More Information about Nintendo's New Multiplayer Shooter: Splatoon </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-07-04 23:17:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Kotaku's Divinity: Original Sin First Impressions </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-07-04 17:07:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The state of Elder Scrolls Online: 3 months after launch </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-07-04 06:54:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Preview of The Chinese Room's "Everybody's Gone to the Rapture" </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-07-03 15:13:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Spaceteam: Cooperative mobile party game based on Star Trek-like technobabble </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-07-01 01:19:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Kickstarter for awesome cooperative mobile game based on Star Trek technobabble </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-07-01 01:10:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> CK2 2.1.5 patch released </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-06-30 17:41:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Shadowrun Returns -75% on Steam, Dragonfall -60% </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-06-28 21:26:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If you have time, why not add a few comments here about the game: www.reddit.com/r/Games/comments/29bxl4/steam_summer_sale_day_10/ </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Xenonauts review (PC Gamer) </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-06-21 05:39:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> "Nintendo has to perform this year, otherwise they will have less games." -Ubisoft CEO </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-06-21 05:38:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Palmer Luckey thinks 30 frames per second is a failure </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-06-16 07:20:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Why no good wikis for Paradox Games? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-06-15 07:16:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The wikis for Vicky II and HOI 3 are kind of lacking. I think that good wikis would help make these games more accessible. I wonder what the problem is? Is that the player base is too small or that no one knows how some mechanics in the games work?

Paradox games in general do a pretty bad job at explaining how they work, so the lacklustre wikis only make the situation worse. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> KerbalSpaceProgram plays football with giant rocket-powered robot </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-06-15 04:33:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Gamasutra - Analysis: The Nintendo bubble </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-06-15 03:53:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Shadowrun and DragonFall on sale at Humble Store </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-06-15 02:41:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Ink-Spewing Squids Won't Save Nintendo </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-06-11 17:52:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The Indie Bubble Is Popping. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-05-29 08:30:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Tropico 5 reviews </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-05-23 07:27:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Dolphin says goodbye to 32 bit support </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-05-20 06:13:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [Album] Ceilings of Deus Ex, Jonathan Jacques-Belletete (art director), 2011 </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-05-10 05:56:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Will Star Citizen have procedural planets? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-05-02 02:45:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Will Star Citizen have procedural planets like in this I-Novae Studios [demo](http://youtu.be/yrcEUO7TC28?t=6m1s)? I think it would be amazing. I haven't been following the development of the gametoo much. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [Troubleshooting] Did my headphones just destroyed my computer? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-05-01 06:15:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I have Sennheiser headphones with a very long cable and they tend to get tangled up everywhere. Last week, I managed to destroy my frontal audio port while moving my chair.

What happened was that as I stood up from my chair, the cable must have been somehow tangled around my legs and it yanked the computer pretty hard. I saw that my 3.5mm connector was bent, again, but no problem I have another one. But then I noticed that the screen was frozen.

I reboot the computer, and I'm only getting a blank screen and the computer reboots after a few seconds. What should I do? The audio port at the back is just on top of the graphics card and the card appeared to be a bit loose. I put it back into place, but it's still not working. Could this have somehow damaged the graphics card or the motherboard? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> How to get Firefox 28 look in 29? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-04-29 06:55:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hi, first post here. My firefox autoupdated to 29.0. Is there any way to get the classic 28.0 look back? I'm a little pissed that I didn't get any warning about the change. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Saturday Crapshoot: The Journeyman Project </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-04-13 03:12:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Ether One review </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-04-12 09:57:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Saturday Crapshoot: SimAnt </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-04-12 09:25:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Snobbery and fear drive criticisms of free-to-play games and ethics </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-04-10 02:38:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The Vanishing of Ethan Carter interactive 3D scans are astonishingly realistic </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-04-02 19:57:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What minor things annoy you in SRR? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-03-20 01:44:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> These are the little things that nag me so far in Dragonfall:

- No control over party equipment
- Items given to party members disappear after mission
- Not much choice for equipment
- Conversation options that disappear. For example, it requires a biotech 3 to ask Zaak about his ears. If I exit the convo, get 3 in biotech and come back, the conversation option is gone. That's just lazy coding IMO. I actually loaded a save 10 min earlier once due to that problem.
- Combat doesn't end properly after a party of enemies has been dispatched
- Bad "papers floating in the wind" animation is everywhere
- Can't talk to everyone. I want to know what that guy is doing sitting on a bench all by himself.
- Some character convos didn't get updated after a certain major event
- Matrix runs need more variety
- Still not that many special options for deckers?
- Can't see character HP outside of battle
- Lack of sophistication of combat model (I guess this is a big one)
- Bug when my mage couldn't cast a spell on himself
- Slowdown in one huge fight
- Alt-tab doesn't stop sound
- Thank God for the save function! I'm so happy they put this in.

That's all I can think about right now. What are yours? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Robot imitates mantis shrimp's weapon </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-03-01 08:30:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Are radio waves also photons? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-02-09 20:08:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Since radio waves are a form of electromagnetic radiation like visible light, are they also photons? If that's true, then could you create light in a dark room by blasting it with radio waves and then changing the frequency of the signal somehow? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Games keep redownloading </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-01-26 02:06:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I don't know if this has happened to anyone else, but in the past month, month and a half, some steam games keep having to be updated. It's always the same games: Company of Heroes, Rome:Total War Alexander, Mafia II, dead space 2, Rage, Stalker games. All the updates are rather large too. They range from 0kb to 1.4Gb for company of heroes. I've downloaded that 1.4Gb update at least 3 times already and I'm starting to be annoyed. There's no way that it's a real update. I'm using Steam beta by the way. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> EUIV End of the Year discussion going on in /r/games </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-01-03 06:50:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I think it would be great to get some comments from you guys! link: /r/Games/comments/1ua5vy/end_of_2013_discussions_europa_universalis_iv/ </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> How to login to Paradox forums </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-11-09 22:14:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Paradox's forum registration is the worse I've ever seen. I'm caught in an endless loop of "Please enter the login information for your forum account to verify that it is indeed your own account. Once you finalized this process you will be using your Paradox Account to log in also here on the forums." I click on the Paradox Account login button. "This forum account has already been merged with a Paradox account. From now on you can only login with your Paradox account using the Paradox login button above.
". It will never let me actually login to the forums. And yes, I've clicked on all the activation links. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [Troubleshooting] Finding a hidden minimized program (Asus GPU Tweak) </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-10-17 17:17:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm told there are no stupid questions. I told Asus GPU Tweak to minimize on startup (Windows 7). It worked but now I can't open it or find it. If I try to open it again it tells me it's already opened. It's not in the notification center. Is there some kind of trick to finding it? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Graphics cards hitting a low? (Canada) </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-10-08 16:14:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Do you think that the prices will go up? The GTX 660 are really pretty cheap at the moment. http://ca.pcpartpicker.com/part/gigabyte-video-card-gvn660oc2gd </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Why do so many AMD motherboards have bad reviews? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-09-19 00:03:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Newegg links: [ASUS M5A97](http://www.newegg.ca/Product/Product.aspx?Item=N82E16813131872 AID=10657534 PID=3938566 SID= nm_mc=AFC-C8junctionCA) ;
[AS Rock Extreme 3](http://www.newegg.ca/Product/Product.aspx?Item=N82E16813157394) ;
[MSI 970A-G43](http://www.newegg.ca/Product/Product.aspx?Item=N82E16813130679 AID=10657534 PID=3938566 SID= nm_mc=AFC-C8junctionCA) ;
[GIGABYTE GA-970A-UD3](http://www.newegg.ca/Product/Product.aspx?Item=N82E16813128519 AID=10657534 PID=3938566 SID= nm_mc=AFC-C8junctionCA)

These boards range from cheap to not so cheap and I'm surprised at the number of 1 star(egg) reviews from failed motherboards. Is there really a benefit to buying a more expensive board in terms of reliability? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [Build Ready] Budget Micro AMD PC </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-08-14 21:49:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm looking for a cheap PC and it seems like going micro was less expensive (plus it's smaller). My only worries are that I won't be able to fit a full sized PCI-Express card. I'm planning on putting in an old RADEON HD 4870. Also, the memory is incredibly cheap and CAS 10. Will that slow down everything? And I sort of picked a motherboard at random. Oh, and this would be used for gaming.

[PCPartPicker part list](http://ca.pcpartpicker.com/p/1rX6f) / [Price breakdown by merchant](http://ca.pcpartpicker.com/p/1rX6f/by_merchant/) / [Benchmarks](http://ca.pcpartpicker.com/p/1rX6f/benchmarks/)

Type|Item|Price
:----|:----|:----
**CPU** | [AMD Phenom II X4 965 Black 3.4GHz Quad-Core Processor](http://ca.pcpartpicker.com/part/amd-cpu-hdz965fbgmbox) | $89.99 @ Newegg Canada 
**Motherboard** | [Gigabyte GA-78LMT-USB3 Micro ATX AM3+ Motherboard](http://ca.pcpartpicker.com/part/gigabyte-motherboard-ga78lmtusb3) | $63.99 @ NCIX 
**Memory** | [G.Skill Ripjaws X Series 8GB (2 x 4GB) DDR3-2133 Memory](http://ca.pcpartpicker.com/part/gskill-memory-f32133c10d8gxm) | $14.99 @ NCIX 
**Storage** | [Seagate Barracuda 3TB 3.5" 7200RPM Internal Hard Drive](http://ca.pcpartpicker.com/part/seagate-internal-hard-drive-st3000dm001) | $119.79 @ DirectCanada 
**Case** | [Rosewill R363-M-BK MicroATX Mid Tower Case w/400W Power Supply](http://ca.pcpartpicker.com/part/rosewill-case-r363mbk) | $65.98 @ Newegg Canada 
**Optical Drive** | [Samsung SH-224DB/BEBE DVD/CD Writer](http://ca.pcpartpicker.com/part/samsung-optical-drive-sh224dbbebe) | $16.79 @ DirectCanada 
 | | **Total**
 | Prices include shipping, taxes, and discounts when available. | $371.53
 | Generated by PCPartPicker 2013-08-14 15:54 EDT-0400 | </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Any way to change the difficulty? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-07-27 06:19:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Actually, I have no idea what difficulty I'm playing. Any way to find out or change it? And can I revert before my last checkpoint? I stupidly started a mission with only two runners. I hope I won't have to start over from the start. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Crowdfunding and taxes </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-06-19 17:36:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> 500$ gaming PC (Canada), no graphics card </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-06-11 02:44:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I already have a decent video card, so no need to buy one. I was trying to build something decent, but here's the best I could do:

PCPartPicker part list: http://ca.pcpartpicker.com/p/1564S

CPU: Intel Core i5-3350P 3.1GHz Quad-Core Processor  ($183.39 @ DirectCanada) 

Motherboard: ASRock H77M Micro ATX  LGA1155 Motherboard  ($74.99 @ Newegg Canada) 

Memory: G.Skill Ripjaws X Series 8GB (2 x 4GB) DDR3-1600 Memory  ($70.40 @ DirectCanada) 

Storage: Seagate Barracuda 3TB 3.5" 7200RPM Internal Hard Drive  ($129.99 @ Canada Computers) 

Case: Antec Three Hundred Illusion ATX Mid Tower Case  ($64.99 @ Newegg Canada) 

Power Supply: Antec EarthWatts Green 500W 80 PLUS Bronze Certified ATX12V / EPS12V Power Supply  ($64.99 @ NCIX) 

Optical Drive: Lite-On iHAS124-04 DVD/CD Writer  ($16.99 @ Newegg Canada) 

Total: $605.74

I'm sure it's possible to get something almost as good for under 500$. I'm guessing cheaper memory, power supply and case. Maybe there's also a better cpu. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Elder Scrolls mod for CK2 </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-04-22 04:46:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Republic too dominant after Republic DLC? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-04-13 21:09:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hi, I don't have the Republic DLC, so I'm not playing as a republic, but I noticed that in my latest game (first after the DLC), the merchants republics seem to be dominating. Pisa has established a small empire in the Tunis region (in fact it has lost Pisa and moved its capital there). Venezia commands huge stacks of troops and has started expanding all around the gulf as well as in other areas of the Mediterranean. I get the feel that these republics really are the most significant forces in the world right after the HRE and maybe France (I play as Napoli so I'm mostly focused on the area around Italy, Sicily and the North of Africa).  England seems to be weaker than Venice with all their problems with revolts. In fact, one factor helping the republics is that they seem much less prone to internal conflicts.

These are just my impressions from one game, so I don't know how others feel, but so far my problem is that this seems more like a Renaissance game with powerful merchants than a Medieval game with powerful kingdoms. We are only in the 1100s. Merchant republics are not supposed to be, IMO, a dominant force. Another more general problem might be the fact that ships are a bit OP compared to the time period. They cost a lot in maintenance, but they can never be lost and so allow these very rich republic to just pick whatever coastal province around the world and build a sort of international empire. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> How Simcity came to life and was acquired by EA </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-03-31 04:49:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Game Industry in turmoil - Moving to Mobile </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-03-25 06:41:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Door Kickers - Topdown "realistic" tactical shooter </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-03-23 21:24:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Epic Games partially acquired by Chinese behemoth </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-03-22 04:42:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Most up-to-date summary of SimCity simulation flaws </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-03-14 04:06:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Things keep getting worse for Simcity - Sims don't need jobs: 200k pop. city without any commercial or or industrial zones </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-03-13 17:32:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> SimGod creates cruel trap of madness for Sims </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-03-09 21:01:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> How Bioware games are written - Lead Dragon Age writer discusses creative process </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-01-10 17:25:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Interview with the father of Mass Effect </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-08-21 02:39:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
