<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject2952</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-07 12:02:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> In FFXIV: ARR (I know its completely different) they have a free company (clan) system which is great, you can rank up the clan to get perks such as bonus xp for doing day-to-day actions such as dungeons and raids. You can also set a clan emblem.

There is also clan housing where you build and customise your own house. Why not have something similar where you can purchase an area of the tower to customise yourself or have a clan ship that you can customise. If all six of your fireteam are clan members you can travel together in this "mother ship" in the loading screens. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-07 11:55:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Auto fireteam balancing would be great too. Games where you have 6v3 are annoying, just needs to auto balance to make it 5v4 still not quite fair but better. I Joined a game the other day where it was 6v1, why he hadn't left already I don't know.

Also, please bring back the larger (combined arms) maps like last light, I know they can turn into a bit of a sniper fest but some people like that. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-06 13:23:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Agreed that would be nice to have, Also the ability to skip cutscenes would be a godsend </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-06 11:54:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Warlock. Hunters are pretty poor besides having invisibility and warlocks have self res and nova bomb, although the glide jump takes a little getting used to compared to the Titans beautiful jump.

Make a 'Lock but regardless, Titan master race all day. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Can we please have some more Ghost shells? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-07-06 11:30:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
