<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject3180</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-02 22:17:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yessss I make a mustard cream sauce with greek yogurt all the time, it's amazing on top of chicken. [Recipe is more or less this](http://cuisinicity.com/chicken-in-creamy-dijon-sauce/). </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-02 22:11:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I've made paneer several times, and it is delicious and amazing and so easy!! I leave mine sitting under pressure for a lot longer than that particular recipe but YMMV - sometimes people have trouble with it being crumbly and lots of weight + plenty of time can fix that.
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-02 20:27:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Like everyone else, greek yogurt for basically everything.

For some reason I'm not big on spaghetti squash, but love zucchini noodles.

Also the other night I tried mashed white beans which I guess you could consider a "substitute" for mashed potatoes. I sauteed some garlic in olive oil and then added chopped spinach, and then mashed a can of beans in with all of that. It was a liiiittle dry (maybe it needs greek yogurt?!) but really tasty! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-02 19:11:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> My ~~spring~~ current fantasy is the really hot bearded muscley guy I see at the gym all the time... I normally see him on weekday mornings, but this weekend he showed up as I was finishing a long, difficult workout. So naturally I stayed to do a bunch of unplanned deadlifts just so I could creep on him. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-01 23:29:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I used [these ones](http://www.amazon.com/Sennheiser-CX-685-Adidas-Headphones/dp/B0094R4POC/ref=sr_1_3?ie=UTF8 qid=1425248863 sr=8-3 keywords=adidas+headphones) for a while, that top bit actually kind of hooks inside your ear which sounds strange but it worked well, and they're adjustable. I broke them eventually and have Yurbuds now but I find them kind of big (even though I got the women's ones) so you might too. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-18 21:33:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Seriously, I actually stared at the word "banana" for a very long time, feeling like I must be going insane.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-11 22:17:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> We just schedule our fridge cleanouts ahead of time and send office-wide email reminders that week. So just for that one week... don't do that. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> I'm sorry, what? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-08 16:07:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-05 18:13:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You can actually do that on the subway website too. You build your sub, it will tell you all the nutrition details. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-03 12:34:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> News says it's running but severely delayed and they recommend avoiding it. It doesn't sound like they're running shuttle buses, and are just recommending you wear warm clothing and expect to wait a lot. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Major delays on red, green, and blue lines </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-03 12:16:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hearing on the news that the MBTA is warning people of major delays on these lines due to the weather/cold temps, and to avoid the red line in general. Good luck everyone...

Edit: And now also moderate orange line delays and some commuter rail delays too. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-27 18:43:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> 1. Great username
2. Trick question, there are 2 cars! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-27 18:41:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Those are some serious crazy eyes. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-27 17:39:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah I was going to say, premature gif! The snow is supposed to go all day and night still. I think the blizzard warning is in effect until 1AM. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-26 18:10:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah, I never use it for trip planning - Google Maps is way better and will still show you things like overall traffic and accidents coming up. I only use it when I'm actually in a traffic jam and want to read comments from people farther up about what the hell is happening - it's great for that. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-23 15:06:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Oh my god, you are all my people. I couldn't even look at the photo because I knew it would make me gag. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-20 21:09:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah, I don't mind showering there, I do that now at my current gym, but that gym is right along my route to work so it's just a stop halfway there, whereas TPS is the opposite direction. If only there were more! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-20 20:46:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I looked at that gym at some point and considered it! But I think it's too far out of my way to be worth it :( </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-20 20:42:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Those are my BSC's! Haha. But I probably will never run into you (whoever you are) unless you are there at 6AM... :) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-20 18:22:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I had anoles when I was a kid and absolutely loved them. A tank around that size (or even a bit smaller) worked fine, but they do need stuff to climb on and hide under, plus a heat lamp. And you have to feed them crickets and mealworms, if that weirds you out. But I used to take mine out and let them chill on my shoulder sometimes. They're cute and I loved having them as pets. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-20 17:18:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I think Shake Shack reigns supreme, mostly because of the cheese fries, but everything is delicious. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-20 17:17:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Culver's! And B Bops, because I grew up in Iowa. That shit is amazing, and I think they're both better than In-N-Out (I still like In-N-Out's burgers, but their fries were meh).

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-20 17:13:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Culver's is amazing. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-20 12:10:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Low fat cottage cheese is a sin. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-20 02:35:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  Says who?

He does, in the book he wrote about himself. It's much different than the movie, IMO. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-20 02:26:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Seriously, all of these comments are about what the movie did or didn't portray... read the book. I wanted to punch Chris Kyle in the face the entire time. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-18 17:49:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That's because it's refined - refined coconut oil typically doesn't really have a taste or smell. Unrefined would. Has nothing to do with organic or not.
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-10 16:19:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm a big fan of [this brand](http://www.amazon.com/Armarkat-B6802-68-Inch-Tree-Ivory/dp/B003BYQ1L4/ref=sr_1_1?ie=UTF8 qid=1420903065 sr=8-1 keywords=aramark+cat+tree) of cat trees - they have a bunch of different options. When I was looking around, they seemed like pretty good quality and price for the size. I actually have the one linked there, I've had it for a bit over a year and my cat practically lives on it. Plus Amazon Prime means they shipped it to me in 2 days for free. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-07 23:10:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hah I love this! I just do the crazy-looking hair flip back over the bar when I'm squatting. Duck under it and violently flip the pony back over it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-07 23:07:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Ohhhh how terrible! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-07 18:54:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Wait is the bench like the kind you'll see near dumbbells? Usually those ones have two separate sections so you can adjust the angles and do incline bench or whatever. Put the small section by your butt instead of your head! Unless that's not at all what you're talking about.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-05 21:16:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Abs have nothing to do with how much you can eat - see bodybuilders, with great abs and huge appetites!

But anyway, it's fine as long as you feel fine, more or less. If your activity/energy levels aren't impacted and you're getting enough protein, don't overthink it. If you start to struggle (which I predict you will at some point), eat a bit more.

My point was, the calorie count is not coming out to a lot because you're not eating a lot. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-05 20:15:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's possible some of it is wrong (not clear if you entered your own recipes into MFP or if you looked them up), but you're also just not eating a lot. You had a cup of mashed cauliflower as your entire lunch...  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-05 16:38:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Neither one is particularly accurate. I would ignore the number itself and just pay attention to the trend. As long as it's going down, don't worry about the number itself. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-04 20:16:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I don't time it, just take it like I'd take any vitamin or supplement. It's stored in your body so timing shouldn't really matter. It does make you retain water, I gain a few lbs, but the water is retained in your muscle tissue. I don't notice a visual difference, some people say they feel more "pumped." I feel like it helps my strength increase faster/easier, but YMMV. Here's a good amount of research-based info:

http://examine.com/supplements/Creatine/ </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-04 05:12:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> /r/paleo </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-04 04:28:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I do greek yogurt and fruit or overnight oats. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-04 04:13:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Honestly, religiously eating every hour seems like way more effort to me than just eating reasonably-sized meals, but it's up to you. No harm in giving it a try.

I think there's a happy medium to be found, personally... you probably don't need to eat hourly to avoid getting hungry. I find some amount of snacking to be helpful to me. For example, I know if I let myself get too hungry in the afternoon, I might make bad dinner decisions (I always plan my dinner, but I'm more likely to go nuts and order pizza if I feel starving), so a planned snack helps. But I'm talking maybe 1 or 2 snacks a day, outside of normal meals. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-04 00:03:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Check out /r/fitmeals, that might already cover what you're looking for. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-03 23:31:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah, duh, because more food makes you poop more which makes you skinnier. Obviously. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-03 22:29:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thanks you too!

I just ordered Thai food, because I'm pretty sure I can always eat Thai food regardless of how hungry I am... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-03 21:44:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I workout just about first thing in the morning, and the only thing I can stomach at that point is a bit of coffee. I've tried pre-workouts before and I'm just not a huge fan of taste/cost. I take creatine later in the day, assuming I remember. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-03 21:22:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Ughhh I'm home sick right now too, with zero appetite. It's 3:30PM and I haven't had a bite of food all day.

The problem is that I'm supposed to be bulking... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-03 17:49:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Many boxes of rice will specifically say cooked/uncooked in the nutritional info (e.g. 1/2 cup uncooked or 2/3 cooked). When in doubt, it's uncooked. Just measure the rice before you cook it.

Nutritional info for meat is also for the raw meat before you cook it, unless otherwise specified. If you have a food scale, you should be able to weigh exactly how much raw meat before you cook it, and then you can reference calorie counts per ounce (lots of sources online, or many food scales come with a reference book). If you don't have a food scale, you at least have a label with the total weight for the package of meat - divide logically into servings. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-03 17:35:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Well I once saw a fat lady wearing skin-colored leggings under a long coat, so.... yes. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-03 17:26:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Whenever I re-start taking creatine (sometimes I just forget for long periods of time) I tend to get a bit of indigestion but otherwise no side effects. It is known to cause some water retention, which won't necessarily make you look bloated (I think water is actually retained within muscle tissue?), but will tend to make you weigh a few lbs more.

Just get normal unflavored creatine (I get ON) - no idea what difference there would be in a "women's" version.

If she is worried about taking it, she can also try other things instead to help get her through cardio sessions. My understanding of creatine as a complete non-scientist is that the benefits tend to relate more to muscle recovery/growth/strength than cardio endurance (though it certainly wouldn't hurt). Something like increasing her carb intake before cardio might help as well. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-03 17:00:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Almost no one loses fat the way they'd like to. It comes off of different places at different speeds. I have a flat stomach but love handles that seem like they won't budge. If you still have fat to lose, it'll likely come off - you just have to be patient. Otherwise, talk to your doc. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
