<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject8180</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-05-03 03:33:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> LEAGUES. I think I mentioned in an earlier comment on a different post, there needs to be a leagues feature. Too many games rely on just multiplayer and half the time just that isn't going to get people interested. I want to play a game where an advancement in your skills means an advancement in your league. Just like you did offline leagues, online leagues could be a place (or even a battleground) for users of a similar level to get credits. Message me if you're interested in logic and how to put it together, this is just an idea! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-21 15:27:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Awesome game...

BUT WHEN THE HELL IS ZOMBOX COMING OUT!!!

THE MOBILE GAME INDUSTRY NEEDS YOU, TYSON IBELE!!!! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-14 23:37:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Might make a subreddit dedicated to this game, having played it for a week almost every day and having plenty of experience, as I know there's a learning curve! 


Multiplayer is a MUST for a  future update. I can really see this becoming a big thing because you could do like Leagues and things and you have to beat real players to be entered into the next league which ultimately will have harder opponents in it... Great job, OP! Absolutely love this game, bit of a grind, but once you get to the Sector League and you get tons of dosh for like two games it's a little easier...  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-05 02:48:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> NP.  :) hope you find something fun! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-04-05 02:18:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> As far as I know, there aren't any multiplayer tbrpgs but if you search for Text Adventure on the play store it should come up with some good results.  :) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-03-08 15:17:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> go for something a little different;what do yo have experience making? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-21 03:13:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thanks for your reply... But there doesn't seem to a be a video or series of videos that simply encapsulates the need to knows about the sport. Can you recommend anything inparticular?
I have madden and it's great fun but it's kinda hard to enjoy it to the fullest when I don't understand everything... And why not packers? XD Ps I live in the UK so I don't know many teams  Youtube probably has helpful videos to introduce you to the sport. If you play videogames, madden nfl 15 is the latest in a long standing franchise. Nfl network will have more coverage than any seasoned fan can handle. Pick a team to follow, preferably near where you live (and not the packers).

Its an extremely well covered sport with a long history so there are tons of books, documentaries, ect.

Season starts in the fall so you have a long time to prep. Good luck and go bears!

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Beginner advice? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-20 03:51:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm really into football but being a good old englishman I'm not too sure of how everything works behind the scenes and things... I know how to play but anything I should really know about the game or teams or whatever would be greatly appreciated :)
Also positions and their roles would be useful :) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> WP: The world has stopped moving, causing a massive chain reaction that almost completely flattens the earth leaving nothing but rubble... And three astronauts have witness the whole thing, and decide to come back to earth to experience the chaos first hand </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-02-20 02:29:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-25 19:26:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Looks great! May I suggest a different art style though...? I feel like a minimalistic redo on the graphics would make the game look and feel a lot smoother..  Just a suggestion,  but nice work! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-12 19:37:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hey! What games do you play? And you Guhixica?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Savant - Sons of Babel [Electronic] Something Different. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-12 14:10:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Favourite types of crisps? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-11 19:41:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-01-05 04:28:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hey man/woman,

Love your opinion, think it would be really interesting to see whether age and race and gender really matter... Like when our labels are removed, who we really are. Anyway enough with the deep stuff, would love to chat. Will pm you. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
