<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject7165</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-03 18:43:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Okay thanks.  I like your idealism.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-03 18:43:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Agreed.  A lot of my Democratic associates routinely blame gerrymandering for the party's failure to win. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-03 18:42:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yes we can agree on that.  Freedom of the press and all that.  The Pentagon Papers.

How do you feel about Wikileaks?  They use the same argument, however.  (I myself am not a big fan of Wikileaks.) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-03 18:40:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What do you think about gerrymandered "minority" districts? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-03 18:39:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Okay thanks for the response.  I get what you mean.  Are you a neoliberal? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-03 18:37:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Now that is awesome.  Excellent post.  What do you think that means?

I actually would believe that FBI leakers on the russian matter do have permission. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-03 18:35:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I got invited to reddit by some real life friends for a tiny little subreddit they started.  The sub went defunct pretty quick.  I wanted to use my account to discuss politics, but I deleted all posts on that sub (and a few other entertainment/sports related subs) to streamline the account.  I'm not a right wing troll.  I might be a left wing jokester, however. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-03 18:32:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yes me too.  A lot of people seem pretty freaked out about this, however.  I guess that due to data collection and computer technology, gerrymandering will get more and more precise as decades roll on. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Hi everyone! I'm new here. Quick question about gerrymandering. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-03 18:26:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> A lot of my fellow lefties complain about gerrymandering.  Gerrymandering has been around for centuries but has gotten a lot more "efficient" because of computer technology.

If the Democrats/liberals can re-capture some state legislatures and governor seats by 2020 they can gerrymander their own Democrat-friendly district maps for the entire decade of the 2020's -- and presumably the computer software we can use in 2021 will be even more powerful than the software the GOP used in 2011.  

Is this the wrong way to think about the issue? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-03 18:22:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Okay, noted.  Thanks for the tip. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-03 18:20:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Haha.  Awesome. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-03 18:19:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Ok thanks!  I'll check it out.  Good day to you, sir. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-03 18:18:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Comey just today, in his testimony to the Senate Judiciary Committee, lauded and encouraged the formation of "Good Troll Armies" to combat right wing trolls and spammers!

That's awesome.  Let's get to work! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-03 18:15:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The key word here is "claims."  

You've been buying into hizzoner's self-aggrandizing nonsense.  He's a sad old man who has been out of the game for years.  Same thing with that pathetic Newt character. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-03 18:11:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Not contributing to the neoliberal circle jerk?  Oh dear heavens. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-03 18:10:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  Giuliani could easily have used coercive tactics to get information that are simply not available to journalists.

Such as . . .    </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-03 18:10:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's all in good clean fun.  I am new to Reddit however. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-03 18:09:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The OP didn't say anything about the journalists being liable. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-03 18:08:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Palm Beach is one of the most affluent villages in the United States.

# MPBGA! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-03 18:02:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Comey just lauded and encouraged the formation of "Good Troll Armies" to combat right wing trolls and spammers!

# HELL YEAH! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-03 17:53:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So the leadership is thinking about bringing the bill up on Thursday?

That's gonna be wild!  Especially when they lose. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-03 17:50:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I wonder if some here think this way:

FBI leaks to Guiliani about Clinton = Treason.

FBI leaks to the Press about Trump = Nobel Peace Prize.

EDIT:  The downvotes on this comment answer the question **resoundingly**. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-03 16:55:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Just how accurate are those strictly local polls anyhow? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-03 16:51:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Former AGA Yates's testimony next week is going to blow the VP out of the water.  Did you know that?  Stay tuned . . .  (It's true, no hyperbole.) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-03 16:30:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Trump might like "playing the heel" but perhaps he should choose his attacks more wisely?  Bringing up this Russia stuff all the time can't possibly be good for him in the long run.

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-03 16:23:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Excellent idea!  

Be honest:  How many of you here have contemplated that at some point?   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-03 16:21:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I find this statement harsh and unpleasant to be sure.  I'm not condoning it.

However, I want to give some perspective here.  I've heard managers and senior partners say this exact same thing regarding young "educated professionals" in *private sector* fields which traditionally pay much more than teaching.  Do you follow me? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-26 21:50:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Ok thanks for the advice! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-26 21:26:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That might prompt a pretty strong pushback from various factions, including conservative Republicans and the press. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-26 21:19:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The source was a woman commenting on CNN; the article had the exact same substance and sourcing as the OP here. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-03-26 21:16:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'd be stunned if the WH said anything about it at all. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
