<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject9825</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Stupendous Man vs Superman </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-11-02 07:04:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Stupendous Man is trying to destroy an elementary school, and Superman must stop him. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Could Macbeth win the Game of Thrones? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-10-29 01:20:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What if Macbeth and Lady Macbeth were high nobles of Westeros living in Kings Landing at the start of the TV series. Would they be able to get Macbeth to sit on the Iron Throne? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Do members of Congress have Secret Service members protecting them? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-10-27 21:18:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I know most members of the Executive Branch have people protecting them, but that's only ~20 people. There are over 500 members of Congress, which seems like a lot to protect. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Could the Box Ghost control a Borg Cube? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-10-25 05:31:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The Box Ghost vs a Borg Cube. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-10-25 05:20:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Can Steve and Blue solve the Bay Harbor Butcher investigation? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-10-21 03:58:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Steve and Blue's house is suddenly transported to Miami. Can they discover who the Bay Harbor Butcher is?

BONUS ROUND: Steve and Blue get Joe's help. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> How I feel after writing college essays for the past week. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-10-21 02:40:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What if the United Kingdom had refused to hand over Hong Kong to China in 1997? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-10-20 23:32:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What if after China refused to meet the UK's demands regarding Hong Kong's autonomy and rights of the citizens after the planned handover, they refuse to hand it over as per the 99 year lease? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> I may be late to this but here's my transformation! </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-10-20 03:31:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Why did no European country attempt to colonize Liberia during the Scramble for Africa? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-10-20 03:13:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Were they afraid of angering America, because my understanding is that America lost interest in Liberia by the late 19th century, and many of the European Great Powers regarded America to be a much weaker country then themselves. So what was stopping them? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [General] Do all time machines work the same way? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-10-17 22:18:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Does a Flux Capacitor power the TARDIS? Could Bulma fix the Time Machine from HG Welles' story? Or do all time machines work by different principles? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> In the 1999 film, The Mummy, many of the characters speak in "Ancient Egyptian". How close is it to what Ancient Egyptian actually would have sounded like, and how are we able to find out what it did sound like? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-10-11 16:41:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> When and why did monarchs stop having court jesters? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-10-08 03:34:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If you look back to any representation of medieval times, there is always a jester running around the King's court. Today there are none. Why is this? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Why are Europeans joining ISIS? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-10-08 00:40:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It seems like every day I'm reading about British or French people joining ISIS. What on earth do they have to gain from that? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> ELI5: HDI, Gini, GDP (PPP), and GDP (Per Capita) </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-10-05 07:06:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Whenever you go to a country's Wikipedia page, you always see these stats. But what exactly do they mean? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [General] What is the difference, if any, between a wizard and a warlock? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-10-05 03:06:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [Avatar] So...What exactly was Ozai's plan for the comet? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-10-04 07:25:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> He says he wants to burn down the Earth Kingdom. Did he really expect to be able to burn down the whole thing with only 16 airships? The Earth Kingdom is [*HUGE*](http://fc06.deviantart.net/fs32/f/2008/229/7/4/The_World_of_Avatar_Map_by_felinoel.png). A couple of guys on airships isn't going to cut it, even with the comet. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Avatar Aang vs Danny Phantom </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-10-02 22:08:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Both are at their most powerful. Aang has access to the Avatar State.

BONUS: Aang learns how to [spirit-bend](http://img4.wikia.nocookie.net/__cb20131006111644/avatar/images/f/f7/Korra_trying_to_calm_a_dark_spirit.png). How does this change the fight? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Uncle Iroh [A:TLA] vs. Uncle [Jackie Chan Adventures] </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-10-02 06:21:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Who is the wiser and more badass Uncle?

Round 1: Fist fight. No magic or firebending.

Round 2: Iroh must run the antique shop and Uncle must run the Jasmine Dragon. Who can make more money?

Round 3: Bloodlusted fight. Uncle has full access to all magic items that he uses throughout the series and Iroh has his firebending. 

Round 3.5: Battle takes place during Sozin's Comet.

Round 4: Iroh must train Jackie and Uncle must train Zuko. Who trains the better hero?

BONUS ROUND: Both play each other in a game of Pai Sho and Mahjong. Who wins each? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Samurai Jack vs. Cthulhu </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-10-02 03:40:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Cthulhu awakens, but this time a foolish samurai warrior wielding a magic sword steps forth to oppose him. Can he defeat Cthulhu?

The fight takes place in feudal Japan. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Samurai Jack vs Captain America </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-10-02 01:49:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Samurai Jack vs Captain America.

Round 1: In character.

Round 2: Bloodlusted. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> That guy's so good at basketball. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-09-29 22:43:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's probably because he's black. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Derek Zoolander joins NASCAR. Who's the greatest racer he can beat? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-09-28 05:35:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The man who can't turn left joins a sport that consists of only left turns. Who could be worse than him? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Is it illegal to throw the trash back into someone's car if they littered? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-09-20 23:34:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What was the reaction to the Acts of Union in British America and the rest of Europe? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-09-20 17:18:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Was Scotland a major power in Europe before the Acts of Union in 1707? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-09-20 15:51:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What exactly was the Red Lotus' original plan, and how did Unalaq's plan play into it? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-09-19 04:09:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> I ate a bowl of nails for breakfast. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-09-18 01:33:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Without any milk. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> ELI5: Why are young Westerners going to the Middle East to join ISIS? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-09-17 22:20:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> You should learn. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-09-17 22:00:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Aang [A:TLA] vs. Aku [Samurai Jack] </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-09-17 21:29:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> A question about the Avatar's past lives. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-09-17 05:32:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So...what exactly are they doing in there the whole time? Are they like, asleep when they're not being accessed? Can they talk to each other in there? Do they have parties in the current Avatar's subconscious? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The Incredibles vs The Avengers [MCU] </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-09-17 00:56:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> BONUS: Frozone is included for the Incredibles. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The Fire Nation invades Westeros </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-09-16 21:31:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Let's say a little bit West of the Iron Islands is the Fire Nation. The Fire Lord wants to spread his nation's good fortunes with lesser peoples, and stages an invasion. Can they conquer Westeros?

The Fire Nation is from the beginning of A:TLA and Westeros is from the beginning of Game of Thrones. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Who is the strongest character Aang [A:TLA] could defeat? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-09-16 04:20:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Aang is in his prime and has access to the Avatar State. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Sokka vs Asami </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-09-16 00:15:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Sokka has his space sword and boomerang and Asami has her shock glove.

The arena is a field with a creek next to it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What do you think happened to Hawky? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-09-15 23:14:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [Image] Map of Ancient Civilizations of the Eastern Hemisphere. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-09-13 22:01:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [WALL-E] What are the mechanics of the Axiom? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-09-12 00:59:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> There's no Earth anymore, so where are they getting a constant supply of food from? And for that matter, it looks like it's out past the edges of the Solar System. Why not just have it floating a bit closer to Earth? It would have made the return trip a lot easier. Not to mention the fact that it was in space for over 700 years. Things are bound to break, or become outdated, or get hit by a rogue meteor. How are they able to sustain themselves at all with no outside resources? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [Avatar/Percy Jackson] Could Percy Jackson bloodbend? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-09-09 22:35:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [Calvin and Hobbes] Is there any limit to the Transmogrifier's power. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-09-09 05:00:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Like, if Calvin were to fight Superman or something, couldn't he just transmogrify him into a worm, or would Superman not be affected? Is anyone safe from the Transmogrifier's power? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Galactus vs Calvin </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-09-09 02:43:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Galactus has come to devour Earth and his first stop is Calvin's house. Can he be stopped?


Round 1: Normal Calvin

Round 2: Spaceman Spiff

Round 3: Stupendous Man

Round 4: **OLD** God Calvin

BONUS: Add Hobbes to any round. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What was the attitude towards the Ancient Greek city-states (such as Athens and Sparta) during the time of the Byzantine Empire. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-09-09 00:04:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Sometimes the Byzantine Empire is called the Greek Empire. What did its citizen's think of the city-states that had once ruled the area. Were they considered barbaric and violent, or were they respected for being able to defeat Persia, the Romans' traditional enemy? I've never heard anything about this topic and I'm really interested in hearing about it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [DC] Why has the Joker never gotten the death penalty? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-09-07 21:46:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm sure he's killed enough people to get the death penalty 100s of times over, but all that seems to happen to him is he gets sent to Arkham and escapes again and again. We know the courts are willing to sentence criminals to death as the [Penny Plunderer](http://4.bp.blogspot.com/-9c_MpUAI5m0/TwH-62zhZmI/AAAAAAAAGug/Hn-gVCRTArM/s1600/pennies%2Bdeath.jpg) has been sentenced to death before. So why not the Joker, who is clearly far more dangerous and has killed far more people? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> ELI5: How can some countries have territory in Antarctica when the Antarctic Treaty says no state can have territory? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-09-07 05:04:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [This map](http://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/c/c4/Antarctica_territorial_claims.png) shows territorial claims in Antarctica. How is that allowed when the Antarctic Treaty states that no state can claim territory on the continent? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> How did the Vandals, a Germanic tribe from Poland, come to establish a kingdom all the way in North Africa? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-09-03 23:47:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Did the Romans (or any other ancient civilization) know about Macaronesia? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-09-03 21:37:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [It just seems like it was way too close to Europe and Africa for people to be completely unaware of it.](http://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/b/b4/Macaronesia_location.svg) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Does anybody else think that these games are the greatest things The Walking Dead franchise has produced? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-09-03 04:52:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Don't get me wrong, I love the comics and the TV show, but I don't think they hold a candle to these games. I can handle anything that they throw at me in the comics and the show, but I *feel* the decisions and story in the game. Like, when [](/s "Glenn") died in the comics, I was shocked and saddened for the loss of the character, but by the next issue it was fine. But when [](/s "Lee died") last season, that stuck with me for days. Does anybody else think that? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What were the politics of the Crusader States? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-09-01 23:39:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Did they have foreign relations with other European nations? Were they completely independent, or were they more like client kingdoms of the Church? Are there any major treaties involving them? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [Stories] People who have been banned from Disney, why are you banned from Disney? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-08-31 03:06:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Many countries had huge amounts of suffering and death after communist revolutions. How did communism still gain support from revolutionaries? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-08-31 01:55:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> After Russia turned communist, Stalin's purges killed millions of people. China didn't seem to care, and had their own revolution, and millions of people died due to famine. Then Cambodia became communist and the Khmer Rouge killed millions of people as well. Then even after that North Vietnam still continued to fight for communism. Hungary also tried to start a revolution to get *rid* of communism, and most of the Eastern Bloc countries were unhappy with communism. How did communism continue to gain support from the masses when almost every example of a country turning communist made the people unhappy and caused a lot of death? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Have you ever successfully convinced someone that a conspiracy theory is bullshit? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-08-27 01:15:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Mint-Berry Crunch vs. Superman </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-08-25 06:52:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Aku [Samurai Jack] vs Vaatu [TLOK] </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-08-24 06:23:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Round 1: Both are at full strength. The battle takes place in the Spirit World with both portals open.

Round 2: Same as Round 1 but during Harmonic Convergence.

SUPER BONUS ROUND!: Jack and Korra switch worlds. Can Jack defeat Vaatu and can Korra defeat Aku? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Can we get another one of those things going where if we reblog it on Tumblr they release the finale early? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-08-22 06:19:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Because I will make an account on Tumblr if Nick does that. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> After Christianity became the state religion of the Roman Empire, how did they rectify the fact that Roman officials killed Jesus? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-08-22 04:30:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> I swear to God... </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-08-21 00:34:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If The Jasmine Dragon is being looted right now, I'm going to break something. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [Spongebob] How has the Chum Bucket stayed open this long without any customers? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-08-14 22:21:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [Star Wars/Avatar] Could a firebender redirect force lightning? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-08-12 18:08:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [The Legend of Korra] How was it decided who would get their bending back? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-08-07 04:27:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> After Korra's defeat of Amon and the Equalists, much of the bending population of Republic City had been equalized. And after Korra learned how to energybend, I assume they all wanted it back. But who was allowed to get it back? I'm sure the police and White Lotus guards all got it back, but what about the heads of organized crime, street criminals, and normal people? Could they petition to have it restored, and have a formal trial? Could Korra be forced to restore people's bending by the city, or would she use her position as the Avatar to pick and choose who she liked? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> ELI5: How do extremely small countries function? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-08-02 06:21:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm talking about *really* small countries such as Monaco, Vatican City, and San Marino. How are they able to provide for their citizens? They all have next to no resources. Monaco, for example, has no agriculture industry and very little fresh water. How can they make sure their country has enough to keep a high standard of living? And San Marino is landlocked, so they have no way to fish. I understand tourism is a major part of these countries' economies, but how were they able to stay independent for so long and trade with other countries if they have no natural resources? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Why didn't the Ottoman Empire conquer all of the Arabian Peninsula? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-07-30 04:57:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Every map I've seen of the Ottoman Empire has it hugging the coasts of the Arabian Peninsula. The former Caliphates were all able to take the entire peninsula. Was there a reason the Ottomans didn't do the same?

[Example Map](http://media.web.britannica.com/eb-media/83/89983-004-C90ACD71.gif) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What if the Roman Empire had been divided into Northern and Southern halves instead of Eastern and Western? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-07-28 04:34:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What is Theodosius had divided the Roman Empire into North and South, with the North having Europe and the Mediterranean and the South having Africa and Asia.

[Here is a map of the Empire at the death of Theodosius.](http://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/4/49/Theodosius_I's_empire.png) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Yen Sid vs Dumbledore </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-07-18 06:25:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Mermaid Man and Barnacle Boy vs Aquaman </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-07-18 05:32:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The battle takes place in the Pacific Ocean.

Round 1: Mermaid Man and Barnacle Boy in their prime.

Round 2: Mermaid Man and Barnacle Boy in the show. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> General Zod vs. Vegeta </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-07-15 01:12:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Vegeta can go into SSJ2 at any time. Both are bloodlusted. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Amazon.com vs the Amazons </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-07-12 07:40:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Silver Surfer [Marvel] vs Jay Moriarity in a surfing competition. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-07-12 07:30:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The competition takes place in Hawaii. Whoever can ride the wave for the longest without wiping out is the winner. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [Twilight] Why do vampires sparkle in sunlight? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-07-12 03:13:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It is my understanding that vampires disintegrate upon contact with sunlight. Why do vampires from Twilight sparkle? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What happened to the Byzantine New England? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-07-10 19:07:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I've heard stories of the Byzantine Emperor giving some land in the eastern Black Sea to English refugees who were fleeing William the Conqueror in the 11th century. What became of it? Did it even exist? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> CMV: The United Nations should have their own army. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-07-10 17:44:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I think the United Nations should have their own army made up of volunteers from the member states, and under their sole jurisdiction. Currently, for peacekeeping missions, the UN must ask their members nicely for them to send volunteers, and this can lead to conflict of interest between nations. Take the Rwandan Genocide. The United States chose not to send troops after their failure in Somalia, and other nations also chose not to get involved. With a private army, the United Nations may get involved without needing to ask for troops.

_____

 *Hello, users of CMV! This is a footnote from your moderators. We'd just like to remind you of a couple of things. Firstly, please remember to* ***[read through our rules](http://www.reddit.com/r/changemyview/wiki/rules)***. *If you see a comment that has broken one, it is more effective to report it than downvote it. Speaking of which,* ***[downvotes don't change views](http://www.reddit.com/r/changemyview/wiki/guidelines#wiki_upvoting.2Fdownvoting)****! If you are thinking about submitting a CMV yourself, please have a look through our* ***[popular topics wiki](http://www.reddit.com/r/changemyview/wiki/populartopics)*** *first. Any questions or concerns? Feel free to* ***[message us](http://www.reddit.com/message/compose?to=/r/changemyview)***. *Happy CMVing!* </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Were any claims of a "Third Rome" recognized by other countries. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-07-10 17:28:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If we assume the Roman Empire was the "First Rome" and the Byzantine Empire was the "Second Rome", several nations made claims of being the "Third Rome". The Ottoman Empire claimed to be it when they conquered Constantinople. The Russian Empire claimed to be it because Ivan III married Sophia Palaiologina, the niece of the last Byzantine Emperor. 

Basically, after the fall of Constantinople, did any nations say, "Okay, those guys are Rome now". </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [Harry Potter/General] What is magic made of? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-07-10 17:12:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> In Harry Potter, as well as many other fantasy series, magic is shown as a sort of spark/beam of light that shoots out of the wand. But what is that light? Is it plasma? Is is something else entirely? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [GIF] MRW I got gold for the first time and went to /r/lounge. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-07-09 21:19:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Van Halen vs. Valhallen [Dexter's Lab] </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-07-06 18:49:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The band Van Halen and Justice Friend Valhallen fight to the death to see who are the true gods of rock. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [Picture] Me when I forget to shave. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-07-06 18:28:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> When I'm about to open my report card. [GIF] </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-06-20 16:01:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> I love summer. [Meme] </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-06-19 23:29:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [Pokmon] Do vegetarians eat Grass-Type Pokmon? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-06-08 18:10:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The Alien Fleet [Independence Day] vs. The Empire [Star Wars] </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-06-08 17:50:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The Independence Day aliens need to consume the resources of every planet in the galaxy. The Empire needs to stop them. It takes place 2 years before Episode IV. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [GIF] When you win the school election. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-06-05 02:13:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> ELI5: The difference between an "autonomous area" and "country". </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-06-05 01:58:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Many nations around the world have territory that is considered to be an "autonomous area". These areas are usually self-governing, and commonly have their own governors or leaders and do not partake in the government of the nation. But what exactly makes these areas different from a country if they can control themselves? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [GIF] When you read your notes from the beginning of the semester. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-06-04 01:12:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [GIF] When you get your Yearbook but they didn't put your sport in it. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-06-04 00:44:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [GIF] When the teacher give us the whole period to study for the final. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-06-03 22:45:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Samus Aran vs Iron Man </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-05-31 00:35:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Both have their strongest suits. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Steve vs. Joe [Blue's Clues] </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-05-31 00:25:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Both are bloodlusted. The fight takes place in the house, and all of the other characters are present. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> With the creation of large Colonial Empires by the European powers throughout the 16th-20th century, why did most monarchs choose to keep the title "King" instead of Emperor? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-05-23 02:10:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The Survey Corps (Attack on Titan) vs the Metalbending Police Force (A:TLA) </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-05-22 13:10:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The setting is Republic City. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Reddit, what's something you never thought you would see, but did because of Reddit? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-05-22 04:58:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Every Pokmon vs Godzilla </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-05-22 03:17:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> All 719 Pokmon need to take down Godzilla. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The Stay Puft Marshmallow Man vs. Godzilla </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-05-22 02:55:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Cyborg (DC) vs the Terminator </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-05-21 00:02:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Round 1: T-800 (The Terminator)
Round 2: T-1000 (Terminator 2)
Round 3: T-850 (Rise of the Machines)
Round 4: T-X (Rise of the Machines) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Firelord (Marvel) vs the Fire Lord (A:TLA) </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-05-20 23:42:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Bonus: Sozin's Comet has arrived. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Dexter (Dexter's Lab) vs Jimmy Neutron (Jimmy Neutron) </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-05-20 22:18:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> They both have access to every invention they've made that has been seen in their shows. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The Incredibles (Pixar) vs the Avengers (Marvel) </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-05-20 13:19:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The Incredibles and the Avengers are dropped in the middle of Times Square in New York. They are all bloodlusted.

BONUS: Frozone helps the Incredibles </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Spider-Man (Marvel) vs. 1 of every spider on Earth </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-05-20 04:20:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> There are an estimated 35,000 different species of spiders on Earth. Spider-Man is dropped into an arena filled with them and must kill every one before he can leave. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Elsa (Frozen) vs. Iceman (Marvel) vs. Frozone (The Incredibles) </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-05-20 03:39:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> A three way battle of the Disney-owned ice masters. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Keeping a lookout for Season 5. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-05-17 23:43:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> How do enclaves and exclaves come about? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-05-15 02:48:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> If UV light can cause skin cancer, does that mean you have a higher risk of cancer if you stand in a violet room than you do if you stand in a red room, since violet is closer to UV light on the electromagnetic spectrum? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-05-09 20:20:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Joseph Stalin vs. Superman </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-05-07 04:15:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Who is the ultimate Man of Steel? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The Iron Giant vs. Optimus Prime vs. Voltron vs. a Megazord vs. Gipsy Danger </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-05-06 03:31:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The Infraggable Krunk [Dexter's Lab] vs The Incredible Hulk [Marvel] </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-05-05 05:00:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The Justice Friends [Dexter's Lab] vs the Justice League [DC] </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-05-05 04:41:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Practicing for the Kentucky Derby </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-05-04 04:17:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> When we establish colonies on other planets, what will become the replacements for sayings such as "The Greatest ______ on Earth"? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-05-02 04:53:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Will we need to say, "This is the best food in the world and the colonies?" </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What was the shark's favorite movie? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-05-01 04:32:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The Shaw-Shark Redemption </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Redditors who were jurors in famous trials, what was the experience like? Did the media frenzy surrounding it have any affect on the way you view the case? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-04-29 02:06:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Spyro the Dragon vs. Crash Bandicoot </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-04-21 00:17:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> They both have access to all abilities and power-ups.   </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Aang (A:TLA) vs. Krillin (DBZ) </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-04-20 21:49:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Assume that they fight each other at the height of their power. The battle takes place in an open field filled with boulders and a river flowing through it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Taking care of my best friend's daughter </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-04-09 01:05:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Doin' some negotiatin' </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-04-02 06:01:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Burning down the barn </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-04-02 02:11:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Why does squinting make it easier to see in bright light? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-04-02 01:36:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What causes the "snap" sound when I snap my fingers? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-04-01 02:44:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [Show Spoilers] Most surprising death. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-03-31 23:58:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What was the most surprising death on the show? Was there a character that you think was killed too early, too late, or somebody still alive that you thought would've been dead by now? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Killing Prisoners </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-03-31 21:17:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What's the best animated movie ever made? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-03-31 21:12:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Animated can be traditional, computer, anime, or stop-motion. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Hiding in tanks </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-03-31 08:25:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Shooting little girls </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-03-31 04:30:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Arresting criminals </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-03-31 04:07:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Talking to my dead wife </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-03-31 03:55:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Killing my best friend </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-03-31 03:53:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [WP] You have the ability to stop time. One day you find somebody immune to your power. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-03-31 00:07:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> If today we discovered conclusive proof that life existed on other planets, how would society react? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-03-30 23:22:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> How would society be affected if the world were to end in 1000 years? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-03-21 01:10:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Let's say that today we discovered that the world would be destroyed on March 20, 3014. How do you think people would react and how would it affect our future society? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> How will plate tectonics affect governments and countries in millions of years? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-03-19 01:06:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> For the sake of argument, let's assume the worlds current countries remain the same. But in millions of years, some areas will be flooded and continents will ram into each other, and borders will in no way stay the same. What would be some impacts. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Looking at the flowers with Carol </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-03-18 04:17:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What is the best song featured in The Walking Dead? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-03-18 04:16:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I think it's "Lead Me Home" by Jamie N Commons. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [Show Spoilers] A question about The Grove episode. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-03-18 00:32:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [Comic Spoilers] A question about the group. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-03-17 23:13:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I've heard many people on here say that they may stop reading the comics if the "original group dies". But my question is, what makes it the "original group"? I assume they mean the Atlanta group, but with only Rick, Carl, Andrea and Sophia left of them, there are many other characters who weren't there from the beginning who are still awesome. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Watching my dad die </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-03-17 23:01:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Request for a Reddit Alien as Lizzie from The Walking Dead for /r/justlizziethings </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-03-17 22:52:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Feeding a walker </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-03-17 20:23:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Mauling rats </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-03-17 03:50:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Suffocating babies </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-03-17 03:37:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Shooting people in the head </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-03-17 03:34:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Thinking Walkers are Alive </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-03-17 03:26:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Teachers of Reddit, what's your worst helicopter-parent story? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-03-14 01:32:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> If a zombie apocalypse were to occur, what would be the best car to have? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-03-11 00:26:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm talking about gas milage, durability, space for supplies, noise level, and even color. Anything that you think would improve the chance of survival. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Who's the biggest douchebag you've ever met? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-03-10 03:11:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What's your zombie apocalypse plan? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-03-10 02:53:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What's your greatest cheating story? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-03-07 04:16:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I mean on tests, not on SOs. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Reddit, what's the scariest story you can tell in 2 sentences? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-03-05 03:43:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> With the Oscars happening tonight, what other awards do you think the Academy should add? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-03-02 07:32:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What is the most thought provoking question you can ask in one sentence? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-02-25 04:04:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What scientific advancement or invention do you want to see in your lifetime? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-02-24 04:14:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It could be nuclear fusion, the hoverboard, interplanetary travel, or anything else. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> With awards season upon us, what new award categories do you think should be added to the Oscars? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-02-22 19:41:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Redditors from US territories (Puerto Rico, Guam, etc.), what are your opinions of the rest of the USA? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-02-18 20:44:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Do you think of yourselves as US citizens first, or as citizens of your territory? Do you like living in a territory? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> If a helicopter were to float 1 foot off the ground in the same place, would it eventually end up in a different location due to the Earth's rotation? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-02-09 19:02:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> If a colony is established on the Moon or Mars, who would have jurisdiction? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-02-04 03:14:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I understand that if a country establishes one, they would likely have jurisdiction, but if a private company does, will it essentially be its own country? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What do you think the Noodle Incident is? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-02-04 01:28:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> In Calvin and Hobbes, the Noodle Incident is often referred to, but never explained. What do you think it is? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
