<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject8557</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-24 04:29:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Wow...did someone think this was a good idea or what?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-23 15:53:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Let's change our name to the Democratic People's Republic of America. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-22 21:05:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'd still like to see a drift racer go in wrc. Not saying it's not possible and there's no similarities between the two, I just think it takes more skill to race a rally than it does to drift.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-22 20:25:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I thought that was just the co driver. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-22 20:24:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yes, however, he was racing rallycross before drifting. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-22 19:13:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Personally, he might have done it somewhat unintentionally(most slides arent so long), but rally racing on dirt is filled with this sort of turning. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-22 19:11:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Watch more rally racing, that'll fix you unbelievers.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-22 19:08:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Super knobby tires. https://www.google.com/search?q=rally+tires client=ms-android-sprint-mvno-us prmd=sinv source=lnms tbm=isch sa=X ved=0ahUKEwiS79K4-rzQAhVKh1QKHbnoBRYQ_AUICSgC biw=320 bih=452#tbm=isch q=rally+tires chips=q:rally+tires,g_1:gravel </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-22 19:04:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That's called rally racing. I'd love to see some drift racer even just try that. Why? Because the drivers don't know the roads. They have a navigator giving out directions while they drive like madmen on all  road surfaces, ice, snow, gravel, dust, tarmac, and while they race against the clock without knowing how they compare to the other drivers' times on race segments. Best auto racing on the planet. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-21 16:10:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> He's making fun of our spelling fetish!? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-21 16:09:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> They secretly like it when a man just fixes it... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-21 16:06:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So now's the best time to cook it, right? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-21 15:30:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Every single day. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-21 06:02:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You'll benefit from high spoke count and durable rims(also keep an eye on the tire pressure, too low will cause pinching flats). Mavic and dt swiss come to mind, but there are many suitable rims on the market. Keep in mind that many road frames are designed for "normal" road riding(think endurance, rather than technical skill ), so a race frame might not be so well suited to stairs, etc as a touring or cyclocross frame. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-21 02:21:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I did, and all the dictionary said was that the "preferred" word was hanged. So, ultimately, I guess you were a half correct self-righteous, pedantic son of a bitch. Congratulations?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-20 07:12:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Sadly, this seems like an American automaker. Even worse they're making it difficult to pay. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-19 16:17:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Well, considering that its going to be impossible to get the roots for those trees into the tiny holes they're in, it must have been the contractors for the pavers who done it. Not to mention those trees  look like they've been there for 5 years. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-18 15:10:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> In other words, don't chase the white whale? I like to get news from both right and left wing sources, or varying radical leanings, and I'm surprised at how much it changes my opinions.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-18 15:00:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah, the rape of Cassandra and the death of Priam aren't in there either.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-18 13:03:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Fuck you. I don't answer to you. Go to hell . </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Harris County Judge says that Arrests of Poor People Good for Job Security. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-18 04:02:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-17 17:33:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It gets better. Just try to remember why you were doing it and it'll start coming back eventually.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-17 15:31:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm asking you but someone didn't have the civility not to get upset when they got called out, so I dont believe you. They call people who act like that bullies. I might look it up someday.
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-17 15:28:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah, you could probably find a botanist who'd say that parts of the pumpkin are still holding on too. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-17 04:54:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Is this really a thing? Do you have a source?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-16 15:21:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hi Ira! I really, really enjoy your show and all of the quirky yet undeniably intriguing things you discuss. How exactly do you hear about the oddly fascinating stories you cover? Also how many people contribute to your fabulous tongue in cheek delivery, they're really funny for nerds like myself?  Keep up the good work! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-16 01:18:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I have to agree with u/stoppage_time on this one. The moon not only pulls on the land, but increases the sea level also which puts pressure on land masses. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-16 00:18:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That was #awesome!!! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-15 02:37:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Ego non baptizo te in nomine patris, sed in nomine diaboli.

Melville later wrote in a letter that this was the theme of the book. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-14 21:16:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Well, we'll see I guess.  Whatever you do, don't fertilize it again until it has some new growth, and do your best not to overwater it. Always helps a lot to have it mulched.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-14 16:45:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> "Please stop with the nonsense."

I fucking love it, well played mom! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-14 16:13:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I've never seen anyone make them so finely ground. I'd put it in the garden, it wont hurt anything.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-14 15:57:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It should be fine. Just return to normal watering and it'll come back in the spring. 


Edit: in the future, do not fertilize weak, stressed or damaged plants, it puts more stress on the plant and often leads to death. And it won't  make a big difference if you leave the dead leaves or if you pull them.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-14 15:54:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What are all the symptoms?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-14 01:36:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> War and Peace. Great book, very insightful, introspective, I could associate with characters in ways no other book has let me. 10/10. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-13 21:30:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> There's a person who puts paper in our door 6 days a week, he's a threat to the safety of our home and the owners don't understand the threat!  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Where do I find tide charts and a lunar calendar for April 1906 without going to the library? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-13 19:44:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> I'm looking for a tide chart and lunar calendar for April 1906 in San Francisco. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-13 19:34:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-10 22:34:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Sounds so...mischievous, i wanna be a naught child! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-10 21:50:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Helicopters are people too! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-10 21:28:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah, nobody really cares about protests anyway.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Anyone know why the CHP chopper is circling the marina? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-10 21:12:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm at work and its been flying over for almost an hour... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-09 03:54:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yes, more than 100,000 muslism. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-09 03:53:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Spelling? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-08 17:56:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Looks like a schleffera to me. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Gore: 'Take it from me, every vote counts' </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-08 15:15:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-07 04:22:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Tit for tat justice...great </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-06 23:04:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What classics disappointed you? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-06 23:00:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Worst non-answer here. Just saying.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-06 22:57:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Moby Dick's better. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-06 07:28:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It happens, its just one of the symptoms. Training oneself to get over becoming frustrated or upset easily is difficult. Maybe there's some sports he likes that might be done to help release those frustrations. 


But, personally, it happens. It gets better. Maybe you can coax him into getting on reddits ptsd subs and he can spend some time around people who understand. I hope that helps. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-05 05:07:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I remember my childhood,  but I got PTSD way after that. I totally forget my keys, and most stuff about the first 6 to 7 years afterwards. My other memories are hit or miss though, I must say. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-05 03:51:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Well I'd still argue punishment does deter crime; you dont punch everyone that you'd like to now, do you. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-04 22:18:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Not in the least? I think that's a stretch. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-04 05:37:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I know this is kind of a personal question, but it doesnt seem very republican to support Bernie...Sooo, are you more right leaning or what gives? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-03 15:58:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Let's make Americans great again. 



It's just meaningless rhetoric. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-03 06:22:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> *neuter


Not to be pedantic, but it took me a minute to figure out what you meant.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-02 17:43:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Good to know, thanks fir the info </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-01 20:44:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That might not be too bad of a movie. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-01 16:31:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Grab America by the pussy, to make her great again

A Novella 
By Donald J. Trump </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-01 15:52:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> We're talking more than one's daily intake here, thus the 'high salt content is unhealthy' statement. Let me know if you're still confused about any of this. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-01 15:48:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Ok, well it looks like a viral or a fungal problem. There are some antifungal spray treatments available, but I must say that it really does not look too bad. Personally, I would remove the leaves that look particularly bad and not worry about it until it gets worse. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-01 06:16:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Corporate rules... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-01 05:35:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The yellow spots?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-01 02:30:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It is recommended to compost it. Some will put it in a compost bin with some organic fertilizer for like a month or two.if you're concerned about microbes, then you can boil water and put it in the soil then allow the soil to dry out before planting. Thats what I do, I hate throwing it away. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-01 01:43:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If you squeeze them and they feel ripe, then pull it. They can ripen off of the tree too. Hope that helps. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-01 01:40:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Usually i lift the pot and see how heavy it is or stick my fingers in to see how dry it is when i am trying to determine if it needs water. I hope that helps. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-31 19:32:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Totally awkward though, right, i mean, naturally, when you inevitably start thinking about brexit. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-31 18:47:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Welp, that just aint right much none now. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-31 18:44:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So I guess we lost the war on drugs? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-31 18:36:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I cant ever find the Austin Powers ringtone i want, so yeah... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-31 18:26:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thanks, i knew that sentence had something in it that could be improved! We are all so much better off for your contribution! Thanks!!! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-31 18:23:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Another redditor expressing overwatering concerns here. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-31 18:22:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> If you're into thissort of thing and dont mind being thought of as a conspiracy theorist, then The Tower of Basel by Adam Lebor might be something you're interested in reading.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-31 18:17:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'll bet he'll go slower next time around </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-31 17:28:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Ha, i like that im gonna start saying it  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-31 14:46:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Pc clown, brilliant! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-30 08:01:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You know your dyslexic when you read bacon hammered for emotionally compromised. That just happened, but to be fair, the pbr might have helped... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-30 07:36:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Save the seeds and send them to me! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-30 07:15:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Sounds like a recipe for another invasive species. One mutation, like nature is wont to do, and Pandora again. Haven't we learned from our past mistakes that this sort of thing is a bad idea?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-30 05:33:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> But, in my case, just fucking them up.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-29 17:41:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I am no longer the most diplomatic person. I would totally call him out on that, and I would do it in front of people. Sounds like hes a pathological liar to me.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-29 16:38:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I almost always cook in cast iron pans. I use soap half the time and just put some shortening or veggie oil in afterward. My eggs never stick and i dont have to worry about getting cancer like with so called non stick pans. If your pan needs seasoning or oil just heat it up and put some oil in.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-29 06:48:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I would still not be able to sleep if it weren't for alcohol. But thats me. Exercise helps too. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-29 06:19:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I really hate to say this, but i drank alcohol and smoked weed. It gets better after a couple years. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> $20 Munchery "friend referral" </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-26 00:02:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-25 18:54:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Well, put him in the jar until he becomes a butterfly I guess.

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-25 02:31:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The birds and the bees...
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-25 00:01:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Whats with the pruners in the last pic, that part made me take way too long to understand... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-24 16:52:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I believe the word you're looking for is transpiration, evapotranspiration would indicate the entire environment, possibly in this case local environment, whereas transpiration refers solely to the process of plants evaporating water through leaves, which seems to be what you meant, as evaporation indicates cooling. Thanks again for your input, but you really haven't added to this discussion and I question your knowledge and intentions and thus I am now blocking you. Have a nice life!  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-24 16:33:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I actually thought it was colder than the environment surrounding it. Thanks for your input. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-24 09:15:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Why do I sense a tone of condescention in your message? Was that actually a dumb question given the fact that others, more respectful I might add, in this thread have responded that some plants thermoregulate? Is there some problem with probing the unknown and posting it in this thread? Please let me know, thanks. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-23 15:58:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Good to know thanks.
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-23 15:57:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thanks
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-22 16:31:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thank you
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-22 16:30:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Ok, that makes sense thank you. I thought the warmer temperature of the house below the panels would prevent the panels from reaching dew point. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Where can I find the specific temperatures of plants? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-22 16:28:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Humans are 98.6 fahrenheit, but how do I find out how warm a pansy is naturally? Are there books or is there some website? Thanks guys.. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Why do some things, like pansies, some aluminum panels, cars, etc, allow water to condense on their surfaces overnight and other surfaces do not? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-22 06:18:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Facebook has repeatedly trended fake news since firing its human editors </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-13 07:34:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Facebook has repeatedly trended fake news since firing its human editors </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-13 07:04:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Why does this remind me of Hannibal lector and horizontal Japanese vaginas... </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-10 16:20:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Reddit, what objects(preferably able to be produced in metal) would you like that would have the ability to easily bend back into their original shapes after being damaged or bent? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-06 05:30:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Reddit, what are products that you wish would last longer but don't because they're manufactured to get you to buy more in a shorter period of time? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-06 05:18:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> A little disappointed by the downvotes on this recent reply, maybe you could tell me where I went wrong? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-01 05:54:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Well, despite studying latin for two years, I don't have an altogether confident response for you. I can say that what you said is What was able the man, or so.

I think you want an indirect statement

What is it that man can do

Quae possit hominem facere.

But don't give that too much credence until I get some feedback or someone else responds.
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> How long will the first LGBTQ flag be in space before it becomes disintegrated by solar radiation? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-30 06:15:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [Serious] Do you guys really think your votes matter? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-27 19:18:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Bike manufacturer sees huge reduction in delivery damage by printing TV on the box - Cycling Weekly </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-25 16:16:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> FS: Schwalbe One 700x28c tires, clinchers, only 40 miles. SF, Ca. $50 </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-10 20:52:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Like new, too big for new bike. Prefer local cash trades. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Bianchi Boron XL 51cm </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-09-03 16:40:26 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm selling my Bianchi Boron

Handmade in Italy with Boron Steel

Campagnolo Record 9 speed carbon ergopower levers(like new less than 400 miles not a mark, 2004 model, installed 2 months ago, still have the box)

White industries hubs laced to pacenti sl23 rims, super smooth(will come with spare front wheel)

Phil wood titanium Bottom Bracket

Campagnolo Daytona derailleur

Campy Athena Brakes, Koolstop pads

Brooks B17 black saddle, 700 or so miles, getting well broken in

Specialized short and shallow handlebars

Ritchey Carbon Matrix Stem

Brooks leather bar tape, teal

Specialized carbon seatpost

Michelin Pro 4 tires, plenty of life, rear has less than 200 miles

This is a super fast and rare early 2000 model Bianchi. Very light and fast, climbs excellently, handles very well, keeps up and passes carbon no problem. Gets looks all the time. Shifts so smooth that oftentimes you don't even realize it shifted. 3x9 setup12-25 or thereabouts, I think. I am the third owner. The second owner was a woman who owned it briefly, the first owner was a man who had it stored in his garage after riding it apparently only briefly. There is no rust and the bike, despite the patina is in excellent structural and mechanical condition.

The pictures are before the campy makeover, has one more bottle holder. will come with that front wheel as well as the pacenti/white industries.



It's a bit small for me and I need the dough. She'd fit up to about 5'7 I reckon. Cash only, local. Email me any questions.


http://sfbay.craigslist.org/sfc/bik/5764003189.html
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> I can't really see any difference between this presidential election and the Southpark episode where a turd sandwich ran against a giant douche. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-07-01 17:51:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> honestly took me awhile to realize that wasnt a huge rolly polly on the rubbery rolly </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-30 21:47:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Removing rust and preserving the frame of a fancy ass 2001 bianchi boron </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-19 01:32:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So I bought one of my dream bikes, a Bianchi boron XL(2001). I have sublime dreams of putting lovely Campagnolo parts all over it albeit tempered by the sobering reality of expensive Italian components and my finite purchasing ability. Although luckily I have 60 percent of the group parts and the ultegra components on it are in really good shape.


So, I pulled out the seat post and it has a little rust in there. It's presumably been in storage just inland from the coast in northern California for a few years(moist air) and I got it from a guy who bought it at an estate sale. So, obviously, I've gotta stop the rust and prevent any more from happening, but it has a sticker note saying that chemicals should be avoided when washing because it has structural foam. So I guess I'll just wash it with mild dish soap, that's whatever, but what does that mean for the rust. I read somewhere that they used structural foam similar to stuff they used in high end automobiles but I'm not sure if that really helps.


So what would you guys do about this? How would you clean out the rust and prevent any more from occurring? I'd really appreciate any advice you can give. Thanks in advance!



Tl;dr: bought a bike with a structural-foam reinforced steel frame that has the beginning signs of rust and I want advice on rust removal and prevention </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Amazon user reviews keyboard. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-06-10 01:09:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
