<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject8635</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> There is something wrong with my daughter </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-11 01:58:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> About two weeks ago my daughter started to act strangely.  When I say strangely, its important to note that my daughter is a strange person:  She is a 23-year-old woman with an obsession in Disney movies and dolls, and with the colour black.  I know she has some interests in weird things, but this is now becoming too much.

Leah isnt my daughter, shes my stepdaughter, but I consider her my daughter because Im the one that raised her.  Her father threw her away.  His words? Id rather not see her ever again than pay the alimony.

It crushed her.  She hated him after that.  It was the first time I saw such a dark emotion rise up in her, it was the first time I saw her cry in anger, and the first time she said that she hated someone out loud.  
My daughter still lives with me and my wife (her mother).  We have a little flat outside our house where she and her pup, Kira, live.  So she is on her own, she even pays us rent.  My wife and I still rely on her a lot, because Im 58 and my wife is turning 62 this year.  

We call on her for coffee when we wake up midday after our afternoon siesta, we ask her to bathe the dogs, and she does it with a smile.

But lately her smile isnt as sincere as it used to be.  Or maybe it hasnt been sincere in a while, I dont know.  She keeps giving me these looks.  Like shes planning something evil.

I know she loves horror films and books.  I know she paints her nails black and pretend shes such a hard-ass, but shes just a scared little girl.  Shes still playing with dolls, for crying out loud!

The coffee shes been bringing us is tasting a bit stronger.  At least to me; my wife didnt notice anything when I asked.  My daughters been going along with the jokes I make, as though they arent that much of an issue.  She usually got angry at them, but now she just she smiles at my jokes.
Im not a funny man.  My wife keeps reminding me of this. 

My daughter well, she hasnt been herself in ages.  Shes been busy.  I always see her on the laptop, and I just assumed that she was bus with assignments.  But then I looked closer.  I saw.  I screamed.
Her laptop was open on a sort of poison.  She heard me and arrived in her doorway.  Her eyes flicked to the screen and then to me.  A haunting smile crossed her face.

What is it, daddy? She asked in a voice that I shudder to remember.

What is this? I asked, pointing at her laptops screen.

Oh, daddy, its for my History class.  What types of poison was used on the ships during the slave trade.  She smiled innocently, and sat down a coffee mug next to her laptop.  Honestly, if I was planning on killing anyone, I would be less obvious about.
I laughed nervously and retreated.  This was my baby girl, and I knew for a fact that she didnt have history this semester.  

Or did she?

I can never remember.  Sometimes she speaks to me, but I dont hear it.  I usually just nod along.  Leah is very smart  scarily smart  and she knows it.  So, I dont listen to her gloating, because it messes with my head.  It gets annoying after a while, so I just block it out.

Dont get me wrong: Leah is a wonderful, sweet girl.  Shes smart as hell, but she isnt humble about it.  Shes much smarter than I ever was at school, thats for sure.  But I looked after her, I looked at her history on the internet, and this is the first time shes looked up poison.  Maybe I was wrong.  Maybe I wasnt.

She hasnt been home lately either.  I know she works  shes an au pair to a pair of rich folks with one kid who cant be bothered to look after him  and she stays late.  I dont mean until 7pm, I mean until 1am.  I dont know what she does there.  The kid is 10 and his parents are ALWAYS home, they just dont have time for him.

So where does she go?  

I shrugged it all off.  I thought I was imagining things.  Maybe she really did have an essay due on poison, maybe her employers had parties or functions to go to

Then why was she standing in the hallway when I went to take a piss?  Why was she smiling that sick, twisted smile again?  

Why was she coming towards me?

Hi, daddy. She said, and her voice was haunting.

Leah? I asked.  It was the middle of the night and I was spooked as fuck.  Why arent you in the flat?
She didnt answer.  She just kept looking at me.  Her smile stretched nearly around her face.  It wasnt her usual sweet smile, but a smile that reminded me of a clown.  An evil clown.

STOP! I screamed, Stop it, Leah!

Or what, daddy? She giggled, her smile not becoming any smaller.  I looked at the bedroom.  Maybe my wife was awake.  I screamed for Leah again to stop, but she laughed loudly.

Fucking stupid daddy.  What will you do if I dont shut up?  Or stop?  What I just go on?  Would you like that?  Would you want that? Her voice good lord, her voice was made out of nightmares and darkness.  It cracked, she cackled.  And should I fucking listen, daddy?  Like you did?

LEAH!  I screamed at the top of my lungs.

Pete? My wifes muffled voice came.  I heard the bedsprings beneath her as she got up and walked to me. Why are you yelling, honey?

Its Leah! I screamed, Shes

Mary, my wife, switched the light on.  There was no Leah. She wasn't in the hallway and my wife now thought I was imagining things.

The next day I cornered her.

"What the hell was that last night, missy?" I demanded. She raised an eyebrow and smiled a skew smile.

"Did you find the wine or the weed?" She asked. She always said this when she was in trouble. We had raised her not to touch a drop of alcohol or anything addictive. It was forbidden.

Plus: the joke was getting old.

I moved closer to her and she held her ground. Usually she would back away, but now she just folded her arms.

"Seriously, dad, was my gaming too loud?" She asked next. "Because I was just having fun fucking with people online."

I dropped it. It must have been my imagination.

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-08 10:25:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Find the chem lab, get your hands on some acidic stuff and you have some type of weapon. Go for the eyes. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
