<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject4584</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-10 15:50:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I LMAO at him calling Meryl Streep an overrated actress. Bet she did too.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-10 15:48:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Actually, it's a happy day. The right wing supporters listen to him. He can get through to them. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-10 15:46:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That's why I keep saying the press should ignore the tweets and concentrate on the important stuff.
1 - it will drive him crazy not to get the attention and 
2 - he won't be able to slide things under the radar while we're fighting over his tweets

The Repugs have always been the party of distraction. They keep their supporters distracted with issues like abortion and gun rights while they are robbing them blind. Someone needs to clue them in on this, but the dems don't seem to know how. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-10 15:44:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Wow. I love that quote.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-10 15:44:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Exactly! He craves the respect of the rich and famous, and they hate him. NYC society nor Palm Beach society have ever accepted him.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-10 15:40:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You may be joking, but that's actually the truth. I can't remember where I read this, but his father preferred his older brother, but Freddy refused to go into the family business. Donald was always trying to suck up to daddy, who was very cruel to him, and never loved him as much as he did Fred. When Fred died, Donald assumed that his father would love him more, but he kept on comparing him to Freddy, and calling Donald a loser. Donald went into Manhattan to prove to his father that he was better.

Also, this. 
http://www.rawstory.com/2016/11/former-classmate-shares-chilling-account-of-trump-abusing-donald-jr-who-loathed-his-famous-dad/
He abuses his own children, which isn't hard to believe. There was a recent report of him calling one of his sons a "retard" behind the scenes at The Apprentice.

He is a classic abused child who now abuses his own family and others. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-10 15:34:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What do you mean by "automation?" Is that outsourcing or automated rewriting or what? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-07 03:22:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So sweet! Thanks! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-07 03:21:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Wow! That sounds awesome! Sounds like $35 could get me lots of food. I don't eat a lot, so if I brought tupperware and took two helpings home, I'd have plenty for the day. 

Just got a job offer, but it doesn't start for two weeks, so this will be a lifesaver. I live close to the house, too, about 6 blocks away. 

About the free food, someone just told me to ask if you can help serve for free food. I wouldn't mind serving a couple of days to repay their kindness. I love Indian food, too, so win-win!

Thanks, everyone. People were right. This sub is a lifesaver. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-07 02:08:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thanks, but I can't risk having my computer infected. I make my living working online. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-07 02:00:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> And these youngsters think nobody over 50 has anything to contribute. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-07 01:57:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I read other people's online articles on topics I am very interested in. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-06 23:34:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Funny how when you show a Trumpite FACTS to prove they are wrong, they revert to this kind of bullshit. #sad </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-06 23:32:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> He probably doesn't even know what the OSI model is. He'd probably say "Yeah, I know that model. Beautiful model. If I wasn't married, I'd definitely be going out with her." </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-06 23:31:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> And that one froze my computer from all the spam uBlock Origin blocked on it. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-06 23:29:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So we have to do all the work for the entitled people on mobile devices? Fuck that. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-02 17:36:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  I think that reclassifying emails and then claiming you violated rules on accessing such info is ridiculous.

Well, yes, there is that, and it is last year. We need to work on winning at least the Senate back in 2018. Forget Hillary. Forget Trump. Work on regaining some power. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-02 15:47:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  I also think that because Democrats and the left take a softer approach that they think we're "pussies."

My daddy always said "It's the quiet ones you have to look out for." And I read your whole comment. :) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-02 15:46:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> They have truly lost their way. I don't think they can be salvaged. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-02 15:45:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yes, that's true, but there are always going to be those people. They've calmed down now, though. ETA: I cannot imagine what it would have been like if Trump lost. Remember, he promised riots in the streets. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-02 15:43:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> True, but I don't think the majority of Americans are that naive, and he will be investigated to death every time he claims something. We do have the freedom to criticize our President here, which they do not have in Russia. YW for the LinkedIn stuff.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-02 15:41:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> No doubt the Clinton Foundation was a scam, and even I admit that. It was set up to provide high-paying jobs to all the Clintons' friends and family. After Chelsea could not keep a job, they gave her a job there making over $600K a year. I'm glad it's going down, honestly. I hate to see people hurt by such organizations, but watch carefully -- I just saw an article about how Trump raised $450 million for access to him at Mar a Lago's New Year's Eve party. His son was trying to sell access to Ivanka recently, disguising it as charitable, and Trump has already moaned about its unfairness. They have their own foundation which was shut down by the State of NY for not being licensed to collect money, and which he took money out of for personal gain and to pay off politicians.

This will just continue, so are you going to scream "unfair!" when we try to hold him accountable for all of that and call us all "libtards?"  I would say yes, most Trumpites will, because it's only unfair if it goes against what "Daddy Trumpbucks" does. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-02 15:34:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Well, o.k., I give you the military clearance thing, but classifying a communication after the fact is pretty commonplace. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-02 15:32:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> True.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-02 15:31:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Really? Like more pathetic than when Bill Clinton whipped both his Republican opponent's asses in 92 and 96 by more than 200 electoral votes? Or maybe more pathetic than when Barack Obama did the same to McCain in 2008, or even when he beat Romney by 126 electoral votes in 2012? 

Remember, Trump only won by 67 electoral votes. You can think that is amazing, but it isn't. It's actually one of the closest elections in history. Bush only won by 5 electoral votes in 2000 when he was "crowned" President by the SCOTUS. He only won by 35 electoral votes in 2004. The only other modern Presidents who have won by lower margins than Trump were Kennedy in 1962, Nixon in 1968, and Carter in 1976.

Source:
https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/List_of_United_States_presidential_elections_by_Electoral_College_margin </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-02 15:16:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Good point. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-02 15:15:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I honestly think he is a malignant narcissist. I base this on his always vowing revenge on people. Malignant narcissists enjoy hurting other people and are very big on revenge. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-02 15:13:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm sure not as secure as he thinks it is, but then, Putin has probably already hacked it and is blackmailing him as we speak. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-02 15:12:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Google is your friend. I don't have time to do your fucking research for you. It was in an article about how no former presidents other than Jimmy Carter are going to Trumps's inauguration.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-02 15:11:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Did Jim Baker ever get out of jail? That man and his crazy wife scammed so many people. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-02 15:09:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> BECAUSE TRUMP IS DANGEROUS!!! I hate to say it, but you'll learn this eventually, then you'll feel like a fool for posting this. He will destroy this country, turn us into a fascist, if not communist, state if we let him. WHY CAN'T YOU SEE THIS???  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-02 15:07:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> We are fighting for the country, not for the election, and if you think Trump and his ilk would not doing the same thing if Hillary had won, you are naive. This man is probably certifiably insane and surrounded by dangerous people. That's why we are still fighting and will keep fighting until he is gone. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-02 15:04:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You underestimate Hillary. She will work her women's and girls foundation to death, do wonderful things, and emerge a hero. She will never be a nobody. She will not "go quietly into the night." It's not her style. And Bill -- you have to watch out for Bill. I can't imagine the revenge scenariios running through his mind right now. Honestly, I'd be terrified to be Trump. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-02 15:00:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'd be more worried about Bill than Hillary, actually. He's' the dangerous, devious one. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-02 14:59:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I see it. I didn't know it had a name. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-02 14:58:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's a deal, but only after we get a copy of Trump's tax returns, which would outline his many illegal activities and conflicts of interest, and set up a special prosecutor to investigate that shit. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-02 14:56:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yes, he would, because as we have heard in the days since the election, THEY DON'T CARE! We told them about his bankruptcies, how he didn't pay his workers, how he stole money from the casinos then declared bankruptcy, how he tried to have an old woman evicted so he could build a parking lot for his casinos, and THEY DON'T CARE! All they hear is "Make America Great Again!"  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-02 14:54:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yep. So brain dead. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-02 14:53:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> For real. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-02 14:52:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Just like Trump, they will never admit they fucked up. If he got us into a nuclear war, and LA was destroyed, he'd say it wasn't his fault and no great loss because LA is a cesspool anyway. Now if NYC was destroyed, that would be a different story, because that's HIS city, but it still wouldn't be his fault. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-02 14:51:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Masters of deception, and all the ignorant followers will fall for it. Sad. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-02 14:49:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Have you seen what congress has in store for the first 100 days? Repeal of Obamacare, Repeal of Roe v. Wade, Repeal of all environmental regulations for manufacturing, Repeal of the minimum wage...FUCK NO!!! I WILL DIE FIGHTING AGAINST THIS SHIT!!!! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-02 14:48:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  http://gri pdownload.com/356103

scam page.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-01 19:49:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Which is exactly why the press needs to MAKE IT important again. Don't let themselves get dragged down into the muck with the faux news sites. Most people read mainly MSM, so if we don't play their game, they will lose by default. If we don't report it, most of the world will think it's fringe news. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-01 19:47:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Of course they will, because they simply cannot see the truth. Must be sad to walk around the world completely oblivious to what is really happening.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-01 19:46:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> ROTFLMAO!  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-01 19:46:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> No. Usually, they concede and go on with their lives. Like Hillary did. Trump is the one who keeps referring to the election and what Hillary did wrong and how the dems lost and blah, blah, blah. I've been on this earth for 60 years and I've never seen the President Elect be this insanely ungracious and unprofessional. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-01 19:44:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Or anyone waving a Russian flag.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-01 19:43:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> For now. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-01 19:38:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> WTF does Hillary have to do with ANYTHING?? She's not saying a word or doing a thing to get in his way. Why can't he let it go? Just leave her the fuck alone!  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-01 19:36:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thus, the "enemies" tweet. HE's the one who can't stand that the American voters didn't put him in there, and that we can take him out. We've faced down Russia before when it was a lot bigger and a lot more powerful. They've lost a lot of their power; we have not, and we have the world behind us. He'll find out soon enough. Congress is already standing him down on this. Stay tuned for a world-class tantrum when he doesn't get his way. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-01 19:33:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yep. Do what you have to do to live to fight another day. Choose your battles wisely. Trump does not understand how powerful the people in Congress who hate him actually are, and how little power he will have against them.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-01 19:29:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> And he thinks he's the only one who can take revenge on their enemies -- he needs to pay close attention to Hillary's crew. The Clintons' enemies die in strange ways. Not saying the Clintons are responsible, but someone loves them enough to take care of things for them. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-01 19:25:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Like people who tote around the Russian flag. AAAAAGH!!! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-01 19:24:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Oh, Lord help the Arts! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-01 19:23:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I wasn't outraged. I was amused. He was banning them in a temper tantrum because he said they were "very, very unfair" to him, which is 2 year old behavior, quite honestly. He's a whiney little crybaby who will do anything to get attention, even insult more than half the country he is supposed to be leading by calling them his enemies. SERIOUSLY???? ENEMIES???? He sounds more like Duterte every day. Soon he'll be bragging that he killed someone.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-01 19:20:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> They need to give it up. It's getting old, but they are just following in Trump's footsteps. He was bitching about it all last week, and now this New Year's tweet -- JESUS H. CHRIST! Get a life! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-01 19:18:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That's my hope. It used to be awesome when it first started, but it's just a spam fest now, as is LinkedIn, which is usually the one spamming you! I had to quit LinkedIn because of their incessant spammy emails no matter how many times I unsubscribed from them. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-01 19:17:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I heard Bill might go to the Inaugural Ball - sans Hillary. I think it would be great watching Trump's face when everyone crowds around Bill, who they love, and leaves him to his own devices. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-01 19:16:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Not really, but usually, you can decipher what they are trying to say. All cleared up now. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-01 19:15:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Which is just what she is doing.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-01 19:14:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> O.k. Sorry. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-01 19:13:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> They have been brainwashed into hating liberals for years. What do you think Faux New, Rush, Breitbart and other have been doing all this time? They don't even know why the fuck they hate us. They just know that their "heroes" tell them to.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-01 19:12:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah, true, but we can't keep dwelling on idiotic 3 a.m. tweets. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-01 19:11:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What? She was Secretary of State! She had every security clearance in the freaking world! When are you talking about her not having security clearance? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-01 19:10:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> He's denying the hacking because he can't face the fact that without Russia interfering, he would have lost. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-01 19:09:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I wouldn't worry about it. Those are people who stick their fingers in their ears and sing "lalalalalalalala" whenever you tell them the truth. They'll find out when not one single manufacturing job comes back, mimum wage is repealed and they don't reopen the freaking coal mines -- oh, and when they lose their SS disability and medicaid. It's hard to be patient, but it will come. It will happen.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-01 19:07:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Did he? Well, then, why did his press secretary say this, and why does he call everyone who didn't vote for him his "enemies?" He's on Twitter every night stirring shit. Can you deny that? The man is pathological! PLEASE WAKE THE FUCK UP!!! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-01 19:05:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah, it does -- but it has no flow. :) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-01 17:40:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Every time he gets caught doing something illegal or unconstitutional, he'll do this. Over and over and over. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-01 17:39:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Trump is scared Hillary is plotting his demise as we type, which she well may be, and there are a shitload of people who would help her for free. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-01 17:38:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> In TrumpWorld. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-01 17:38:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Never heard of that, but yeah, exactly. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-01 17:37:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  Why did Hillary wrote all these top secret emails when did she did not have the security clearance to read them? 

What does that even mean? It makes absolutely no sense! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-01 17:36:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Most people would be ashamed to be followed around by Don King.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-01 17:35:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  Hillary being punished by not being president elect.

But mostly by having to watch him destroy the country. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-01 17:33:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I have never seen a party that WON the election still be so obsessed with the loser and the election in general. It's so beyond insane. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-01 17:32:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Ignorance is bliss, isn't it?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-01 17:31:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> That will never happen, mostly because Twitter is in trouble and needs the traffic he gives them. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-01 17:31:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I've long said that if the press just ignores every insane thing Trump does, it will hurt him much more than giving him attention. He can't live without attention, which is why he posts those insane tweets. The press should just stop covering anything other than policy issues.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-01 17:18:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Let's face it. Trump and his entire family care nothing about the law. They have always felt they were above it. It's a typical sociopathic trait. They know there are laws and rules, they seriously just don't know why they apply to them. 

Trust me, he'll do something to get impeached for two reasons: the disregard for the law and the fact the most of congress hates his guts. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-01 16:29:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> In other words, he went to one security briefing and is willing to disclose the classified information to the whole world. Now THAT would be an impeachable offense. Let's get on with it, Donald! Start spilling state secrets so we can get rid of you now! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-01 16:27:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I predict that Webster's dictionary will add a definition to "unfair" in the next year that reads "Anything or anyone not in complete agreement with Donald Trump, or any legitimate report of his wrongdoing by the press."

Every fucking time he uses that word, I picture a 2-year-old throwing a tantrum screaming "That's not fair!" </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-01 16:20:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I missed this, because I've been trying to avoid all things Trump the past few days. 

So, in effect, he just called over half of the U.S. citizens his enemies and sore losers? Just when you think he can't get any worse, he outdoes himself.

Wait....didn't he say he would be President to all of us? Guess he changed his tiny little mind. Now he wants to be President to Russia, I suppose. Wait until he realizes THEY are his enemies.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-01 16:15:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Might as well start a Fuck 2017! now, because -- Trump. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-01 16:13:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I knew she would, but I'm still celebrating! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [ebook] M.C. Beaton "Pushing Up Daisies" epub or mobi </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-01 00:20:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I have the audio book, but want the epub or mobi. Thanks! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-30 20:56:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I wish I could go back to FPL. I'm on this horrendous city utility that has the highest rates in FL now and I hate it.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-30 20:52:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  Liam is so good for her. I hope she goes back to her country roots and gives up all this craziness.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-30 18:36:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> A police homicide detective told me that the increasing numbers of murders indicate that Kim Jong Un is a serial killer who is escalating, which makes him the most dangerous kind of psychopath. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Kim Jong Un Killed Hundreds Of Government Leaders </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-30 18:34:46 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-30 16:41:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It makes me so sad that there are people willing to work for this amount.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-30 16:39:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Of course they will. And then when Russia attacks us because Trump is an idiot who actually trusts Putin, they will blame that on Obama throwing their spies out of the country. I do think we should have pulled everybody out of our embassy before we did that, though, because I'm afraid Russia will now arrest them at the airport and not let them leave. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-30 16:37:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I think Mitch McConnell hates everybody. And he's ugly. At least Paul Ryan is reasonably attractive, not that that means HE doesn't hate everybody too. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-27 19:41:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> My dad always said that it didn't matter who was President because Congress ran the country and the special interests ran Congress. Maybe that's true anywhere, but this place is going to hell in a handbasket very quickly, and I don't want to live to see what happens. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-27 19:33:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> LOLOLOL! They are the most confused people I've ever seen. And since their party is in control of congress, who do they think is passing all these unconstitutional laws?  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-27 19:32:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> They won't realize it until their health care and welfare disappear, since they are the biggest recipients of these benefits. Once they start having money come out of their pockets, and see no jobs forthcoming for over-50 ex-factory workers, they will finally understand.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-27 19:29:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> This is so sad, because it only proves that if any of them had actually listened to Bernie, he might be President now. There was another reporter who said he went to W. Virginia and asked all the Obamacare recipients what they would do if Congress repealed the ACA, and they said they didn't believe they would. Obviously, none of them have noticed that they have tried to repeal it how many times since it was enacted, and only Obama's continually vetoing it kept it in place. They honestly think that the Republicans won't do anything to their supporters, just to "liberals," so in their minds, if you're a "liberal," you won't have any benefits, but if you're a conservative, you can keep yours. Ignorance is our biggest problem in this country. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-27 19:15:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's all just alt-insanity to me. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-27 15:08:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Ever since this first started during the Arab Spring, I could not understand how anyone could do this to their own people and why the world didn't do something to stop it. Oh yeah -- that's right -- not enough oil. I hate this country so much sometimes. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What if you are happy with lower wages? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-19 20:41:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I see a lot here and elsewhere about "moving up" and getting better-paying work, but a lot of that comes with a lot more stress. Private clients come with personality conflicts and billing problems, etc. 

There are a lot of us who just want a few hundred extra bucks a month, and we're perfectly fine with writing easy articles for low pay on a site where the expectations are low and there is little stress, such a Textbroker or some other mill. 

Yet we are constantly berated for bringing down the entire industry. I think that's unfair. Different people have different needs, and not everyone has great ambitions or aspirations. Some of us are older and have absolutely not desire to build a new career. 

I'm really sick of being treated like dirt by younger writers who think I'm holding them back. I'm not holding anybody back. There is plenty of well-paying work out there -- go get it -- and leave the rest of us to do what works for our lives. 

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Something I found interesting about the debate </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-10 04:51:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I don't know if his advisors told him to do this, or what, but Hillary immediately went to talk to the panel members on stage and Trump went to his family. He took a few pictures with people, then he was ushered out. Hillary and Bill remained talking to people and taking pictures for almost 30 minutes after the debate, and had to be made to leave by their security. If you want to know who is in touch with the American people, it's the Clintons, not The Donald.

I'm not crazy about either one of them, but this really struck me. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
