<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject9655</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-03-20 19:35:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Why was she even looking in the first place? Unless it was an accident of course </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-03-20 19:34:38 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> And it still rings true </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-03-20 19:33:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I hear you. I don't think my boss or my professors would like a sudden Chris Brown rant blaring across the room

Edit: I think I read your comment backwards the first time and now I'm wondering what kind of job **only** allows porn and reddit but not other videos </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-03-20 19:30:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> They employ redditors

Their employees are redditors

I think you combined them but I might just be dumb and not able to read so take it with a grain of salt </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-03-20 19:28:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Did you know EA sucks? EA sucks man. EA is probably worse than the taliban. Man fuck EA. 

This is the community opinion at the moment apparently. They get nominated from a community vote and this post is already is hot. Everybody hates EA. **We get it** </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-03-20 19:08:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Exactly, it's just you and me here buddy </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-03-20 19:06:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> It's all good. I just knew I would hear that when I started using it but it was too late and I had already made it. I think I'll try again

Edit: Also, sorry for being a sensitive bitch in the other comment, my fears were just confirmed and it was like my first or second comment. I was sad </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-03-20 19:03:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> But he can tell the difference between blacks and whites

You people are mild today </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-03-20 01:01:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I never claimed to be one. I don't have any desire to be one. I just had to create a new account after having some issues on my original one.


And in regards to the obnoxious username comment below, I was listening to Biggie and the line was "Who the fuck is this" and I liked it but it was taken so I used "that" </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-03-19 21:20:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'd recommend a trim </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-03-19 21:09:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> You need to slut it up a little more  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
