<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject72</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-03 20:54:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I do understand where you are coming from. But if you recall, in season 1, Ragnars intentions weren't to become famous, but instead to become rich and expand viking settlements. That is why during season 1 his main goal was to travel west and loot the lands. 

And I don't think referring to historical records would  be good in this case. Because after all in reality Rollo isn't Ragnar's brother. And Ragnar has over 10 children. The show has created many extra elements to the show to make it more entertaining. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-01-03 17:56:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Although Ragnar started to 'doubt' his gods, I really do think that in the inside he still believes in them. Just like his brother Rollo, who converted to Christianity and now is a prince amongst them (Christians). But deep inside, he still believes in the Vikings. He even said to his wife (Gisla) that she would hear thunder but he still hear's the God Thor beating his hammer. 

I feel like there is a very strange connection between the two brothers. They seem to doubt their fate quite often, but they still believe in their viking gods, Valhalla.....in the inside.

And yes I actually do believe that Ragnar is blaming the Christian god on Athelstan's death. And that, in my opinion is why he ordered his son Ivar to seek revenge on Ecbert. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-31 05:48:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yeah. I saw that facebook post soon after I posted this one. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-29 19:39:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thank u for ur time </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> All His Angels ending </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-29 19:37:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Who is that one-eyed man at the end??? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-28 06:10:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Whilst secretly dabbing.... </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-28 05:56:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Ladies and Gentlemen, that's why most people have a hard time trusting them. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-28 05:49:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> A lot of them do </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-15 08:34:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Region: EU Battletag: Dioxyboiiiii#2619

Five (i)s at the end </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-14 11:36:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Region: EU Battletag: Ace#22320
 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-13 06:15:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> 
Region: EU Battletage: Ace#22320 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-13 06:01:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Region: EU
Battletage: Ace#22320 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-10 19:42:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Bro I lost over 100 points from DC this week. My MMR got so messed up because of that. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-06 10:28:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Add me for group up in EU Ace#22320 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-06 10:24:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Been disconnected twice in the beginning of a comp match. Literally lost over 100 for that shit. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-12-01 09:16:57 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Are you still accepting submissions? There are a couple of clips that I wanna share </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-28 17:36:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> So where will the montage be? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-11-28 09:02:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=X6PVnu8LPvk                                        
https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=6QqI_QSYYQo                
This one is special:
https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=5vOtwOXIbC0

You can definitely use some of my clips. This last one is quite the special one though. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-27 10:13:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Its just a hard type of shot to pull off when an enemy is not close to your crosshairs, but have to finish him off. (It kinda showcases the players skill) Btw they most efficient way it to flick once, then lock on. But some keep on flicking out of a habit. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-27 06:41:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Awesome work. But can you please do ones without the quotes as well? Thank you! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-10-26 12:21:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I guess top 4 Ana in the world. What's your gamertag? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
