<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject4978</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-01 12:10:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I use mostly curse, but their selection of mods is kind of crappy to be honest. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Whats better? Spacedock or Curse? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-01 11:54:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I honestly don't know which one has better mods, and Im kind of stuck in between. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-01 11:52:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Might have collided with something and broke, not sure if that even possible though  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-01 11:49:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Nice, good lightweight design man! (Although not sure tue purpose this rover fills but ok) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-05-01 11:45:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I have every single on of those except near future, those parts never made sense to me. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-30 19:15:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thanks man, I hope this helps a bunch of people who aren't really familiar with sats ;) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What are some of the best mods available? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-30 19:09:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I already has Mechjeb, KIS, KAS and some part packs, but am looking for some new and interesting stuff </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-30 18:59:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Just pause and edit the difficulty in settings. Not that hard. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What are the most important things to add to a satellite? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-30 18:57:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Im playing a normal difficulty science game, and am not very familiar with satellites, transmitting science, ect, and I dont want to send up a satellite and then realize I'm missing something. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Reddit is only place where you can know if people are talking about you behind your back </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-30 18:40:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2017-04-30 18:34:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thank god Apollo 11 just stay Apollo 11

Interesting lander concept though </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
