<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject4306</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-08 22:19:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Yes! They sniff each other's faces too, actually. Sometimes it's kind of hard to tell if they're playing or fighting, but in the past couple days whenever they're 'fighting', their ears have been perked up and there wasn't any growling or anything, so I think they're just playing and learning to be friends. Good luck with your new cat! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-08 20:05:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> A lot better! They can be in the same room and not fight now. Daisy still swats at Max occasionally, but overall they're doing great. :) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-06 21:14:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Thank you :) they actually are doing much better already!  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Old cat hates new cat - what can I do? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-04-06 00:54:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> TL;DR: My newest cat (2 y/o Daisy, female) and my oldest cat (11y/o Max, male) have been growling and hissing at each other ever since I adopted Daisy. I don't know how to make them like each other, or at least tolerate each other. 

Hi, all! I recently (as in two days ago) adopted a beautiful 2 year old domestic short haired grey cat, Daisy. She was a little apprehensive on the first day, but I set up a cat lounge in my bedroom complete with her food/water, litter box, hiding places, and toys and she seems to be adjusting to her new life pretty well. She sleeps in my room with me at night and is very snuggly. 

Daisy wasn't put in a cage with other cats while she was in the shelter as she had a respiratory infection and some other (resolved) illnesses that the volunteers didn't want spreading to the other animals. She is completely healed now, but as far as I know she hasn't had contact with other cats. 

My problem is, I have an 11 year old long haired ginger male named Max, and they do not get along. Max is the most kind and tolerant cat I've ever met; he's been around dogs and cats alike and has never had an issue with them, aside from some hissing if dogs are too close. He's very gentle, and never seems aggressive with other animals, more so scared. 

I tried to follow the internet's advice and introduce them gradually, but my parents ruined this by letting them into the same room the first day Daisy was home while I was busy doing something. Daisy growled a little, and they hissed at each other, and then I found out and put her back in my room. Since then, I've let them hang out for 10-15 minutes until one hisses and then I take her back to her cat lounge.

Max hasn't been eating, and he is a very food oriented cat. He even seems disinterested in treats, and he never comes when my mom calls him. In the 11 years we've had him, he has completely bonded to her and barely leaves her side. Now he spends his time chasing Daisy and swatting or hissing at her. 

I'm really at a loss, Max seems kind of depressed that there's a new cat in his house, and I don't want Daisy to hurt him, as she swats back. I know I can't go back in time and keep them apart until Daisy is adjusted better and then gradually introduce them, but is there anything I can do as far as damage control? They don't have to be best friends, but it would be good if I could let Daisy out of my room during the day and not worry about her getting stressed out because Max is following her around and bugging her. 

Any and all advice is appreciated, thank you for reading!  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-02-08 08:56:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Willamette Stone from If I Stay. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Cannibalism isn't a turn on </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-23 08:21:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2016-01-22 06:56:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Username checks out. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-11-16 02:10:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> My best friend had a coworker she was interested in over the summer, even though he had a girlfriend. The two ended up sleeping together for 3 months without the girlfriend ever finding out.
A week ago, she found out her on and off boyfriend of 1.5 years has been cheating on her since January.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-11-01 12:13:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'd suggest using oil free facial cleansers, if you aren't already. Urban Decay has a really good setting spray for oily skin, called de-slick or something like that. If you want something cheaper, NYX has a mattifying setting spray as well. You can also buy blotting papers if you're having an extra oily day! Good luck :) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-10-30 11:38:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I honestly swear by Johnson's baby lotion. It's like $5 for a huge bottle and I put some on before my primer and foundation. It's never made me break out, but I've always had good skin so I would start with a small bottle just in case it doesn't agree with your face. Hope this helps :) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-10-01 10:51:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I have the Naked 2 palette and I absolutely love it, but I would ask someone at wherever you're buying it for their opinion, because it can depend on your skin tone. Especially considering the cost, it would suck to buy one and then end up looking washed out because it doesn't compliment your skin/eye colour. Good luck :) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-09-21 07:23:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm Canadian and one of my friends actually died from an asthma attack because he couldn't afford an ambulance and didn't get to the hospital on time as a result.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-09-16 05:10:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I'm so pale I'm almost translucent and I use the Hard Candy Glamouflage concealer. It's liquid and covers everything (I think it was originally made for tattoos). I'm Canadian as well so it's available here, and it was about $5 at Walmart. My skin has more yellow/neutral tones though, but they have a few shades so if you can find yours I'd definitely recommend!  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE>   </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2015-09-16 04:51:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The Tarte Amazonian Clay foundation is great, however it's full coverage and pretty thick, so I would recommend having a good matte setting powder to go over top, especially if you have combination skin.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
