<INDIVIDUAL>
<ID>subject1298</ID>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Elizabethan Superheroes and Movie Characters by Sacha Goldberg. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-11-19 12:21:02 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Robocop Title Theme (Gameboy version) </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-11-14 00:36:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What Trion just did could turn out to be a masterstroke in the long run. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-11-08 10:25:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Everyone is crying about what just happened with the Thunderstruck tree prices and the fall in Archeum costs. As I also understand it, fishing will be nerfed soon too.

All this will do is make the best way of attaining gold being long range trade runs. This will promote in game travel over teleporting (as people will have to carry packs), which in turn will create more pvp confrontations in the world. This also means global gold production will drop making the value of each gold piece rise.

While this is happening, seeing as Archeum is now farmable fairly cheaply compared to how it was two days ago, crafting materials will drop in cost reducing the amount of gold required for high end crafting of armour and weapons. This will not only cause more people to try crafting (increase in typical farm produce sales such as pelts) but will also make buying bought gear more attractive than just grinding Hasla for tokens.

The drawbacks to this is the small amount players that "cashed out" in the last few says will be super rich in a few months if they hold onto their gold, and the larger amount of people who thought they had 1000's of gold worth of items in their bank, but just had that price crash.

For me though, it is a small price to pay for increased world pvp encounters and proper trading, which is what attracted me to the game in the first place. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [Big Spoilers] So this alien... </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-11-03 20:22:39 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> ...is the only single alien we encounter for the whole game up to the nest is discovered??

I kept wondering while playing if there was more than one slinking about :P </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [NSFW Language] A young lady taking her kids out for a day trip. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-10-24 17:00:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Two people freaking out over a she-bro taking her children out for the day </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-10-24 15:52:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> A catchy wtf. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-10-23 23:25:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Probably the funniest idea for a prank on a chat show host i've ever seen </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-10-15 14:41:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Every supermarket has a price beating promise on my tea bags. So why are they not now free? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-10-11 11:00:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Seriously, every time I walk into Waitrose I tut loudly whenever I see one of 'those' signs. It isn't just applicable to tea bags either. 

It makes me want to write a strongly worded letter of complaint. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> PsBattle: Elderly crazed grinning Batman jumping out of a plane. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-10-08 16:56:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> PsBattle: Elderly crazed batman jumping out of an aeroplane </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-10-08 16:19:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [Potential Spoilers] No tutorial on game mechanics? Perhaps a thread about different methods of passing encounters throughout the game? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-10-07 17:02:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Howdy,

I notice there isn't *really* a tutorial of sorts showing you how the mechanics of the game work. The thing that bugged me about it was that there are these little power boxes where you can re-route power to other systems like speakers or air vents. I don't see how these work and don't recall anything explaining it in game, so perhaps we should make a thread about tactics and how you passed certain situations, not just with the alien? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> FF7 remake confirmed?? Smells like click bait but what do you think? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-10-05 09:03:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> http://www.kdramastars.com/articles/42183/20141004/final-fantasy-vii-remake.htm

Not seen any other sources for it, but does anyone else know anything about it?? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> All Police Leave Cancelled in Scotland, violence expected </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-09-17 11:41:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Crucible Lag? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-09-10 23:21:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Anyone else experiencing terrible lag in crucible matches? I'm seeing deaths sometimes 4-5 seconds after the kill and get disconnected 50% of the time </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [Discussion] Co-Operative Multiplayer is awkward </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-09-10 14:20:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Howdy peeps.

I bought into the hype early on somewhat mainly because the impression I got from Bungie was that this was going to be verging on an MMOFPS. 

You could go round, meet up with some randoms, do a few quests, move on and find another few people in the world and do some more quests. While in a way, it's true, it's also pretty difficult to do it.

I need to invite people to a group to interact with them. When I do that, it takes me back out into orbit where I then have to start anew and get back to where we were.

I haven't got that far in it yet to find out for myself, but apparently you can only do some of the harder content with people you have listed as Friends outside of the game. This will severely limit the amount of people playing those missions, as people will have to pre arrange to do those parts of the game, and not just be able to login and find people to play with.

Don't get me wrong, the game is a LOT of fun, it's just it went from being what I think could have been revolutionary and forge a new niche in the genre, into Borderlands with a Halo skin.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [QUESTION] Need help finding a funny DayZ video </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-09-02 11:17:51 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Howdy, just wondering if anyone can help me.

I am looking for a video of a guy who was walking around trolling people "hello, i'd like to tell you about the lord jesus christ" etc, and in one of the videos he sneaks up to a sniper who just dies while he's talking to him.

I'm pretty sure the guy is wearing some kind of baseball cap too if that helps.

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [SPOILERS ALL] [Query] Question about Brans mentor and a maester </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-08-29 08:20:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I've just been reading AFFC and during the start of Sams voyage to become a maester, Aemon describes when he himself left to become one. He mentions he left with a certain Brynden Rivers / Bloodraven but how is this possible when he apparently is far older (at least appears to be) than Aemon?

Did I miss something? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> r [X-Post - /r/movies] TIL Wookie designs come from a George R.R. Martin novellette </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-08-26 13:57:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Is it fair to have a 'womens' section in a gym, and not a mens? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-08-22 13:29:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Howdy people,

I might be over reacting about this, but my gym group (not at my specific 'home' gym though) have introduced in many of their locations that there are designated 'womens' sections. In these sections only women may enter, yet there is no mens section where women can't go.

I would understand it if they had some new premesis that women could join as a "female only" gym, but is it discriminating against men that there are these sections for women with equipment that isn't in the rest of the gym where a man can use it?

EDIT: Just to make myself clear, I do think that women should have 'Women only' gyms, as it's a legitimate business and if you want to limit your client base thats down to the business owner. What i'm on about is a man and a woman paying the same fee to the gym, but not being able to use the same equipment. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [NSFW Language] I kinda walked right into that one </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-08-19 14:27:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Could be miss reported but it even possible that Mel Gibson has to pay his ex wife 50% of any future earnings post divorce as this article claims? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-08-18 11:27:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Emily in Vanity Fair </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-08-09 17:28:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> New Warcraft Logo Revealed </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-07-24 16:30:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> So... does Toothless know that Hiccup is responsible for his original injury? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-07-24 11:15:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> In the first film, Toothless is obviously flying around sans prosthesis before he is shot down by Hiccup, but then needs the prosthetic tail fin in order to fly.

Do you think Toothless knows it was Hiccup that shot him down originally and caused this damage? I wonder if he doesn't how it would change their dynamic if he then found out. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Trojan Horse Report finds plot to instill "intolerant and aggressive Islamic ethos" into Birmingham, UK schools, and that the local council looks like they knew about it </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-07-22 15:11:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Trojan Horse Report: There Was Islamist Plot To Takeover Birmingham Schools </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-07-22 14:53:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [No Spoilers] Game of Thrones 8-bit Theme </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-07-19 13:11:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [Possible Leak] Destiny PC release March 2015 on Steam? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-07-19 10:42:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The amazing dance of the Peacock Spider </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-07-18 10:47:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [NSFW] I don't know what to say about this </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-07-17 15:42:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [NSFW] If Eminem had been born in Glasgow instead of Detroit... </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-07-15 08:48:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Gary Little - A Walk in the Park - Glasgow comedy </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-07-14 21:50:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Intended growing a bigass Viking braid but I quite like the beard how it is now. Thoughts fellow beardites? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-06-28 12:30:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> So there was room for Jack on that board after all... </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-06-27 21:11:30 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> So is this proof that there definitely was room for Jack on that wooden board? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-06-27 20:58:45 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> #Define Beauty, Part 4: The Magic Gap by Guy Aroch - NOWNESS </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-06-13 17:46:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Mark Hamill talks Star Wars VII, Disney and more </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-06-06 15:43:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Counting Crows -- Colorblind [Melancholy Rock] </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-05-29 16:22:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> As a casual player, rollbacks are getting really irritating </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-05-27 21:53:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Another redditor changes gender roles of Cosmo headlines, I'm shocked. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-05-24 23:57:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Sorry I don't know his to do X-Posts but this link was top of /r/funny. I am actually pretty shocked if this is true, it's probably the ultimate it mainstream double standards:

www.imgur.com/gallery/ODgLwVs </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> I shot (photo) this vixen a few months back, she was so happy running around at sunset! </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-05-23 13:04:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Anybody else feel too guilty to go through with it? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-05-21 15:56:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hi everyone. 

Many times through my life I have felt like ending it, never more so than these last 12-18 months. Without going into details about *my* situation, has anyone else here thought about it but couldn't do it for the pain it would cause your loved ones?

Part of me feels that it would liberate my family and allow my wife time to find someone else who could support her better than I can, and find a suitable father figure for my daughter before she's too old. Then again though, I can't help but think what a selfish thing it would be for me to do.

Fuck knows.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Halo 5 confirmed for 2015 release on Xbox One, but another Halo release planned for 2014 </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-05-16 14:31:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [Question] So now Disney own Star Wars,, do you think they'll cave in and release blurays of the original, theatrical releases of Episodes IV, V,   VI? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-05-08 14:26:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> As the title reads really.

Now Disney own the rights to the Star Wars universe, do you guys think it's likely that they will release the series on Blu Ray again, only this time including the original theatrical edits of the movies?

I hate to sound all hipster, but to me they are better movies (especially A New Hope) than their updated counterparts. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> TIL it can rain Spiders in Brazil. I'm never going to Brazil. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-05-04 07:38:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Anyone else bug randomly during combat? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-04-20 22:29:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Howdy guys,

From time to time I randomly get a bug where I can't cast any abilities or spells during combat. I can still drink potions, but basic attacks,  abilities etc don't work (if i press numbers, the buttons on the bar move but nothing happens) but I can block alright and use quickslot items.

I was wondering if anyone else had a similar experience or not </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> TEENAGE MUTANT NINJA TURTLES - Official "Brothers" TV Spot - First Glimpse of Splinter </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-04-15 13:50:08 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Thanks for all they great info in this sub, changed my perspective on my recently diagnosed nephew and autism in general. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-04-04 13:10:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> A kinda pointless post, but just wanted to say thanks for all the great info and stories here.

My nephew who is nearly two has just been diagnosed with autism and not knowing much about it, and only having met a couple of people with it who have drastic cases, instantly thought the worst. Coming here, and reading peoples stories and experiences with it has completely changed my perspective on autism. So, thanks for not only educating me, but also making me feel that all is not lost for my nephew.

TL;DR: People in the uk clearly need to be educated about autism, because there are people like me who clearly have the wrong idea about it.

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Security Tokens / Authenticator? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-03-25 20:52:04 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> In some previous MMO's i've played, I quite liked the extra level of security that Authenticators or Security Token Checks gave me such as in WoW or Final Fantasy XIV. I'm quite surprised that ESO doesn't look like it's going to offer such a thing. Is there any other was I can increase security other than regular password changes??

Or more to the point, does anyone know if they plan to implement them later? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Michael Green Re-Writing Prometheus Sequel </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-03-25 16:33:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Gauntlet reboot announced from Magicka and Helldivers studio </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-03-17 21:19:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> First time I saw a Red Squirrel, and the little guy popped a smile at me :P </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-03-16 21:44:35 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [Question] Can anyone point me in the direction of getting my iPad2 prepped for emulation? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-03-08 12:30:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hey peeps,

I want to get my iPad2 (ios5) prepped so it can run iMAME or similar software. Can anyone point me in the direction of resources explaining the best ways to do this please?


Thanks </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Thinking about throwing some big fat Viking braids into the bottom of this puppy. Any advice on doing that? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-03-07 17:26:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Now that landfill prices have soared, my beautiful Surrey air is filled with the denizens of the areas burning rubbish. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-03-01 11:07:49 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Seriously. The old guy two doors down is burning a washing machine.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> My mum as a child playing with my grandad on the beach, love this photo, could you guys draw it for me? Any style welcome! </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-02-28 17:46:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> My grandfather recently passed, and I love this picture of my mother and him. Any chance of a doodle? Any style is welcome </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-02-28 16:36:09 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Seeing as this Beta is going to run on the US server only, will previous EU Beta characters be available? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-02-27 11:31:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Just noticed that this beta test is running on the US server only (presumably further and stronger stress tests, seeing as the last one was buttery smooth).

Does anyone know if my previous EU character will carry over to the US shard? I don't have much time this weekend, and was hoping to try out some PVP :3 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Loudness - Soldier of fortune </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-02-26 18:19:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [Concept Art] Will The Millennium Falcon Be In Star Wars: Episode VII? | Concept News from Empire </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-02-19 14:07:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Anyone else has their client installed twice? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-02-18 22:52:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Howdy,

On checking out folder sizes on my computer, it seems I have 2 folders,almost identical sizes (just over 30GB), inside C:\Program Files (x86)\Zenimax Online\ called 'The Elder Scrolls Online" and "The Elder Scrolls Online EU".

Surely this is a bug of some kind? I tried deleting all the data and re-installing but ended up with the same result.

Does anyone else have the same problem?? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Returning after a long abscence, any suggestions for RP realms?? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-02-11 15:01:19 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Howdy,

I played from release heavily up until WotlK, which I played through, albeit casually. My guild is long gone, but I still have all my toons on Bloodscalp EU.

I'm interested in playing on an RP server instead of a normal PVP one, and wanted to know if anyone can suggest/point me where I can find, a decent EU RPPVP realm if there still are any.

Also, how fundamental are the changes WoW has gone through these last 4 years or so?? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Got a thin beard?? Get a beard transplant. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-02-07 20:25:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Beard and handlebar moustache. Should I keep this look, or grow it all out and go for fat Viking braids? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-02-07 19:49:48 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> BTS of a bikini photo shoot </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-02-07 15:13:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Physical Playtime of Ground Zero's main mission takes 13 minutes. The other near 2 hours are seemingly cut scenes. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-02-05 11:20:14 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The Residents- Constantinople. Need a few minutes after watching this to get my head together </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-02-02 09:00:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> New footage from the Red Bull Stratos jump - "The Full Story". It shows just how much of a feat of endurance this was for Felix Baumgartner. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-02-01 11:15:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Arnold Schwarzenegger's Undercover Gym Trainer </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-01-23 07:56:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [Suggestion] Replacement for Zombies?? How about we remove humanoids altogether and research items? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-01-14 15:44:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> The modern stuff is way, way too easily found imho. It's easy to kill a zombie (I can kill normal and black ones with just a rock) and for the best loot to drop from them just seems too easy. Not to mention that DayZ is zombie survival, and I like the tone of Rust because it isn't DayZ.

So, remove all the zombies, and add more animals. That should help with the newer players not getting food very easily. Then, have the best blueprints in locked 'safes' in random buildings (not just in rad towns) which can be opened with either explosives (but at 75% chance to destroy whats inside), or a safe cracking tool, which could be crafted with a new material, Medium Quality Metal, which would take maybe 20 low quality metal to make, and therefore make them valuable. Safes like this should be rare, maybe only having 1 spawned on the server at a time, and then if the print was for something like an M4, it should be split into parts such as "Blueprint: M4 Barrel", which you learn and make each piece. If items are rare and hard to make it' might encourage trading and bartering amongst players.

Low-fi items (pipe bombs, makeshift armours etc) should be able to be researched by players using a craftable 'research desk'. That could work by selecting the type of item you are trying to create (armour/gun/tool/melee weapon etc), then selecting the components you want to use in the research, one at a time in a step by step process. ie:

I want to try and make leather armour. 

So, step one of research, I want to click on type and select Armour.

Step Two: Choose base item. So i'd pick leather, and add maybe 5 pieces in.

Step Three: Choose Supplement. I'm going to need something to tie it all together, so lets add some thread (thread could be made from cloth). Lets add 10 pieces of thread.

Step Four: Choose Catalyst. I'm going to toughen that leather up. So lets throw some salt in there too. 20x of that added.


Step Five: Research. Hit the research button, and lets see what happens. it's a relatively small item, so could take maybe 30 seconds to research.

Step Six: Result. Ok, research failed to produce a new item. However, it would say something like this:

Research Failed. 

Was not large enough.
Was tight enough.
Was not tough enough.

This would give players an idea of what worked, what didn't and if enough of said resource was used to make an item (players should not know how much of something is needed to make an item, it should be discovered, and be different quantities for each player to a degree to prevent wiki's listing research quotas).

Well? What do you think? You could even have upgradable research desks (and workbenches) where you could add tools for recipes that need them. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Did I meet a hacker?? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-01-11 22:30:18 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I was just in game, in my hut (1 foundation etc) and some dude just came and griefed me.

He planted C4 twice on a wall, then shot me 3 times with a p250 (all three shots were fired in less than a second and all hit me even though I was a good distance away and strafing a lot.

So, I spawn in the bigger house i'm trying to build next door, and I hear his hatchet rapidly bashing my storage. Again, way way too fast for it to be regular swings. It almost sounded as fast as an uzi firing.

Anyone else come across this?? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Videogame Beta Testers of Reddit: If you got kicked off a game for breaking an NDA, what did you do? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-01-11 08:52:29 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Just wondering what actually happens if you post a screenshot from a beta by accident? (for example, accidentally hitting the screenshot key in steam and then=n your friends being able to see it) </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Duggan Killing: Armed Police To Wear Cameras </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-01-09 07:36:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> UK2   UK3 offical servers have been down for sometime </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2014-01-03 12:22:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Anyone have any news? Seems odd that UK1   4 are still going strong. </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> UK servers down? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-12-26 22:41:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Just been trying to log in to UK 2 or 3 and they are missing from the server list.

Anyone know what the situation is? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Diana Death: 'No Evidence' SAS Involved </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-12-16 19:48:24 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Where (not) to go in Guildford: 8 clubs and bars to avoid like herpes </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-12-14 19:44:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> 300: Rise of an Empire - Trailer #2 Music #1 (Audiomachine - Blood and Stone) </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-12-13 12:31:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> The Desolation of Smaug (2013) Soundtrack - 'I See Fire' by Ed Sheeran. Genius, or ill suited to Tolkiens world? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-12-13 12:15:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Arrested Development - Mr Wendal </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-11-28 17:12:25 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Lightning Strikes quest line up and rewards </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-11-12 18:19:10 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> NSV (kinda): Got an unorthadox compliment on my body... </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-09-19 11:38:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> How are the servers now? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-09-16 08:52:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hi guys,

I've been trying to get a copy of this for almost two weeks now, but have been unable to because sqeenix held he sales to reduce server congestion. Does anyone have any idea how the servers are now? Are they still really bad?

Just trying to get an idea when sales will start again so I can start playing :p


EDIT: Thanks guys! Hopefully the digital store will be back up in the next few days. Cya inside! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Cookie Monsters favourite cookie recipe. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-09-09 14:06:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Advice on stopping the snacking? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-08-28 11:42:15 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hey fellow Loser-buddies (that sounds so great and so awful at the same time),

I started my journey about 10 months ago (October) at 157.6kg. I joined the gym, and then lost 12kg in around two months but after my wife had our first baby in January, i've not managed to lose anymore, only hover around the 145-147kg mark this last 5-6 months. I still go to the gym 3-4 times a week and have personal training once a week included in that, so it can only be the snacking thats stopping me lose weight.

It's awkward as I know my problem and I snack on the wrong stuff way too much, even though I eat really well most meal times (we eat home prepared an cooked food at home, never ready meals, and we eat out 1-2 times a week at proper restaurants, and never eat fast food.) 

What I want to know, is what can I do to stop myself from snacking? It's really annoying that I can go most of the day on just my meals, and then 10 minutes of binging and thats the day ruined :P

I'd appreciate any advice guys/gals </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Syria: Hundreds Killed In 'Gas Attack' </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-08-21 12:22:11 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Got bored of waiting for Season 4 of GoT so did a self portrait season 3 style </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-08-11 23:41:59 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Joined BNi, while docked in Amarr Throne Worlds Civic court... </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-08-08 15:17:43 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Just realised, that if I undock, i'm going to get toasted pretty fast hahahahaha

Should I sell all my stuff, then buy new when I get to Barleguet? Should I load up my newly bought Maller cruiser (which I can't really afford or fit properly yet, yup, definitely noobish here) and warp stabliser it to its eye balls (also potentially the most entertaining option), or do I simply quit BNi and rejoin when I get all my stuff to Barleguet?

7o peeps </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> To young to start PVP? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-08-03 08:44:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hey chaps/chapettes,

I started playing a week or two ago and am enjoying the game although I'm only running agent security missions and a little mining until I get a mining barge (to pay for PVP) properly. 

My question is am I going to need to wait a week or two until I'm skilled up enough to start flying cruisers or some other combat ship more capable than a frigate or destroyer? Or should I just head for low sec and get shot. A lot. 

I'm currently in amarr noob zones (Deepari and surrounding systems) and don't even know what direction to head out in when I'm ready to go :p

Oh another thing. When I make the transition from high to low sec and find where I want to head out to, should I sell everythingi have, buy a shuttle and then rebuy stuff when I get out there? I hear there are plenty of 'bubble traps' around 0.5/0.4 gates so beware shipping stuff through those.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> A guy asks 100 girls for sex and gets turned down flat, but the girl asking guys has a 50% success rate. Why is he creepy, but she's fine? (2nd Vid in comments) </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-07-29 20:40:01 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Tim Burton was trying to get a superman film made in the 90's starring Nicholas Cage </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-07-19 15:39:50 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Building Cloud's Buster Sword (Final Fantasy VII) - MAN AT ARMS </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-07-16 18:35:17 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Man At Arms builds Cloud's Buster Sword </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-07-16 11:15:28 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Rob J Madin - 'Everybody On The Internet's An Idiot'. I think this song perfectly sums up some of us redditors :P </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-07-02 15:01:21 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What do you think is the best comic book adaptation of all time? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-06-29 13:10:47 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> What do you think is the most faithful comic book adaptation to film?

I don't necessarily mean the best film (probably The Dark Knight imo), but I mean the closest a film has gotten to capturing the look and feel of the comic/graphic novel.

/discuss please </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Amazing medley of soundtracks performed by Jason Yang </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-06-29 13:00:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Photographers, do you feel technology is damaging photography? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-06-24 13:53:05 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hi guys,

I was talking to someone about Quentin Tarantino wanting to quit film making due to the digital age, and was trying to explain to him why I think he felt that.

I'm a dSLR shooter, and have never shot film. Now i've been working as a photographer professionally for a while, I have a whole new appreciation for film shooters. If I under or over expose an image, I can fix that in post in a few seconds. However, as a film shooter that is going to be very difficult. Since realising this some time ago, I have a whole new appreciation for film shooters, and try to be triple sure I get the shot right in camera instead of thinking thats alright I can fix that later.

Whilst two shooters, one with film the other with digital can come up with the same finished image, it takes far more skill to get it right on film, and I can understand now why alot of film shooters rue people like me who shoot on dSLR's.

However, now things iike Instagram and the Lytro are happening, people with no training or experience can create decent images, and I now feel a bit like that towards those types of people. Whist tech cannot replace skill, it certainly makes a solid substitute.

TL;DR: art is art whatever process is used to make it, however, the older ways are more difficult and technology opens that field of people capable of making a good standard of art far wider. 

Anyway, how do you guys feel about tech and photography </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> UFO ALIEN DISCLOSURE By Canadian Minister of Defence MAY 2013 </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-06-08 09:49:44 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> BREAKING!!! UFO ALIEN DISCLOSURE By Canadian Minister of Defence MAY 2013 </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-06-08 09:26:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> David Hayter posts another dubious message, says he has "Laryingitis" coming on... </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-06-05 23:16:54 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Venezuela: Toilet Roll Stash Found Amid Crisis </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-05-31 14:56:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> I would like to ask the Ex-Muslims of reddit if "terrorism" was preached to them. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-05-23 08:43:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I don't just mean by people in and around them, but actively in the mosques and other places of worship. 

As someone who knows little about the faith but hears regularly from non Muslims about how people are encouraged to assault/abuse/kill non Muslims, I would like to know if there is any truth to these rumours.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Here are two screens of powdered toast mans assistant from Ren and Stimpy. Dead ringer for Elizabeth? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-05-19 10:51:42 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Wolfenstein: The New Order revealed 'bout time Wolfenstein got a makeover. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-05-07 16:16:16 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Season 3 not available in the uk for download? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-05-05 13:05:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hey guys. 

I waited, I emailed apple, I emailed AMC asking them several times (never even got an answer, not so much as even acknowledging my question) and nobody can tell me why walking dead season 3 is available everywhere else in the world but not on uk iTunes. I've bought the previous two seasons and wanted the entire series saved to my iTunes library, and now that doesn't look like happening. 

So two questions. 

1, where can I see season 3? Anyone have any ideas? I'd prefer to buy it if I'm honest so if anyone know any online retailers I can download it from I'd be grateful. 

2, does anyone know what the problem is with home release in the UK for season 3? </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Creepy or Cool? Portraits Derived From the DNA in Hair and Gum Found in Public Places - If this works, why isn't every police force in the world using it? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-05-04 09:21:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> After seeing Wolfram alpha pull off some pokemon, I thought I'd try it with some of Valve's finest </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-04-30 22:36:41 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Weebl does it again. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-04-30 20:31:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> TIL That Disney won an oscar for a documentary on lemmings, by faking their deaths and throwing them off cliffs. (more Disney facts in video) </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-04-23 07:47:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [Spoiler up to end of ACOK/Season2] A pretty accurate painting of Tyrion (as depicted in the books, minus the necklace) Artist: Jorg </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-04-11 12:33:36 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> LulzSec - PSN hackers plead guilty in UK court </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-04-10 15:15:40 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> What happens when your news on politics link reaches the front page </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-04-10 14:34:55 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Margaret Thatchers death causes Ding Dong the Witch is Dead to climb itunes to number 2 </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-04-10 12:28:22 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> If you are in a male/female changing room, would it make you uncomfortable to know there was a gay/lesbian person in there with you? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-04-07 21:20:03 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> [removed] </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> More evidence about always online next gen XBox. (psuedo source in comments) </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-04-05 16:06:06 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [Spoilers] Significance of final scene BEFORE credits? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-04-02 22:04:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> I see a few people noticed that Elizabeth wasn't wearing her choker in the final scene where Booker is drowned, but did anyone else notice that Booker wasn't wearing the bandage on his right hand also? (FYI the scene where you can point a gun or badger a guy in a ticket stall for a ticket, one option ends up with you getting stabbed in the hand, and Elizabeth applies a bandage which stays on your characters model for the rest of the game)

I see that some think that this Elizabeth isn't the same one we went through the game with, (makes sense seeing how remorseful she seems before she lets you go through the door to the baptism, and then how cold she is after), but doesn't that also mean that the Booker here isn't the same one we played as? Or did Irrational drop the ball and forget to code it in :P </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [SPOILERS] did I miss something about the twins actions? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-04-02 13:25:12 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Well, seeing as the whole game was  a plot by the twins to right a wrong they committed, they obviously knew what had to happen to resolve the problem. 

So... Why go through all that trouble pulling booker through 122 times when they could have just murdered him before the baptism? Did they not know that comstock and booker were the same person?

 </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Starting my LOSEIT journey. Any tips? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-03-27 16:52:56 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hi guys!

Long time lurker to this subreddit, and thanks to everyone of you to helping me motivate myself to getting this bulk shifted.

About me:
I'm male, 6'3'', 32 years old, married and have one 2 month old kid. I weigh 148.9kg's / 327.5lbs today and need to get things under control. I've always had a weight problem and have tried lots of diets (atkins, cambridge etc) which usually work for the most part, but when I come off the diet I always put on weight after (eating pretty healthily) and then I lose faith and start eating the crap again, and I usually end up heavier than I started. 

I am a pretty broad guy too, so i'm lucky in so far that I don't look as heavy as I actually am, and that in turn should mean I will have less loose skin than I might have had if I'd be of a more slight frame. If I continue to gain weight I will more than likely need surgery to remove the excess skin, however my personal trainer assures me that provided I stick to the plan and keep it off for a few years, my skin will be almost like I'd never been (dare I say it) fat, save for the stretchmarks on my stomach.

I actually started this in November, but the birth of our first baby and a recent back injury kinda stopped my momentum. I was 154.6kgs then, got down to 144.4kgs and have increased (again mainly through eating crap and not being able to get to the gym due to baby/wife health worries - all fine now) to about halfway. Anyway:

My plan:
Work out at the gym 3 days a week, with an additional session with my personal trainer one day a week. I have a pretty active job anyway, and that coupled with walking the dog almost everyday I hope will be enough.

I also plan to NOT go "on" a diet (weight loss program like before) and instead change my diet (regular day to day eating habits). I don't care if it takes five times longer to get results, I'd lile to think i'm more likely to keep the weight off if I haven't got to "come off" a diet. I don't even want to keep a food diary this time, I want to try and keep it as "normal" and make as small of a deal of it as possible. I also found when I did that, i'd read though it and make myself hungry after :P

I have also set fitness goals. I intend to run Spartan Race in August, which considering where I started will be a feat. I still have 5 months to train for it, so I am confident I can complete the race provided I put in the effort before hand with both weight loss and fitness.

What I'd like from you guys:

If you have any tips at all about keeping the weight off after I get to a comfortable size, please let me know! Also, anything you can think of to help me lose the weight that wouldn't be common sense would be great.

Thanks in advance, and your stories have motivated me to make the change!

Grid

EDIT: That actually felt damn good writing that :P </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Season 3 open iTunes uk? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-03-21 17:58:31 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hi guys,

I've seen the first two seasons and have put off watching season 3 on the tv as I like to buy the episodes on iTunes and watch it down the gym while I bust out some cycling or cross training. 

The thing is, normally each episode is available as it airs on tv, but there is nothing for season 3 on uk iTunes. It is however available on the US and Australia stores.

Does anyone know why this is or know when it will come to the uk store? I asked apple and they said they didn't know.  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> I work in a carpet shop and brought my pug when he was a puppy in for his first day at work. This is the result. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-03-21 14:16:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> George doesn't like his bed </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-03-21 14:05:53 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [Possible spoilers] What do people think of Jamie. Is he an ass or a good guy? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-03-04 13:13:32 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> After reading several threads about season 3 and what people are looking forward to, a lot talk about being excited to see Jamie's story milestone at the end of the season, and I got the impression that people really hate him, yet warm to him after the events of ASOS. 

What do you guys think of him really?

I don't see him as that bad a guy, just he feels a bit miffed that people ridicule him for killing the king he was supposed to protect, when said king was making his people suffer. 

I think because of this he doesn't care what people think of him as he's already disliked by most, which leads him to act like a bit of a prat. 

/discussplease </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Here's my 5 week old daughter wearing a top hat </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-03-03 20:15:20 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> An answer to our energy problems? We have LOTS of coal and the tech for clean coal energy is here at last. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-02-21 12:51:07 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Joss Whedons Firefly MMO - Seeking funding - Looks like this time its not a fake </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-02-05 10:03:33 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Professional X-Box Support on twitter. How they stay professional with support requests like this... </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-01-04 16:31:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [NSFW-Language] Prob a repost, but Pug Life is just something that has to be shared :P </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-01-03 14:42:52 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Just discovered this subreddit, thought you'd like to see my George after playing in last years snow. </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-01-03 12:23:34 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> I brought George to work with me and bought him a new bed to sleep in while there. George doesn't like the idea of temping work... </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2013-01-03 12:10:27 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [NSFWish] Just made my first game using RPG Maker VX Ace </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-12-23 11:38:58 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> http://www.filedropper.com/legendofpentax

http://dl.degica.com/enterbrain/rpgvxace/RPGVXAce_RTP.zip (run time files)

I just finished my first RPG. It's just a quick test of the software really so don't expect much, the whole thing doesn't last more than half hour or so, less if you're quick. The NSFW tag is used as theres a little swearing in it, and yes the girl with green hair is supposed to be annoying.

I just thought it was impressive that I put the whole thing together in a couple of hours, and that was it.

Let me know what you think, i'll start working on a full game soon! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Uk season 3 on iTunes?? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-12-14 13:59:00 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hi guys,

I see that season three is available on iTunes in the USA but currently nothing is available in the UK even though its aired here. Anyone have any idea when it's coming?

I'd download it to my iPad and watch it in the gym and now I've finished season 2 I have to see who the guy with the sword is :p


Thanks </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> Grade of challenge for a 339lb man? </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-12-13 09:06:37 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT> Hey guys!

I recently joined a gym, got a personal trainer and started on the long road to slimness. 

Now a couple months down the road and about 20lb down, my trainer is so impressed with the level of fitness increase he wants me to think about running in a spartan race with him. 

What I'd like to know is obviously there is some intense challenge there what what chance do I have of finishing one or all the three races? I live in the uk so the next one isn't until the middle of next year so I have about seven months to train for it, but what's the deal? Are you pitted against everyone else? Does it work like ironman where the goal is simply to finish in your own time? And most importantly, I'm on some medical steroids and will be for some time, I know that they inhibit weight loss, but will they be dangerous for that level of activity?

Thanks Spartans!


subject1298

Ps, if I go and finish, I'll change my net name to subject1298 Prime haha! </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> [NSFW] I see your sticky Vicky flyer, and raise you a video I found of her show... </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-11-22 14:43:13 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
<WRITING>
	<TITLE> WTF Japan? Would you drink this brand of milk?? [NSFWish] </TITLE>
	<DATE> 2012-11-15 14:51:23 </DATE>
	<INFO> reddit post </INFO>
	<TEXT>  </TEXT>
</WRITING>
</INDIVIDUAL>
